<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>ZX Spectrum</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).z80</path>
		<name>Alien</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>"In space no-one can hear you scream." That tagline from the movie is apt for this strategy adaptation that follows the plotline of the first movie in the franchise. The action starts after the chestburster scene which unleashes an alien organism into their enclosed spaceship. The remaining crew members must attempt to destroy it while the traitorous android tries to protect the alien.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Concept Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Argus Press</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien (1984)(Argus Press Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ant Attack (1983)(Quicksilva).z80</path>
		<name>Ant Attack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An early isometric game that predates Ultimate's classic Knight Lore by a year. Used what it called the "softsolid 3d" algorithm to represent a large scrolling city from a switchable isometric perspective. The city, identified in the inlay blurb as Antescher, a combination of Ant and Escher, the famous visual paradox artist, is teeming with deadly giant ants. The player controls a boy or a girl and races around the city trying to find his/her lost half while jumping on structures to avoid the ants, or fighting the insects by either jumping on them or throwing grenades.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quicksilva Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Quicksilva Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ant Attack (1983)(Quicksilva).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ant Attack (1983)(Quicksilva).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).z80</path>
		<name>Atic Atac</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As the game begins, you fall through a trapdoor and end up inside an evil castle with only one way to get out of it - find all the pieces of the great ACG key that lets you unlock the main door. Many problems lie on your way to freedom, however - not only is the castle pretty big and spread out over several floors, it is also littered with enemies that must be avoided or dispensed of. For some doors, you need keys to open them.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Atic Atac (1983)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ATV Simulator - All Terrain Vehicle (1987)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>ATV Simulator: All Terrain Vehicle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Viewed side on, and with a split screen 2-player option, this game simulated the then-new All Terrain Vehicles in an action-based way. The game features a succession of courses, which must be navigated in 30 seconds. You must run to the vehicle initially, and will also have to manually remount if you fall off - all costing you more precious time. Careful use of the wheelies and jumps is crucial to completion. Each hazard must be taken at the right speed, which you'll learn through experience.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/ATV Simulator - All Terrain Vehicle (1987)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ATV Simulator - All Terrain Vehicle (1987)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Auf Wiedersehen Monty (1987)(Gremlin Graphics)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Auf Wiedersehen Monty</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Auf Wiedersehen Monty the intrepid coal thief Monty Mole fled to the rocky island of Gibraltar. However, the Intermole agency is on to him, and his only hope of escape is to trek across Europe, collecting enough cash to buy the Greek island of Montoss and live there in luxury.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Auf Wiedersehen Monty (1987)(Gremlin Graphics)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Auf Wiedersehen Monty (1987)(Gremlin Graphics)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avalon (1984)(Hewson Consultants).z80</path>
		<name>Avalon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 408 AD the Roman Empire is crumbling and the Romans have mostly left Britannia. you play Maroc the mage, a "Lore Seeker", who has set out to defeat Avelach, Lord of Chaos. You control Maroc's astral projection which can cast spells to achieve various parts of the quest, the objective is to advance in sixteen ranks by exploring the world and collecting spells and ultimately destroy the Lord of Chaos.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Ltd, Steve Turner</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Avalon (1984)(Hewson Consultants).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Avalon (1984)(Hewson Consultants).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Back To Skool (1985)(Microsphere).z80</path>
		<name>Back to Skool</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this sequel to popular Skool Daze you once again you must try and save your own neck! Having managed to steal your report during the last few skooldaze of term, you've spent the whole holiday forging teachers' signatures and handwriting to make yourself look like the brightest, sweetest natured, most helpful little soul ever to carry a satchel. Now all you've got to do is get it back into the Headmasters's safe!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Serma Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Back To Skool (1985)(Microsphere).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Back To Skool (1985)(Microsphere).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BMX Simulator (1987)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>BMX Simulator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is an overhead-viewed racing game similar in style to Super Sprint. There are 7 courses of increasing difficulty, incorporating ramps and bumps which significantly affect the bike's handling. Each course has a time limit you must complete 3 laps of the course within, or it's game over. The further inside the time limit you are, the more points you score.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/BMX Simulator (1987)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BMX Simulator (1987)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bobby Bearing (1986)(The Edge).z80</path>
		<name>Bobby Bearing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bobby Bearing is a young steel ball who lives in the land Technofear, carefully avoiding the dangerous Metaplanes. One day his evil cousin comes along and lures him and his four brothers directly into said Metaplanes and leaves them for good. So Bobby's quest of the day is to find his way home and rescue his brothers. The Metaplanes are a big maze of isometric screens without scrolling. The main challenge is to find orientation in this maze with various dead ends and junctions; there are also lifts, magnets, air ducts and hidden switches to complicate matters.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Robert Figgins, Trevor Figgins</developer>
		<publisher>The Edge Software</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bobby Bearing (1986)(The Edge).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bobby Bearing (1986)(The Edge).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomb Jack (1986)(Elite Systems).z80</path>
		<name>Bomb Jack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Bomb Jack, the player controls Jack, who must collect all the bombs in order to complete the current round and go onto the next one. This sounds easy, right? Wrong! Making Jack's task difficult are numerous enemies such as birds, mummies, turtles, and orbs. In each round, collecting a number of bombs results in a bonus coin appearing, and collecting this coin will make the player's score increase 2 to 4 times. More often than not, the "power ball" appears, and when you collect this, you can defeat enemies and have more time to collect all the bombs. There is also the "E" coin, which gives Jack one additional life, but rarely does this coin appear.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tehkan Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bomb Jack (1986)(Elite Systems).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bomb Jack (1986)(Elite Systems).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boulder Dash (1984)(First Star Software).z80</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You're Rockford and have to dig through monster infested caves in search of diamonds. In each level you must collect a certain number of these diamonds, in order to open a portal to the next stage. Enemies can be squashed by falling boulders, which are released when the ground below them is removed or they are pushed onto empty ground, but be careful because these can also squash you. In later levels, difficulty is increased by many puzzle elements and shorter time limits.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software</developer>
		<publisher>K-Tel Software</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Boulder Dash (1984)(First Star Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Boulder Dash (1984)(First Star Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bounty Bob Strikes Back (1984)(US Gold).z80</path>
		<name>Bounty Bob Strikes Back</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bounty Bob Strikes Back! is the sequel to Miner 2049er and features similar gameplay. As Bounty Bob, your goal is to claim every inch of 25 challenging mines. To do this, you must walk over each segment of the framework in the mines. To reach each segment of framework, you will need to figure out a way to jump, climb, or use one of the many devices occasionally available to get there.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Five Software</developer>
		<publisher>Big Five Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bounty Bob Strikes Back (1984)(US Gold).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bounty Bob Strikes Back (1984)(US Gold).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cauldron (1985)(Palace).z80</path>
		<name>Cauldron</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Playing a witch, you must assemble the six ingredients required to kill off your arch-rival, an evil pumpkin. The ingredients are all located in underground buildings, each of which can only be entered once you've found the appropriate key. The keys are located overground, and you must fly around on your broom to collect them. The overground sections play like standard shoot 'em ups, as your broom is not affected by gravity and can fire bullets using your magic energy. Bats, fireballs and even seagulls are among the many creatures trying to stop you.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Palace</developer>
		<publisher>Palace</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cauldron (1985)(Palace).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cauldron (1985)(Palace).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cauldron_II_The_Pumpkin_Strikes_Back_1986_Palace_Software.z80</path>
		<name>Cauldron II: The Pumpkin Strikes Back</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An evil witch has brought evil and darkness to the enchanted wood, wiping out all but 1 of the innocent pumpkins. As the poem in the instructions sheet explains, the only way to put things right is to capture a lock of her hair, then take it to the cauldron and cast a spell to undo things.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RamJam Corporation, The</developer>
		<publisher>Palace</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cauldron_II_The_Pumpkin_Strikes_Back_1986_Palace_Software.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cauldron_II_The_Pumpkin_Strikes_Back_1986_Palace_Software.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Jet Ski Simulator (1989)(Codemasters)(Side A).z80</path>
		<name>Championship Jet-Ski Simulator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jet Ski-ing is an up andcoming sport - fast furious and above all fun! The Oliver Twins have incorporated Jet Ski-ings' best aspects with some stunningly sophisticated programming.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Philip Oliver, Andrew Oliver</developer>
		<publisher>IBSA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Championship Jet Ski Simulator (1989)(Codemasters)(Side A).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Championship Jet Ski Simulator (1989)(Codemasters)(Side A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chase HQ (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Chase H.Q.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As an undercover agent of Chase Headquarters, your job is to patrol the streets and track down five criminals. You are given a mission briefing before you start which gives information on the suspect and what car they drive. Then you drive across the city without crashing into other cars, and catch up with the criminal's car. To arrest the suspects, you must keep bumping into their car until it is no longer functional. And you have to do this under a strict time limit. You can't afford to crash into cars or buildings or you waste time getting on the road again.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chase HQ (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chase HQ (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chuckie Egg 2 - Choccy Egg (1985)(A &amp; F Software).z80</path>
		<name>Chuckie Egg 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the game, Hen House Harry must build a giant chocolate egg, with the ingredients (cocoa, milk and sugar), that are found in the factory. Eight of each must be included. Also, the eight parts of a toy kit must be found, to place inside the egg. In order to get all the items you must find your way around the factory, avoiding many types of enemy, and solving puzzles using various items that you can carry.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A&amp;J Software</developer>
		<publisher>A&amp;J Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chuckie Egg 2 - Choccy Egg (1985)(A &amp; F Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chuckie Egg 2 - Choccy Egg (1985)(A &amp; F Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CJ's Elephant Antics (1991)(Codemasters)[a].z80</path>
		<name>CJ's Elephant Antics</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>CJ the baby elephant has fled captivity, and is desperate to reach his home in Africa. That means trekking halfway around the world, armed only with an infinite supply of peanuts and a handful of bombs (fortunately more can be collected as you go along).</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genesis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/CJ's Elephant Antics (1991)(Codemasters)[a].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/CJ's Elephant Antics (1991)(Codemasters)[a].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contact Sam Cruise (1986)(Microsphere).z80</path>
		<name>Contact Sam Cruise</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's Whodunit time in this licensed arcade adventure starring Sam Cruise. As Sam you must collect the clues by walking over them, with the hope of finding the killer. Money is an issue as well, as more can be collected, but it will be needed as the game goes on.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Contact Sam Cruise (1986)(Microsphere).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Contact Sam Cruise (1986)(Microsphere).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Curse Of Sherwood, The (1987)(Mastertronic).z80</path>
		<name>Curse of Sherwood, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil cult of Sagalia has taken over Sherwood Forest and installed fear into the hearts of the dwellers. You play the role of Friar Tuck as you search the surrounding area for the objects needed to complete your mission. As you explore you will come across various creatures who will shoot at you and if you're touched by them or their weapons then you lose one of three lives.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Derek Brewster</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Curse Of Sherwood, The (1987)(Mastertronic).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Curse Of Sherwood, The (1987)(Mastertronic).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon (1988)(Mastertronic).tap</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in a post-apocalyptic New York, Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers trained in the fighting style of Sou-Setsu-Ken. Together, they manage a small martial arts training school, teaching their students in self-defense. One day, Billy's girlfriend, Marian, is kidnapped off the street by the "Black Warriors", a savage street gang led by a man named Willy. The Black Warriors demand the Lee brothers disclose their martial arts secrets in exchange for Marian's freedom. The Lee brothers set out on a rescue mission to crush the Black Warriors and save Marian..</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Double Dragon (1988)(Mastertronic).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Double Dragon (1988)(Mastertronic).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dun Darach (1985)(Gargoyle Games).z80</path>
		<name>Dun Darach</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dun Darach may be the first ever videogame prequel – to Tir Na Nog. As such, it features the warrior Cuchulainn of Muirmethne, in a war against the Conachta. When he and his colleague Loeg meet a beautiful woman named Skar in an inn, they do not suspect that she is a spy, and will kidnap Loeg to the secret city of Dun Darach (the 'Oak Fort' in Celtic). Cuchulainn will not stand for this, and sets off to Dun Darach to rescue him.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gargoyle Games Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Gargoyle Games Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dun Darach (1985)(Gargoyle Games).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dun Darach (1985)(Gargoyle Games).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynamite Dan (1985)(Mirrorsoft).z80</path>
		<name>Dynamite Dan</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game starts where Dan lands his airship on the top of the evil Dr Blitzen's hideout. The aim of the game is to find eight sticks of dynamite that are placed randomly around the playing area whilst avoiding the perils of the game such as moving monsters, drowning and falling from great heights. Once Dan has all eight sticks of dynamite, the player must make their way to the central safe to blow it open and steal the plans for the evil doctor's Death Ray and escape to his airship.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rod Bowkett</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dynamite Dan (1985)(Mirrorsoft).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dynamite Dan (1985)(Mirrorsoft).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynamite Dan II - Dr Blitzen And The Islands Of Arcanum (1985)(Mirrorsoft).z80</path>
		<name>Dynamite Dan II: Dr. Blitzen and the Islands of Arcanum</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Implanting subliminal messages in music seemingly worked for Judas Priest - the evil Dr. Blitzen is trying to make it work for himself, by planting messages in popular records. Blitzen has used the 8 islands of Arcanium for this task - each contains a jukebox as well as a record containing a clue to the location of the secret factory in which he produces these horrors. Dynamite Dan is back to put a stop to this, by exploring the 8 islands in turn to find the pieces of the puzzle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mirrorsoft Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dynamite Dan II - Dr Blitzen And The Islands Of Arcanum (1985)(Mirrorsoft).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dynamite Dan II - Dr Blitzen And The Islands Of Arcanum (1985)(Mirrorsoft).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eric And The Floaters (1983)(Hudson Soft).z80</path>
		<name>Eric &amp; the Floaters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first title in the Bomberman series, released as Eric &amp; the Floaters in the UK, introduces the gameplay concept the series is known for, but otherwise bears little resemblance to the later, more famous entries, with series mascot the White Bomberman nowhere in sight.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Sinclair Research</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Eric And The Floaters (1983)(Hudson Soft).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Eric And The Floaters (1983)(Hudson Soft).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exolon (1987)(Hewson Consultants)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Exolon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This action game combines shoot 'em up and platform elements, as you control a flying man who can gain an exoskeletal suit for extra protection (hence the name). Your task is to progress from left to right in each level, either along the ground or by using the arrangement of platforms. Most of the baddies can be avoided rather than shot, and this is often easier, especially as you can duck or jump to avoid them. As well as a standard gun (activated by tapping fire) you also have a limited number of missiles to take out installations (activated by holding down fire, which makes autofire facilities useless).</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Exolon (1987)(Hewson Consultants)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Exolon (1987)(Hewson Consultants)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fairlight - A Prelude (1986)(The Edge)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Fairlight - A Prelude: The Light Revealed</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The land of Fairlight no longer lives up to its name, its culture and society having declined over centuries. The former ruler's castle Avars is shrouded in mystery, and Isvar chooses to investigate it. Unfortunately, he finds himself trapped in a mysterious castle from which he must escape. Viewed isometrically, Isvar's adventure features complex object manipulation: each object has its own physical properties and resultant characteristics in terms of how much else can be carried alongside it. The castle is guarded and full of trolls, who can weaken Isvar's energy - food and wine can restore it.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge, The</developer>
		<publisher>Edge, The</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fairlight - A Prelude (1986)(The Edge)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fairlight - A Prelude (1986)(The Edge)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Feud (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Feud</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wizards Learic and Leanoric have a long-standing feud, and would do anything to see off their rival. As Learic, this is your task. Collecting herbs to cast spells is the main basis of the game. There are 24 herbs and flowers to be collected, which are used to make one of 12 spells (the herbs are only used for 1 spell, so there’s no need to decide which spell you’d prefer to have access to). You can use a combination of the spells (including a teleporter, invisibility and a fireball, which you must work our how to use). Leanoric’s direction relative to yourself is indicated by a compass.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Binary Design, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Feud (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Feud (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Finders Keepers (1985)(Mastertronic)[Magic Knight 1].z80</path>
		<name>Finders Keepers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The King of Isbisima has entrusted you, Magic Knight, with the task of getting a present for his daughter. He sends you into the castle of Spiteland, which is overloading with treasures to uncover. Whether you return with them to please the King, or simply flee with everything you can get, is up to you. Either way, the gameplay is platform-based, with enemies floating around to rob you of energy on contact. There are also scrolling mazes to move through. As you collect objects (often by using some of the other items you collect, to create chemical reactions of sorts and adding an element of lateral thinking), you must try to trade them for the most valuable items you can get.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mastertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Finders Keepers (1985)(Mastertronic)[Magic Knight 1].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Finders Keepers (1985)(Mastertronic)[Magic Knight 1].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Firelord (1986)(Hewson Consultants).z80</path>
		<name>Firelord</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The land of Torot has been oppressed by the Evil Queen; fortunately you (as Sir Galaheart) are on hand to put things right. Initially you have no weaponry as you progress through the 500 screens of Atic Atac-influenced streets and towns, but fireballs can be collected and used against the Queen's forces. Trading is a large part of the game, a unique aspect for a game of this type at the time. While many objects are lying around, many more must be obtained by entering the homes of people, and negotiating with them to arrange a swap. You can also attempt to steal from them, but you risk being caught and sentenced to death (losing a life in the process).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Firelord (1986)(Hewson Consultants).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Firelord (1986)(Hewson Consultants).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FlyingShark.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Flying Shark</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Top Down shooter similar to Raiden. You start off with four lives and three bombs.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Ltd, Dominic Robinson, John Cumming, Gavin Wade, Drew Northcott</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/FlyingShark.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/FlyingShark.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frankie Goes To Hollywood (1985)(Ocean Software).z80</path>
		<name>Frankie Goes to Hollywood</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Playing a thoroughly drab, mundane and predictable character, your aim is to become interesting enough to reach the Pleasuredome. After discovering a gruesome murder, your interest in something greater than the routine of 80s Liverpool is awoken. You explore the streets and houses in the search of a way out. The main basis of the game involves picking up objects and using them in the correct way - most objects have more than one potential use, and misusing them is the only way the game can be lost. There are several sub-games along the way, including shoot 'em ups, a maze and a jigsaw puzzle.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Frankie Goes To Hollywood (1985)(Ocean Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Frankie Goes To Hollywood (1985)(Ocean Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fruit Machine Simulator 2 - Mega Trek (1990)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Fruit Machine Simulator 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the sequel to Codemaster's Fruit Machine Simulator and is programmed by the same people who developed the original.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fruit Machine Simulator 2 - Mega Trek (1990)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fruit Machine Simulator 2 - Mega Trek (1990)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet (1987)(US Gold).tap</path>
		<name>Gauntlet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gauntlet, the original arcade smash hit, is a fighting game where you choose a character and let rip into the hordes of enemies that assault you on you way to the end of the level. One or two players must make their way through 100 levels of mayhem and magic.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gauntlet (1987)(US Gold).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gauntlet (1987)(US Gold).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elite128.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Elite</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You have a ship with virtually no equipment. Take her and trade among the different star systems. You can be safe and trade on razor-thin margins among the safe systems, or take some risks and trade with anarchic systems while watching out for pirates. You can save on fuel costs by buying a fuel scoop and fly near the sun, but again, watch out for pirates! Or be a pirate yourself and raid other ships. Don't get a bad rep as the police will come after you. Dock with space stations and do your trades (some may take contraband) Upgrade your ship with your proceeds with better weapons.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus, Philip Mochan, Ricardo J.M. Pinto, Dominic M.N. Prior, Mark Wighton</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird Software Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Elite128.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Elite128.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Prix Simulator (1987)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Grand Prix Simulator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Calling it a 'simulator' was a stretch, as with many of Codemasters' titles. In reality it was an overhead-view Super Sprint style arcade racer for 1 or 2 players, similar in many ways to the company's BMX Simulator. There were up to 14 circuits depending on the format, which incorporated many underpasses (some of them deliberately unrealistic) and tight curves. There were oil slicks to avoid and points bonuses to pick up. The cars have slow acceleration but a lot of power down the straights. You are scored based on your overall time and your fastest lap. Lose to the computer car and it's game over.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Grand Prix Simulator (1987)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Grand Prix Simulator (1987)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Prix Simulator 2 (1989)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Grand Prix Simulator 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A sequel to the previous Grand Prix Simulator, a popular Super Sprint style racing game. As before, the action is viewed from overhead across a succession of tracks featuring hairpins, oil slicks and similar hazards. You must complete each race within the time limit; and time left after one race is added to your allowance on the next one. After the race you can view a replay.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./boxart/Grand Prix Simulator 2 (1989)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Grand Prix Simulator 2 (1989)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Great Escape, The (1986)(Ocean Software).z80</path>
		<name>Great Escape, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Great Escape is an isometric action-adventure game. Gather round, kids, and listen to grandpa tell of his time as a prisoner of war in Germany. ‘Twas back in 1942. Those were rough times, lads. Rough times. Been shot down in my plane. Darn shame it was, it being a good plane and all. Next I know, there’s this group of German soldiers standing round me, and off we go to a P.O.W. camp.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Great Escape, The (1986)(Ocean Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Great Escape, The (1986)(Ocean Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun Fright (1985)(Ultimate).z80</path>
		<name>Gunfright</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cowboy Shooting Game.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate Play the Game</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gun Fright (1985)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gun Fright (1985)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyroscope (1985)(Melbourne House).z80</path>
		<name>Gyroscope</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Releasing a game which resembles a well-known arcade game before any official license can be released was always a challenge for publishers, and in this case Melbourne House released a game similar to Marble Madness. Controlling a gyroscope, you most navigate your way down a sloping track full of hazards.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Catalyst Coders</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gyroscope (1985)(Melbourne House).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gyroscope (1985)(Melbourne House).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harrier Attack (1983)(Durell).z80</path>
		<name>Harrier Attack!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Harrier Attack! is viewed from the side, and instantly resembles titles such as Wings of Fury and Jetstrike. You're on board a Harrier and must reach the enemy island, destroying planes and ground installations as you go, then destroy their base and fly back to yours. Your Harrier is armed with both bombs and a gun. You must be careful not to fly at full speed throughout your journey as fuel is limited. There are 5 difficulty levels - the latter ones increase the volume and pace of the enemy, and add more mountains to avoid.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Durell Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Harrier Attack (1983)(Durell).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Harrier Attack (1983)(Durell).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Head Over Heels (1987)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Head over Heels</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Two distinct characters called Mr Head and Mr Heels are played in this arcade adventure. They are separated at the shoulders but capable of joining together to maximize their abilities in some situations (but reduce them in others, so they can be split again). The game is presented from an isometric perspective, and presents the characters with a number of puzzles involving switches, jumps and climbs. The levels are 3 dimensional, and the characters must collect crowns as they progress. Objects can be picked up and manipulated as necessary.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Head Over Heels (1987)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Head Over Heels (1987)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Highway Encounter (1985)(Vortex Software).z80</path>
		<name>Highway Encounter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this isometric 3D action-strategy game, the player uses a Vorton droid to push a bomb to the end of the highway into an alien base. There are 30 screens, most of them filled with hazards trying to block (like barrels) or destroy (mines and aliens) your bomb. The perspective and guidance concept are not the game's only original features; there are 4 more bombs with you, representing your extra lives - pushing you forward on your mission. If these other Vortons are destroyed, one of your extra lives is lost without the player being able to use it.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vortex Software</developer>
		<publisher>Vortex Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Highway Encounter (1985)(Vortex Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Highway Encounter (1985)(Vortex Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Horace Goes Skiing (1982)(Psion).z80</path>
		<name>Horace Goes Skiing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A more accurate title for this would be "Horace Goes Skiing, but only if he can brave a Frogger clone first", as you start the game by having to reach the ski shop to get skis, and then get back across to reach the slopes. The road is full of cars and bikes, contact with each of which costs $10 in ambulance fees out of your starting $40, and the skis themselves cost $10. The actual skiing section has a pseudo-3D view, similar to a roving camera mounted above the course.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psion Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sinclair Research</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Horace Goes Skiing (1982)(Psion).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Horace Goes Skiing (1982)(Psion).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Match Day (1987)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>International Match Day</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Football viceo game part of the match day series. International Match Day is an Improved version of Match Day with better sound and full screen images.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jon Ritman, Chris Clarke, F. David Thorpe</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/International Match Day (1987)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/International Match Day (1987)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jack The Nipper (1986)(Gremlin Graphics).z80</path>
		<name>Jack the Nipper</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jack is an evil and wicked toddler. You play Jack and you have to cause as much trouble without being penalized for it. To see how naughty you've been there is a naughtyometer at the bottom of the screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jack The Nipper (1986)(Gremlin Graphics).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jack The Nipper (1986)(Gremlin Graphics).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Set Willy 2 - The Final Frontier (1985)(Software Projects).z80</path>
		<name>Jet Set Willy II: The Final Frontier</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This platform game is the sequel of Jet Set Willy. Again has each room its own hazards, such as spikes, revolving razors and ropes. The route through the house must be navigated carefully, due to the multiple entrances to some rooms - this is perhaps the first action game where mapping is an advantage. Another innovation, to the chagrin of players everywhere, is manual protection - a sheet of colour-coded numbers.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Projects Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Software Projects Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jet Set Willy 2 - The Final Frontier (1985)(Software Projects).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jet Set Willy 2 - The Final Frontier (1985)(Software Projects).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kikstart 2 (1988)(Mastertronic).z80</path>
		<name>Kikstart 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based around the Kikstart TV show, the game allows you to recreate all those death-defying stunts in the comparative safety of your home. Viewed from the side, there are many hazards to avoid along the way. Some of these include steps to jump over, tyres and hedges to plough through at maximum speed, and mud which will slow you down. 24 courses are built in, and you can choose a set of 5 of these to race at a time, or let the computer choose them at random. More importantly, a course designer allowing you to create one of your own is included, with full control of the placement of the many hazards.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mr Chip Software</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kikstart 2 (1988)(Mastertronic).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kikstart 2 (1988)(Mastertronic).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).z80</path>
		<name>Knight Lore</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game uses the isometric viewpoint in a manner similar to the later Head Over Heels, using monochrome but detailed graphics and techniques to avoid flickering sprites. The game lasts for 40 days and nights - at night your character turns into a werewolf. Ultimate's individual style of eschewing straightforward instuctions in favour of feature lists and riddles is put to good use here, with the story detailed in a rhyming poem of sorts.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Knight Lore (1984)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knight Tyme (1986)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 3].z80</path>
		<name>Knight Tyme</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After rescuing the wizard Gimbal, the Magic Knight finds himself transported into the 25th century aboard the peaceful trade starship USS Pisces. He must find a way back to his own time. Knight Tyme is the third game of the Magic Knight series. As in Spellbound, the previous game, the player interacts with the environment through the "Windimation" system: pressing a button brings up a window with a list of commands (pick up/drop/take/give an object, examine, command a character, read something, cast a spell and wear/unwear object).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mastertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Added Dimension</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Knight Tyme (1986)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 3].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Knight Tyme (1986)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 3].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).z80</path>
		<name>Lunar Jetman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once again taking on the role of Jetman, players find themselves on the surface of a small purple moon. Similarly to its predecessor, the player can move around slowly on foot, or use a jetpack to leave the ground and navigate the moon faster. However, unlike Jetpac, Jetman's jetpack has limited fuel and must be topped up regularly.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lunar Jetman (1983)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Midnight Resistance</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Midnight Resistance fighters are up against the awesome powers of mad scientist King Crimson and his Crimson Corps. Crimson has kidnapped your scientist grandfather and five more of your relatives, and aims to put his advanced plans to evil use. Take control of a Resistance fighter in this scrolling shoot 'em up consisting of nine platform-based levels, each ending with a Boss to defeat.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Midnight Resistance (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mikie (1985)(Imagine Software).z80</path>
		<name>Mikie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mikie puts you in charge of Mikie, a high school student who likes to win hearts of every girl that he can lay his eyes on. There are several classrooms to explore like the Quantum Physics Room, Locker Room, Canteen, the Aerobics Dancing Class, and the Playground. In each classroom, Mikie has to collect all the hearts that are found in each classroom to form a message. In order to collect these hearts, Mikie must stand somewhere near them and shout out. There are two type of hearts: small and large. Mikie needs to shout out only once to collect the small hearts, and multiple times to collect the large ones.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mikie (1985)(Imagine Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mikie (1985)(Imagine Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Myth - History In The Making (1989)(System 3 Software).z80</path>
		<name>Myth: History in the Making</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this platform game, you are a mere mortal who has been called by the Gods to defeat several mythological creatures that have been turned bad by the evil Dameron. Myth: History in the Making is a platform game with a lot of fighting. The levels of this game deal with different mythologies, from ancient Greece to the Vikings, over to Valhalla (where none other than the hammer-wielding Thor awaits you), and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Myth - History In The Making (1989)(System 3 Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Myth - History In The Making (1989)(System 3 Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nixy128k_v1.tap</path>
		<name>Nixy the Glade Sprite</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Nixy the Glade Sprite is charged with protecting the Gaia stone. This stone gives life to the vegetation of the forest but it's been corrupted and now flowers, plants, and the once-friendly Mushroom people have been mutated into dangerous monsters. To restore things back to normal, the Gaia stone must be collected and cleansed with water from the sacred pool.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bubblesoft Games</developer>
		<publisher>Bubblesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nixy128k_v1.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nixy128k_v1.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paperboy (1986)(Elite Systems).z80</path>
		<name>Paperboy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, the object of Paperboy is to deliver papers to your customers while inflicting as much damage as possible to the houses of your non-customers. To make things more difficult, numerous obstacles get in your way including construction workers, rogue tires, skateboarders, dogs and cats, cars, and even the occasional tornado.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Paperboy (1986)(Elite Systems).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Paperboy (1986)(Elite Systems).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pssst_1983_Ultimate_Play_The_Game_16K.z80</path>
		<name>Pssst</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Growing the best Thyrgodian Megga Chrisanthodil possible is the sole purpose of Robbie the Robot. When insects invade his garden, he has to stop them ruining his work. He has a canister of insect repellent, a smoke-bomb and a startling streamer, each placed on walls at the side of his garden. Each will stun any particular vermin, but you will need to find out exactly what kills what.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pssst_1983_Ultimate_Play_The_Game_16K.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pssst_1983_Ultimate_Play_The_Game_16K.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble 2 - Rainbow Islands (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Rainbow Islands: The Story of Bubble Bobble 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sequel to Bubble Bobble, Rainbow Islands sees Bub and Bob (in 2 player mode), who are now curiously small boys rather than dinosaurs, attempting to rid the Rainbow Islands of bad guys. Using the power to cast rainbows, trapping anything underneath, the boys must ascend vertically 4 levels each island, with a big, bad boss at the end of each. By trapping beasts under your rainbows, then jumping on them to break them you can collect seven different colored gems, and there are also power-ups for extra speed and rainbows.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bubble Bobble 2 - Rainbow Islands (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bubble Bobble 2 - Rainbow Islands (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rana Rama (19xx)(Hewson Consultants).z80</path>
		<name>Rana Rama</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The purpose of apprentice courses is for young people to learn a trade gradually, without putting yourself or your employers at risk. Unfortunately, nobody explained this to Wizard’s apprentice Mervyn, before he tried to cast a spell to make him irresistible to females, as the spell misfired, and made him attractive only to female frogs. However, his dungeon was soon invaded, and Mervyn was not killed, as he appeared to be a humble frog.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rana Rama (19xx)(Hewson Consultants).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rana Rama (19xx)(Hewson Consultants).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rebelstar - 2 Player (1986)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Rebelstar</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A turn-based, tactical squad combat game for one or two players, from the creator of the later X-COM series. Moonbase Delta may look like an unassuming mining colony, but in fact, it is the secret location of the ISAAC super-computer, used by the Empire to break the Rebels' secret codes. The Rebelstar Raiders' mission is to break in, get past the patrolling robot guards and destroy the computer. It won't be easy.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Julian Gollop</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rebelstar - 2 Player (1986)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rebelstar - 2 Player (1986)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Renegade (1987)(Imagine Software)[128K].z80</path>
		<name>Renegade</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is set on the mean streets of Brooklyn, which you must venture through to meet your girlfriend, and then rescue her from her kidnappers. This is split into five levels, taking you through the subway and the docks as well as some inhospitable streets. A wide range of aggressive moves are on offer, including headbutts, kicks, punches and flying kicks. Much of the game's violence is depicted in a fairly tongue-in-cheek style, with an element of attempted humour along the way.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Renegade (1987)(Imagine Software)[128K].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Renegade (1987)(Imagine Software)[128K].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./River Raid (1982)(Activision).z80</path>
		<name>River Raid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>River Raid is a vertically scrolling action game. You fly a jet up a river in an attempt to destroy bridges which are vital to the enemy. The river is heavily guarded, however, with balloons, ships, choppers, and enemy aircraft trying to stop you. Along the way you will need to fly over fuel stations to refuel your jet and keep flying. The plane is armed with a cannon with unlimited ammo. It can be used to destroy the enemy vehicles and bridges, but a careless player can accidentally destroy a fuel station. Colliding with the riverbanks or with the enemy aircraft destroys your plane and makes you lose a life.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/River Raid (1982)(Activision).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/River Raid (1982)(Activision).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Robocop (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>RoboCop</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Patrolman Alex Murphy was killed on the streets of Detroit. The major corporation there, Omni Consumer Products (OCP) saw an opportunity to sell a new kind of law enforcement officer to the troubled city. They took what was left of Murphy, encased it in titanium armor, wiped his memory and created RoboCop. Now it's up to RoboCop to clean the streets of Detroit and eliminate the one responsible for his murder, Clarence Boddicker. But it looks like Clarence might not be the kingpin of this town. Based on the 1987 movie of the same name, RoboCop allows the player to control RoboCop.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Robocop (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Robocop (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Robocop 2 (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>RoboCop 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>RoboCop 2 is a mission-based platform game. Missions have various objectives, such as destroying nukes or killing all the enemies. If you didn't destroy/kill enough, you'll be transported to a training mission, which is a first-person perspective shoot 'em up. Should you also fail the training, you must go to the beginning of the previous mission. Successfully completed mission or enough points scored by training allow you to proceed to the next stage. Unlike in the first RoboCop, there's no time limit, and you are able to jump.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Robocop 2 (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Robocop 2 (1990)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rockstar Ate My Hamster (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Rock Star Ate My Hamster</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Cecil Pitt, a wannabe rock star manager. You must choose from 1-4 rock stars (with names such as Tina Turnoff and Wacko Jacko) to manage by viewing their audition tapes. Once you chosen your artists you then have to choose what kind of gear to get them - spanking new, second hand or dodgy. The dodgy gear is dirt cheap but you might pay for your choice later on in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rockstar Ate My Hamster (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rockstar Ate My Hamster (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Run The Gauntlet (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Run the Gauntlet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Competitors in this ITV television game show had to show their prowess on a range of vehicles including Buggys, Speedboats, Quad Bikes, Jetskis and Inflatables. Players of this licensed version must do the same, on horizontally and vertically scrolling levels on land and water.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Impact Software Development, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Run The Gauntlet (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Run The Gauntlet (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (1987)(Durell)[a5].z80</path>
		<name>Saboteur II: Avenging Angel</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The ninja hero of the original Saboteur game has been killed, and his sister Nina is out to avenge this injustice. She has an array of kung-fu moves on offer, and must put them to use through 700 screens of action. The game design is very similar to the original, right down to the unusual background graphical style. The sections of the game are on multiple levels, separated mainly by ladders, and with lots of weapons and ammunition to pick up along the way. To beat the game you'll have to collect tapes and collect a 14-part computer code.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Durell</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (1987)(Durell)[a5].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Saboteur II - Avenging Angel (1987)(Durell)[a5].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scuba Dive (1983)(Durell).z80</path>
		<name>Scuba Dive</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take on the role of a fearless pearl diver, as you plunge into the unknown ocean depths! You'll be swimming with sharks, squid, jellyfish and all manner of strange and deadly creatures. When you find a clam, wait for its shell to open, then swoop down and grab your prize!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Durell Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Scuba Dive (1983)(Durell).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Scuba Dive (1983)(Durell).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scuba Kidz (1989)(Silverbird).z80</path>
		<name>Scuba Kidz</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players take on the role of a scuba driver, and it is up to them to navigate a series of underwater caves in search of their kidnapped friends. While exploring these caves, their air supply depletes so they must go up to the surface to refuel on air. Finding an air tank enables players to swim underwater for a longer period of time. If players have no air left, the game is over.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silverbird Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Silverbird Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Scuba Kidz (1989)(Silverbird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Scuba Kidz (1989)(Silverbird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silk Worm (1988)(Mastertronic)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Silk Worm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Silk Worm is a classic horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up based on the 1988 Tecmo arcade game. The main difference between this game and many other side-scrolling shoot-em-ups is that you got to be on land as well as in the air.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Silk Worm (1988)(Mastertronic)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Silk Worm (1988)(Mastertronic)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skool Daze (1985)(Microsphere).z80</path>
		<name>Skool Daze</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This highly original game concept sets you as Eric, a typical scamp of a schoolboy whose school report is due, and it is so bad that his parents can't be allowed to see it. This means retrieving it from the headmaster's safe, by obtaining every piece of the pass-code from the teachers, by hitting each of the shields with your catapult. All this has to be done around all the rigors of a typical school day. you must go to class when the bell goes, or else it's detention, and the other kids will often play around to block you.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Skool Daze (1985)(Microsphere).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Skool Daze (1985)(Microsphere).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spellbound (1985)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 2].z80</path>
		<name>Spellbound</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Magic Knight's second game (after Finders Keepers) sees him travelling through time to rescue 8 people including his tutor Gimbal, who have become locked in time thanks to a faulty spell. The game invented a whole new control system, essentially pioneering the use of icons and windows in adventure games. You control a pointing finger, which can be moved onto each of the menus to reveal sub-menus, which contain the main options for object manipulation.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mastertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Added Dimension</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spellbound (1985)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 2].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spellbound (1985)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 2].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spike In Transylvania (1991)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Spike in Transylvania</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After a rough crossing of the North Sea, Spike the Viking is washed ashore. He ends up in Transilvania, which seems to be just an ordinary village. However, he finds out that his shipmates have been captured, and are being imprisoned in the dungeons of the local castle. Spike must rescue his friends from the mysterious castle, but first he has to escape from the (apparently friendly) villager's house where he finds himself, as the door won't open.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genesis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spike In Transylvania (1991)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spike In Transylvania (1991)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spy Hunter (1985)(US Gold).z80</path>
		<name>Spy Hunter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A conversion of the arcade game, Spy Hunter is a driving action game played from an overhead point of view. Your car is equipped with machine guns to help you get past the numerous enemies out on the road (be careful not to shoot any civilians, though!) Occasionally you will come across a weapons van, and if you drive into the back of the van your car becomes equipped with a second weapon (such as smoke screen, oil slick, or missiles.) At several points the road splits and you can enter a boathouse which transforms your car into a boat temporarily.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bally Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spy Hunter (1985)(US Gold).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spy Hunter (1985)(US Gold).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spy Vs. Spy (1985)(Beyond).z80</path>
		<name>Spy vs Spy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>M.A.D. magazine’s comic strip of the same name comes to life in this game which was designed for one or two players. The innovative split-screen shows both spies at the same time. Play with a friend or against the machine. The black crow and the white crow are out to beat each other before the time bell rings. Find the needed objects by digging through drawers, closets and furniture in the house. Foil your opponent by setting creative booby traps in the various rooms (a bomb in a dresser drawer, for instance). Fights ensue when both spies enter the same room.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software</developer>
		<publisher>Beyond - Challenging Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spy Vs. Spy (1985)(Beyond).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spy Vs. Spy (1985)(Beyond).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starquake (1985)(Bubble Bus Software).z80</path>
		<name>Starquake</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As BLOB, the Bio-Logically Operated Being, you are sent into an unstable planet and charged with the task of preventing it from exploding. This involves collecting various items (the exact combination is different every time you load the game) and taking them to the planet's core.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bubble Bus Software</developer>
		<publisher>Zafiro</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Starquake (1985)(Bubble Bus Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Starquake (1985)(Bubble Bus Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stop The Express (1983)(Hudson Soft).z80</path>
		<name>Stop the Express</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The ITA Express is under the control of the vicious Redmen, and cannot be allowed to continue its momentum. This is where you come in as a Security Guard, as you start on top of the final carriage of the train and must walk across it, jumping over the gaps, to reach the front. Redmen must be kicked into oblivion with a precise contact before they can throw you off the train; they will also throw knives, which must be ducked. You can turn the tables thanks to the Snakebird, which will pick you up if you jump into it, and allow you to drop on top of a Redman. You have a limited amount of time to reach the front.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Sinclair Research</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stop The Express (1983)(Hudson Soft).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stop The Express (1983)(Hudson Soft).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stormbringer (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 4].z80</path>
		<name>Stormbringer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Stormbringer is the fourth and final game to star Magic Knight, and the only one to make it onto 16-bit systems. Magic Knight must meet with his alter-ego, the Off-White Knight, by reaching his castle hideout - which means clearing 64 screens of adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mastertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Added Dimension</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stormbringer (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 4].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stormbringer (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k)[Magic Knight 4].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TLL - Tornado Low Level (1984)(Vortex Software).z80</path>
		<name>T.L.L.: Tornado Low Level</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>TLL sets you as a skilled pilot who must take on a tough mission - shooting out six discs representing enemy strongholds in build-up areas. This must be done by lowering your altitude as you approach each one, making it crucial to avoid trees and buildings which are closer to ground level.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vortex Software</developer>
		<publisher>Vortex Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/TLL - Tornado Low Level (1984)(Vortex Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/TLL - Tornado Low Level (1984)(Vortex Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thanatos (1986)(Durell)[a].z80</path>
		<name>Thanatos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player adopts the role of a dragon, Thanatos the Destroyer, who must rescue a sorceress Eros from imprisonment by an evil Lord of the underworld.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Durell</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Thanatos (1986)(Durell)[a].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Thanatos (1986)(Durell)[a].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords Of Midnight, The (1984)(Beyond).z80</path>
		<name>Lords of Midnight, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Lords of Midnight brings to life this epic land, as Doomdark's forces aim to wrest control of its 4000 screens. Your initial party of the task contains four fighters - Luxor the Moonprince, Morkin (his son), Corleth the Fey and Rothron the Wise, each of whom has their own characteristics. Many more lords can be recruited as the game progresses, with names such as Lord Dreams, Lord Blood and the Utarg of Utarg. If Luxor is killed, only Morkin remains under human control.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mike Singleton</developer>
		<publisher>Beyond Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lords Of Midnight, The (1984)(Beyond).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lords Of Midnight, The (1984)(Beyond).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sacred Armour Of Antiriad, The (1986)(Palace).z80</path>
		<name>Sacred Armour of Antiriad, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mixture of a platform and maze game. The player controls Tal who at the start is simply a man dressed in a lioncloth with thrown rocks as his only weapon.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chris Stangroom, Dan Malone, Richard Joseph</developer>
		<publisher>Palace</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sacred Armour Of Antiriad, The (1986)(Palace).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sacred Armour Of Antiriad, The (1986)(Palace).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trapdoor, The (1986)(Macmillan).z80</path>
		<name>Trap Door, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Berk is trying to obtain a chest of treasure from within a castle inhabited by the Bad Tempered Thing. This involves completing five tasks, although a learner mode in which only 4 are required is also provided. The first task is to provide a can of worms, whilst crushed eyeballs must be provided for task two. You then need to boil Slimies, fry eggs (getting them is a dilemma in itself), and then force everything back into the trapdoor.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Don Priestley</developer>
		<publisher>Piranha</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Trapdoor, The (1986)(Macmillan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Trapdoor, The (1986)(Macmillan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Three Weeks In Paradise (1986)(Mikro-Gen)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Three Weeks in Paradise</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This place would indeed be paradise, were it not for the fact that the Can Nibbles inhabit it. Herbert and Wilma Week are trapped by them, so Wally has become the third Week in paradise in his attempt at rescuing them. This is an arcade adventure resembling the other Wally Week games, although it represents David Perry's design debut. There are many animals to avoid including stinging bees and butterflies, but the toughest foe is the Indian chief, best avoided with a well-timed jump. There are multi-stage puzzles to solve on each screen, and a limit of carrying 2 objects at a time.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mikro-Gen Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Mikro-Gen Ltd</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Three Weeks In Paradise (1986)(Mikro-Gen)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Three Weeks In Paradise (1986)(Mikro-Gen)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trashman (19xx)(New Generation Software).z80</path>
		<name>Trashman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>While few young people aspire to the role of a Dustman, New Generation Software felt they would enjoy pretending to be one on this innovative arcade game. Each section presents you with a road of houses, drawn from forced-perspective 3D, with flick-scrolling as you move up the road. Each house's dustbin must be collected, emptied and replaced within the time limit, which is indicated by the Bonus timer at the top of the screen. If this reaches zero, you receive the first of 3 warnings - a third sees you out of a job.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New Generation Software</developer>
		<publisher>Microbyte</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Trashman (19xx)(New Generation Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Trashman (19xx)(New Generation Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Underwurlde (1984)(Ultimate).z80</path>
		<name>Underwurlde</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sabreman’s second game (following Sabre Wulf and preceding Knight Lore and Pentagram) finds him trapped in an underground cavern network, split into nearly 600 side-viewed screens. There are three ways to escape, each protected by a guardian who can be killed using one of the three major weapons you can locate – a dagger, a torch and a knife. As you explore the levels, you will encounter randomly-moving nasties, who can’t kill you but can knock you off your path and cause you to fall. Eagles can grab and drop you in mid-air. Falls of much more than a screen’s height cost you a life, although extra ones are available. Jewels can be collected for temporary invincibility.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Underwurlde (1984)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Underwurlde (1984)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wacky Darts (1991)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Wacky Darts</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The bar-room game of darts involves aiming small projectiles at a circular board. The board is divided into 20 shapes around the edge, each of which has a value from 1 to 20 points, a special 'double' area around the edge, and a special 'treble' area in the middle (each of which multiply the shot score). There is also a Bullseye right in the middle for 50 points, and an Outer Bull around it, worth 25 points.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Red Software</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wacky Darts (1991)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wacky Darts (1991)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wheelie (1983)(Microsphere).z80</path>
		<name>Wheelie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Wheelie you ride a Zedexaki bike (a combination of the famous Kawasaki brand and the ZX in ZX Spectrum), but this is no ordinary racing game. You are trapped in Nightmare Park, and must find an escape before you can race the Ghost Rider. The park is made up of four linked levels of road, which you can move up and down at by finding a ramp headed in that direction and moving the joystick in that direction. Standard direction changes on each piece of road must also be navigated.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Microsphere Computer Services Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wheelie (1983)(Microsphere).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wheelie (1983)(Microsphere).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wriggler (1985)(Romantic Robot).z80</path>
		<name>Wriggler</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of the few games to set you as a maggot, in Wriggler you must negotiate the four stages of the Maggot Marathon. This involves trekking through a garden, a shrubbery, an underground lair, and finally a mansion. Viewed form above the game is maze-based, with lots of Atic Atac style sections where you can see other parts of the level on the same screen, but can't access them because the design of the maze puts something in the way. Graphics are quite large and chunky - this is perhaps the closest anyone came to borrowing Rapscallion's unusual visual design.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Devonshire House</developer>
		<publisher>Romantic Robot UK</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wriggler (1985)(Romantic Robot).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wriggler (1985)(Romantic Robot).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type (1988)(Activision)(128k).zip</path>
		<name>R-Type</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>R-Type is a side scrolling shoot 'em up best known for its extremely tough and strategic gameplay. You control the R-9 spaceship as it launches a last-ditch effort to repel the evil Bydo empire. The R-9 comes equipped as standard with a small gun which can only take down the smallest of enemies without firing several shots.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Electric Dreams Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/R-Type (1988)(Activision)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R-Type (1988)(Activision)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Movie (1986)(Imagine Software)[a].zip</path>
		<name>Movie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The feel of a gangster movie is recreated isometrically in this game. You play a private detective who has the task of retrieving a vital cassette from a Mob boss' hideout. Two twin girls are in the area - one is on your side, the other is connected to the mob. Needless to say, you will have to work out who you can trust. You control the detective with either directional (key or joystick press corresponds to motion) or rotational (forward to move, left or right to rotate) control. Pressing fire activates the main command menu, which allows you to pick up or drop objects, use your gun, and communicate with people. You can carry 3 items at a time; a command exists to swap between them.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dusko Dimitrijevic, Dragoljub Andjelkovic, F. David Thorpe</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Movie (1986)(Imagine Software)[a].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Movie (1986)(Imagine Software)[a].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Operation Wolf (1988)(Ocean Software)[h](128k).zip</path>
		<name>Operation Wolf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You have been recruited for Operation Wolf, a desperate attempt to rescue prisoners from the enemy. Through a series of missions, you'll engage a variety of enemies, from soldiers to ninjas, patrol boats to helicopters, and more. Can you carry the day? Operation Wolf is an arcade conversion of the game by Taito.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Operation Wolf (1988)(Ocean Software)[h](128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Operation Wolf (1988)(Ocean Software)[h](128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sentinel, The (1987)(Firebird).zip</path>
		<name>Sentinel, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In The Sentinel, the player takes the role of a Synthoid a telepathic robot who has to take control of a number of surreal, checkered landscapes of hills and valleys.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Geoffrey J. Crammond</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sentinel, The (1987)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sentinel, The (1987)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./HallsOfTheThings(FirebirdSoftwareLtd).tap.zip</path>
		<name>Halls of the Things, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Using the gaming engine and graphical style that would be seen again in The Warlock Of Firetop Mountain, Halls of the Things places our adventurous hero in a randomly generated tower. A long hallway with seven doorways in it at the start offers the player the opportunity to enter dungeon areas of varying difficulty (easiest and more open at the top, hardest at the bottom). In these areas of the tower, the player can explore, finding treasure and elixir bottles (which can be used to replenish the player's magic). Of course, things aren't that simple.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Design Design</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Computing</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/HallsOfTheThings(FirebirdSoftwareLtd).tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/HallsOfTheThings(FirebirdSoftwareLtd).tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien 8 (1985)(Ultimate).zip</path>
		<name>Alien 8</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is a puzzle solving game. You are on board a space ship that is heading towards a remote planet. The Cryonaughts, the name of the planets inhabitants have been frozen during the journey. You have to find 24 valves and the cryogenic chambers that they are to be plugged into before the ship reaches its destination. The ship contains many rooms filled with obstacles that you have to negotiate. There are several types of enemies such as Dalek-like mice and clockwork mice. Both should be avoided! You might need a valve to climb over some walls.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien 8 (1985)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien 8 (1985)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cookie (1983)(Ultimate).zip</path>
		<name>Cookie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the game Charlie the Chef has to bake a cake, but the ingredients (Mixed Peel, Chunky Chocolate, Crafty Cheese, Sneaky Sugar and Colonel Custard) are reluctant. To bake the cake Charile have to mix ten ingredients in the cake but a whole lot of other things (nuts, bolts, screws) flies around and end up in the mix as well and spoil the cake. So Charlie have to watch out what and what not to but in the mix. Every time a non-eatable item is mixed in Charlie have to but in an extra eatable item.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tim Stamper, Chris Stamper (Ultimate Play the Game)</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cookie (1983)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cookie (1983)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./All Or Nothing (1984)(Abbex Electronics)[Speech].zip</path>
		<name>All or Nothing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The mission in All or Nothing is to retrieve secret files from an enemy camp and escape, all within a time limit. The game has an isometric display that utilises four cameras. If the character is obscured by an object, the camera will change automatically to keep the character in view.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paul W. Reynolds</developer>
		<publisher>Abbex Electronics</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/All Or Nothing (1984)(Abbex Electronics)[Speech].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/All Or Nothing (1984)(Abbex Electronics)[Speech].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chaos - The Battle Of The Wizards (1985)(Games Workshop).z80</path>
		<name>Chaos: The Battle of Wizards</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chaos: The Battle of Wizards is a fantasy strategy game written by Julian Gollop, who later became famous for X-Com. In it you are a wizard who battles it out against up to seven other wizards that can be both player and/or computer controlled. The last one alive wins. The game is turn based and each turn is divided in two parts. In the first you select and cast spells and movement is done in the second. There are several different spells available. Some of them let you summon creatures to attack the opponent while others will improve your abilities or are offensive (like lightning) or defensive (summon castles).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Julian Gollop, Le Doux</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chaos - The Battle Of The Wizards (1985)(Games Workshop).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chaos - The Battle Of The Wizards (1985)(Games Workshop).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fruit Machine Simulator - Cash Bash (1987)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Fruit Machine Simulator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Billed as the first real fruit machine simulator this is a game for 1-4 players that starts you off with £1.50 and sets about helping the player lose it.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fruit Machine Simulator - Cash Bash (1987)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fruit Machine Simulator - Cash Bash (1987)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rescue (1987)(Mastertronic).z80</path>
		<name>Rescue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Aliens are attacking the research station. As the security chief you have to guide the scientists to the rescue ship, along with their experiments, when they each wake up and start running around. Rescue as many as you can, because one of them has the answer to winning the whole war, but you don't know which. And don't forget to collect fuel for the trip.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Icon Design Ltd, Ste L. Cork, Mark O'Neill, Tiny Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rescue (1987)(Mastertronic).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rescue (1987)(Mastertronic).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost Hunters (1987)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Ghost Hunters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hunk Studbuckles brother Chuck answered the call to go to Nightmare Mansion and rid it off the ghouls and ghosts that inhabit the place.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Oliver Twins</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ghost Hunters (1987)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ghost Hunters (1987)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Manic Miner (1983)(Bug-Byte Software).z80</path>
		<name>Manic Miner</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play the role of Miner Willy, a bold explorer and adventurer. He discovers a network of underground caverns used by an advanced but now extinct civilization, and realizes that the mines contain lucrative metal ores. Through 20 caverns, you must collect all treasures before all time (air) runs out, watching out for the nasty guardians, the obstacles, dead falls, quicksands and all elements to be found in a classic platform game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Matthew Smith</developer>
		<publisher>Software Projects</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Manic Miner (1983)(Bug-Byte Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Manic Miner (1983)(Bug-Byte Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sir Lancelot (1984)(Melbourne House).z80</path>
		<name>Sir Lancelot</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this Manic Miner variant Sir Lancelot is exploring a castle in the hope of finding treasures. He must navigate his way through 24 platform screens (in a predefined order on the Spectrum but in any order on the Amstrad), collecting every object on each one to reveal the exit within a time limit. There are enemies on fixed attack paths to avoid - Lancelot has no weapon but can jump, and survive any length of fall.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Studio B Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sir Lancelot (1984)(Melbourne House).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sir Lancelot (1984)(Melbourne House).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Robin Hood (1987)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Super Robin Hood</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Robin Hood, the world's first socialist, pushes wealth redistribution to one side here - his only concern is rescuing Maid Marion from the clutches of the Sheriff of Nottingham. This will involve crossing Sherwood Forest, before entering his castle and progressing through it's enemy-strewn rooms.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Robin Hood (1987)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Robin Hood (1987)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy IV - Magicland Dizzy (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy IV: Magicland Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dizzy, the egg protagonist, is back in his fourth installment: Magicland Dizzy. The land has been corrupted by an evil wizard, and it's Dizzy's job to set everything right. To do this, he must walk, jump and flip through a large number of screens, pick up and use various items, and talk to people.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy IV - Magicland Dizzy (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy IV - Magicland Dizzy (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy V - Spellbound Dizzy (1991)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy V: Spellbound Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Spellbound Dizzy is a continuation of the adventures of the egg and his friends, this time containing over 100 screens with individual names. Dizzy has trapped himself in a strange world whilst experimenting with a spell book, and must find his way out. Gameplay is mostly similar to the previous games, combining puzzle-solving and object manipulation with arcade-style jumps and hazard-dodging. Lateral thinking is required to decipher the riddles found on scrolls. There are also extra arcade sections on a runaway mine-cart and for a spot of scuba-diving.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Red Software</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy V - Spellbound Dizzy (1991)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy V - Spellbound Dizzy (1991)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy VI - Prince Of The Yolkfolk (1991)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy VI: Prince of the YolkFolk</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rockwart the Troll has cast a spell on Daisy, leaving her asleep for 100 years. Dizzy sets off to put this right in a compact and concise arcade adventure following the conventions of the Dizzy series. You start the game trapped underground, thanks to the results of an errant spell, but can find your way out to explore the castle and find Daisy. There are stars to collect along the way, as well as food to replenish energy lost in contact with the many hazards. Succeed and you and Daisy will ride off into the sunset together.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Big Red Software</developer>
		<publisher>Code Masters</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy VI - Prince Of The Yolkfolk (1991)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy VI - Prince Of The Yolkfolk (1991)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy VII - Crystal Kingdom Dizzy (1992)(Codemasters)(WORKING).tap</path>
		<name>Dizzy VII: Crystal Kingdom Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The magical crystal treasure has been stolen and scattered all over the islands, so it is up to Dizzy to find them and restore order. Once again, Dizzy's main enemy is the pirates, and some deadly island creatures, but all Dizzy's friends are around to help out when the going gets tough.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Impact</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy VII - Crystal Kingdom Dizzy (1992)(Codemasters)(WORKING).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy VII - Crystal Kingdom Dizzy (1992)(Codemasters)(WORKING).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kwik Snax (1990)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy VIII: Kwick Snax</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dizzy must rescue four of his 'Yolkfolk' (groan) chums in this game, from Cuckoo Land, Ice Land, Cloud Land and Zak's Castle. Like Fast Food it doesn't directly resemble the main series of arcade adventures, instead being a single-screen action game, resembling Pengo.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kwik Snax (1990)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kwik Snax (1990)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Saboteur (1986)(Durell).z80</path>
		<name>Saboteur!</name>
		<sortname>Saboteur</sortname>
		<desc>Saboteur combines platform, beat 'em up and adventure elements, setting you as a lone samurai trying to infiltrate an enemy complex. You are capable of all manner of ninja-style moves including kicks and punches, as well as using weaponry. You must travel through an underground complex linked mainly by platforms and ladders, before triggering a bomb and escaping the complex. Your energy recharges if you stay still, so finding areas free of guards (kill these for money) and dogs (avoid them; killing them gains you nothing) is useful, especially as you only have one life.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Durell Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Saboteur (1986)(Durell).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Saboteur (1986)(Durell).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Movie (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Batman: The Movie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the 1989-Batman movie. The game consists of five different parts, each resembling well known game types.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Batman - The Movie (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman - The Movie (1989)(Ocean Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Renegade II - Target Renegade (1988)(Imagine Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Target: Renegade</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mr. Big is back in town, and this time he's captured your brother! He's being held at Big's Pig Pen which is located on the upper side of town. The problem is, every gang in the city is out looking for you. It is now up to you to beat the odds and rescue your brother. You start the game armed only with your fists, and along the way there are some additional weapons to be found such as baseball bats or garbage cans. Gameplay is an arcade style side scrolling action game for one player.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagine</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Renegade II - Target Renegade (1988)(Imagine Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Renegade II - Target Renegade (1988)(Imagine Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (1990)(Image Works)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>With April O'Neil held hostage by The Shredder's thugs, Bebop and Rocksteady, once again, it's up to the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles to come to her rescue! Play as all four of the turtle heroes, rescue April, and then rescue your sensei Splinter from Mecha-Turtles clutches than go after The Shredder deep in the bowels of The Technodrome itself.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Image Works</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (1990)(Image Works)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (1990)(Image Works)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Thrust (1987)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Thrust</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Thrust took a unique game style by bringing realistic physics and inertia-based movement into arcade games, directly influencing titles like Oids, not to mention the same author's Exile from Audiogenic. The action is viewed from the side, with the graphics drawn in vectors, in keeping with the mathematical nature of everything that unfolds.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David Lowe, Simon Clarke</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Thrust (1987)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Thrust (1987)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wanted Monty Mole 1984 Gremlin Graphics Software.z80</path>
		<name>Wanted! Monty Mole</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Monty Mole is keen to steal as much coal as he can, and if possible, obtain control of coal production. Once he's got the loot, his job is to escape through the castle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wanted Monty Mole 1984 Gremlin Graphics Software.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wanted Monty Mole 1984 Gremlin Graphics Software.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Football Manager 1982 Addictive Games.z80</path>
		<name>Football Manager</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The football management game style has been one of the most enduring since Kevin Toms pioneered it in 1982. You start in the 4th division with the team of your choice, and can play on indefinitely in the hope of reaching the top division and dominating it, as well as winning the cups. Players can be bought or sold, with their transfer values varying according to the size of any bid. Their skills and morale vary as the season goes on, with resting key players in easy matches often a key move. You can take out a loan, limited depending on your division, while day-to-day bills must be covered. Matches feature short animated highlights sequences of key moments.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Addictive Games</developer>
		<publisher>Investrónica S.A.</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Football Manager 1982 Addictive Games.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Football Manager 1982 Addictive Games.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Night Shift (US Gold Ltd).Z80</path>
		<name>Night Shift</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Night Shift is a strange platform/puzzle combo of a game. Thriving Toy Company seeks energetic employee to operate unconventional machine. Generous rewards in store for you if you can meet the challenge!</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Attention To Detail</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Night Shift (US Gold Ltd).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Night Shift (US Gold Ltd).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowfire (Beyond Software).Z80</path>
		<name>Shadowfire</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>General Zoff is holding Ambassador Kryxix captive in his spaceship. Plans for a new type of spaceship are hidden in a micro-disc embedded in the Ambassador's spine. If Zoff had the plans, the empire would be in great danger, and it is only a matter of time until his inquisitors will discover them. The Emperor has assembled the so-called "enigma team", a group of six reckless mercenaries, to take care of the situation.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Beyond - Challenging Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadowfire (Beyond Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadowfire (Beyond Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Carrier Command (1989)(Rainbird Software)(128k).zip</path>
		<name>Carrier Command</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Carrier Command was one of the first real-time strategy games. You control an advanced cybernetic aircraft carrier complete with fighters, amphibious assault vehicles, laser defenses and a fleet of decoy drones. Your mission is to build a series of resource, factory, and defensive bases spanning an island chain. The only problem? At the other end of the chain is an even more advanced carrier under control of a terrorist organization with the same mission.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Carrier Command (1989)(Rainbird Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Carrier Command (1989)(Rainbird Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Amaurote.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Amaurote</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your task in this isometrically viewed game is to clear the city of Amaurote of the many bugs and insects which have invaded it. You are supplied with an Arachnus 4 ship and 5 million units of cash. There are 3 different types of ants - drones, queens and scouts, each representing their real function in the natural world, so queen bees are the most lethal opponents as they generate new ants. Money must be spend on buying improved weaponry (including that needed to destroy the Queen Bees) and repairing the ship throughout the 2500 screens Amaurote is depicted in. As your main weapons are bombs, you need to consider their bounce and distance before firing, to avoid being caught up in stray explosions yourself.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Binary Design</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Added Dimension</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Amaurote.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Amaurote.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Antics.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Antics</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Boris the Bee (star of the first game) has been kidnapped by a gang of antisocial Chavs, and his fantastically-named cousin Barnabee must rescue him. You control Barnabee as he travels through the underground ant complex, which has two different entry points from the four above-ground screens which are initially in view. In the main bulk of the game, the side view screens contain ants which must be anticipated and avoided, as they reduce your strength. The action is rather frantic at times. At the risk of being pedantic, you need to touch flowers to restore your energy through pollen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bug-Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Bug-Byte</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Antics.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Antics.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Booty.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Booty</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Like any good pirate ship, the old vessel upon which Booty is set is overloading with treasure, and you play Jim the Cabin Boy as he tries to collect as much of this as he can. The ship is viewed side-on in a platform-type perspective, and contains 20 holds, each of which is split across 8 screens of treasure. Once you have cleared each one, you have 45 seconds to escape the hold and prepare for the next one.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>John F. Cain</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Booty.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Booty.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Buggy Blast (1985)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Buggy Blast</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The planet Endra has been overtaken by the Lurgons and been under their control for over three centuries. The Lurgons are a race of sentient robotic lifeforms dedicated to the obliteration of all organic life. Buggy Blast is a first person 3D shoot 'em up where you as the pilot are tasked to make it to Central Lurgon Corridor and cause a power reversal that will consume the entire Lurgon complex.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paul Hibbard, David Lowe</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Buggy Blast (1985)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Buggy Blast (1985)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Android 2 (1983)(Vortex Software).z80</path>
		<name>Android Two</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Android Two places the player in a maze featuring 5 Militoids to destroy within a time limit. Although they don't shoot back at the player, there are plenty of other hazards in the maze. Aliens are present, which can shoot at the player, as well as land-mines and 20 indestructible robots to block the player's path. There are 3 mazes to clear, each of which has a wrap-around design similar to the original Pac-man game and fills more than one screen. The player have five lives in which to progress as far as possible and try to beat the high score.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vortex Software</developer>
		<publisher>Vortex Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Android 2 (1983)(Vortex Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Android 2 (1983)(Vortex Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family, The (1992)(Ocean)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Addams Family, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Addams Family is a platformer based on the movie of the same name. The player takes the role of Gomez who searches for his missing family members. To find them he has to explore different parts of the mansion, e.g. the woods, while jumping a lot and avoiding enemies. In comparison to the other versions of the game this one is more puzzle-oriented, meaning the player has to find keys to access certain parts of the game world. Another big difference is that this version is not side-scrolling, the player is always sees the whole room and the game switches to another one if the player leaves the screen or enters a door.</desc>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Addams Family, The (1992)(Ocean)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Addams Family, The (1992)(Ocean)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Smash TV.tzx</path>
		<name>Smash T.V.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 1999. The world's most popular television show is Smash T.V., an ultra-violent contest between two armed-to-the-teeth combatants, set loose in a series of deadly arenas that are filled to bursting with hordes of mindless beasts and killer robots. The aim of the game is to blast everything in sight and try to grab more cash and prizes than the other guy. Toaster ovens, VCRs, fancy cars and luxury holidays are there for the taking for anyone who can survive long enough to enjoy them.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Smash TV.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Smash TV.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Transformers (1986)(Ocean Software).zip</path>
		<name>Transformers, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Earth has been invaded by extraterrestrial shapechanging robots which have made our planet their battleground. The struggle between the good Autobots and the evil Decepticons centers around energy as the objective is to collect four pieces of the Energon Cube and getting them back to the Autobot base. The Decepticons will do their best to get in the way and use the cubes to their own nefarious means.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Denton Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Transformers (1986)(Ocean Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Transformers (1986)(Ocean Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WildBunchThe.z80.zip</path>
		<name>Wild Bunch, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in the Wild West, The Wild Bunch is an adventure game with some graphic and arcade elements where you have to prove your innocence for the murder of a man. You discovered the body of the dying man who describes his killer who is a member of the notorious gang, The Wild Bunch, before he draws his last breath. Standing over the body with a gun in your hand, you are discovered by the Sheriff so you flee the scene and begin a life on the run. With a Pinkerton Agent on your trail, you must search the surrounding area and it's five towns to look for the mans killer and bring him to justice with $50 in your pocket and a gun.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kevin Smith</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/WildBunchThe.z80.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WildBunchThe.z80.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./InsideOuting.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Inside Outing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An eccentric millionaire has died without leaving a will, instead hiding his money and gems in obscure places around his large house. His widow has hired a professional thief to find and retrieve these items. However, the dead millionaire's strange pets have now overrun the mansion and do not take kindly to interlopers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Michael St Aubyn</developer>
		<publisher>The Edge Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/InsideOuting.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/InsideOuting.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MoonAlert.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Moon Alert</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Moon Buggy style of games are viewed from the side, and involve trying to guide a Buggy across the jagged surface of the moon, shooting out rocks and occasional aliens in the process. In most games of the type, the moon setting affects the surface but not the atmosphere, yet in this implementation Ocean have attempted to add a feeling of gravity in the way the buggy moves. The game features over 300 screens worth of gameplay, split into 26 sections which are identified by the letters of the alphabet. These markers also act as restart points for when you lose one of your 3 lives. The aliens drop bombs at you, which must be dodged.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/MoonAlert.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MoonAlert.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy III - Fantasy World Dizzy (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy III: Fantasy World Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dizzy's third adventure sees the introduction of the Yolkfolk, including Daisy, who has got lost in the fantasy world of the title. Dizzy sets off to rescue her, braving dragons, rats and alligators along the way. The lands are littered with coins, and as well as completing the main task you should aim to collect as many of these as possible. There are puzzles on most screens, involving collecting objects such as keys, food and water buckets, and using them on doors, flames and such. Unlike the first two game, dialogue boxes between Dizzy and various other characters are included, giving the game a sense of character and humor as well as guiding you through the puzzles somewhat.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy III - Fantasy World Dizzy (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy III - Fantasy World Dizzy (1989)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quazatron (1986)(Hewson Consultants).zip</path>
		<name>Quazatron</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Quazatron started life as Steve Turner's port of Commodore 64 shoot 'em up Paradroid , by his longtime partner Andy Braybrook, but during the design process he decided to change the view to an isometric one, as this would suit the system more. Knowledge of Paradroid is an advantage (not least because it's a splendid game), as most aspects of the game overlap, including the plot, which sets you as the renegade robot KLP-2, armed with experimental technology to attack enemy droids. Your task is to deactivate robots, which can be done in a number of ways - shooting them, gaining control of them so as to deactivate them (known as 'grappling') or pushing them off their circuits.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Creative Software</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Quazatron (1986)(Hewson Consultants).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Quazatron (1986)(Hewson Consultants).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rex(Winner).tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Rex</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rex the dinosaur is fed up of the environmental damage being done by a nearby nuclear plant. As a result, he takes to the heavily-guarded tunnels that lead to it, with the intention of ridding the world of nuclear power forever. The game is viewed from the side in a flick-screen format. Rex jumps and shoots, staking out various walking and flying enemies. Walking on to a Beam Pad means that upon losing a life, you will resume from the screen on which you died. As enemies are dying, keep shooting at them to keep increasing your score.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creative Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Martech Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rex(Winner).tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rex(Winner).tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eliminator(ErbeSoftwareS.A.).tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Eliminator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A shoot ‘em up set on a patchwork-quilt coloured road, Eliminator puts you in control of a ship with a basic weapon, flying along at breakneck speed. There are barriers along the way to avoid, often set in quick succession, and lots of bad guys to shoot at or avoid - their shots must be avoided too. Some parts of the track are blocked unless you can shoot through obstacles before reaching them, or hit a jump pad. At some points you can change to travelling along the ceiling as well. Tokens can be collected en route, and used to obtain better weapons, but losing a life costs you the best one you’ve currently got.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Eliminator(ErbeSoftwareS.A.).tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Eliminator(ErbeSoftwareS.A.).tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MightyFinalFight.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Mighty Final Fight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mighty Final Fight follows the same premise as the original Final Fight. The Mad Gear Gang, the dominant street gang of Metro City, have kidnapped Mayor Haggar's daughter, Jessica. After Haggar is informed of her kidnapping, he sets out to rescue her along with his two friends: Cody, Jessica's boyfriend; and Guy, Cody's training partner. The story is presented in a more comical fashion compared to the original game due to its satirical nature. For example, Belger's motive for kidnapping Jessica in this version is to force her into marrying him, having become infatuated with her.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SaNchez</developer>
		<publisher>SaNchez</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MightyFinalFight.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MightyFinalFight.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Agent X II (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Agent X II: The Mad Prof's Back!</name>
		<sortname>Agent X2</sortname>
		<desc>With Agent X having been a success in both critical and commercial terms, a sequel was inevitable. The Mad Professor's cunning plan this time is to infect everybody with acne, thus causing the economy to crumble (and not just the economy for Valentine's cards).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Agent X II (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Agent X II (1987)(Mastertronic)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dan Dare - Pilot Of The Future (1986)(Virgin Games).z80</path>
		<name>Dan Dare: Pilot of the Future</name>
		<sortname>Dan Dare I:</sortname>
		<desc>A licensed game based around the cult comic strip character, recreating his daring attempts to defeat Mekon and save the earth. The Anastasia ship is attacked by the Treens as soon as Dan steps onto it, although fortunately he picks up a laser on board. From then on, he must act as fast as possible. The main task is to find each of the 5 parts of a planetary-destruction mechanism to the control room, so that it can be safely diffused. He can only carry one at a time, and once he gets the back he must find the correct socket for each one.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gang of Five</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dan Dare - Pilot Of The Future (1986)(Virgin Games).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dan Dare - Pilot Of The Future (1986)(Virgin Games).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AgentX.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Agent X</name>
		<sortname>Agent X1</sortname>
		<desc>A mad professor has kidnapped the President, and the ransom note says he plans to turn him into a war-mongering maniac (shouldn't be too difficult as I write this). As Agent X, you must rescue him before he can be brainwashed. The game is multi-section, and loads in a number of parts (as they are too big to all fit in the memory together), unusually for a budget-price release . The first section involves driving along a diagonally-scrolling road, attempting to ram various cars and trucks into holes, while avoiding them yourself. Later on you must negotiate shooting galleries and Green Beret-esque beat 'em up sections.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mastertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/AgentX.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/AgentX.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alchemist.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Alchemist</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play an Alchemist (no surprise there) and is aiming to kill a wizard. To do this, he must collect all four parts of a spell, and all the objects required to enact it. Plenty of beings are out there to stop him, and spells can be cast to vanquish these - your spell energy constantly restores, so finding quiet spaces to wait for it to recharge can be beneficial. By pushing down into the ground, you can turn into an eagle so as to fly across gaps, although activating this mode takes a bit of energy, and you can't use spells while eaglified. Pushing into the ground returns you to human form.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagine</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alchemist.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alchemist.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AlternativeWorldGames.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Alternative World Games</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alternative World Games Is a series of mini games based around the theme of a Olympiad for the non-sporting minded.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Novotrade Software Kft.</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/AlternativeWorldGames.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/AlternativeWorldGames.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AttackOfTheKillerTomatoes.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Attack of the Killer Tomatoes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are a factory worker and start your shift at the PuraTom processing plant and you find that all tomatoes have mutated. You have to stop the mutated killer tomatoes by put them into holes. The smaller bouncing tomatoes must be crushed. This must all be done before your shift is over! This means wandering to various rooms to locate the tomatoes and to find various objects you can use to kill them. There are some punch cards around, those cards will buy you some extra time. The cards must be inserted in the cube objects in the factory plant.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Global Software</developer>
		<publisher>Global Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/AttackOfTheKillerTomatoes.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/AttackOfTheKillerTomatoes.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avenger_2.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Avenger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the sequel to The Way of the Tiger, Yaemon the Grand Master of Flame is the villain of the piece. He has killed your foster-father Naijish and stolen the Scrolls of Kettsuin. Your quest to recover the scroll and avenge your father's death is viewed from above and superficially resembles Gauntlet. You start outside the Quench Heart Keep, and must initially find enough keys in the grounds and connected buildings to penetrate it, and then kill each of the 3 guards.</desc>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Avenger_2.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Avenger_2.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AxeOfKoltThe128.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Axe of Kolt, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Alaric Blackmoon, a penniless ex-mercenary soldier, reduced to wandering the land and doing odd-jobs in return for food and a place to sleep. You have just left the town of Greenwych and you have hitched a ride on a haywain. The driver tells you that you might have luck finding gainful employment in the village of Hengemire.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Adrift</developer>
		<publisher>FSF Adventures</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/AxeOfKoltThe128.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/AxeOfKoltThe128.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BlackHawk.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Black Hawk</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are piloting the Black Hawk plane through a series of island bases, each of which has hardware such as tanks, missile launchers and planes. Destroy these to maximise the enemy's Strategic Loss Factor. The game is split into two sections, both of which scroll up the screen. In the first, you are in control of your missile camera, and must guide it over things to destroy by holding down fire to guide a shot and releasing to direct it. The second section is a Xevious-influenced scrolling shoot 'em up. You can't lose any of your 3 lives in the first section, but anything you do not successfully destroy during this will be out to get you in the second section.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creative Sparks</developer>
		<publisher>Creative Sparks</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BlackHawk.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BlackHawk.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BobbyYazzShowThe.z80.zip</path>
		<name>Bobby Yazz Show, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This the action puzzler is set under the premise of a futuristic TV game-show, hosted by the madcap Bobby Yazz. The gameplay is divided into four distinct types of levels, with restart points after every 8 stages, and some amusing adverts (for products such as "Soapo Plus. Better than our last rubbish. It almost works" and "Kill 'Em - the nuclear game for all ages").</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cybadyne</developer>
		<publisher>Crash</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BobbyYazzShowThe.z80.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BobbyYazzShowThe.z80.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BoggitThe.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Boggit: Bored Too, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After Bored of the Rings parodied JRR Tolkien's classic Lord of the Rings series, Delta 4 did the same thing with its predecessor The Hobbit, preceding New Line Cinema's identical sequence by 20 years. There is a logical 3-part structure to the adventure, but there are also jokes such as the Old Ford location on the map being near a New Ford - a new Ford Sierra car. This interactive fiction with graphics game thus features reluctant adventurer Bimbo Faggins and devious magician Grandalf attempting to gain treasure, ultimately by appearing on a TV game show. VERB NOUN inputs are used for most instructions, although you have to TALK someone before SAYing anything to them.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delta 4 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>CRL Group</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BoggitThe.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BoggitThe.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BrianBloodaxe.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Brian Bloodaxe</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Brian Bloodaxe is a viking who has been stuck in an ice block for hundreds of years. After the ice has thawed out, Brian vows to conquer Britian, but little does he know he woke up in 1983. Brian must wander through 100 locations looking for the Crown Jewels and sit on the throne. Objects are scattered throughout each location, and Brian needs to figure out their purpose. Monsters – such as ducks, Daleks, Mad Scotsmen, and Turkish soldiers – roam each location making Brian's task of getting these objects difficult. Up to three objects can be carried at any one time, and they can be used to block the path of monsters or to make extra platforms.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge, The</developer>
		<publisher>Edge, The</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BrianBloodaxe.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BrianBloodaxe.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BugabooTheFlea.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Bugaboo (The Flea)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A Flea arrives to the Cebolla-7 planet on board of a space probe. This planet is an intrincate caverns labyrinth, on which our only enemy is a Pterodactilous that will do the possible to devour us, for which we will have continuously to avoid it in each attack that he makes, because he is not always present. The objective is to find the exit of each labyrinth, and you know it since a good principle, but isn't so easy, you must to ascend very carefully, avoiding the rock projections and the branches, with sufficient care as to don't fall (and start from the ground).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indescomp</developer>
		<publisher>Investronica</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BugabooTheFlea.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BugabooTheFlea.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cobra.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Cobra</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This Green Beret-style arcade game follows the plot of the film starring Sylvester Stallone. As Stallone's Cobra character you must rescue Ingrid Knutsen before the Night Slasher gets to her. There are 3 levels of gameplay, set in a city, the countryside and a factory. All have multiple ledges and platforms to negotiate. Cobra starts without a weapon, but he is tough enough to attack with a precisely timed head-butt, although this method of killing is risky, as it will kill Cobra if mistimed. Fortunately there are weapons to pick up along the way, by picking up hamburgers. The weapons include daggers, pistols and machine guns, but all are time-limited.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cobra.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cobra.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DanDareII-MekonsRevenge.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Dan Dare II: Mekon's Revenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mekon, the arch-enemy of humanity with an insatiable lust for power, is back. He’s created the SuperTreens, a genetically engineered species bent on destruction, as well as a new spaceship. As Dan Dare, you must stop him. You have gained access to Mekon’s spaceship, which is packed with SuperTreens. When you find each one you must disable each control box before the time limit, and then reach the next level. Mekon will be trying to reach and activate each one, with the help of his existing race of Treens.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gang of Five</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/DanDareII-MekonsRevenge.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DanDareII-MekonsRevenge.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DanDareIII-TheEscape(DroSoft).tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Dan Dare III: The Escape</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the third game in the Dan Dare series, Dan has been kidnapped by an evil alien race known as the Treens and taken to their scientific satellite orbiting Venus, but it doesn't take long for Dan to break free and goes down into their ship. While searching it, he eventually finds an escape shuttle sitting in the launch bay, only to discover that it is out of fuel. He returns to the satellite in an attempt to find some.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/DanDareIII-TheEscape(DroSoft).tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DanDareIII-TheEscape(DroSoft).tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DodgyGeezers.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Dodgy Geezers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dodgy Geezers is a graphic text adventure with text on the screen describing your location with some locations having a picture showing what you see (except on the Acorn versions). You use the keyboard to type in commands to interact with your surroundings.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashminster Computing Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/DodgyGeezers.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DodgyGeezers.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dracula.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Dracula</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An English lawyer travels to Carpathia to meet Count Dracula regarding a routine property transaction, but soon learns that his client has sinister ulterior intentions.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zen Room, The</developer>
		<publisher>CRL Group</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dracula.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dracula.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BearBovver.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Bear Bovver</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bear Bovver stars Ted the Bear, proud owner of a new Sinclair electric truck, but not of a set of batteries for it. Parked outside a building site, he must climb to the top so as to retrieve a set of batteries. The area is patrolled, but you have some bombs to drop in the hope of snaring them. There is a Baby Bear Mode, which allows you to practice negotiating the platforms without coming under threat. The game promises multi-colour cartoon quality graphics with animation and special effects (unrealistic on the Spectrum, but people were looking for this sort of thing in those days).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artic Computing</developer>
		<publisher>Artic Computing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BearBovver.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BearBovver.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Side (1988)(Incentive).zip</path>
		<name>Dark Side</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Driller, the Ketars attempted to blow up the moon Mitral, but you stopped them. Now, they have Energy Collection Devices collectively known as EGOs, and hope to stock them up to use towards the Zephyr One device, and direct its energy at the planet Evath, resulting in a catastrophic radiation overload.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Major Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Incentive Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dark Side (1988)(Incentive).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dark Side (1988)(Incentive).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DaleyThompsonsDecathlon.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Daley Thompson's Decathlon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of the earliest person-licensed computer games, Olympic legend Daley Thompson lent his name to an old-style joystick waggling frenzy. Ten events were featured, including long and high jumps as well as the predictable sprints, which made for some gameplay variety. You have 3 lives, and lose one every time you fail at an event, which you usually get 3 attempts at. For each event you see both the qualifying time and the world record, which gives you something to aim at.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/DaleyThompsonsDecathlon.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DaleyThompsonsDecathlon.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darkman.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Darkman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the film by Sam Raimi. You play Peyton Westlake, returned from the dead as the many faced "Darkman", seeking your revenge against mobster Robert G.Durant. Live through all the high spots of the movie, the breathtaking helicopter fight sequence, the skyscraper shoot-out dice with death as you swing into heaving freeway traffic dangling from a helicopter.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Twilight</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Darkman.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Darkman.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Torc (1985)(Hewson Consultants).zip</path>
		<name>Dragontorc</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It’s sword and sorcery time with this tale of wizards, evil shapeshifters and spooky forests. It’s your task as the wizard Maroc to rescue the great Merlin from the evil Morag. Control is through a series of command icons. An additional task is the retrieval of the five crowns of Britain, forged from the mystical Dragontorc. Over 200 locations stand between Morag and success.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Torc (1985)(Hewson Consultants).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Torc (1985)(Hewson Consultants).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./HobbitTheV1.2.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Hobbit, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Relive Tolkien's The Hobbit as Bilbo Baggins. A piece of Interactive fiction (with graphics to illustrate locations), you follow the plot of Tolkien's book (before the Lord of the Rings trilogy), starting with an encounter with Gandalf and Thorin. The implementation is rich enough that you can play entirely without pictures if you wish. Also, gameplay happens in realtime, uncommon for interactive fiction.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19820101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Melbourne House</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/HobbitTheV1.2.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/HobbitTheV1.2.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Codename Mat (1984)(Micromega).zip</path>
		<name>Codename Mat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mission: Alien Termination involves all the knowledge of science, space combat and military tactics being implanted into the strong, agile and future-proof body of a 13-year-old boy. You play Mat, at the helm of the USS Centurion prototype fighter, and have the task for saving the world. The game's basic space combat component is fast and smooth, with raging battles resembling Star Raiders. However, in addition to this you must plan your course carefully, both during and between fights. You also have the option of taking on command duties, directing all the other ships in the force.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micromega</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Codename Mat (1984)(Micromega).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Codename Mat (1984)(Micromega).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Star (1985)(Design Design).zip</path>
		<name>Dark Star</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Billed as the fastest vector graphics ever seen on the Spectrum up to that point, and with full colour to boot, Dark Star has similarities with the Star Wars arcade game. Viewed from your cockpit, you fly the LIAR spacecraft around the galaxy, with the hope of achieving liberation, by destroying all the Evil Lord's main bases.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Design Design</developer>
		<publisher>Design Design Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dark Star (1985)(Design Design).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dark Star (1985)(Design Design).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deactivators (1986)(Ariolasoft UK)(128k).zip</path>
		<name>Deactivators</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Deactivators is an arcade-puzzle maze game which puts you in control of a squad of bomb disposal droids. You must pick them up and quickly throw them out of the building to safety - failure to do this costs you a droid and a room (occasionally blocking off other essential rooms). The game's levels have grid-like arrangements with doors, trapdoors and poles, and increase in size as the game goes on. For both these reasons, mapping is essential.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tigress Marketing</developer>
		<publisher>Ariolasoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Deactivators (1986)(Ariolasoft UK)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Deactivators (1986)(Ariolasoft UK)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Enduro Racer (1987)(Activision)(128k).zip</path>
		<name>Enduro Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this game you play the role of an endurance bike racer. The gameplay involves you racing against the clock to get to the finish line and jumping over ramps. At the end of each race you get points for how many cars or bikes you have overtaken with which you can upgrade your bike. There are various different terrain for you to race on including desert beach and dirt tracks plus a number of things to slow you down or even knock you off of your bike all together. The main idea is to find the best route through each level to shave off valuable seconds in order to over take more cars and bikes.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Enduro Racer (1987)(Activision)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Enduro Racer (1987)(Activision)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guardian 2 (1990)(Hi-Tec Software).zip</path>
		<name>Guardian II: Revenge of the Mutants</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The mutants are back and this time they're faster. In your Mk.II Fighter you have to stop the Raiders flying across the planet and picking up Earthlings and turning them to Mutants when they reach the top of the screen. When all Earthlings are gone then it's game over.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Citizen Software</developer>
		<publisher>HiTech Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Guardian 2 (1990)(Hi-Tec Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Guardian 2 (1990)(Hi-Tec Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LightForce.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Light Force</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Regulus system has been attacked by alien forces, and you are the only Terran fighter in place to clear the area and rescue the captured hostages. The game is a vertically-scrolling shoot 'em up with 5 levels. The first of these involves clearing their defences to reach the alien sector, then you face the jungle, ice and desert planets, before reaching the final alien compound. The game's enemies have a variety of attack patterns and formations, as well as varied and colourful appearance.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Carter Follis Software Associates</developer>
		<publisher>FTL - Faster Than Light</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/LightForce.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/LightForce.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maziacs (1983)(DK'Tronics).zip</path>
		<name>Maziacs</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Maziacs is a maze game. The maze in Maziacs has no edges but has around 100 locations and a new maze is generated at each game start. The aim of Maziacs is to find the treasure and take it to the point the game started. All scattered over the maze are prisoners, food, swords and treasures for you to collect but you are chased by monsters that will attack you.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>dk'tronics</developer>
		<publisher>dk'tronics</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Maziacs (1983)(DK'Tronics).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Maziacs (1983)(DK'Tronics).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sim City (1989)(Infogrames).zip</path>
		<name>Sim City</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sim City sets you as the mayor of a new municipality, with the responsibility of building and maintaining a place where citizens can move to and work and be happy. The first task is to place essentials such as housing, transport links, schools, factories and shops. There are 50 types of these, allowing for homes of all standards and different types of businesses. Make sure to consider which sites are effective for which tasks. Some power sources pollute, others don't but are more expensive. Taxes must be raised to ensure an income, and then portions allocated to public services such as policing and roads. Earthquakes, floods and fires are all emergency situations that must be dealt to contain any damage.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sim City (1989)(Infogrames).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sim City (1989)(Infogrames).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Technician Ted - The Chip Factory (1984)(Hewson Consultants)(128k).zip</path>
		<name>Technician Ted: The Chip Factory</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ted is an enthusiastic worker at a computer chip factory, which takes the form of dozens of hazardous platform screens, most of which lead to more than 2 other rooms, through holes in the floor and ceiling as well as a lift. Each room is littered with moving sprites as well as lava pits and dangerous drops, all of which will drain the energy from Ted's single life.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hewson</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Technician Ted - The Chip Factory (1984)(Hewson Consultants)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Technician Ted - The Chip Factory (1984)(Hewson Consultants)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Set Willy (1984)(Software Projects).z80</path>
		<name>Jet Set Willy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cult hero Matthew Smith followed up Manic Miner with a seminal platform game. Having struck it lucky in the first game, Willy now owns a lavish mansion with over 60 rooms linked in a 3D plane, and must tidy it all before his housekeeper will let him sleep. Each room has its own hazards, such as spikes, revolving razors and ropes. The route through the house must be navigated carefully, due to the multiple entrances to some rooms - this is perhaps the first action game where mapping is an advantage. Another innovation, to the chagrin of players everywhere, is manual protection - a sheet of colour-coded numbers.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20140101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Projects Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Spud</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jet Set Willy (1984)(Software Projects).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jet Set Willy (1984)(Software Projects).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien_Girl_-_128k_Updated.tap</path>
		<name>Alien Girl</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Aliana, the first hybrid between human and xenoform from the planet Atlas, takes her ship to start a personal war with the only help of her aLMa onboard system and thus rise to the throne as the only queen to achieve balance between the races.</desc>
		<releasedate>20210308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JavierFopiani</developer>
		<publisher>JavierFopiani</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien_Girl_-_128k_Updated.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien_Girl_-_128k_Updated.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr. Freeze (1984)(Firebird).zip</path>
		<name>Mr. Freeze</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mr. Freeze is a flick-screen platformer where your task is to de-ice six compartments of a giant fridge by moving from the bottom-left of each compartment to the top-right to touch the de-icer. In each compartment are various platforms and you climb ladders or drop down through gaps but you can only fall a certain height. A compartment doesn't have to be de-iced to move to the next one but you can only move between them where an arrow points. There are various deadly obstacles that need avoiding and they are ice cubes, robots, other creatures and a laser at the top of the screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David T. Clark</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mr. Freeze (1984)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mr. Freeze (1984)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batty (1987)(Hit Pak).z80</path>
		<name>Batty</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Batty is influenced by Arkanoid's method of reviving the Breakout phenomenon. You control a paddle at the bottom of the screen, with the top half of the screen containing an arrangement of bricks, most of which can be destroyed. You must move the paddle left and right so as to make contact with a ball, and thus deflect it (using the walls at the sides strategically) into the bricks, some of which require multiple hits to destroy. Wipe the destructible bricks out, and you move on to the next level; fail to keep the ball in play and you lose one of your 5 lives.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Dennis Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Batty (1987)(Hit Pak).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batty (1987)(Hit Pak).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyclone (1985)(Vortex Software).zip</path>
		<name>Cyclone</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A cyclone is sweeping across a small group of islands. As the pilot of a lone rescue helicopter, it is up to you to locate and pick up five crates of vital medical supplies, while rescuing as many stranded islanders as you can. You will have to check your map and watch your wind force gauge, to stay out of the cyclone's way. You'll also have to keep an eye on your fuel. Cyclone is played out in a colorful, pseudo-3D world that can be viewed from two different angles, to help you locate those pesky crates.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vortex Software</developer>
		<publisher>Vortex Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cyclone (1985)(Vortex Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cyclone (1985)(Vortex Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FatWormBlowsASparky.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Fat Worm Blows a Sparky</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fat Worm is locked inside a Spectrum's architecture, and is looking for a disk drive, in order to produce a clone of himself, which he presumably will Write Once and Read Many. He moves around the arrangement of chips, processors and boards, with the aim of finding his way through. On the way he will encounter bugs (of the insectoid type) which must be shot at, by 'blowing a sparkie' - releasing a bolt of electrical energy. Mines and impact shots can both be fired. Contact with these bugs causes them to jump on you, gradually slowing your movement and sappoing your energy. You must collect spindles in order to get rid of them.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software</developer>
		<publisher>Durell Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/FatWormBlowsASparky.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/FatWormBlowsASparky.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kayleth (1986)(Adventuresoft UK).zip</path>
		<name>Kayleth</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Zyroneans were an advanced, pacifistic civilization until the arrival of the tyrant Kayleth. Sending down armies of androids from his space ship, he enslaved the planet Zyron and forced its inhabitants to work in mines and gather Chromazin, a rare mineral, for him. You are a Zyronean who has made a plan to free the planet from Kayleth' reign. However, as the game begins, you find yourself trapped in an unknown place with no memory of the events that led you to this situation. In order to find out where you are, what happened to you and ultimately save your home planet, you will have to interact with several (android) characters, solve various puzzles and survive encounters with ferocious creatures.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Adventure Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Adventure Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kayleth (1986)(Adventuresoft UK).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kayleth (1986)(Adventuresoft UK).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MatchPoint.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Match Point</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is for one player against the computer or two players against each other, although the flexible front end allows you to enter not only your own name but also that of the computer so if you want to you can have the thrill of beating McEnroe (or being beaten by him of course!) or Navratilova if you prefer.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psion Software Ltd, Steve Kelly</developer>
		<publisher>Sinclair Research</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/MatchPoint.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MatchPoint.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Viking Raiders (1984)(Firebird).zip</path>
		<name>Viking Raiders</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A turn-based strategy, which involves moving boats, men, and catapults to capture the castle of each opponent. Playing pieces can move in any direction up to a distance of nine grid squares in a straight line, obstacles permitting. Collecting extra gold in the game allows players to buy further units.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mark Lucas</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Viking Raiders (1984)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Viking Raiders (1984)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WorseThingsHappenAtSea.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Worse Things Happen at Sea</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Taking control of a robot ship captain, your task is to ensure that the ship travels successfully from port to port. Sadly the ship isn't particularly well-sealed, and soon starts letting water in. Every time one of these leaks appears, it is your job to get to the appropriate deck (there are 11 in total) and seal it. Completing this task each time involves using the hatches to access the room, picking up a sealing patch, and then using it to plug the leak, before draining any water which did get in from the area. Robots and water don't mix, so you'll only be able to withstand any water for a short amount of time.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mind's Eye</developer>
		<publisher>Silversoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/WorseThingsHappenAtSea.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WorseThingsHappenAtSea.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xeno (1986)(A &amp; F Software).zip</path>
		<name>Xeno</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Xeno is a future sport resembling Air Hockey. Each of the two players (the second being either human or computer controlled) controls a ground skimmer, which is aiming to hit a puck so as to knock it into their opponent's goal. This is done in a turn-based manner, in which each player controls a movement line which sets up their intended move before it is enacted.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Binary Design</developer>
		<publisher>A&amp;F Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Xeno (1986)(A &amp; F Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Xeno (1986)(A &amp; F Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jumping Jack (1983)(Imagine Software).z80</path>
		<name>Jumping Jack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Reaching the tops of 20 screens is the aim of Jack's life. The ledges go right across the screen, with gaps emerging at random intervals, through which Jack must aim. He can move along each ledge, and must avoid holes which open, as they can cause him to drop further. Later levels add aliens, snakes and all manner of other hazards, as well as an increasing number of holes. The control combination is unusual, and only comfortable on earlier Spectrum models - the game has no joystick mode.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagine</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jumping Jack (1983)(Imagine Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jumping Jack (1983)(Imagine Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chuckie Egg (1983)(A &amp; F Software).z80</path>
		<name>Chuckie Egg</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the game you play Hen House Harry who has to collect 12 (a dozen) eggs from each level, while avoiding the ducklings. The levels each occupy a single screen, and are made up of platforms, ladders and lifts (or elevators), and are thus similar to those in classic platform game Donkey Kong. Corn can also be collected, which stops the time limit from ticking down and also stops the bonus, collected when the level is completed, from decreasing.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>A&amp;J Software</developer>
		<publisher>A&amp;J Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chuckie Egg (1983)(A &amp; F Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chuckie Egg (1983)(A &amp; F Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SportOfKings.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Sport of Kings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sport of Kings is a horse racing simulation. The procedure is simple: the player sets a bet, the game calculates the race results (the graphical representation is side-scrolling) and, depending on the result, the winnings are paid out. If less then eight horses participate (the number can be freely set up to 75), only the 1st and 2nd place count.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jeff Calder</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Added Dimension</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./boxart/SportOfKings.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SportOfKings.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gremlins - The Adventure (1985)(Adventure International).zip</path>
		<name>Gremlins</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the movie of the same name, Gremlins: The Adventure is an interactive fiction game by Brian Howarth, author of the Mysterious Adventures series. Players take the role of Billy, who has already been tricked into feeding Gizmo after midnight, and now Kingston Falls is in danger of being overrun with Gremlins. With Gizmo's help, Billy must save the town before it is too late. There are some animated graphics in this one. The game has less than 50 locations, though time is a factor - the gremlins home in on Billy with every move he makes, so there is no chance to dawdle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brian Howarth</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Gremlins - The Adventure (1985)(Adventure International).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gremlins - The Adventure (1985)(Adventure International).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Buggy Boy (1988)(Elite Systems)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Buggy Boy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The object of the game is to drive around one of five courses (Offroad, North, East, South or West) in the shortest time possible. Each course has five legs, each filled with obstacles such as boulders and brick walls. Points are awarded for driving through gates and collecting flags. Offroad is a closed-circuit course that takes five laps to complete while North, South, East, and West are each a strict point A to point B style course.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Palace</developer>
		<publisher>Tatsumi</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Buggy Boy (1988)(Elite Systems)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Buggy Boy (1988)(Elite Systems)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Olli &amp; Lissa II - Halloween (1987)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Olli &amp; Lissa II: Halloween</name>
		<sortname>Olli 2</sortname>
		<desc>In the second game of the series, Olli and Lisa's friend Arabella the fairy has made a cake that due to a spell error has exploded, and strewn 16 objects all over Olli and Lisa's castle. Arabella needs to go out and find all the objects and return them to their original locations.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ionis Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Silverbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Olli &amp; Lissa II - Halloween (1987)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Olli &amp; Lissa II - Halloween (1987)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Olli &amp; Lissa III - The Candlelight Adventure (1989)(Codemasters).z80</path>
		<name>Olli &amp; Lissa III: The Candlelight Adventure</name>
		<sortname>Olli 3</sortname>
		<desc>This is the third game starring the doggie duo, and it features Olli's attempt to retrieve the parts for his car which have been stolen and scattered all over the Spooky Castle. Finding these and reassembling the car is done in several stages. First you must find a magnifying glass, and use this to examine the screens thoroughly to find each part. Once you obtain the car part, you will need a spanner to be able to do anything with it. Armed with these, you must head to the basement, to be able to put it back together.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hard &amp; Software</developer>
		<publisher>Cartoon Time</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Olli &amp; Lissa III - The Candlelight Adventure (1989)(Codemasters).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Olli &amp; Lissa III - The Candlelight Adventure (1989)(Codemasters).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Olli &amp; Lissa - The Ghost Of Shilmoore Castle (1986)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Olli &amp; Lissa: The Ghost of Shilmoore Castle</name>
		<sortname>Olli 1</sortname>
		<desc>Panic at Shilmore Castle! For years it is inhabited by ghost Sir Humphrey and his pals Olli and Lisa but it is bought up by Eugine Portcullis III Jnr who wants to break it down and ship it to the States, bit by bit. Being rather attached to his castle, Sir Humphrey wants to scare Eugene away for good. Unfortunately, Sir Humphrey has lost his ability to make himself invisible. He can only regain his power by mixing special ingredients that Olli must find.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>D&amp;K Software Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Olli &amp; Lissa - The Ghost Of Shilmoore Castle (1986)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Olli &amp; Lissa - The Ghost Of Shilmoore Castle (1986)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yie Ar Kung Fu (1985)(Imagine Software)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Yie Ar Kung-Fu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the popular arcade game, Yie Ar Kung-Fu follows Oolong's quest to become a Kung-Fu master. Of course this involves fighting a wide range of opponents in a traditional one-on-one 2D environment. Oolong has a wide range of attacks he can use to lower his opponent's life bar, including traditional punching and kicking attacks as well as jumping ones. Opponents are well armed with unique weapons and attacks, so Oolong's task won't be easy.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Yie Ar Kung Fu (1985)(Imagine Software)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Yie Ar Kung Fu (1985)(Imagine Software)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turbo Esprit (1986)(Durell).z80</path>
		<name>Turbo Esprit</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Turbo Esprit puts you in control of a Lotus Esprit cop car, with the challenge of breaking up a drugs gang and protecting the innocent. A map is built into the car, which can instantly show the positions of the baron's cars - this is crucial because you can't interrupt them before the initial deal is done, as this will simply make them leave and try again another time.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Durell Software</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Turbo Esprit (1986)(Durell).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Turbo Esprit (1986)(Durell).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jetpac (1983)(Ultimate).zip</path>
		<name>Jetpac</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jetman has crash-landed on a distant planet, with ledges suspended in mid-air and populated by various nasties, and he must escape and find his way home. Your first task is to retrieve each of the three parts of his spaceship, in order, and carry them over the base part. After this, you must collect enough fuel to be able to fly away, again by picking it up and dropping it over the ship (you don't have to actually make contact with the ship in doing this). Once you've filled the ship up, you can fly on to the next level, in which you must again refuel.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate</developer>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jetpac (1983)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jetpac (1983)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy II - Treasure Island Dizzy (1988)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy II: Treasure Island Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is Dizzy's second adventure. Dizzy is a cute little egg character who must explore the strange magic kingdom that is Treasure Island, solving problems and puzzles, and end the terror of the evil Pirates that rule the island.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy II - Treasure Island Dizzy (1988)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy II - Treasure Island Dizzy (1988)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dizzy - The Ultimate Cartoon Adventure (1987)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Dizzy I: Ultimate Cartoon Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dizzy's world is being harassed by the evil wizard Zaks! You play as Dizzy, the anthropomorphic egg, and you must search the land for a Leprechaun's Wig, a Cloud's Silver Lining, a Vampire Dux Feather, and Troll Brew, to make a potion to defeat Zaks with. This is the first game in a long line of platform/adventure games starring Dizzy. In this game, like all Dizzy adventure games, gameplay is standard platformer fare, except there inventory items scattered around the world, which are necessary to overcome obstacles and progress through the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>By the Oliver Twins</developer>
		<publisher>Code Masters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dizzy - The Ultimate Cartoon Adventure (1987)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dizzy - The Ultimate Cartoon Adventure (1987)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Barbarian - 2 Players (1987)(Palace).z80</path>
		<name>Barbarian: The Ultimate Warrior</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Barbarian: The Ultimate Warrior is a fighting game that supports one or two players. Players assume the roles of sword-wielding barbarians, who battle in locales such as a forest glade and a "fighting pit". The game's head-to-head mode lets a player fight against another or the computer in time-limited matches. The game also features a single-player story mode, which comprises a series of plot-connected challenges.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Steve Brown, Shaun Griffiths, Richard Joseph</developer>
		<publisher>Palace</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Barbarian - 2 Players (1987)(Palace).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Barbarian - 2 Players (1987)(Palace).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Airwolf (1985)(Elite Systems).z80</path>
		<name>Airwolf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game of the TV show is viewed from the side and puts you in command of an attack helicopter. Your task is to rescue 5 scientists from an underground lair by destroying its layer of protection and then getting to the core. Moving onto a screen at a time you must shoot out anything and everything in your path, including lots of regenerating static targets. Realistic gravity takes effect, so you can't simply hover in a set position.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Elite Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Airwolf (1985)(Elite Systems).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Airwolf (1985)(Elite Systems).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Syndrome (1988)(ACE)(128K)[t +2].z80</path>
		<name>Alien Syndrome</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alien Syndrome is a scrolling shooter arcade conversion. Your job is to run around and rescue all the captives and make it to the escape hatch before the time bomb explodes. Then face the mother alien at the end of the level. You can play as a single player or two people, taking turns. Player 2 starts the game after Player 1 dies and vice versa.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>ACE Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien Syndrome (1988)(ACE)(128K)[t +2].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien Syndrome (1988)(ACE)(128K)[t +2].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./APB (1989)(Domark)(128K)[aka All Points Bulletin].z80</path>
		<name>APB</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are police officer Bob, whose aim is to apprehend a certain quota of criminals (litterbugs, speeders and the like) each day. This is done by chasing them and sounding your siren at them in some cases they will need ramming off the road. There are also hardened criminals to catch - if you can get one of these to confess, your day's work is considered done.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/APB (1989)(Domark)(128K)[aka All Points Bulletin].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/APB (1989)(Domark)(128K)[aka All Points Bulletin].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Caped Crusader - A Bird in the Hand (1988)(Ocean).z80</path>
		<name>Batman: The Caped Crusader - A Bird in the Hand</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Batman: The Caped Crusader is a combination of an arcade and adventure game. "A Bird In The Hand" featuring the Penguin. The game is played with a side scrolling view, with each new location opening in a new panel similar to the appearance of a comic book. The game has two parts to it, and these can be played in any order. In A Bird In the Hand, The Penguin is back, and planning on taking over the world with an army of robotic penguins. In A Fete Worse Than Death, The Joker has kidnapped Robin, and it's up to Batman to save him.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Special FX Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Batman - The Caped Crusader - A Bird in the Hand (1988)(Ocean).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman - The Caped Crusader - A Bird in the Hand (1988)(Ocean).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Caped Crusader - A Fete Worse than Death (1988)(Ocean).z80</path>
		<name>Batman: The Caped Crusader - A Fete Worse than Death</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Batman: The Caped Crusader is a combination of an arcade and adventure game. A Fete Worse Than Death" featuring the Joker. The game is played with a side scrolling view, with each new location opening in a new panel similar to the appearance of a comic book. The game has two parts to it, and these can be played in any order. In A Bird In the Hand, The Penguin is back, and planning on taking over the world with an army of robotic penguins. In A Fete Worse Than Death, The Joker has kidnapped Robin, and it's up to Batman to save him.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Special FX Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Erbe Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Batman - The Caped Crusader - A Fete Worse than Death (1988)(Ocean).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman - The Caped Crusader - A Fete Worse than Death (1988)(Ocean).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beast of Torrack Moor, The (1988)(Marlin Games)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Beast of Torrack Moor, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As a junior reporter for the LOWSEA GAZETTE, life was one continual round of jumble sales and church bazaars, with the occasional vicarage tea party to liven up the week.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Marlin Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Beast of Torrack Moor, The (1988)(Marlin Games)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Beast of Torrack Moor, The (1988)(Marlin Games)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bionic Commandos (1988)(Go!)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play a soldier with a bionic arm that extends and contracts. Your arm allows you to grab on to fixed objects to swing around and climb up levels no jumping allowed! The arm also grabs opponents and pull them towards you. Your mission is to infiltrate the enemy fortress, find your missing comrade, "Super Joe", and take out the evil leader, "Generalissimo Kilt", of the invading force that has been attacking your people for the last 2 years.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Go!</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bionic Commandos (1988)(Go!)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bionic Commandos (1988)(Go!)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blinky's Scary School (1990)(Zeppelin Games)(48K-128K).z80</path>
		<name>Blinky's Scary School</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first of Blinky the ghost's three outings, the ghost with the most has to progress through a series of levels and remove the hazards left by ghost-busters (who aren't called Peter, Egon, Winston or Ray for licensing reasons). He does this by collecting the right objects to cast the all important spells.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zeppelin Games</developer>
		<publisher>Zeppelin Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blinky's Scary School (1990)(Zeppelin Games)(48K-128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blinky's Scary School (1990)(Zeppelin Games)(48K-128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Thunder (1984)(Richard Wilcox).z80</path>
		<name>Blue Thunder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blue Thunder is a side-scrolling shooter and tie-in with the short-lived TV series of the same name which has you piloting a new 'jetcopter' as the only survivor of an alien assault. As it turns out, you're not alone after all, so you depart from your ship and fly across a sea full of heavily defended islands to reach the enemy stronghold, disable its defenses and rescue your comrades.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Richard Wilcox Software</developer>
		<publisher>Richard Wilcox Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blue Thunder (1984)(Richard Wilcox).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blue Thunder (1984)(Richard Wilcox).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bounder (1986)(Gremlin Graphics).z80</path>
		<name>Bounder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Bounder, the player controls a tennis ball that constantly bounces on the screen. The player has to move the ball around between two bounces so it lands on friendly areas like grass or the main hexagonal-patterned floor. If it lands hazardous areas like spikes and sand, or hits the enemies which move around, one of the seven lives the player starts with is lost. There are beneficial squares though - arrows which keep the ball in the air longer or teleports which clear part of the game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bounder (1986)(Gremlin Graphics).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bounder (1986)(Gremlin Graphics).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brainstorm (1987)(Firebird)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Brainstorm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Brainstorm is a game where the aim is to get a high enough score on a screen that beats the score you received on the last screen you played when a timer reaches zero.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tom Prosser</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Brainstorm (1987)(Firebird)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Brainstorm (1987)(Firebird)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commando (1985)(Elite Systems)[cr][aka Space Invasion].tzx</path>
		<name>Commando</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Several levels await your super-tough Commando in this arcade conversion. Armed with only a standard rifle and a few grenades you must take on hordes of Nazis. Some are wandering around in the open, while others have picked out hiding places, which you must approach from certain angles. Trees, rivers and bridges create a varied combat-like terrain and must be incorporated into your thinking. Extra grenades can be collected, and will definitely be required, as they allow you to kill form distance and thus avoid some enemy shots.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Elite Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commando (1985)(Elite Systems)[cr][aka Space Invasion].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commando (1985)(Elite Systems)[cr][aka Space Invasion].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Critical Mass (1985)(Durell).z80</path>
		<name>Critical Mass</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An anti-matter power station on an orbiting asteroid is used by the local star system for energy. The station has been taken over by hostile aliens who are threatening to overload the power system which will turn the reactor into a massive black hole and destroy not only the planetary system, but several nearby stars as well.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Simon Francis, Julian Breeze</developer>
		<publisher>Durell Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Critical Mass (1985)(Durell).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Critical Mass (1985)(Durell).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Custerd's Quest (1986)(Power House, The)(128K)[re-release].z80</path>
		<name>Custerd's Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Custerds Quest is a humorous text adventure with graphics where you play the role of Sir Coward de Custerd, who needs to save the world from an evil necromancer. The game doesn't take itself very seriously and features tongue in cheek humor.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>The Power House</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Custerd's Quest (1986)(Power House, The)(128K)[re-release].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Custerd's Quest (1986)(Power House, The)(128K)[re-release].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyberun (1986)(Ultimate Play The Game).z80</path>
		<name>Cyberun</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The planetary system called "Zebarema" is the only place in the universe where you can find cybernite, the hardest material known to man, and key to generating enormous power and wealth. To exploit the unique resources of the planets, a ship is constructed and sent to Zebarema.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Ultimate</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cyberun (1986)(Ultimate Play The Game).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cyberun (1986)(Ultimate Play The Game).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Draconus (1988)(Zeppelin Games).z80</path>
		<name>Draconus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Draconus is an arcade platformer with adventure elements where the player gains control of Frognum - a beast similar to a serpent or a dragon. His mission is to destroy the Tyrant Beast, an evil ruler of the dark and dangerous world in which Frognum lives. The main weapon in the game is fire breath, but on his quest Frognum will find many magical artifacts and, thanks to those, gain new powers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zeppelin Games</developer>
		<publisher>Zeppelin Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Draconus (1988)(Zeppelin Games).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Draconus (1988)(Zeppelin Games).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Druid (1986)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Druid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Druid is an action game inspired by the arcade hit Gauntlet. As the eponymous hero, your job is to destroy four magic skulls hidden over eight levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dene T. Carter, Andrew E. Bailey</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Druid (1986)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Druid (1986)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Earthlight (1988)(Firebird)(48K-128K).z80</path>
		<name>Earthlight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Earthlight is pseudo-3D side-scrolling shooter, with gameplay similar to Uridium. The player controls a special spaceship on a mission to collect matter transmitters (small boxes) while avoiding all the sentry and industrial robots.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Earthlight (1988)(Firebird)(48K-128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Earthlight (1988)(Firebird)(48K-128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./E-motion (1990)(U.S. Gold)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>E-Motion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This strategic action puzzle game features original gameplay. You control a spacecraft situated on a globe which you can rotate and move around the screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/E-motion (1990)(U.S. Gold)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/E-motion (1990)(U.S. Gold)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Escape from the Planet of the Robot Monsters (1990)(Domark)(48K-128K).z80</path>
		<name>Escape from the Planet of the Robot Monsters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, in Escape from the Planet of the Robot Monsters you are sent in on a rescue mission to Planet X. This planet has been taken over by robots and you must find and evacuate the remaining humans. It's a shooter similar to Gauntlet, only with an isometric viewpoint. You run around the levels shooting robots, rescuing humans and picking up items.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Escape from the Planet of the Robot Monsters (1990)(Domark)(48K-128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Escape from the Planet of the Robot Monsters (1990)(Domark)(48K-128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Empire Strikes Back, The (1988)(Domark)(48K-128K).z80</path>
		<name>Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The arcade game from Atari Games based on the second Star Wars movie features four action sequences inspired by the film. The graphical style is similar to the first Star Wars game, using vector graphics with a first-person perspective.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Empire Strikes Back, The (1988)(Domark)(48K-128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Empire Strikes Back, The (1988)(Domark)(48K-128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Garfield - Big, Fat, Hairy Deal (1988)(Edge, The).z80</path>
		<name>Garfield: Big, Fat, Hairy Deal</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the earliest licensed entertainment videogame of Jim Davis' lazy cat cartoon character, you play Garfield in his attempt to rescue Arlene from the cat pound. The primary gameplay involves object manipulation, gaining objects either by picking up or receiving them from other characters (usually in exchange for other objects).</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Softek Software</developer>
		<publisher>Edge, The</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Garfield - Big, Fat, Hairy Deal (1988)(Edge, The).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Garfield - Big, Fat, Hairy Deal (1988)(Edge, The).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./19 Part 1 - Boot Camp (1988)(Cascade Games)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>19 Part 1: Boot Camp</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As one of up to four newly recruited soldiers at the time of the Vietnam War (these people had an average age of 19, as the title refers to), you must first face the tough Boot Camp. Conceptually it’s similar to Boot Camp, a fact which can’t be disguised even by the Konami game being known as ‘Combat School’ in Europe. Show enough stamina, skill and determination in these four events and you have proved yourself worthy to fight for the US.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artronic</developer>
		<publisher>MCM Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/19 Part 1 - Boot Camp (1988)(Cascade Games)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/19 Part 1 - Boot Camp (1988)(Cascade Games)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deathchase (1983)(Micromega).z80</path>
		<name>3D Deathchase</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>3D Deathchase sees you riding a motorcycle through 14 stages, with the aim of shooting out a succession of riders. Each stage starts with 2 bikes to shoot out, although planes and tanks also appear on the horizon, to be shot for bonus points. You start with 3 bikes and an infinite supply of bullets, with one bike lost every time you crash. The levels are tree-lined, and at top speed it can be terrifying as you try to muscle through the gaps so as not to lose distance on the target bike. Every second level is played out at night, which changes the colour scheme.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mervyn J. Estcourt, R.B.</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Deathchase (1983)(Micromega).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Deathchase (1983)(Micromega).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunattack3D.tap.zip</path>
		<name>3D Lunattack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The war on the Seiddab rages on, and you now take part in an attack on their moon base. You fly a hovercraft a bit above the moon's surface, and must shoot down the enemy's DAB tanks. After that ring of defense is penetrated, you must dodge your way through a space minefield above a mountain range, and then a missile firing range before reach the Seiddab's command base.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lunattack3D.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lunattack3D.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3D Starstrike.tzx</path>
		<name>3D Starstrike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Both regarding graphics and gameplay, 3D Starstrike is essentially a clone of Atari's Star Wars. Using wireframe graphics with a first-person perspective, the player controls the Starstrike fighter in several distinct phases: the first phase is the approach to the enemy base, where Outsider space fighters must be destroyed. The second phase takes place close to the surface of the base, where enemy bunkers and laser towers await. The third phase is a trench run, where gun turrets await at the side of the trench, and catwalks blocking the way must be dogded. The run culminates in the reactor room, where two reactor pods must be hit to destroy the base.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software</developer>
		<publisher>Realtime Games Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<image>./boxart/3D Starstrike.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3D Starstrike.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3D Starstrike II (1986)(Realtime Games Software).z80</path>
		<name>Starstrike II</name>
		<sortname>3D Starstrike II</sortname>
		<desc>In Realtime's previous Starstrike game (not to be confused with Star Strike), the evil Outsiders attacked the Federation and had to be forced back. This time, the boot's on the other foot, as the Federation have sent their Starstrike II vehicles in to take them out. Armed with sophisticated computers, lasers and shields, all it needs is a good pilot, such as yourself. Twenty-two planets fall under Outsiders control, and each has grid-based defenses which must be taken out, complete with all their command computers and production droids.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Games Software</developer>
		<publisher>Realtime Games Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<image>./boxart/3D Starstrike II (1986)(Realtime Games Software).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3D Starstrike II (1986)(Realtime Games Software).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Academy.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Academy: Tau Ceti II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After an incident on 61 Cygnus in 2197 when a rookie pilot selected the wrong gear when docking with the main central reactor and reduced half the planet to molten lava, Gal-Corp decided that a special training facility was needed to provide an elite corps of pilots for the advanced military skimmers used in colonisation and reconnaisance work. The Galcorp Academy for Advanced Skimmer Pilots (GASP) was founded in 2213 to meet this requirement. With an intake of over a hundred would be skimmer pilots a year, only a few meet the exacting requirement of flying and combat skills. In order to graduate from the Academy cadets must complete 20 missions, grouped in five levels of four, successfully.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRL Group PLC</developer>
		<publisher>CRL Group</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Academy.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Academy.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ActionForceII.tap.zip</path>
		<name>Action Force II: International Heroes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The task in Action Force II: International Heroes is to rescue each of the citizens who have been taken hostage by COBRA. It's a two-man operation, with Quick Kick scaling the building, and Airtight destroying hazards along the way from the safety of his helicopter.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gang of Five</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/ActionForceII.tap.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ActionForceII.tap.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ActionReflex.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Action Reflex</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Action Reflex involves steering a bouncy ball through 75 screens of hazards. These include lakes, drains, daggers, and a network of pipes which can send you back several screens. You play against a time limit, and contact with one of these hazards deducts time from your limited amount (there are no 'lives' to worry about), and puts you back at the start of the screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mirrorsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Mirrorsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/ActionReflex.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ActionReflex.tzx.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forgotten Worlds (1989)(U.S. Gold)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Forgotten Worlds</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Forgotten Worlds features two characters known as The Nameless Ones, who both look like Arnold Schwarzenegger, one even has a mohawk. It's their job to rid the planet of the attacking aliens. Guiding your character around the screen as they fly with jet-packs, guns on full auto, you control a satellite which you rotate around your character for the direction in which your gun is firing. At the end of each level is a boss which needs to be killed to progress.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Forgotten Worlds (1989)(U.S. Gold)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Forgotten Worlds (1989)(U.S. Gold)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Full Throttle (1984)(Micromega).z80</path>
		<name>Full Throttle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This early motorcycle racing game uses an enhanced version of the 3D Deathchase game engine. This time the view is from behind your bike, so this is visible on screen. The road itself moves sideways, a detail which is part of fairly advanced 3D routines for the time. Contact with the 39 computer bikes will cause your bike to slow, and probably cost you several places. 11 circuits are featured, including favourites such as Spa, Donington and Misano. Races can be set for up to five laps, and times are recorded for comparisons.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mervyn J. Estcourt</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Full Throttle (1984)(Micromega).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Full Throttle (1984)(Micromega).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Pyramid, The (1991)(Zenobi).z80</path>
		<name>Golden Pyramid, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Being a 'free-lance' reporter has it advantages and sat here supping a decent cup of 'Earl Grey' is most certainly one of them not to mention the slab of 'Cherry Genoa' that had accompanied it.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Zenobi Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Golden Pyramid, The (1991)(Zenobi).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Golden Pyramid, The (1991)(Zenobi).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heartland (1986)(Odin Computer Graphics)[aka Kimera].z80</path>
		<name>Heartland</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Heartland's meta-referential plot involves a struggle between good and evil, as depicted in a book, the last six pages of which have become lost. As a result, you must dive into the game's world to complete the story, and ensure that evil doesn't win, by saving the white pages and destroying the black ones.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Odin Computer Graphics Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Odin Computer Graphics Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Heartland (1986)(Odin Computer Graphics)[aka Kimera].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Heartland (1986)(Odin Computer Graphics)[aka Kimera].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Herbert's Dummy Run (1985)(Mikro-Gen).z80</path>
		<name>Herbert's Dummy Run</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Herbert was visiting a large department store with his Mum and Dad (Wally and Wilma!) when he got lost! Now the store is a scary place and full of beasts which will hurt Herbert and make him cry! Help Herbert to explore the store, manipulating the objects he finds to help him get into the lost children office where Wally and Wilma are waiting for him. Objects are picked up by walking into them, but you can only carry two objects at any one time. Some rooms in the game are presented in the form of arcade sub-games. These aren't just for fun - you have to complete them to finish the game!</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>David Perry</developer>
		<publisher>Mikro-gen</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Herbert's Dummy Run (1985)(Mikro-Gen).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Herbert's Dummy Run (1985)(Mikro-Gen).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hero Quest - Return of the Witch Lord (1991)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Hero Quest - Return of the Witch Lord</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A Hero Quest expansion pack with a set of new quests (adapted from a similar expansion to the original board game). This time the quests follow an ongoing storyline. The Witch Lord is back, and the heroes enter the ruined city Kalos to find and defeat him. Return of the Witch Lord plays similarly to the original game, but as the manual warns, is more difficult.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hero Quest - Return of the Witch Lord (1991)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hero Quest - Return of the Witch Lord (1991)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hero Quest (1991)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Hero Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The famous fantasy-themed board game was converted into an isometric-viewed role playing game in which the evil Wizard Morcar must be defeated. You take control of a wizard, a dwarf, a barbarian and an elf, each with different strengths and weaknesses, who each start the 14 missions from opposite sides of the board.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>221B Software Development</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hero Quest (1991)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hero Quest (1991)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hydrofool (1987)(Faster Than Light)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Hydrofool</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After his improbable success in Sweevo's World, the world's least capable robot is back, and must go to the heavily-polluted Deathbowl and clean it up. The Deathbowl's four plugs must be removed, in order, so as to drain the poisonous water and allow it to be refilled.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Carter Follis Software Associates</developer>
		<publisher>FTL - Faster Than Light</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hydrofool (1987)(Faster Than Light)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hydrofool (1987)(Faster Than Light)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper Sports (1985)(Imagine).tap</path>
		<name>Hyper Sports</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Six tough events await in this joystick-waggling action game. The full sequence of events is - swimming, skeet shooting, gymnastics, archery, triple jumping and weightlifting. You must complete each event in order to be allowed onto the next one.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Imagine Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hyper Sports (1985)(Imagine).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hyper Sports (1985)(Imagine).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./I Ball II (1987)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>I, Ball II: Quest for the Past</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After rescuing their people and surviving (in the first game), the Ball race wish to discover something about their history and heritage. You have been sent down mines, to explore 50 screens, on each of which you must collect a key and reach the exit. You also have to pick up a sacred artifact on every 5th level. Your character is very bouncy, requiring small movements in order to keep control. You can shoot at the surrounding enemies and collect weapons, although the initial one only shoots horizontally. There are many pickups on offer, including extra lives, bounciness boosts and opposition-slowers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Timothy Closs</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/I Ball II (1987)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/I Ball II (1987)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./I, Ball (1987)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>I, Ball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Terry Ball (terrible, geddit?) has kidnapped Lover Ball, No Ball, Eddy Ball and Glow Ball, and I,Ball must rescue them through 16 stages. The gameplay is shoot 'em up based, with the 16 levels scrolling vertically. They are full of hazards ranging from step-like sequences of blocks and metallic edges, to Terry Ball's unleashed devices including microwave ovens and crabs. The initial weapons is quite puny, but collecting discs allows upgrades to be obtained, including multi-directional fire and turbo boosts. You have four lives, but must complete each level within a time limit.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Timothy Closs, Kevin Wallace</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/I, Ball (1987)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/I, Ball (1987)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./I, of the Mask (1985)(Electric Dreams).z80</path>
		<name>I, of the Mask</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In I, of the Mask the player controls a 2D character placed over a 3D background, where the goal is to navigate around a maze while collecting parts in order to build a robot. These parts need to be collected in a preset order, promoting exploration.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Electric Dreams Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/I, of the Mask (1985)(Electric Dreams).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/I, of the Mask (1985)(Electric Dreams).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Intensity (1988)(Firebird).z80</path>
		<name>Intensity</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The plot of Intensity deals with the space station Canis Major which was overrun by aliens. There is no chance to defeat them by force and therefore the station has to be evacuated.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold</developer>
		<publisher>Firebird</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Intensity (1988)(Firebird).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Intensity (1988)(Firebird).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Into the Eagle's Nest (1987)(Pandora)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Into the Eagle's Nest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pandora's first game combines the Gauntlet style with the World War 2 setting, and specifically the Eagle's Nest building which is being used by a commander as his HQ. Three Allied soldiers have been captured, and you must infiltrate the facilities, rescue your brave comrades, destroy the building, and salvage as much of the stolen art treasures as possible.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandora</developer>
		<publisher>Pandora</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Into the Eagle's Nest (1987)(Pandora)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Into the Eagle's Nest (1987)(Pandora)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (1990)(Virgin Games)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Enter the world of off-road racing as 4 vehicles will face each other, on a series of tracks which are based around flipped and reversed versions of a core selection. Fame, glory and bikini clad women await your victories and the taste of dirt awaits if you fail. Let a computer car beat you and you lose one of your 3 credits.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Leland Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (1990)(Virgin Games)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road Racer (1990)(Virgin Games)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (1987)(Gremlin Graphics).z80</path>
		<name>Jack the Nipper II: In Coconut Capers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Naughty toddler Jack finds himself in Africa, with the aim of progressing through 192 screens of platform action. He starts with nine lives but no weapons, although a supply of coconuts to lob is close at hand. The jungle is full of snakes, rhinos, birds and all manner of other creatures, all of which must be avoided or killed - remember that their attack paths are pre-programmed, and the trajectory of your coconuts is quite limited. Travelling through the levels involves, amongst other things, ladders, mine carts, trees, ropes and logs.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (1987)(Gremlin Graphics).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jack the Nipper II - In Coconut Capers (1987)(Gremlin Graphics).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jasper! (1984)(Micromega).z80</path>
		<name>Jasper!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jasper the mouse must face 22 screens in this platform puzzler. Tonnes of objects are placed throughout the game, and each has a specific use. You select these using the 1-5 number keys, which tells you that only 5 objects can be carried at a time, which makes for a certain degree of backtracking.</desc>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micromega</developer>
		<publisher>Micromega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jasper! (1984)(Micromega).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jasper! (1984)(Micromega).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klax (1990)(Domark)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Klax</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An action/puzzle game, the object is to catch assorted color falling tiles and create rows, columns, or diagonals of a single color. Each level requires a different pattern to be made, and the tiles fall faster, more at a time, and in an increasing number of colors as the game progresses.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mark Incley</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Klax (1990)(Domark)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Klax (1990)(Domark)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mouse - The Computer Game (1988)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Disney's Mickey Mouse: Computer Game, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Ogre King and his minions have taken over Disney Castle, and it's Mickey's task to win it back. The game starts on a sequence of stairways, up which Mickey must move, shooting any creatures that get in his way. Eventually you will come to a door and go through it, at which point the second section of the game begins.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Graphics Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Mickey Mouse - The Computer Game (1988)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mickey Mouse - The Computer Game (1988)(Gremlin Graphics)(128K).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gregory Loses His Clock (1989)(Mastertronic Plus).z80</path>
		<name>Gregory Loses His Clock</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Settling down for a good nights sleep, our hero Gregory finds his alarm clock, pops it on top of the chest of drawers, and clambers into bed for a restoring regime of kip. The first few Zeds have hardly escaped our Gregs sleeping lips when a naughty ghost intervenes, stealing Greg's timepiece. And this ghostie is really wicked - it breaks the clock into five pieces and scatters them around four weird dreamscape locations.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Don Priestley</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic Plus</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gregory Loses His Clock (1989)(Mastertronic Plus).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gregory Loses His Clock (1989)(Mastertronic Plus).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Defenda.tzx.zip</path>
		<name>Defenda</name>
		<desc>Defenda is a clone of the arcade shooter Defender where the player is in control of a craft that flies over the surface of a planet protecting humanoids from the alien forces.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Defenda.tzx.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Defenda.tzx.mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alan J. Lloyd, Peter J. Stevens</developer>
		<publisher>Interstella Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T135700</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./IK+ (1987)(System 3)(128K)[aka International Karate+].z80</path>
		<name>IK+</name>
		<desc>IK+ is a simple side-on beat 'em up. 3 characters appear on the screen, either 1 player and 2 AI, or 2 player and 1 AI and proceed to kick seven bells out of each other via various karate moves.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/IK+ (1987)(System 3)(128K)[aka International Karate+].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/IK+ (1987)(System 3)(128K)[aka International Karate+].mp4</video>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software</developer>
		<publisher>System 3 Software</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T135946</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Puff in Dragonland (1990)(Cartoon Time)(48K-128K).tzx</path>
		<name>Little Puff in Dragonland</name>
		<desc>Puff is a poor little dragon who decides to explore the world beyond his home - Dragonland. Unfortunately, he is now lost and wants to go back home! Puff is too little to do this adventure by himself so you have to guide him through many levels, solving puzzles, avoiding traps and find all four parts of the pass to get back into Dragonland.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Little Puff in Dragonland (1990)(Cartoon Time)(48K-128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Little Puff in Dragonland (1990)(Cartoon Time)(48K-128K).mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Consult Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T140234</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SOS (1986)(Mastertronic).z80</path>
		<name>S.O.S.</name>
		<desc>Sydney the Droid has crash-landed his plane on Alpha Five, and he must search the city for the plane radio so that he can signal a rescue team to his location. While searching for the radio, Sydney must also avoid being eaten by robots that patrol the city. When he gets eaten, one of Sydney's three lives are lost and Sydney restarts from his present location.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/SOS (1986)(Mastertronic).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SOS (1986)(Mastertronic).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Geoff Foley</developer>
		<publisher>Mastertronic</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T140447</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).zip</path>
		<name>Sabre Wulf</name>
		<desc>The ACG amulet (a reference to Ultimate's formal name of Ashby Computers and Graphics), has been split into four pieces, which are located in different parts of a jungle, and you're the intrepid explorer sent to locate them. The game takes place on a thoroughly huge map, and the viewed area often includes section which overlap and can't be reached directly, due to the huge shrubs and trees which are used as borders.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sabre Wulf (1984)(Ultimate).mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19840101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ashby Computers and Graphics</developer>
		<publisher>Ashby Computers and Graphics</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T140646</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Slightly Magic (1990)(Codemasters)(128k).z80</path>
		<name>Slightly Magic</name>
		<desc>In Slightly Magic you are cast as Slightly - mischievous nephew of legendary wizard Bigwiz, who has suddenly taken off on some urgent business, leaving his castle in disarray with dragons and magical spells running amok. One of the dragons kidnaps the princess, and now Slightly has to save her.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Slightly Magic (1990)(Codemasters)(128k).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Slightly Magic (1990)(Codemasters)(128k).mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Astonishing Animations</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T140844</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Total Recall (1991)(Ocean)(128K).z80</path>
		<name>Total Recall</name>
		<desc>Based on the movie of the same name, Total Recall puts you in charge of Douglas Quaid, who must find a way to Mars in order to find the answers to his two questions: why is he being hunted, and who is hunting him. In order to do this, Quaid must go through level after level of beating up bad guys that get in his way.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Total Recall (1991)(Ocean)(128K).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Total Recall (1991)(Ocean)(128K).mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220223T141112</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
