<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Sharp X68000</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Daimakaimura.hdf</path>
		<name>Daimakaimura</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Three years have passed since Arthur defeated the Demon King Astaroth and rescued his beloved Princess Prin-Prin. A new villain, the Great Demon King Lucifer has become the new leader of Ghoul Realm. While returning from a journey, Arthur sees the Princess' castle and her village under attack by Lucifer's forces. While rushing towards her beloved knight, the Princess is struck by one of Lucifer's laser beams.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Daimakaimura.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Daimakaimura.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Etoile Princesse.hdf</path>
		<name>Étoile Princesse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Takes place in the fantasy world of Fail Land, a set of floating land masses above the skies where a self-centered and careless young princess named Rilule</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Exact</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Etoile Princesse.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Etoile Princesse.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight.hdf</path>
		<name>Final Fight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The streets of Metro City are filled with criminals who are part of a gang called Mad Gear. Former wrestler and newly elected mayor Mike Haggar tries to do something about it, much to the displeasure of the Mad Gear Gang who kidnap his daughter Jessica. Only three people are brave enough to venture into the crime-infested streets and try to bring Jessica back.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fight.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fight.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius.hdf</path>
		<name>Gradius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The people of Gradius are in trouble. The ameoboid Bacterions have launched an all out attack against the planet, and it's up to you to fly into battle and save them. Along the way you'll be able to power up your ship with hyper speed, force fields, lasers, missiles, double beam cannons and more to help you battle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Sharp - SPS</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gradius.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gradius.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Granada.hdf</path>
		<name>Granada</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2016, war has broken out in Africa over mining rights to rare metal. Machines of destruction called "maneuver cepters" have been developed as the primary force, but recently a mysterious maneuver cepter has appeared in the northern territories. It is known by the name of "Granada", and has been destroying the weapons of the factions on both sides. You are this machine's pilot, a man by the name of Leon Todo.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Wolf Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Granada.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Granada.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mid-Garts Gold.hdf</path>
		<name>Mid-Garts Gold</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When the epic, thousand-year-old battle between different dragon clans was finally over, and the benevolent White Dragons started ruling the country of Akranis, it looked like the age of peace has finally arrived. But all changes when the dragon rider Kain finds an ancient weapon known as the Rune Blade. He brings it to the old white dragon Yoshua, who tells him that a powerful protective artifact has been stolen, and the fateful hour has come to Akranis with the help of his dragon Sarken, Kain has to restore peace and save Akranis and the dragon race.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Wolf Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mid-Garts Gold.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mid-Garts Gold.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nemesis 90 Kai.hdf</path>
		<name>Nemesis '90 Kai</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Nemesis '90 Kai is an enhanced remake of Nemesis 2. The main difference lies in presentation, with higher-quality music and significantly more detailed graphics. The gameplay is mostly unchanged, with the exception of the possibility to equip four options on the player-controlled ship (as opposed to only two in the original version) and a few tweaks to secondary weapons and power-ups. Two new stages and four boss enemies have been added to this version.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SPS</developer>
		<publisher>SPS</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nemesis 90 Kai.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nemesis 90 Kai.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sol-Feace.hdf</path>
		<name>Sol-Feace</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sol-Feace (Sol-Deace in the Genesis) is a typical 2D shooter with weapon powerups. The game features six levels: Sirius, Enemy Arsenal, ArtifiStar, Pluto Base, Almathea, and Final Battle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19901122T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Wolf Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sol-Feace.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sol-Feace.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II' - Champion Edition.hdf</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II: Champion Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This version of Street Fighter II is similar in most aspects to the original, save that all 12 characters are selectable from the get-go (the boss characters were originally locked), and the game engine has been revamped.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>SPS</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter II' - Champion Edition.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter II' - Champion Edition.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strider Hiryu.hdf</path>
		<name>Strider Hiryu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2048 AD. In Russia, the evil Grand Master Meio has begun his insane plot to take over the universe. A lone figure drops from a stealth glider into Meio's base. He is Hiryu, Super A-Class Strider. His mission is to defeat the Grand Master and put an end to his plotting once and for all. Strider lets the protagonist run, jump, perform acrobatics and climb walls and overhangs. He wields a plasma sword, called a Cypher, through five levels fighting robots and guards, with mid- and end-level bosses.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Strider Hiryu.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Strider Hiryu.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius II Gofer.hdf</path>
		<name>Gradius II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player returns as the role of the pilot of the Vic Viper spaceship to battle the second onslaughts of the Bacterion Empire, under the new leadership of Gofer, the giant head. Gradius II has kept the gameplay from the original game, but infused it with enhancements brought from the spin-off, Salamander (Life Force). This is primarily evident in two of the weapons configurations that are selectable. Another first in the series was the inclusion of the "boss rush" (also known as "boss parade" or "boss alley"), a level designed entirely with only boss confrontations.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gradius II Gofer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gradius II Gofer.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scorpius (1991)(Shinseisha).dim</path>
		<name>Scorpius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Scorpius is a horizontally scrolling shoot-em-up in which the player can choose to control one of the three available spaceships on their way through exotic planets populated by hostile alien races. The ships vary in shape and use modified versions of basic weapon types. Each ship starts with a low-damage gun and can upgrade and change the weapon to spreading fire, slow but powerful lightning attack, and others. The ships are also equipped with a claw-like tail, which is activated with a separate button. The tail can attack enemies in a circular motions and retracts back to the ship. Most stages require alternating between firearms and the tail for successful completion.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Shinseisha</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Scorpius (1991)(Shinseisha).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Scorpius (1991)(Shinseisha).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chourensha 68K.dim</path>
		<name>Chō Ren Sha 68K</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chō Ren Sha 68K (Ultra Fire 68K) is a top-down vertically scrolling DÅ jinshi shoot 'em up. It was originally released in 1995 and later it was ported to PC. It is a shooter with classic mechanics modeled after the Toaplan games. There is one ship and it can be moved around freely. Shooting needs to be done manually as there is no autofire. Points are earned by killing enemies, completing levels and collecting items. It has seven stages with up to eight loops and a final boss after a few. Red power-up ships that are shot leave behind one of three items: a weapon upgrade, a bomb that clears the entire screen and a one-hit shield that also explodes when it disappears.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Famibe No Yosshin</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chourensha 68K.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chourensha 68K.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R+R.HDF</path>
		<name>R + R</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Great looking shoot'em up game programmed by Nin Nikki.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<publisher>NIN-NIKI</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/R+R.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R+R.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Babel no Tou.hdm</path>
		<name>Babel no Tō</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It is an action puzzle game, and it was never released for play outside of Japan. The game consists of 64 "floors" or puzzles that involve the positioning of many L-shaped blocks.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Gamma AWC</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Babel no Tou.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Babel no Tou.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Overtake.hdf</path>
		<name>Overtake</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Overtake is a first-person perspective racing game featuring all teams, drivers and circuits from the 1992 Formula One World Championship.There are 3 game modes available: Quick Race, Test Run and World Championship. There's also a database feature with information about the drivers, teams as well as car specs. In car setting menu players can fine-tune their car including front and rear wings, suspension, camber and gear ratios, plus choose tires, whether to have either manual or automatic gear shifting and select number of gears.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Zoom</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Overtake.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Overtake.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parodius Da!.hdf</path>
		<name>Parodius Da!: Shinwa kara Owarai e</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Similar to the Gradius series with a few differences. Parodius retains the selectability of different weapons configurations but implements via four different characters: Vic Viper (from Gradius), Octopus, TwinBee, and Pentarou.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Parodius Da!.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Parodius Da!.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula.hdf</path>
		<name>Akumajō Dracula</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Akumajō Dracula is the name of the 1993 Castlevania game released in Japan on the Sharp X68000 home computer system. It was a remake of the original Akumajou Dracula game. Due to the X68000 not being released outside of Japan, this game was never released outside of Japan either.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930723T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Akumajou Dracula.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Akumajou Dracula.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zugya (English Translated).hdm</path>
		<name>Zugyā</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The mission is to destroy enemy space stations in each stage within a strict time limit. A map points out where each station is and more points are awarded for taking out the ones that say "TARGET" in order, than just destroying them randomly. You can power up your ordinary shot into a more powerful spread shot. Also your ship has a plasma bar; it is charged by holding the shot button, when full it will protect you from one shot and when released creates a wave of energy around you that makes the ship briefly invincible and destroys whatever is near it. The game has 50 stages and there are two game modes available: normal game and score attack.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Sprite</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zugya (English Translated).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zugya (English Translated).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akazukin Cha Cha Cha (English Translated).hdm</path>
		<name>Akazukin Cha Cha Cha</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Akazukin Cha Cha Cha is an X68000 shooter developed by Sprite. It is based on characters from the manga and animated television series of the same name.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Sprite</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Akazukin Cha Cha Cha (English Translated).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Akazukin Cha Cha Cha (English Translated).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>