<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>PC Dos</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Wacky Wheels (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Wacky Wheels</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wacky Wheels is an MS-DOS arcade kart racing video game released by Apogee Software in 1994. The game strongly resembles Super Mario Kart from the Super NES, but the karts are described as lawn mowers and the eight playable characters are animals from a zoo.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T140501</releasedate>
		<developer>Beavis Soft</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wacky Wheels (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wacky Wheels (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stunts (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Stunts</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of the classic 3D car racing simulations. A variety of cars and opponents to choose from. The game provided unusual stunt objects including loops, corkscrews and jumps. You can watch your race in instant replay from different camera angles. A track editor is included as well. *Copy Protection Guide* home/pi/retropie/RDmanuals</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19901001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Distinctive Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Br?derbund Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stunts (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stunts (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klass of 99.zip</path>
		<name>Skool Daze: Klass of '99</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Skool Daze: Klass of '99 is a remake / update of a classic ZX Spectrum Skool Daze and Back To Skool games from the 1980's. You play as Eric, a troublemaker who is on a quest to delete his permanent record from his school's computer.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19990301T134735</releasedate>
		<developer>RetroSpec</developer>
		<publisher>RetroSpec</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Klass of 99.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Klass of 99.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Supaplex (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Supaplex</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Supaplex is a puzzle game reminiscent of Boulder Dash; find the exit while collecting all Infotrons and avoiding the Zonks that can kill you.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Think!Ware Development</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Integration Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Supaplex (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Supaplex (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Oregon Trail Deluxe, The (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Oregon Trail, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As a covered wagon party of pioneers, you head out west from Independence, MI to the Willamette River and valley in Oregon. You first must stock up on provisions, and then, while traveling, make decisions such as when to rest, how much food to eat, etc. The Oregon Trail incorporates strategy and planning ahead along with discovery and adventure as well as action (hunting and floating down the Dalles river).</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MECC</developer>
		<publisher>MECC</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Oregon Trail Deluxe, The (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Oregon Trail Deluxe, The (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Atomix (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Atomix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Atomix is a puzzle game. On each level, you are given a couple of atoms, and your task is to arrange them into a specific shapes. In a top-down view, you see all the atoms available for you to move, and all the directions they can connect to. Down below on the left side is a small picture of what you must get. That picture represents some molecular structure that you must complete by moving atoms horizontally and vertically. Once you move your atom, it won't stop unless it bumps into something, so you have to use other atoms as blockades to prevent it from going into unwanted areas.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T134636</releasedate>
		<developer>TaleSoft</developer>
		<publisher>Thalion Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Atomix (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Atomix (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Berusky (1999).zip</path>
		<name>Berusky</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An old idea of moving boxes in a maze has been expanded with new logic items such as explosives, stones, special gates and so on. In addition, up to five bugs can cooperate and be controlled by the player.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Martin Stransky</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Berusky (1999).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Berusky (1999).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brix (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Brix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Brix is a puzzle game for MS-DOS, developed by Michael Riedel and produced and published by Epic MegaGames in 1992. It is a clone of Taito's Puzznic, and thus bears strong graphical and some gameplay similarities to Flipull/Plotting, also produced by Taito.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T133313</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic Games</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Brix (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Brix (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystal Caves Volume 2.zip</path>
		<name>Crystal Caves Volume 2: Slugging It Out</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After selling his twibble farm for a loss, Mylo heads back to Altair. A recent war has created a demand for medicinal slugs, so now Mylo wants to buy a slug farm. He collects enough crystals to do so, and for a while, business is booming. However, the slugs soon burrow their way into an abandoned salt mine and perish, depriving Mylo of his stock.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910301T133934</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crystal Caves Volume 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crystal Caves Volume 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystal Caves Volume 3.zip</path>
		<name>Crystal Caves Volume 3: Mylo Versus the Supernova</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A late-night infomercial inspires Mylo to quit farming and try his hand at real estate. He collects enough crystals to buy an entire solar system from Rip Eweoff. Mylo plans to turn the system into a vacation resort: tropical getaways on the inner planets, ski slopes on the outer planets, and luxury hotels in the middle.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910301T133934</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crystal Caves Volume 3.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crystal Caves Volume 3.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./bumpy.zip</path>
		<name>Bumpy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first game in the Bumpy series is, just like its sequels, about a head that can bump a lot. You control whether the head shall bump left or right, and how far up it will bounce, in a similar fashion to Mappy. You have to move across a series of bouncy platforms and pick up all items on the screen. Once all items are collected, the exit will appear so that you can go on to the next screen.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890301T133410</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/bumpy.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/bumpy.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Duck Tales - The Quest for Gold (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's DuckTales: The Quest for Gold</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Although not commonly regarded as a formidable software developer, Disney nevertheless scores big with this game, an entertaining mixture of platform and arcade, with a bit of strategy thrown in (you can buy/sell stocks, and choose where to hunt treasures).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901231T134201</releasedate>
		<developer>Incredible Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Walt Disney</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Disney's Duck Tales - The Quest for Gold (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Disney's Duck Tales - The Quest for Gold (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem II (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the "near future" year 1998, the evil Rigelatins plan to enslave Earth, and they kidnap Duke Nukem (who was performing in an interview about his new autobiography, "Why I'm So Great"), to use his brain to plot the attack for their forces. Duke must break free in order to save the world, once again.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931203T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Duke Nukem II (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Duke Nukem II (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars X-Wing (Collector's CD-ROM) (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars: X-Wing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Star Wars: X-Wing is a space simulation video game, the first of the X-Wing combat flight simulator game series. The player's character flies starfighters, including the eponymous X-wing, for the Rebel Alliance as part of a narrative that precedes and parallels the events of Star Wars Episode IV.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930301T134934</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars X-Wing (Collector's CD-ROM) (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars X-Wing (Collector's CD-ROM) (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./wasteland.zip</path>
		<name>Wasteland: Adventure in Post-Nuclear America</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wasteland takes place in the future after the nuclear holocaust of World War III. The player guides band of Desert Rangers from town to town, gradually uncovering a sinister plot that threatens what's left of mankind.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/wasteland.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/wasteland.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem - Episode 2 - Mission - Moonbase (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem: Episode 2: Mission Moonbase</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in the year 1997, your mission is to stop Dr. Proton, a madman bent on ruling the world with his army of Techbots. As the irrepressible hero Duke Nukem, you'll chase Dr. Proton deep into the Earth, then to his lunar space station, and eventually into the Earth's nuclear ravished future.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Duke Nukem - Episode 2 - Mission - Moonbase (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Duke Nukem - Episode 2 - Mission - Moonbase (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Bash Part 3.zip</path>
		<name>Monster Bash: Part 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil Count Chuck has kidnapped all the world's animals in order to turn them into soldiers in his dark army. Johnny Dash's dog, Tex, has been captured along with the other animals, and it's up to him to enter the Night World and save him!You use a slingshot to combat the ghastly enemies, which include skeletons, zombies, and severed hands.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Monster Bash Part 3.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Monster Bash Part 3.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jill of The Jungle [SW] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc) [Action].zip</path>
		<name>Jill of the Jungle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jill of the Jungle is a platform sidescroller which was released during the same period as Commander Keen and Duke Nukem. Players play as an Amazon woman who can use various types of weapons and enhancements as she progresses through levels slaying monsters and finding keys. The first episode in the trilogy contains 15 playable levels, including a bonus level, each of which can be entered from an overworld resembling another level.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic MegaGames, Inc., Orange Games</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jill of The Jungle [SW] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc) [Action].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jill of The Jungle [SW] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc) [Action].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jill of the Jungle vol. 2- Jill Goes Underground [SWR] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc.) [Action].zip</path>
		<name>Jill of the Jungle: Jill Goes Underground</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jill of the Jungle is a platform sidescroller which was released during the same period as Commander Keen and Duke Nukem. Players play as an Amazon woman who can use various types of weapons and enhancements as she progresses through levels slaying monsters and finding keys. The first episode in the trilogy (Jill of the Jungle) contains 15 playable levels, including a bonus level, each of which can be entered from an overworld resembling another level. This second episode uses 20 sequential levels without an overworld.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic MegaGames, Inc., Orange Games</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jill of the Jungle vol. 2- Jill Goes Underground [SWR] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc.) [Action].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jill of the Jungle vol. 2- Jill Goes Underground [SWR] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc.) [Action].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jill of the Jungle vol. 3- Jill Saves the Prince [SWR] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc.) [Action].zip</path>
		<name>Jill of the Jungle: Jill Saves the Prince</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jill of the Jungle is a platform sidescroller which was released during the same period as Commander Keen and Duke Nukem. Players play as an Amazon woman who can use various types of weapons and enhancements as she progresses through levels slaying monsters and finding keys. The first episode in the trilogy (Jill of the Jungle) contains 15 playable levels, including a bonus level.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic MegaGames, Inc., Orange Games</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jill of the Jungle vol. 3- Jill Saves the Prince [SWR] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc.) [Action].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jill of the Jungle vol. 3- Jill Saves the Prince [SWR] (1992)(Epic MegaGames, Inc.) [Action].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hocus Pocus.zip</path>
		<name>Hocus Pocus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This mission will take Hocus to 16 unique realms, each filled with unique dangers and enemies. Few have survived Terexin's final test. For many it's a one-way trip. Along the way Hocus will encounter dragons, imps, ghosts and 30 more unique creatures, demons and enemies. Survive, and Hocus becomes a full-fledged, card carrying Wizard. The other option is not so favorable. After every two levels of play the level graphics, background and enemies completely change, giving this game unparalleled variety.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Moonlite Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hocus Pocus.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hocus Pocus.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret Agent.zip</path>
		<name>Secret Agent: Mission 1: The Hunt for Red Rock Rover</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Agent 006, you are the world's only hope: the terrorist organization known as the D.V.S. has captured the blueprints to a new, powerful weapon known as the ''Red Rock Rover''. Your mission is to infiltrate an island occupied by the D.V.S. and retrieve the first part of the blueprints.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Secret Agent.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret Agent.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elder Scrolls, The - Arena (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Elder Scrolls: Arena, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Elder Scrolls: Arena is a first-person action role-playing game, in which you must rescue the Emperor Uriel Septim VII from his dimensional prison by recovering the eight pieces of the Staff of Chaos. The emperor's position has been usurped by impersonator Jagar Tharn whose slain apprentice rallies the player in his dreams to find the eight pieces of the staff and return the status quo.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Bethesda Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>Bethesda Softworks</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Elder Scrolls, The - Arena (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Elder Scrolls, The - Arena (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Descent II (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Descent II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The second Descent game features new levels, new weapons and new robot enemies. It also comes with helpful ideas for the player like the Guide-bot, the ability to fly with afterburner or energy-to-shield converter that many times they become a must!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parallax Software Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Descent II (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Descent II (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need for Speed, The - Special Edition (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Need for Speed, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Drive some of your favourite sports cars through wild and fast tracks, including the Dodge Viper, Lamborghini, Ferrari, Porshe, Corvette, Mazda RX7, Toyota Supra Turbo, and Acura NSX. Some of the tracks are open road, meaning you simply fly down a huge highway, with cops following in hot pursuit. One of the options in the game allows you to pick which time of the day to race in.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19950902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Need for Speed, The - Special Edition (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Need for Speed, The - Special Edition (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DOOM (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Doom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Doom is divided into three episodes: "Knee-Deep in the Dead", "The Shores of Hell", and "Inferno". A fourth episode, "Thy Flesh Consumed", was added in an expanded version of the game, The Ultimate Doom, released in 1995, two years later and one year after Doom II. The campaign contains very few plot elements, with the minimal story instead given in the instruction manual and in short text segues between episodes.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/DOOM (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DOOM (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Epic Pinball (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Epic Pinball: The Complete Collection</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Epic Pinball The Complete Collection is a pinball video game played from a 2D top-down view within a scrollable window. This release is an Epic Pinball compilation with some exclusive content.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Digital Extremes</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Epic Pinball (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Epic Pinball (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fallout.zip</path>
		<name>Fallout</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gameplay in Fallout consists of traveling around the game world, visiting locations and interacting with the local inhabitants, and is typically in real-time. Occasionally, inhabitants will be immersed in dilemmas which the player may choose to solve in order to acquire karma and experience points.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Isle Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fallout.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fallout.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate DOOM, The (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Ultimate Doom: Thy Flesh Consumed, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Ultimate Doom takes you far beyond the realms of your experience. All three original episodes of the greatest, splattertastic, adrenaline pumping game ever made are here - that's 27 levels of doomogerous gameplay to challenge even the most hardened gamer. But that's just for starters Then, but only if you're tough enough, you can pick up the gauntlet of an all-new episode.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultimate DOOM, The (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultimate DOOM, The (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem - Episode 1 - Shrapnel City (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem: Episode 1: Shrapnel City</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in the year 1997, your mission is to stop Dr. Proton, a madman bent on ruling the world with his army of Techbots. As the irrepressible hero Duke Nukem, you'll chase Dr. Proton deep into the Earth, then to his lunar space station, and eventually into the Earth's nuclear ravished future.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Duke Nukem - Episode 1 - Shrapnel City (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Duke Nukem - Episode 1 - Shrapnel City (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chip 'N Dale Rescue Rangers - The Adventures in Nimnul's Castle (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers: The Adventures in Nimmul's Castle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers: The Adventures in Nimmul's Castle is an action video game developed by Riedel Software Productions and co-published by Hi Tech Expressions and Walt Disney Computer Software based on the Disney animated series of the same name.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T133642</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Hi Tech Expressions, Disney</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chip 'N Dale Rescue Rangers - The Adventures in Nimnul's Castle (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chip 'N Dale Rescue Rangers - The Adventures in Nimnul's Castle (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Christmas Jetpack.zip</path>
		<name>Jetpack Christmas Special</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jetpack Christmas Special is a freeware edition of Jetpack featuring new, Christmas themed levels from the original developers.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930201T133745</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Software Creations</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Christmas Jetpack.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Christmas Jetpack.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem - Episode 3 - Trapped in the Future (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem: Episode 3: Trapped in the Future</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in the year 1997, your mission is to stop Dr. Proton, a madman bent on ruling the world with his army of Techbots. As the irrepressible hero Duke Nukem, you'll chase Dr. Proton deep into the Earth, then to his lunar space station, and eventually into the Earth's nuclear ravished future.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Duke Nukem - Episode 3 - Trapped in the Future (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Duke Nukem - Episode 3 - Trapped in the Future (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Settlers II, The (Gold Edition) (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Settlers II: Veni, Vidi, Vici (Gold Edition), The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You start your settlement with only one main building. To build any other buildings, you first must find a source for stones and wood. So you start to build little roads where your men transport all the different goods along. There exist more than 30 different professions your men can have, and many different building types. Of course, there are other settlers in your area, too, so war is unavoidable. The graphics are now in SVGA, and the soundtrack is available as CD-Audio or MIDI.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960417T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Blue Byte</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Settlers II, The (Gold Edition) (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Settlers II, The (Gold Edition) (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Albion (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Albion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2227. The powerful DDT Corporation has sent a factory ship called the Toronto to harvest minerals and resources from Albion, a newly discovered world which is supposedly barren of life but rich in resources. The space pilot Tom Driscoll is sent to take some atmospheric readings on the planet, but crash lands after an apparently accidental systems failure of his shuttle. Upon recovering from the accident he is shocked to discover that Albion is in fact a rich, life-filled world inhabited by various races with their unique cultures. It then becomes his task to explore the strange new world, helps its inhabitants, and eventually find his way back to Toronto.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Blue Byte</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Albion (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Albion (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WarCraft - Orcs and Humans (1994).zip</path>
		<name>WarCraft: Orcs &amp; Humans</name>
		<sortname>WarCraft 1</sortname>
		<desc>The Orcs originated from another world, where the majority were bloodthirsty warriors driven by strife. However, their Warlocks remained aloof, devoted to the research of magic. The Warlocks noticed a rift between the dimensions and, after many years, opened a small portal to another world. One Warlock explored and found a region, whose Human inhabitants called it "Azeroth", from which the Warlock returned with strange plants as evidence of his discovery.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/WarCraft - Orcs and Humans (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WarCraft - Orcs and Humans (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Simpsons - Bart's House of Weirdness (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Simpsons: Bart's House of Weirdness, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bart Simpson has been sent to his room and it’s up to you to help him escape and collect the items he’ll need to rescue his hero Krusty the Clown. Along with the standard side scroller jump/duck, Bart is armed with a variety of weapons such as a slingshot, spray paint, and water balloons which he can use to dispatch the space mutants, basement ghosts, and other uncool things getting in his way.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rory Armes</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/The Simpsons - Bart's House of Weirdness (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/The Simpsons - Bart's House of Weirdness (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima Underworld - The Stygian Abyss (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima Underworld: The Stygian Abyss</name>
		<sortname>Ultima X</sortname>
		<desc>Ultima Underworld is set in Britannia, the fantasy world of the Ultima series. Specifically, the game takes place inside a large, underground dungeon called the Great Stygian Abyss. The dungeon's entrance lies on the Isle of the Avatar, an island ruled by Baron Almric. The Abyss first appeared in Ultima IV: Quest of the Avatar, in which it contains the player's final goal, the Codex of Ultimate Wisdom.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Sky Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima Underworld - The Stygian Abyss (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima Underworld - The Stygian Abyss (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen 3 - Keen Must Die! (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen 3: Keen Must Die!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the third episode, Keen journeys to the Vorticon homeworld of Vorticon VI to find the Grand Intellect. He travels through Vorticon cities and outposts to gain access to the Grand Intellect's lair, fighting mostly against the Vorticons themselves. Upon reaching the lair, he discovers that the Grand Intellect is actually his school rival Mortimer McMire, whose IQ is "a single point higher" than Keen's. Keen defeats Mortimer and his "Mangling Machine" and frees the Vorticons from mind-control; the Vorticon king and "the other Vorticons you haven't slaughtered" then award him a medal for saving them.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen 3 - Keen Must Die! (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen 3 - Keen Must Die! (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen 4 - Secret of the Oracle (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen 4: Secret of the Oracle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Commander Keen in Goodbye, Galaxy was released for MS-DOS on December 15, 1991 as the second main game in the series. Consisting of episodes four and five of the series, "Secret of the Oracle" and "The Armageddon Machine", and stylized as Commander Keen in Goodbye, Galaxy!, it was developed by id and published through Apogee. Like the first trilogy of episodes, "Oracle" was released for free, and the other episode sold by Apogee. The game incorporates a more polished version of the graphical updates in Keen Dreams, along with further gameplay changes and additions.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen 4 - Secret of the Oracle (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen 4 - Secret of the Oracle (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen 5 - The Armageddon Machine (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen 5: The Armageddon Machine</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Commander Keen in Goodbye, Galaxy was released for MS-DOS on December 15, 1991 as the second main game in the series. Consisting of episodes four and five of the series, "Secret of the Oracle" and "The Armageddon Machine", and stylized as Commander Keen in Goodbye, Galaxy!, it was developed by id and published through Apogee. Like the first trilogy of episodes, "Oracle" was released for free, and the other episode sold by Apogee. The game incorporates a more polished version of the graphical updates in Keen Dreams, along with further gameplay changes and additions.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen 5 - The Armageddon Machine (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen 5 - The Armageddon Machine (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen 6 - Aliens Ate My Baby Sitter! (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen 6: Aliens Ate My Baby Sitter!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Commander Keen in Aliens Ate My Babysitter is a side-scrolling platform video game: the majority of the game features the player-controlled Commander Keen viewed from the side while moving on a two-dimensional plane. The player can move left and right and can jump, and can use a pogo stick to bounce continuously and jump higher than they can normally with the correct timing.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen 6 - Aliens Ate My Baby Sitter! (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen 6 - Aliens Ate My Baby Sitter! (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima I - The First Age of Darkness (1986).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima I: The First Age of Darkness</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ultima revolves around a quest to find and destroy the Gem of Immortality, which is being used by the evil wizard Mondain to enslave the lands of Sosaria. With the gem in his possession, he cannot be killed, and his minions roam and terrorize the countryside. The player takes on the role of "The Stranger", an individual summoned from another world to end the rule of Mondain. The game follows the endeavors of the stranger in this task, which involves progressing through many aspects of game play, including dungeon crawling and space travel.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima I - The First Age of Darkness (1986).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima I - The First Age of Darkness (1986).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Abuse (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Abuse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It is the unimaginably distant year 2009. You are Nick Vrenna, falsely locked inside a high security prison. The genetic experiments conducted in the prison, combined with a full-scale riot that took place recently, caused all guards and inmates to be transformed into insane, aggressive mutants. Your job is to escape while stopping the genetic plague from transforming the whole world.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crack dot Com</developer>
		<publisher>Crack dot Com</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Abuse (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Abuse (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Rampage (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Alien Rampage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alien Rampagne is a 2D side-scroller with large animated sprites and multiple layers of parallaxing backgrounds. You are a lone angry alien dude with a bad attitude. You crash landed on an inhospitable planet, and thus you set out to get back to a ship so you can leave this horrible place. To make it, you'll blast hundreds upon hundreds of nasty creatures, enemy bounty hunters, and you'll use some pretty impressive weaponry to do it. You'll also get to buy power ups and get help from the goofy local troll-like natives, to solve puzzles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inner Circle Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Softdisk Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien Rampage (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien Rampage (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ark of Time (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Ark of Time</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play the sports journalist Richard Kendall. In the summer of 1997, an expedition of four explorers have set out into the abysses of the Atlantic Ocean to find any traces of the mythical sunken city of Atlantis. They are the archeologist Professor Caldwell, the scientist Helen, the sponsor of the journey Mr. Blower and his nephew Simon. When they suddenly stop communicating Richard is the one whose task it is to find them. He would much rather stay in London and cover football matches but his editor insists and he complies. His search takes him to several locations around the world including the Caribbean, Stonehenge, Easter Island and Atlantis itself. The puzzles are mostly inventory based.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Trecision S.p.A.</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ark of Time (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ark of Time (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Betrayal at Krondor (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Betrayal at Krondor</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on Raymond E. Feist's Riftwar saga (and co-written with Feist himself) is Betrayal At Krondor, a new tale in the Riftwar universe. The story begins as Gorath, a moredhel (dark elf) renegade, who intended to warn the people of Krondor of the upcoming moredhel invasion, is attacked by an assassin. Locklear, a nobleman who serves the crown of Krondor, and a young magician named Owyn decide to accompany Gorath to Krondor, where they'll have to think of a plan to stop the moredhel leader Delekhan. Exploration in a 3D world and turn-based combat complement the story, which is divided up into nine chapters. Each chapter has a goal to achieve before moving on to the next chapter, but how that goal is met is up to you.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dynamix</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Betrayal at Krondor (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Betrayal at Krondor (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Big Red Racing (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Big Red Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A diverse arcade racing game with 16 different vehicles (not just cars, but also boats, trucks, spacecraft, and helicopters) to race. There are 24 circuits across 7 distinct terrains such as dirt, inner city and a futuristic sci-fi setting. Multiplayer games can be split-screen, modem or network based. In addition to a yoof-style soundtrack, audio commentary is on offer. The appearance of your vehicle can be customised, and the action viewed from multiple camera angles.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19960229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Big Red Software Company Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Domark</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Big Red Racing (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Big Red Racing (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Biing! Sex, Intrigue and Scalpels (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Biing!: Sex, Intrigue and Scalpels</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Biing!: Sex, Intrigue and Scalpels is an erotic hospital-management simulation. You must build a hospital, starting from buying a building for it, then hiring doctors, nurses and receptionists. The game contains typical management simulation elements, albeit with a humorous twist: the doctors are idiots who don't really care for their patients, and the nurses have huge breasts and even do a little striptease from time to time.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>reLINE Software</developer>
		<publisher>Magic Bytes</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Biing! Sex, Intrigue and Scalpels (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Biing! Sex, Intrigue and Scalpels (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bio Menace (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Bio Menace</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The CIA has learned that gigantic mutants are wreaking havoc in Metro City and their sources say that the destruction is caused by a scientist calling himself Dr. Mangle. For this reason, they send Snake Logan, the CIA's top secret agent, on a dangerous mission: fly over Metro City, investigate what?s going on, then report back to the captain. Unfortunately, Snake?s plane is shot down, forcing Snake to walk the streets and kill mutants. There are three episodes in this game: In ?Dr. Mangle's Lab? and ?The Hidden Lab?, Snake must destroy two labs and Dr. Mangle himself.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bio Menace (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bio Menace (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blake Stone - Aliens of Gold (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Blake Stone: Aliens of Gold</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Aliens of Gold, the first game in the Blake Stone series, pits the space-age British secret agent against Dr. Pyrus Goldfire; a madman bent on world domination. Using a mastery of genetic engineering and a tremendous reserve of wealth, Dr. Goldfire intends to unleash a mutant army upon the Earth. The first chapter begins in Goldfire's S.T.A.R. Institute headquarters building. Each level has Blake fighting through guards to find an elevator keycard for the next level. Dr. Goldfire will personally appear along the way to fire shots at Blake, and his genetic creations also pose a tough challenge.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>JAM Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blake Stone - Aliens of Gold (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blake Stone - Aliens of Gold (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blood and Magic (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Blood &amp; Magic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blood &amp; Magic is a real-time strategy game focused on unit management rather than base construction. It uses the Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons license (and thus has AD&amp;D type units) and takes place in the Forgotten Realms AD&amp;D setting. There are five separate storyline scenarios of increasing difficulty with three missions per scenario, playable from the side of both factions each, for a total of 30 missions in the game. The game is tile-based with a 2D top-down perspective.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tachyon</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blood and Magic (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blood and Magic (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Caesar (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Caesar</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first in the strategy series set in the Roman Empire’s peak era starts off with you as ruler of a small province, although if you’re successful you will get tougher assignments. You must build the city, placing crucial features such as housing estates, roads, policing, water supply, social events and the like. You’re not restricted to one city – you can build another area, linked by roads, once you’ve got the first one running smoothly. You have slaves at your disposal to build and maintain everything.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Impressions Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Caesar (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Caesar (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Cthulu - Shadow of the Comet (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Call of Cthulhu: Shadow of the Comet</name>
		<sortname>Call of Cthulhu 1</sortname>
		<desc>In 1834, in the small New England fishing village of Illsmouth, the distinguished British scientist Lord Boleskine lost his mind. After studying ancient manuscripts of evil repute, he had travelled to this place to observe the passing of Halley's comet. What he observed that night, however, turned him into a raving lunatic. Now, 76 years later, Halley's comet is coming back, and young astronomer John T. Parker has travelled to Illsmouth to try to uncover the truth in Boleskine's wild claims, and see the comet for himself. Shadow Of The Comet is a unique horror adventure, inspired by the terrifying writings of H. P. Lovecraft.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>I?Motion, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Call of Cthulu - Shadow of the Comet (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Call of Cthulu - Shadow of the Comet (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prisoner of Ice (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Call of Cthulhu: Prisoner of Ice</name>
		<sortname>Call of Cthulhu 2</sortname>
		<desc>Another game in Infogrames' line of H. P. Lovecraft inspired games started by Alone In the Dark, Prisoner of Ice puts you in the role of Lt. Ryan, an American agent stationed aboard the submarine H.M.S. Victoria on a rescue mission to the Antarctic. The Victoria picks up two mysterious crates during the course of the rescue. Before you know it the Captain is eaten alive by the cargo, a horrific monster with whom you are trapped aboard the submarine. And that's just the start of your problems.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chaosium Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>I?Motion, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Prisoner of Ice (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Prisoner of Ice (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Colony 28 (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Colony 28</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In one bad day for humans, mankind was overwhelmed by an alien's captors. It was written year 2013 and human armies lasted only several weeks. And now it's over. These who had been talented become robots, with embedded control chip to assure theirs obedience, serving as supervisors in remaining human colonies.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>5th Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Napoleon Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Colony 28 (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Colony 28 (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Command and Conquer (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Command &amp; Conquer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Includes Covert Operations Add-On. Command &amp; Conquer developed ideas from Westwood's previous game Dune 2, forming a real-time strategy (RTS) game which has influenced many. The control system involves selecting units with the mouse and then directing them, while the opponents make their moves without waiting for a ''turn'' to end. The game focuses on a war between two organizations, The Brotherhood of Nod and the Global Defense Initiative. The player can take control of either side for more than 15 missions. Both have different units and structures, including artillery, tanks and light infantry.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Command and Conquer (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Command and Conquer (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Command &amp; Conquer - Red Alert (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Command &amp; Conquer: Red Alert</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>What if Hitler never existed? Einstein pondered the question and created a time-machine to eliminate Hitler as a young man, thus preventing World War II as history remembers it. However, Einstein stopped one evil only to create another - because Stalin's Soviet Union is now poised to conquer Europe and Allies must stop them!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19961118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Command &amp; Conquer - Red Alert (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Command &amp; Conquer - Red Alert (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen 1 - Marooned on Mars (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen 1: Marooned on Mars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is broken up into three episodes: "Marooned on Mars", "The Earth Explodes", and "Keen Must Die!". In the first episode, eight-year-old child genius Billy Blaze builds a spaceship and puts on his older brother's football helmet to become Commander Keen.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen 1 - Marooned on Mars (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen 1 - Marooned on Mars (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen 2 - The Earth Explodes (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen 2: The Earth Explodes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the second episode, the Vorticon mothership has locked its X-14 Tantalus Ray cannons on eight of Earth's landmarks, and Keen journeys to the ship to find and deactivate each of the cannons. Keen does so by fighting more varied enemies and hazards and a Vorticon at each cannon's control. At the end of the episode, he discovers that the Vorticons are being mind-controlled by the mysterious Grand Intellect, who is actually behind the attack on Earth.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen 2 - The Earth Explodes (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen 2 - The Earth Explodes (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crusader - No Remorse (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Crusader: No Remorse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As a Silencer -- one of the elite enforcers of the World Economic Consortium -- you're supposed to be incorruptible. But if the system you serve is utterly corrupt, where does that leave you? You go over to the Resistance, the same pack you used to hunt down. Now, your former employers better watch their backs because you're coming after them with all the firepower at your command.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Origin</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crusader - No Remorse (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crusader - No Remorse (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dangerous Dave.zip</path>
		<name>Dangerous Dave</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The object of the game is to collect gold cups to move on to the next level. Since the original 1988 publishing of Dangerous Dave on UpTime, there have been three sequels and three ports of the original to other platforms.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dangerous Dave.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dangerous Dave.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dangerous Dave in the Haunted Mansion (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Dangerous Dave II: Dangerous Dave in the Haunted Mansion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this side-scrolling action game you run through a huge mansion with many different levels, battling all kinds of monsters and collecting items (mostly bonus points). Every so-and-so points you get an additional life, and every so-and-so levels you combat a boss. One of the things that make this game unique is that instead of just having a limited amount of ammunition, you have a shotgun and can shoot 8 bullets at any given time. However, you must wait in order for Dave to reload his gun. Another thing that sets the game apart is the ability to aim your gun in several angles (generally: up, down or straight ahead).</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Gamer's Edge</developer>
		<publisher>Softdisk Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dangerous Dave in the Haunted Mansion (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dangerous Dave in the Haunted Mansion (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dangerous Dave's Risky Rescue (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Dangerous Dave's Risky Rescue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dangerous Dave's Risky Rescue (known informally as Dangerous Dave 3) is a platform game developed by Gamer's Edge and published by Softdisk in 1993 for DOS computers. It is the sequel to Dangerous Dave in the Haunted Mansion, and is also the first Dangerous Dave game to not be programmed by John Romero. This is because he, John Carmack, Adrian Carmack and Tom Hall had left Softdisk by this point to form id Software. It was followed by a sequel, Dave Goes Nutz!, which shares similar gameplay element.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dangerous Dave's Risky Rescue (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dangerous Dave's Risky Rescue (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darklands (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Darklands</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Deep in the twilight of the Black Forest, you and your companions crouch before the robber-knight's tower. Hans, the alchemist, places his mysterious potion by the door. Ebhard the friar implores Saint Dunstan to bless your weapons and armor. And you and Gretchen grip naked longswords, praying your plate mail won't squeak.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MPS Labs</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Darklands (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Darklands (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death Rally (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Death Rally</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Death Rally is a top-down racing game where the player can rely on more than speed to be the number one, and brains must be riding along brawn to get the most from each race.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Remedy Entertainment Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Death Rally (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Death Rally (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Descent (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Descent</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Post-Terran Minerals Corporation (PTMC) digs up minerals on all nine planets of the solar system, employing humans and robots to do its job. Unfortunately, the mining robots are now being controlled by a hacker, and have taken the human workers hostage. The PTMC has tried to get the robots back under their control, but communication with the mining stations has been lost. In desperation, the PTMC modifies a Pyro-GX ship for combat and hires a mercenary, codenamed ''Material Defender'', to fly it. The mission is to destroy the infected mines and rescue human hostages, destroying any hostile robot that gets in the way.Descent is a 3D first-person game that puts the player at the controls of the Pyro-GX spaceship.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Parallax Software Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Descent (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Descent (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Die Hard (1989).zip</path>
		<name>Die Hard</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the movie, a group of terrorists has taken control of a high rise tower in an attempt to take $600 million. Your job is to rescue your wife who is trapped in the building and stop the terrorists. The game is played with a 3-D point of view allowing you to search the building for useful items and fight terrorists with a variety of weapons or by hand. Cut scenes keep you informed of the plot as it progresses.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dynamix</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Die Hard (1989).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Die Hard (1989).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duke Nukem 3D - Atomic Edition (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Duke Nukem 3D: Atomic Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Atomic Edition of Duke Nukem 3D contains the three original episodes of the main game, the Plutonium Pak expansion, and many additional features like Windows themes, screensavers, jigsaw puzzles and an image carousel.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3D Realms</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Duke Nukem 3D - Atomic Edition (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Duke Nukem 3D - Atomic Edition (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Electronic Popple (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Electronic Popple</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Electronic Popple is an action/puzzle game. Play as MIN or MAX, two chips who must journey through six levels of a large computer to eventually defeat the evil Overclock King. Two players can play simultaneously. The game is similar in concept to fighting games such as Double Dragon.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ByteShock</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Electronic Popple (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Electronic Popple (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final DOOM (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Final Doom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Final Doom is the last ID-Tech 1 Doom game. It includes two separate 32 level episodes: TNT: Evilution and the Plutonia Experiment Neither episode was made by ID Software themselves, but rather by two groups of individuals hired by ID; Team TNT (hence why Evilution has ''TNT'' in front of it and it's Iwad is named ''TNT.wad'') and the Casali brothers.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19960531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>id Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final DOOM (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final DOOM (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Football Glory (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Football Glory</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>From Croatia came this overhead view football game resembling Sensible Soccer. The standard selection of competitions are on offer, with a full range of club and national competitions. Far more moves are possible in this one though, including overhead kicks, backheelers, riding tackles and even some impressive overhead kicks, all of which need practice to be perfected. Passing works in a similar way to Sensible, but requiring a longer tap, and giving more versatility in where the pass is placed. Extra details such as an on-screen referee and a zoom feature on replays are included. Kits can be edited in more detail than most games of the time as well.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Croteam Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Black Legend Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Football Glory (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Football Glory (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gorillas (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Gorillas</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>his is what happens when one takes the classic ballistic artillery game (perhaps the first major application for computers, and a field whose advancement was arguably single-handedly responsible for numerous categories of mathematical development in the West), replace the cannons and cannonballs with gorillas and bananas, place them, like King Kong or George from Rampage, atop buildings of varying heights instead of in the bowls, on the slopes and peaks of hills and valleys, and package it with the QuickBasic interpreter included with MS-DOS 5.0.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Microsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gorillas (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gorillas (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvester (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Harvester</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The town of Harvest is home to all sorts of strange, twisted, and violent people and things. The game's protagonist, Steve, is suffering from a bad case of amnesia. In assuming his role, you must help him find out the horrifying truth about this quiet little 'burb, and how to escape.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>DigiFX Interactive, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Merit Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Harvester (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Harvester (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heretic (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Heretic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The world has been attacked by the three Serpent Riders from the Abyss. Their mysterious power makes people obey and follow them like sheep. Only the ancient Sidhe elves are immune to the Riders' influence, which led to them being branded heretics. With most of their work done, the two elder Riders leave, leaving only D'Sparil, the youngest and weakest Rider, behind to oversee the oppression. He sends the armies of the Seven Kings against the Sidhe, who have no choice but to extinguish the Seven Candles, vanquishing the armies.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>id Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Heretic (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Heretic (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hexen - Beyond Heretic (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Hexen: Beyond Heretic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hexen is the sequel to Heretic. While the Heretic was destroying D'Sparil, the other two Serpent Riders have come to your dimension and slaughtered everyone. Or so they thought. Three humans have managed to escape with their lives and now seek vengeance against the Serpent Rider Korax who remains in their world. Like Heretic, Hexen is a fantasy game based on an enhanced DOOM engine. All of Heretic's innovations like vertical looking, flying, and the inventory system have been carried over. The new major changes this time around are three characters for the player to choose from and the level hub system.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>id Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hexen - Beyond Heretic (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hexen - Beyond Heretic (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ignition (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Ignition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ignition is an action packed racing game viewed from above and slightly behind the player. The cars on offer range from police car and VW Beetle to school bus and truck, each of which has its own strengths and weaknesses - trying to win with the bus, which involves blocking everyone behind the hideously slow vehicle for 3 laps, is perhaps the ultimate challenge. Initially there are 5 tracks available, with practice and single race modes as well as full championship at 3 levels - winning each of the first 2 levels unlocks an extra track. They all have hazards running through them, and sections where you must make a split-second choice between the safer route and the risky but potentially rewarding one.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Unique Development</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ignition (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ignition (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jagged Alliance (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Jagged Alliance</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The land of Metavira needs your help! Contract additional mercenaries as you explore, capture, and hold new territory so the natives can harvest the valuable trees from which a revolutionary medicine can be extracted. The more trees you hold, the more money you make. The more money you have, the more you can do, such as hire native guards, hire more mercs, in order to take the offense and clear the sector of enemies. You will also need to retrieve certain objects from behind enemy lines, rescue captured personnel, capture equipment, and more. Hire a good mechanic in order to get your equipment and guns repaired, and to ''enhance'' them with various add-ons.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Madlab Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sir-tech</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jagged Alliance (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jagged Alliance (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jurassic Park is a 1993 action video game developed and published by Ocean Software, for DOS and Amiga computers. The game is based on director Steven Spielberg's 1993 film, Jurassic Park, and also includes elements from author Michael Crichton's 1990 novel of the same name, which the film is based upon.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jurassic Park (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jurassic Park (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Express, The (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Last Express, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ladies and gentlemen, please pay attention - the Orient Express is about to depart from Paris! Do I hear somebody playing a violin? As the train slowly starts moving away from the station, a young, courageously looking man jumps on it from his motorcycle and makes his way inside. This is Robert Cath, an American about whom we don't know much as we begin the game. In the train, he finds the dead body of the person he was supposed to meet. Now he has to act quickly. The only way not to arise the suspicions of the police is to disguise himself as the murdered man. A very dangerous investigation begins, and the hero soon finds himself involved in a deep net of personal intrigues and political conspiracies.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Smoking Car Productions, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Last Express, The (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Last Express, The (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords of the Realm (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Lords of the Realm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The English throne lies empty in 1268 A.D. You and 5 lords are locked in a struggle for the crown. Reap the benefits of successful feudal governing, castle-building, castle-sieging, and land battle to conquer your rivals and claim the kingdom. You must keep your serfs fed and happy. Then assign them to farming, herding, building, military and other tasks. Design your own castles or build them using actual historical blueprints. Then lay siege to your neighbors' castles and fight out land battles in tactical detail.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Impressions Games</developer>
		<publisher>Impressions Games</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lords of the Realm (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lords of the Realm (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords of the Realm II (1998).zip</path>
		<name>Lords of the Realm II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lords of the Realm II is a mixture of turn-based county and economic management and real-time combat. As the game begins, the king has died and 5 nobles (including yourself) are vying for control of the realm, including the noble Baron, the headstrong Knight, the ice princess The Countess, and the backstabbing Bishop. You have to hold on to your counties by building larger castles and keeping the peasantry happy and well-fed.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Impressions Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lords of the Realm II (1998).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lords of the Realm II (1998).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MAX - Mechanzied Assault and Exploration (1996).zip</path>
		<name>M.A.X.: Mechanized Assault &amp; Exploration</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As its name implies, M.A.X.: Mechanized Assault and Exploration is a conquer 'n' plunder-type strategy game in the same vein as the Warcraft or Command &amp; Conquer series, albeit with a few interesting twists. The goal of M.A.X. is to colonize newly-discovered planets, controlling the resources found there, and defend your colony against other rival factions looking to literally blow you off the planet.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MAX - Mechanzied Assault and Exploration (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MAX - Mechanzied Assault and Exploration (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mad TV (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Mad TV</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mad TV sets you in the role of Arnie (though that can be fixed), an average guy watching some television late at night, when you see a woman you absolutely must meet. The next day, as you wander around the television station looking for her, you run into the boss of Mad TV. Having just fired his executive producer, he hires you. (You're not limited to Mad TV, however; you can also hire yourself in one of the competing stations, Fun TV or Sun TV).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbow Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mad TV (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mad TV (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Master of Magic (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Master of Magic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The plot of Master of Magic is to become the dominant wizard on two 'planes' of existence, the normal Earth-like one and the fantasy based plane ''Myrror''. You can do this by destroying your competing wizards (up to 4 computer players) or by casting the Spell of Mastery.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SimTex, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Master of Magic (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Master of Magic (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Master of Orion (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Master of Orion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Master of Orion overlaps with Civilization insofar as you are the leader of one of several races. Technological advance, realm expansion and combat are all key elements. Where it differs is in being set in space. The planet Orion itself is a lush, fertile planet with vast mineral resources. It is guarded by the Guardian - a powerful vessel which you have to defeat in order to plunder Orion's riches. As you attempt to expand your empire, you will have to trade and steal technologies form rivals, again much like Civ.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SimTex, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Master of Orion (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Master of Orion (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Master of Orion II - Battle at Antares (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Master of Orion II: Battle at Antares</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Legends speak somewhere in space of the mystical planet Orion. Created by the Ancients, it remains unclaimed due to a powerful Guardian that orbits the planet and keeps out intruders. These same Ancients long ago fought a war against the Antarans and banished them into another dimension. Now long after the Ancients empire has vanished, new races take to the stars, wishing to establish their own star empires, defeat the Antarans and become The Master of Orion.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SimTex, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Master of Orion II - Battle at Antares (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Master of Orion II - Battle at Antares (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaRace 2 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>MegaRace 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game also features host, Lance Boyle, played by Christian Erickson. In this installment of the futuristic racing series, you are once again the "enforcer" and you are once again attempting to win a series of races against computer opponents, by finishing in first place, or destroying their cars, automatically disqualifying them. Additions to this game are vast, especially concerning ways to destroy your opponents' vehicles, and ways they will destroy yours. Race tracks are more detailed and often more challenging. The cars are now also rendered in 3D.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Cryo Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MegaRace 2 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MegaRace 2 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Bash.zip</path>
		<name>Monster Bash: Part 1</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil Count Chuck has kidnapped all the world's animals in order to turn them into soldiers in his dark army. Johnny Dash's dog, Tex, has been captured along with the other animals, and it's up to him to enter the Night World and save him!You use a slingshot to combat the ghastly enemies, which include skeletons, zombies, and severed hands.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Monster Bash.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Monster Bash.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Bash Part 2.zip</path>
		<name>Monster Bash: Part 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil Count Chuck has kidnapped all the world's animals in order to turn them into soldiers in his dark army. Johnny Dash's dog, Tex, has been captured along with the other animals, and it's up to him to enter the Night World and save him!You use a slingshot to combat the ghastly enemies, which include skeletons, zombies, and severed hands. You can collect power-ups to increase your slingshot's power (only for a limited number of shots, however), candy for bonus points, hearts for health, and Johnny-shaped voodoo dolls for extra lives.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Monster Bash Part 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Monster Bash Part 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Five Hundred years ago, an ancient and well respected Shaolin fighting tournament, held every 50 years, was corrupted by an evil and elderly sorcerer by the name of Shang Tsung. Shang was accompanied by Prince Goro, a warrior of the Shokan race (a four armed half-human/half-dragon). Knowing that if ten tournaments in a row were won by the Outworld champion, the Earth Realm would be conquered by evil and fall into darkness, Shang entered Goro in the tournament and had him defeat the great Kung Lao. Goro has been reigning supreme as the undefeated fighting champion for five hundred years now.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mortal Kombat (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mortal Kombat (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./One Must Fall 2097 (1994).zip</path>
		<name>One Must Fall: 2097</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One Must Fall 2097 is a fighting game with a twist. Instead of the usual Street Fighter II trend of games, in this game you play one of 10 characters controlling one of 10 huge robots in a fighting match. According to the game, in the year 2097, the human race is controlled by one company known as W.A.R., which started as a small company providing the Earth government with construction robots. After a while W.A.R. grew further and further and eventually took over Earth Gov.In the year 2097, W.A.R. decided to colonize Ganymede, one of Jupiter's moons.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Diversions Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Epic Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/One Must Fall 2097 (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/One Must Fall 2097 (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Prince of Persia was originally released in 1989 for the Apple II by Jordan Mechner. Mechner used film of his younger brother David running, jumping, and performing many of the Prince's actions. Mechner then rotoscoped the film to create the animations that give the Prince his fluid movement.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19891003T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Prince of Persia (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Prince of Persia (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pushover (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Push-Over</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You're playing a small ant that is willing to help a friend in rather inconvenient situation. Apparently, your friend, doggie, likes to eat cookies that has his picture on their box, and he got himself so carried away that he lost the balance, and a bag of cookies fell deep down into an ant-hill. Now, you're goin' in, in a mission of solving puzzles, and retrieving the cookies for your friend.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Red Rat Software Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pushover (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pushover (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pyro II (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Pyro II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play as a pyromaniac with a special system of burning down buildings: the night before you strike at a location, you hide gas cans all around the building. Then, the next day after all the people have left the building, you go to the top floor with a ball of cotton. You light it up and carefully go down the building floor by floor, picking up gas cans, pouring their contents all over the place, sometimes just running the fuse over them and letting them explode. This is depicted in ASCII graphics and using speaker sound.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Freeware</developer>
		<publisher>Freeware</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pyro II (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pyro II (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Race Mania (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Race Mania</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Race Mania brings you fast and furious 3D action racing. In this racing game there is no such thing as fair play. Bump and smash your opponent racers off the track. Up to 8 human players can join the racing action. Split-screen mode for 2 players is possible. It includes 20 exciting tracks and 10 different cars. Racing management: You can buy and sell cars and repair them. Create your own tracks with an included track editor. Create own racing leagues or choose one from the ten existing ones. Choose your style of play: Peaceful, Normal or Brutal.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Microvalue</developer>
		<publisher>Flair Software</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Race Mania (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Race Mania (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Raptor - Call of the Shadows (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Raptor: Call of the Shadows</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It features smooth scrolling VGA graphics, a variety of enemies on ground, air and sea, and an original soundtrack. After completing each level you have the option of upgrading your ship with a powerful arsenal of weapons and goodies. Some weapons are effective on only ground or air targets, while some are on both. There are some really advanced weapons like the auto-track mini-gun which can effectively destroy almost any kind of targets without aiming the ship. Dying in shoot'em ups can be annoying, especially if you have to start all over the beginning. However, in Raptor you can save your game between each level. If you have enough credit you can even buy multiple shields for further protection.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cygnus Multimedia Productions, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Raptor - Call of the Shadows (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Raptor - Call of the Shadows (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Big Adventure (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Relentless: Twinsen's Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Twinsen, a young Quetch, the player is on a long journey to release your home world from the domination of the evil doctor Funfrock. The game combines action and adventure. You must talk to other characters, and collect and use objects. On the action side, there are platform jumps. Twinsen can move in different ways such as 'Sneak' mode and 'Aggressive' mode, to deal with foes in different ways. The game universe is rendered with characters in full 3D, and the environment using isometric graphic tiles.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Adeline Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Little Big Adventure (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Little Big Adventure (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rex Nebular and the Cosmic Gender Bender (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Rex Nebular and the Cosmic Gender Bender</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A priceless vase is lost on a distant planet that doesn't exist! An irate colonel wants the vase back! And only one man is exprienced enough. skilled enough And foolish enough to retrieve it! Rex Nebular interstellar adventurer and bungling bachelor extraordinaire!</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rex Nebular and the Cosmic Gender Bender (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rex Nebular and the Cosmic Gender Bender (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rise of the Triad - Dark War (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Rise of the Triad: Dark War</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A madman with power to kill millions has been discovered, and HUNT (High-risk United Nations Taskforce) has been dispatched to discover his plans. Your team was infiltrating his island stronghold when everything went to hell. The infiltration boat exploded and fire came from all directions. The only way out is in, into the the fortress, but to stay out here would be certain death. So in you go, guns blazing Rise of the Triad, a first-person shooter, is the successor of Wolfenstein 3D, with a somewhat improved 3D engine.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Developers of Incredible Power, The</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rise of the Triad - Dark War (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rise of the Triad - Dark War (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Warrior (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Shadow Warrior</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lo Wang has been working as a Shadow Warrior (a bodyguard and mercenary of sorts) for the powerful Zilla Corporation for years. But when he discovered the evil Zilla's plan to summon monsters from other dimensions and conquer the world, he left in disgust. Realizing that Lo Wang might jeopardize his plans, Zilla sends his assassins after him. Shadow Warrior is a first-person shooter similar in style and gameplay to Duke Nukem 3D. The game set in a generic ''Asialand'', which looks like China and Japan conflated together.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>3D Realms</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadow Warrior (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadow Warrior (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SimAnt - The Electronic Ant Colony (1991).zip</path>
		<name>SimAnt</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>SimAnt explores the detail of the lives of ants, as you take full control of an ant colony. Build up your colony to conquer the other colonies in the yard. Foes include spiders and humans - make their lives a misery by invading their homes. A Quick Game option focuses on battles with other groups of ants, and a full Tutorial mode is provided. Biological detail of real ants is provided, to help make the package more educational.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Maxis Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/SimAnt - The Electronic Ant Colony (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SimAnt - The Electronic Ant Colony (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SimCity 2000 - CD Collection (1994).zip</path>
		<name>SimCity 2000</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>SimCity 2000 is the successor to the ground breaking city simulation game Sim City. You are once again the mayor, but this time you can fully customize the terrain before building your city. The graphics are isometric, whereas the original had graphics displayed in a top-down fashion.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Maxis Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/SimCity 2000 - CD Collection (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SimCity 2000 - CD Collection (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SkyRoads (1993).zip</path>
		<name>SkyRoads</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pilot your starglider on a ''road'' through space, avoiding obstacles and holes along the way, and without running out of fuel or oxygen. Full version includes 30 roads in 10 areas.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Bluemoon Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Bluemoon Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/SkyRoads (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SkyRoads (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Slipstream 5000 (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Slipstream 5000</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take over control of one of many futuristic racers which fly through courses all over the world. A very nice feature is the ability of picking up weapons during fight to keep your opponents under control. You're able to upgrade your racer after every track.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Software Refinery, Ltd., The</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Slipstream 5000 (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Slipstream 5000 (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Hulk (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Space·Hulk</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Space·Hulk is a real-time conversion of the original board game by Games Workshop set in the Warhammer 40,000 universe. Players control a squad of Space Marines in an maze allowing 90 degree turns which they may view through multiple first person cameras or using an overhead map. Their mission: to wipe out the Genestealers, a vicious alien race inhabiting the derelict ships. The 5-man squad (sometimes accompanied by another), encased in Terminator armors and armed with long range and melee weapons, can be given tactical orders (executed simultaneously) via map - with an option to temporarily freeze time (to give player more room for thinking).</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Space Hulk (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Space Hulk (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Trek - 25th Anniversary (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Star Trek: 25th Anniversary</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Space the final frontier. These are the voyages of the Starship Enterprise. Its 5-year mission: To seek out new life and new civilizations, to explore brave new worlds, to boldly go where no one has gone before. Based on the 1960s Star Trek TV Series, Captain Kirk and the USS Enterprise are representatives of the United Federation of Planets. Their role in space is that of explorers as well as a military presence. The Enterprise routinely encounters strange adventures and bizarre situations, each laid out as a separate ''episode'' which must be played in order. The first episode involves the USS Enterprise being called to a world to investigate strange ''demons'' have appeared from the mines and begun attacking the settlers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Trek - 25th Anniversary (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Trek - 25th Anniversary (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Trek Deep Space 9 - Harbinger (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Star Trek: Deep Space Nine: Harbinger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A first-person perspective action/adventure game on board DS9. You are an alien envoy who unwittingly becomes involved in a murder plot, which leads to war with an evil alien race.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Stormfront Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Viacom New Media</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Trek Deep Space 9 - Harbinger (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Trek Deep Space 9 - Harbinger (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Trek - Judgement Rites CD (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Star Trek: Judgment Rites</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sequel to the award-winning Star Trek: 25th Anniversary, Judgment Rites brings back the entire Enterprise crew in 8 all new episodes. Strange things are happening in distant space, such as dead planets spawning life and WW1 planes in outer space. You need to survive these situations. You must navigate your way through space, and send away teams onto planets to investigate situations, communicate with other characters and solve puzzles. Unlike the previous game, action sequences are optional</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Trek - Judgement Rites CD (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Trek - Judgement Rites CD (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Dark Forces (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Dark Forces</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kyle Katarn is a former Imperial officer turned mercenary, now hired by the Rebel Alliance. After having stolen the Death Star plans from a remote facility, he is tasked with investigating the sudden destruction of a hidden Rebel base. This leads him to face off against Imperial General Rom Mohc and the various iterations of his ''Dark Troopers'' - cybernetic soldiers with the armor and firepower to turn the tide of the war. Dark Forces is a close prequel to the original Star Wars movie trilogy.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Dark Forces (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Dark Forces (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stargunner (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Stargunner</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Another side scrolling aircraft fighting game. You fight through a colorful landscape to do what is always done in these types of games, blow up everything in sight.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stargunner (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stargunner (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stormlord (1989).zip</path>
		<name>Stormlord</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Badh the queen has imposed a terrible vengeance on the land by kidnapping the fairies. To restore things their rightful way, you must rescue them. As you progress through the levels of platform-adventure action, you will come across fairies which are rescued by touching them. Enemies include Venus Fly Traps, localized acid rain showers and dragons, which can be avoided or shot in the bonus shoot 'em up sections. You will need help to reach some levels; this comes from Mael Dvin the Eagle. After each level there's a bonus game in which tears must be collected for points.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Razorsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Hewson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stormlord (1989).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stormlord (1989).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Rod 2 The Next Generation (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Street Rod 2: The Next Generation</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Interface is thankfully the same as the first but that's where the similarity ends. More is the name here, more cars and parts to buy giving you every edge to regain your crown. Gameplay is it's most significant thing that you will ever remember in this classic. Gameplay control is really tight. You're given 3 venues to race your blood thirsty opponent, betting for money and pink slips. The drag race tests how fast you can engage 1st gear. You're ultimate goal is to beat the new king on these three courses that if you do you get to regain your long lost crown and take home his girl, again.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Logical Design Works, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>California Dreams</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Rod 2 The Next Generation (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Rod 2 The Next Generation (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strife (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Strife</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the distant future, the Earth is ruled by a group of people who call themselves ''The Order''. Many disasters have plagued the planet, and after many wars, misery, and death, the Order controls people's lives and deprives them of their freedom. A rebel organization has been formed, seeking to overthrow the Order and whoever else might be behind their rise to power. Somewhere in the depths of a ruined Town Hall, a group of people who oppose the Order's regime welcome a lone wanderer to become the one who will free the Earth from terror.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Rogue Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Velocity</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Strife (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Strife (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strip Poker III (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Strip Poker Three: A Sizzling Game of Chance</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The 3rd edition of Strip Poker allows you to play with three girls at once. Now Master disk presents VGA photos of three new girls. Digitized speech at intro is introduced. Rules of five cards poker are not changed. During your play you can undress your woman opponent by winning all her money.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Artworx Software Co, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Artworx Software Co, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Strip Poker III (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Strip Poker III (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./System Shock (1994).zip</path>
		<name>System Shock</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2072. A hacker from a Saturn colony breaks into computer system of TriOptimum Corporation and gets arrested. He is taken to the Citadel Station, where Edward Diego, a TriOptimum executive, offers to drop all charges against the hacker, as well as grant him a valuable neural implant, if he agrees to hack into SHODAN (Sentient Hyper-Optimized Data Access Network) , the artificial intelligence that controls the station. The hacker removes the AI's ethical constraints and undergoes the promised implant surgery, after which he is put into a six-month healing coma. The hacker awakens into a horrifying reality: with her ethical restrictions removed.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Looking Glass Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/System Shock (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/System Shock (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Manhattan Missions (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Manhattan Missions</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Shredder will assume control of New York City in 48 hours. The Ninja Turtles must stop him and at the same time fight even the lesser crimes taking place in New York City. No surprise that each of these crimes leads to Shredder.Along with the standard side scroller, each turtle uses a different weapon (just like in comics, Leonardo has swords, Michelangelo nunchakus, etc.) to fight criminals. Each turtle has stats (strength, speed, energy) that increase the more they fight; furthermore, when they reach a certain level of strength, they gain additional attacks!The player has 48 hours to complete the game.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Distinctive Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Manhattan Missions (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Manhattan Missions (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terminal Velocity (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Terminal Velocity</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the far future, armadas from surrounding systems have suddenly waged war on Earth, destroying crucial installations and major cities - Earth is quickly brought to its knees. You are a pilot from the Ares Squadron, flying the fastest, most dangerous crafts ever made. You pilot the TV-202, a fighter few can handle. Given that the previous model, the TV-101, has chalked up more dead pilots than any experimental craft in history, many consider you lucky to be alive. You're outgunned, outmanned, and strapped into a flying coffin.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950531T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Terminal Velocity (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Terminal Velocity (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Commando (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Time Commando</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the near future, the military has created an advance computerized combat simulation, which allowed participants to be trained in various forms of combat throughout human history. However, a programmer working for a corporation that seeks the downfall of the simulation developers infects the system with a virus. This virus creates a dimensional vortex that threatens to swallow the entire world. Stanley Opar, a member of S.A.V.E (Special Action for Virus Elimination) enters the vortex with one goal: destroy the virus before the universe ceases to exist. Time Commando is an action game with light puzzle-solving elements.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Adeline Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Time Commando (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Time Commando (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Transport Tycoon Deluxe (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Transport Tycoon Deluxe</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Transport Tycoon, you are in charge of a transport company starting in 1930 in the midst of The Great Depression, and your aim is to build up an empire of trains, ships, lorries, planes and helicopters, with technological evolution to be taken into account. You can play alone, or with a number of computer-controlled rivals. At the beginning of the game, you (and your rivals) have a large terrain at your disposal. The terrain includes hills, rivers, lakes, bridges, industrial facilities and a lot of small towns. It is up to you to decide how to start building your empire.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T140540</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Transport Tycoon Deluxe (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Transport Tycoon Deluxe (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima II - Revenge of the Enchantress (1983).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima II: Revenge of the Enchantress</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The plot of Ultima II revolves around the evil enchantress Minax, taking over the world and exacting revenge on the player for the player's defeat of Mondain in Ultima. The player travels through time to acquire the means to defeat Minax and restore the world to peace. Ultima II has a larger game world than Ultima I, and hosts advances in graphics and in gameplay.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Sierra</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima II - Revenge of the Enchantress (1983).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima II - Revenge of the Enchantress (1983).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warcraft II - Tides of Darkness (1995).zip</path>
		<name>WarCraft II: Tides of Darkness</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players must collect resources, and produce buildings and units in order to defeat an opponent in combat on the ground, in the air and in some maps at sea. The more advanced combat units are produced at the same buildings as the basic units but also need the assistance of other buildings, or must be produced at buildings that have prerequisite buildings.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Warcraft II - Tides of Darkness (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Warcraft II - Tides of Darkness (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego CD (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego?</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Carmen Sandiego and her international gang are behind the thefts of some of the world's most priceless treasures. It is your job, as a rookie detective, to identify the thief, obtain an arrest warrant and to finally track down the crook to his/her hideout before time runs out. As you solve more cases, your rank will rise, thus enabling you to tackle more and more difficult cases. This CD-ROM version is an update of the original classic and features many enhancements and additional features.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego CD (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego CD (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wing Commander II Deluxe Edition (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Wing Commander II: Vengeance of the Kilrathi (Deluxe Edition)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2655. The TCS Tiger's Claw, pride of the Terran Confederation's fleet, is on campaign in the Enigma sector, near the Kilrathi sector headquarters, the K'tithrak Mang starbase. In a sudden attack, it is lost with all hands, save a few pilots who had been transferred off, and one who was out on patrol: the player's character, whose name and call sign are specified by the player. Origin personnel, in these days, called him "Bluehair" after his most defining feature; in Wing Commander III: Heart of the Tiger, his name was changed to Christopher "Maverick" Blair. Blair's claims that some sort of "Kilrathi stealth fighter" destroyed the Claw are summarily dismissed, especially since his flight data recorder is damaged.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wing Commander II Deluxe Edition (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wing Commander II Deluxe Edition (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wing Commander III Heart of the Tiger (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Wing Commander III: Heart of the Tiger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The war against the Kilrathi is going badly for the Confederation. Its flagship, the Concordia, has been destroyed, battles are lost on all fronts. War hero Colonel Christopher Blair is transferred to the old carrier Victory. Take the role of Blair and ensure the success of the Confederation's last-ditch attempt for victory: the destruction of the Kilrathi homeworld. Wing Commander III has the usual mix of space battles and cinematic storytelling. Changes from the first two games include SVGA graphics, the use of texture-mapped polygons instead of bitmaps for spaceflight sequences and real Hollywood actors appearing in the cinematic scenes.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wing Commander III Heart of the Tiger (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wing Commander III Heart of the Tiger (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wing Commander Privateer (CD-ROM) (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Wing Commander: Privateer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are a privateer. Start with the lowly scout, and upgrade to one of the three other superior ships: Galaxy (superior cargo space), Orion (superior protection), or Centurion (superior offense). Buy optional equipment such as armor, engines, shields, weapons, launchers for torpedoes/missiles, and MUCH MUCH more. Take on missions (multiple sources, from the cheapest mission computer, to fixers who has the toughest but most rewarding missions) and earn money for upgrades. Use spare cargo room to trade commodities to further add to your account. Missions can vary from search and destroy to Fedex (i.e. delivery) to bounty hunting, and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wing Commander Privateer (CD-ROM) (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wing Commander Privateer (CD-ROM) (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Z (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Z</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Z is a real-time strategy game in which you fight for control of the sectors, some of which contains manufactories that can gain you additional units. Touch the ''flag'' in the sector and it's yours. Capture the sector before the new unit comes out of the manufactory and the new unit is yours. With six different robots (different armaments, armor, and speed), multiple vehicles (from jeeps to tanks) the robots can utilize, your ultimate objective is to destroy the opponent's base, and prevent him from doing the same to you.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Bitmap Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Z (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Z (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaRace (1993).zip</path>
		<name>MegaRace</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Virtual Television has given us a chance to do the things that we can't make real in everyday life: Race through 14 great tracks in 5 different environments in a totally virtual place where you can kill each other quite easily with sidekicks or guns. In every track you will see some symbols that can make your car speed up, slow up or even blow up, like your mega-host Lance Boyle says, ''Who knows; who cares!'' Everything you see in MegaRace is virtual and no one really dies there. So have fun!</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Cryo Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>The Software Toolworks</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MegaRace (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MegaRace (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cannon Fodder 2 (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Cannon Fodder 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After the success of Cannon Fodder, a sequel was inevitable. The basic gameplay remained the same guide a team of soldiers through a succession of levels populated by trees, huts and lakes. The major change is that the plot involves time travel, rather than straightforward war situations, and this means levels taking place in different scenarios including a strange ?Alien Planet.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sensible Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cannon Fodder 2 (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cannon Fodder 2 (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twinsen's Odyssey (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Twinsen's Odyssey</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Twinsen, the plucky hero of Relentless, returns to face his greatest challenge ever. When strange aliens arrive from a neighboring planet and begin kidnapping magicians and children, Twinsen uncovers a diabolical plot to obliterate his homeworld. In an epic adventure that will propel him across the galaxy, Twinsen must defeat the aliens and their evil god, the Dark Monk, to save his planet.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19970501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Adeline Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Twinsen's Odyssey (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Twinsen's Odyssey (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Al-Qadim - The Genie's Curse (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Al-Qadim: The Genie's Curse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As the youngest son of a Noble Merchant, an easy life lay before you. But the call of adventure beckoned, and so, you left your home for a life of action and danger. Sea serpents, storms and tattered sails have all proved perilous as the years passed. You've taken ships and defeated fiends, at the side of your instructor, the Master Corsair Sinbar. But your thoughts always return to Kara, the Caliph's beautiful daughter. It is for her you devote your skill and honors. And it will be her hand in marriage that will be your reward for attaining your goal of becoming a Corsair. Your adventure begins now, on the hidden isle where Sinbar tests his pupils.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stormfront Studios</developer>
		<publisher>SSI</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Al-Qadim - The Genie's Curse (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Al-Qadim - The Genie's Curse (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Legacy (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Alien Legacy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After an alien attack in 2043, great technological leaps were made and space travel was significantly improved upon. In 2119, fearing extinction, Earth built gigantic seedships designed as ''arks'' to propel people and the sum of human knowledge across the stars. One of these seedships, the UNS Calypso, is sent to Beta Caeli star system which is the farthest colony attempted yet. In 2135, a second seedship, the UNS Tantalus, is dispatched to the same destination in order to better the chances of human survival. The Tantalus is equipped with a more advanced fusion engine and thus will reach Beta Caeli some 21 years ahead of the Calypso.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Ybarra Productions, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien Legacy (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien Legacy (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aliens - A Comic Book Adventure (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Aliens: A Comic Book Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play Lt. Col. Hericksen, an ex-colonial marine who is now the commander of a three-man terraforming team. Your objective is to travel to remote outpost B54-C in order to find the cause of a distress call your vessel received.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Cryo Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Aliens - A Comic Book Adventure (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Aliens - A Comic Book Adventure (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark 2 (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Alone in the Dark 2, you take the role of detective Edward Carnby, one of the two main characters in the original Alone in the Dark. Carnby is now called upon to investigate a bootlegger named One Eyed Jack after an old detective college name Stryker attributes Jack to the kidnapping of young Grace Saunders. Stryker attempts to infiltrate Jack's dilapidated mansion of Hell's Kitchen and rescue the girl, only to disappear himself. That's where Carnby comes in.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alone in the Dark 2 (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alone in the Dark 2 (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark 3 (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After surviving through two encounters with the supernatural in Derceto and Hell's Kitchen, detective Edward Carnby is ready for another round of being Alone in the Dark.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alone in the Dark 3 (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alone in the Dark 3 (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alpha Storm (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Alpha Storm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alpha Storm is a spaceship simulator and a first person shooter. You can travel through star systems. Encounter enemy fleets and battle them with the ship's weapons/devices, or by shooting the enemy ships shields down and teleporting there to kill the crew by your own. If you're not lucky, they may teleport to your ship and eliminate you. You can equip the ship with different lasers, radars, radar jammers, engines or cloaks each with many different power levels. Alternatively, you can combine them with yourself making you a better killing machine. The player is equipped with different types of PSI-abilities and weapons.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>TAG Computer Games</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alpha Storm (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alpha Storm (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Amok (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Amok</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Amok portrays a futuristic storyline on a planet which is identified in the manual as having the same name. There, two gigantic corporations, referred to by the acronyms NONLUN and AZTK, had previously been having an all-out war between them for forty-seven years. The war had involved all possible fronts and theaters, including operations in the air, on the surface of the land and sea, and beneath the water.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Scavenger</developer>
		<publisher>Scavenger</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Amok (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Amok (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BAT 2 - The Koshan Conspiracy CD (1992).zip</path>
		<name>B.A.T. II: The Koshan Conspiracy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This second part of the BAT series takes place in ROMA 2, the most important city of the planet Shedishan. The United Galaxies Organization has contacted the ''Bureau of Astral Troubleshooters (BAT) in order to investigate the murder of a BAT agent named Sylvia Hatford who tried to uncover the businesses of a mysterious dealer of important raw materials. You are playing the second agent, Jehan Menais, now involved in the dangerous investigations.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Computer's Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/BAT 2 - The Koshan Conspiracy CD (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BAT 2 - The Koshan Conspiracy CD (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bedlam (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Bedlam</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A fast paced action game where you run around a machine-gun wielding robot destroying everything in your path. There is a multitude of enemies and you can destroy almost every single thing on the map (buildings, vehicles, etc.). The reason for all this destruction is a revolution led by the robots against their human masters.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mirage Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bedlam (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bedlam (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Caesar 2 (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Caesar II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Caesar II is set in the time of ancient Rome, and lets you try to be the next Caesar. You start with one province and have to build an efficient city. To do this you'll have to manage the water supply properly, make sure the city is policed well, and provide adequate education, entertainment, baths, and temples (which also hold your money and can be robbed if you don't have enough protection).</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Impressions Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Caesar 2 (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Caesar 2 (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Callahan's Crosstime Saloon (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Callahan's Crosstime Saloon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Long Island is home to Mike Callahan's bar, which is, like many other establishments of its kind, a place for people to share their personal problems with the friendly all-knowing bartender and drown their sorrows in alcohol. One small difference between this particular bar and most others is the clientele: mythological beings, time travellers, and aliens all feel at home at Callahan's. So does Jake Stonebender, a traveling guitarist with a tragic past, inclined to help those in need.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Legend Entertainment Company</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Callahan's Crosstime Saloon (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Callahan's Crosstime Saloon (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Capitalism (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Capitalism</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Capitalism is a real-time strategy game where you are CEO of a corporation. Your goal is to defeat your competitors, gain market dominance, and make a profitable business. The game contains countless aspects of real business, including the stock market, research &amp; development, marketing, and hostile takeovers. In Capitalism, you must decide upon what to buy, what to sell, what prices to charge, what to manufacture, what to research, where to buy your supplies from, what to do with your money, and how to defeat your competitors.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enlight Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Interactive Magic Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Capitalism (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Capitalism (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Case of the Cautious Condor, The (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Case of the Cautious Condor, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's the summer of 1937 and the dark clouds of war loom on the distant horizon. The enigmatic industrialist, Bronson Bernard has invited a select group of guests for the historic maiden launch of his latest triumph--the magnificent flying boat Condor. As the posh party progresses, the guests have yet to realize the their host has set a gilded trap for a murderer. Lend a hand to catch the killer as you question suspects and follow leads to the conclusion of the mystery.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Tiger Media</developer>
		<publisher>Compton's New Media</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Case of the Cautious Condor, The (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Case of the Cautious Condor, The (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chaos Control (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Chaos Control</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2071, the aggressive Kesh Rhan aliens have already destroyed the human colonies on Mars and Pluto, and now plan to wipe out all humans from Earth as well. You play as Jessica Darkhill, lieutenant and most skilled pilot of the Orbital Defence Forces. The counter-attack you are about the launch is the last hope to save the Earth of chaos. Chaos Control is a fast-paced shoot'em up featuring 3d pre-rendered environments, which means you cannot actually control the spaceship you are flying in, but are merely in charge of aiming at the various enemies appearing on screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Philips Interactive Media</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chaos Control (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chaos Control (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chewy - ESC from F5 (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Chewy: ESC from F5</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is about a cute pink alien called Chewy, who along with his partner Clint goes on a mission to break into the Borkian high security zone - F5. Their mission: to steal the powerful ''Red Glum'' so that the Borks can't use it for their evil purposes. Chewy's partner Clint manages to steal the glum and escapes with it from the pursuing Borkian starships, but his spaceship gets caught in a wormhole during the chase and crashes on a planet called Earth. That's were the adventure begins with our hero - Chewy in the lead.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>New Generation Software</developer>
		<publisher>Play Byte</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chewy - ESC from F5 (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chewy - ESC from F5 (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conan - The Cimmerian (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Conan: The Cimmerian</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Conan: The Cimmerian was living happily as a blacksmith with his wife in the village of Irskuld, Cimmeria. until one fateful day. A group of horsemen raided his village. Conan was knocked unconscious, awakening only to find his wife and his friends butchered in the aftermath. Conan discovers architect of the slaughter was a wizard named Thoth Amon, a high priest of Cult of Set. Sword in hand, vengeance aflame, Conan now travels south in the land of Hyborea to the city of Shadizar.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Synergistic Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Conan - The Cimmerian (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Conan - The Cimmerian (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crusader - No Regret (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Crusader: No Regret</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Crusader: No Regret is a direct sequel to Crusader: No Remorse, its events starting 46 hours after those depicted in the previous game. The protagonist of the game, a silencer known as the Captain, manipulates his escape pod into a WEC freighter heading towards the moon. There, WEC has established itself as the sole power, overseeing mining procedures and using the moon as prison for dissidents.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960910T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crusader - No Regret (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crusader - No Regret (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Sun - Shattered Lands (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Dark Sun: Shattered Lands</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dark Sun: Shattered Lands takes place in the fictional land of Athas, a dying and hostile desert world. The locale is Draj, a city-state ruled by a powerful sorcerer-king. Nearby are several "free cities", surviving in the desert thanks to the hard work of their citizens.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dark Sun - Shattered Lands (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dark Sun - Shattered Lands (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Under a Killing Moon (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Under a Killing Moon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's December, 2042. And you're the only P.I. that follows the old steps of Philip Marlow, Spade, and other classic detectives. This time, the world depends upon you. How? Why? It's not for me to tell. Take your gun, and see what'll be next. Well, you'll drop it via the window accidentally, but I guess that won't stop you from solving the case.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Access Games</developer>
		<publisher>Access Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Under a Killing Moon (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Under a Killing Moon (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Asterix and Obelix (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Astérix &amp; Obélix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Astérix &amp; Obélix is a platform game where one player can choose to control either Asterix or Obelix or two players can play simultaneously. The mission of the two Gauls is to acquire artifacts from all across Europe. The game, like the comics, is set around 50 BC. It includes some bonus levels like a rugby match and the Olympic Games in Greece. Codes are used to save the player's progress.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Asterix and Obelix (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Asterix and Obelix (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blood (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Blood</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Caleb was once a feared gunslinger, until he met a woman who was involved with a mysterious cult known as Cabal. Caleb, too, is sucked in, and soon becomes one of the Chosen - the most favored worshippers of the evil god Tchernobog. But one day, Tchernobog inexplicably kills the four Chosen, including Caleb. Mysteriously resurrected years later, Caleb is out to get revenge, and learn why his lord cast him down so abruptly.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970531T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Productions, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blood (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blood (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Screamer (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Screamer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Screamer is an arcade racing game, propably the most arcade one which was primarily made for pc! It has very nice arcade-like graphics, comparable with Daytona USA or Ridge Racer whith were popular at that time. The gameplay is not that arcade-like easy to learn, but on the other hand, you will have long-term fun, until you handle all cars perfectly.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Screamer (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Screamer (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ecstatica 2 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Ecstatica II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the original Ecstatica, the hero managed to defeat the recently unleashed Devil and his creatures in the small village of Tirich and rescue Ecstatica, the witch-in-training responsible for the whole mess.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Andrew Spencer Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ecstatica 2 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ecstatica 2 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ecstatica (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Ecstatica</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ecstatica is a 3D graphic adventure, where you must free a the young sorceress Ecstatica from the unholy spell cast by vile supernatural forces. The peaceful village of Tirich was invaded by horrifying monsters. You are a lonely adventurer looking for shelter who finds himself in the role of a hero who must awaken Ecstatica, save the village and its inhabitants, and defeat the forces of darkness who are pulling the triggers behind the scene.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Andrew Spencer Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ecstatica (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ecstatica (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Edna (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Edna</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>2D action platformer similar to Dizzy, created by Czech developers.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Black Raven</developer>
		<publisher>Signum</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Edna (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Edna (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eric the Unready (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Eric the Unready</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A tongue-in-cheek graphic text adventure/point and click adventure hybrid. You are a chivalrous knight attempting to save a princess; your quest takes you through a mad-cap Douglas Adams-style world.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Legend Entertainment Company</developer>
		<publisher>Legend Entertainment Company</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Eric the Unready (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Eric the Unready (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Even More Incredible Machine, The (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Even More Incredible Machine, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The same basic gameplay as the original Incredible Machine, solving a puzzle only using the parts provided. It includes all of the 87 puzzles from the first game, 73 new ones, as well as new parts and music.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dynamix</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Even More Incredible Machine, The (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Even More Incredible Machine, The (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exploration (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Exploration</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Exploration is a strategy-simulation game set during the Age of Sail. From the time of Vasco da Gama and Columbus (the late 1400s) to the French Revolution (1789), you are put in charge of a nation's imperial destiny. This means financing voyages, assembling crews, sending out land and sea expeditions, founding colonies, and occasionally engaging other European powers for global dominance. Exploration may seem familiar to players of Civilization, Colonization, Conquest of the New World, Gold of the Americas, and even Sid Meier's Pirates!, as they borrow from exploration and cover a similar topic.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Software 2000</developer>
		<publisher>Interactive Magic Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Exploration (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Exploration (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flight Unlimited (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Flight Unlimited</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Flight Unlimited is a civilian flight simulator. You can choose between an Extra 300s, a Bellanca Decathlon, a Sukhoi SU-31, a Pitts S-2B and a Grob S-103. Take part in aerobatic competitions or, if you're a beginner, learn how to fly in 34 lessons. Flight Unlimited stresses reality: All ground textures and elevations are based on real satellite photodata, and the flight model has a heavy basis in real world physics. The manual is quite detailed, and combined with the in-flight tutorials, the user is provided with a very gradual introduction to flying.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Looking Glass Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Looking Glass Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Flight Unlimited (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Flight Unlimited (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gateway 2 - Homeworld (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Gateway II: Homeworld</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the original Gateway game, this is also a text based (but graphically enhanced) text game, in which you will explore hazardous situations and new worlds, and ultimately find out the fate of the mystic Heechee race.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Legend Entertainment Company</developer>
		<publisher>Legend Entertainment Company</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gateway 2 - Homeworld (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gateway 2 - Homeworld (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gateway (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Gateway</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gateway is a text (parser) game by Legend Entertainment Company, in which you will explore strange new worlds and locations in the proverbial boots of a prospector, an explorer sent to places in hopes of finding previously unseen artifacts and installations of an alien race, the Heechee, which seemingly vanished from the Galaxy without a trace.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Legend Entertainment Company</developer>
		<publisher>Legend Entertainment Company</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gateway (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gateway (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gene Machine, The (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Gene Machine, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Gene Machine is a point-and-click 2D adventure game with background images that give the perspective of 3D. The story begins in the 1880s in London. British gentleman Piers Featherstonehaugh (pronounced ''fanshaw'') and his faithful servant, Mossop, arrive back home to discover a talking cat on their doorstep. The cat tells them of an outlandish plot concerning genetic mutations gone haywire. It then becomes Fanshaw's goal to stop this ghastly activity and to catch the fiends behind it.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Divide By Zero, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gene Machine, The (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gene Machine, The (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Normality (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Normality</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kent lives in the police state of Neutropolis where everyone and everything is supposed to be normal. But Kent doesn't want to be normal. In this 1st-person 3D animated graphic adventure (ala Tex Murphy, but more cartoony), you must elude the police and solve puzzles as you travel through the many locations.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Normality (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Normality (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-COM - UFO Defense (1994).zip</path>
		<name>X-COM: UFO Defense</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 1998, the amount of reports of UFO sightings has been drastically increased. Stories about abductions and alien attacks became more and more widespread. Finally, after various nations of the world have failed to intercept the UFOs, their representatives met in a conference of global importance in Geneva, Switzerland. It was eventually decided to organize a secret paramilitary group, dubbed Extraterrestrial Combat Unit (X-COM).</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mythos Games Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/X-COM - UFO Defense (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/X-COM - UFO Defense (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wing Commander IV The Price of Freedom (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Wing Commander IV: The Price of Freedom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Christopher Blair, ''Heart of the Tiger'' had retired to a farming planet after the war, content with retirement, so he says. In the depths of space, a new menace has surfaced. Some unknown attackers are killing civilian ships. The tension between the Confederation and the Border Worlds is at an all time high, as both sides accuse the other of staging the attacks. Admiral Tolwyn has recalled Blair back to service, where he will make the most difficult choice of all. And contemplate action he had never dared before, in the name of justice.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wing Commander IV The Price of Freedom (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wing Commander IV The Price of Freedom (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-COM - Apocalypse (1997).zip</path>
		<name>X-COM: Apocalypse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Things have not gone well since the last Alien War. The world resources have been exhausted, and most of the population have been concentrated into the last hope: Mega-Primus, a self-sufficient city. Things are starting look good until a strange portal opened in the sky, and UFOs emerged from it. It seems that the X-COM is needed again. X-COM: Apocalypse is a sequel to X-COM: Terror from the Deep, and is the third entry in the X-COM series. It is a real-time / turn-based strategy game that features a mix of research, resource management, macro tactical combat, and micro tactical combat. At the city screen, the player controls vehicles to engage the threats (everything from rival factions to alien UFOs).</desc>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mythos Games Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/X-COM - Apocalypse (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/X-COM - Apocalypse (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-COM - Terror from the Deep (1995).zip</path>
		<name>X-COM: Terror from the Deep</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>X-COM: Terror from the Deep is the follow-up to the resource management and tactical combat game X-COM: Enemy Unknown. It has been 40 years since X-COM last defeated the aliens. Now, in the year of 2040, aliens begin to appear on the Earth again. This time the threat to humanity is coming from the depths of oceans.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/X-COM - Terror from the Deep (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/X-COM - Terror from the Deep (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lost Vikings, The (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Lost Vikings, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Three Vikings, Eric the Swift, Olaf the Stout and Baleog the Fierce, were kidnapped by the alien Tomator, the evil Croutonian ruler, who is collecting unique life forms to display in his gallery. The three Vikings will have to combine their unique skills to defeat Tomator, as well as a vast array of aliens, robots, giant snails, big lizards and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon &amp; Synapse</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lost Vikings, The (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lost Vikings, The (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic Carpet 2 - The Netherworlds (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Magic Carpet 2: The Netherworlds</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil demon lord Vissuluth has taken control of the realms of the Netherworld. Once prosperous lands have been infested with monsters and several evil wizards, Vissuluth's side-kicks, are up to no good either. Fortunately the magician Kafkar knows a promising young apprentice who may stand up to Vissuluth. You're that apprentice!</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Magic Carpet 2 - The Netherworlds (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Magic Carpet 2 - The Netherworlds (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic Carpet Plus (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Magic Carpet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Magic Carpet is a first-person perspective game, in which you are a mage who flies on a, well, magic carpet and casts spells. The game has 50 levels, called 'worlds' each of those is set in a sea terrain with several mountainous islands. Your goal on each level is to amass enough mana within your castle to 'restore the equilibrium' within the world. Once this happens, you can head to the next level.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Magic Carpet Plus (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Magic Carpet Plus (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pro Pinball - The Web (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Pro Pinball: The Web</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this pinball simulation, you play on a table called "The Web". With the help of three flippers, you must send the ball into the various openings, trapdoors, and ramps. You can gain various bonuses (such as several balls to knock at the same time) if you play particularly well. Some of the targets activate special missions when you hit them with a ball. Those missions vary from aiming at specific targets to playing mini-games, such as shooting asteroids. After you have completed five missions, you'll be able to face the Dark Queen, the off-screen antagonist of the game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pro Pinball - The Web (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pro Pinball - The Web (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Rebel Assault (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Rebel Assault</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play a Rebel space cadet and have various missions to complete: Flying starships, destroying Walkers, infiltrating an enemy base etc. All viewpoints and gameplay is through the use of motion video backdrops.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Rebel Assault (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Rebel Assault (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Rebel Assault II - The Hidden Empire (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Rebel Assault II: The Hidden Empire</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Following his successes for the Rebel Alliance in the previous game, the adventures of the starfighter pilot ''Rookie One'' continue. While out scouting in the Dreighton Nebula, Rookie One's patrols receive a distress call from a freighter. As this is an area where ships are known to disappear, any deviation from the flight path is dangerous. But what they find is an Imperial presence where there shouldn't be one and a new secret project to bring about the destruction of the Rebel Alliance.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Rebel Assault II - The Hidden Empire (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Rebel Assault II - The Hidden Empire (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jeremy Hartwood has committed suicide in his Louisiana mansion, Derceto. You take the role of either Edward Carnby, a private investigator, or Emily Hartwood, Jeremy's niece, and investigate the suspicious death. The three-floor mansion is reputed to be haunted by its eccentric past owner. Very quickly, you realise that it is. Warped rats, zombies and giant worms are among the foes who are after you, and you must somehow escape.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alone in the Dark (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alone in the Dark (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Isle 2 (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Battle Isle 2: Titan's Legacy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Battle Isle 2: Titan's Legacy is the second title in Blue Byte's Battle Isle series. After a long space flight, the player arrives on the planet of Chromos and must save the planet's civilization from the Titan-net Empire. Titan-net, the computer overfiend of part one, and its allies have begun a devastating final campaign against all Drullian forces. The player commands the forces with the computer ''military operations console'', nicknamed MilOp.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Blue Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battle Isle 2 (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battle Isle 2 (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CyberMage - Darklight Awakening (1995).zip</path>
		<name>CyberMage: Darklight Awakening</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2044 AD, world governments have fallen apart and the Earth is ruled by ruthless corporations doing anything for profit. However, rebels are fighting against corporate control all over the planet. The protagonist of the game saves the life of a stranger, sacrificing his own life in the process. Taking the protagonist to his lab, the stranger performs a secret experiment on him, and is able to bring him back to life. The hero awakens with a strange crystal embedded in his forehead, giving him control over a mysterious power known as the Darklight.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/CyberMage - Darklight Awakening (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/CyberMage - Darklight Awakening (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fade to Black (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Fade to Black</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fade to Black is the sequel to Flashback: the Quest for Identity. The player takes control of Conrad, the hero from Flashback who has been imprisoned by his old enemy, the Morphs. Gaining the trust and assistance of the mysterious Ancients, Conrad must fight off the Morph invasion, not knowing whom he can trust. The game uses fully polygonal graphics for both character models and environment. The camera changes angles depending on the location of the player character, similar to the Alone in the Dark series.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delphine Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fade to Black (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fade to Black (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./KKND - Krush, Kill 'N' Destroy (1997).zip</path>
		<name>KKND: Krush, Kill 'n' Destroy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Krush, Kill ‘n’ Destroy Xtreme is a real-time strategy game where oil becomes the primary resource you require to earn the cash to make the flash and construct buildings and train units. Upgrade your buildings with a staggering variety of options while your units gain experience and new abilities that make them more effective on the battlefield.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/KKND - Krush, Kill 'N' Destroy (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/KKND - Krush, Kill 'N' Destroy (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MDK (1997).zip</path>
		<name>MDK</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this 3D shoot 'em up, you play Kurt, and your job is to save the world. Aliens have sent 8 giant fortresses to destroy earth. You run and jump through 6 missions of strange 3D worlds and kill the "Stream Riders" with your machine gun arm. Precise platform jumps are part of the challenge. Kurt is equipped with a special battle suit with an included parachute and a sniper interface (allowing you to aim precise shooting while standing still) embedded in your helmet. Further weaponry enhancements are available as you progress through the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19970430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MDK (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MDK (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Privateer 2 The Darkening (Special Edition) (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Privateer 2: The Darkening</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Ser Lev Arris in this ''sequel'' to the original Privateer. Go on a search to regain your identity and memory in this interactive movie/space combat game. Along the way, you can trade commodities, go on missions, attack strange mutants, rescue damsels in distress, meet weird characters, and visit unusual planets. You can hire wingmen and cargo ships, upgrade your ship or buy new ones, and watch lots of live-action movies.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Privateer 2 The Darkening (Special Edition) (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Privateer 2 The Darkening (Special Edition) (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quarantine (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Quarantine</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Quarantine, you play the part of a taxi driver, desperate to escape from the violent prison city of Kemo. Deliver passengers to their destinations, so you can earn money to upgrade your cab, and take on undercover missions in the hope that somehow you can find a way out. An impressive array of cab-mounted weaponry will help you to survive.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Imagexcel</developer>
		<publisher>GameTek</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Quarantine (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Quarantine (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sid Meier's Colonization (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Colonization</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Colonization is a strategy game which puts you in the role of Viceroy of the New World. You are sent by your King and country to establish colonies in the newly-discovered Americas that lie to the west. You face many of the same challenges that faced colonial organizers of the time-competition from other Old World powers, strange native cultures, the problems of establishing profitable trade programs, and the problems of organizing an army from a rag-tag band of colonists. The game begins with the European discovery of the Americas (1500) and continues until approximately the time of the American.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sid Meier's Colonization (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sid Meier's Colonization (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Trek The Next Generation - A Final Unity (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Star Trek: The Next Generation: A Final Unity</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You're Jean-Luc Picard (best known from ''The Next Generation'' episodes), captain of the Federation starship USS Enterprise-D, on a mission to encounter an ultimate threat to the known galaxy. The game starts with a Federation outpost detecting an unknown ship approaching Federation space; the Enterprise is sent to deal with this new situation. The mystery ship appears to be a small scout-ship from Garid that has lost power to its engines and as a result has sailed off of its intended course. Before you can blink however, a Romulan Warbird battleship from Garid uncloaks itself right between you and this new ship and this is only the beginning of the game's story.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Spectrum Holobyte</developer>
		<publisher>Spectrum Holobyte</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Trek The Next Generation - A Final Unity (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Trek The Next Generation - A Final Unity (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stonekeep (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Stonekeep</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Drake, an adventurer trying to stop the evil Khull-Khumm, and to raise Stonekeep back to it's former glory! A Full screen 3D RPG with Puzzle and Combat elements.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stonekeep (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stonekeep (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syndicate Plus (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Syndicate Plus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the future, the world is controlled by a handful of global corporations (syndicates). You are the Marketing director (hit man) for one of these companies. It is your job to take control away from the competitors. The job is not one of diplomacy, but one of brute force and physical control. Advance your way to the top of the corporation by successfully completing your missions and managing the money you make from your territories.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Syndicate Plus (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Syndicate Plus (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Theme Park (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Theme Park</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dominating the exciting world of Theme Park ownership is your goal in this strategy game from Bullfrog. The first task is to set up your rides within the available land, structuring convenient paths and queues and ideally leaving some space for bigger rides once they become available, and include some lakes and trees to increase the park's allure. Rides range from Teacups and Haunted Houses to the biggest most elaborate roller-coaster you can design, and water rides that loop around other rides.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Theme Park (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Theme Park (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider Gold (1998).zip</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: Gold</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Gold Edition of Tomb Raider adds two new chapters to the original release. The first chapter takes place in Egypt, and occurs several months after the events of Tomb Raider. Lara returns to the city of Khamoon, where she must investigate a hidden temple dedicated to the feline goddess Bast. The second chapter is a prequel to the first, and continues directly the events of the original game, starting with Lara sliding down the slope of the last level, preparing to deal with the remnants of the Atlantean race.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Core Design</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tomb Raider Gold (1998).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tomb Raider Gold (1998).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Track Attack (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Track Attack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Track Attack is a futuristic 3D racing game in the style of Hi-Octane. The player races through futuristic cities and tunnels trying to beat their opponents. This game also features damage, and some special upgrades. Perhaps the most innovative feature is the Dynamic Track System, which allows the 39 circuits to change during the race. There are arrows the player can drive over which make the track behind them change for their opponent (obstacles popping up for example), therefore making it harder for a driver to catch up.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Track Attack (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Track Attack (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tunnel B1 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Tunnel B1</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are on a mission to destroy the ultimate weapon of your enemy. This involves travelling through a set of precarious tunnels in your high-tech hover-craft. The tunnels are filled with enemy vehicles, choppers and sentry guns which you have to take out or avoid. To make life even worse, a lot of sections require you to clear them in a given time limit. The only good thing is that you'll be able to upgrade your weaponry often.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>NEON Software GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tunnel B1 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tunnel B1 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima Underworld 2 - Labyrinth of Worlds (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima Underworld II: Labyrinth of Worlds</name>
		<sortname>Ultima XI</sortname>
		<desc>Ultima Underworld II: Labyrinth of Worlds takes place one year after the events of Ultima VII: The Black Gate. To celebrate the defeat of the Guardian, Lord British invites the Avatar and his companions to his castle. However, in the night of the feast the Guardian attacks again, encasing the castle in a giant gem of blackrock. Deep in the sewers of the castle, another blackrock gem is found, created as an aftereffect of the attack. This gem is a teleporter to other worlds controlled by the Guardian. Now you, the Avatar, must travel to these worlds in order to free the castle from the Guardian's spell.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Looking Glass Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima Underworld 2 - Labyrinth of Worlds (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima Underworld 2 - Labyrinth of Worlds (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Warlords II Deluxe (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Warlords II Deluxe</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Warlords II Deluxe is an eight player game of conquest and empire. Different worlds are provided as a stage for your ambitions, and as a test of your capabilities. In the quest for final victory, you will assemble vast armies, conquer and loot mighty cities, undertake perilous quests, make and break alliances and wield magical artifacts of great power.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SSG Strategic Studies Group</developer>
		<publisher>SSG Strategic Studies Group</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Warlords II Deluxe (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Warlords II Deluxe (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wolf (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Wolf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is, quite simply, a wolf simulator. In the game, you take the role of a wolf, either in a mission (such as survive for a day) or in simulation mode, which alllows you to do whatever you want. All the aspects of life as a wolf are simulated, from eating and hunting to mating and avoiding hunters. The game also features an interactive wolf encyclopaedia.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Manley &amp; Associates, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sanctuary Woods</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wolf (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wolf (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World of Aden - Thunderscape (1995).zip</path>
		<name>World of Aden: Thunderscape</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>World of Aden: Thunderscape is a 3D dungeon-crawling role-playing game. The player creates a party of up to six characters, choosing among several races, including traditional medieval fantasy species such as elves and dwarves, but also some races unique to the game. The player also chooses the class and the initial combat-oriented skills of the characters. Combat is turn-based and takes place on the same screen as exploration. When characters gain enough experience to level up, the player can raise their parameters or have them learn new magic spells.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/World of Aden - Thunderscape (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/World of Aden - Thunderscape (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms - Reinforcements (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Worms: Reinforcements</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Worms: Reinforcements is an add-on to Worms. It includes some modifications to the gameplay, such as the ability to choose the worm the player wants to use each turn, as well as additional levels and multiplayer support. It also allows the creation and the use of custom levels and speech packs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Worms - Reinforcements (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Worms - Reinforcements (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wetlands (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Wetlands</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is very like Cyberia; the moving path is predictable, and all you have to do is shoot at anything that moves, and enjoy the animated sequences in between every mission. The time is set somewhere in the near future, and there is a major war active on your planet. By the time war is battling, the infamous and most dangerous international prisoner was rescued, and the prison guards were killed. As much as you don't want to participate in that action (since you're more interested in winning the war), you, as a great undercover agent are sent to bring the prisoner back. No matter the cost.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Hypnotix, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>New World Computing's</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wetlands (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wetlands (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terminator, The - Future Shock (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Terminator: Future Shock, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2015, and machines, under the leadership of the super-computer Skynet, control the Earth. Deprived of their civilization, the surviving humans continue to resist the mechanical rulers. The protagonist escapes from the machines' extermination camp with the help of resistance soldiers. Eventually he meets the leader of the resistance, John Connor, and the young Kyle Reese, who send him on missions which are vital for humanity's survival.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bethesda Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>Bethesda Softworks</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Terminator, The - Future Shock (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Terminator, The - Future Shock (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pro Pinball - BigRace USA (V1.17).zip</path>
		<name>Pro Pinball: Big Race USA</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set your senses reeling as you're whisked on the wildest pinball ride of your life, in a whirlwind frenzy of colour, sound and adrenaline-pumping action. Take a white knuckle ride across the USA for your chance to complete on the 'big race' and win hoards of cash - but watch out for that police car on your tail. Try real time hand-to hand mode for exciting two player action via LAN or the Internet. Meet innovate opponents - Monster Truck, Hot Rod, Sports Car, Mini Beetle and the ever-present Police Car. Have fun with the frenzy feature - ten balls in play at once! Balls, that really slide and spin!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19981231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cunning Developments</developer>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pro Pinball - BigRace USA (V1.17).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pro Pinball - BigRace USA (V1.17).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Digger (Remastered).zip</path>
		<name>Digger: Remastered</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take control of a mechanical digging machine as you tunnel your way through the earth, searching for valuable gems and the even more valuable bags of gold! But watch out for Nobbins and Hobbins, and don't be careless enough to let the bags of gold crush you!.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19830101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Windmill Software</developer>
		<publisher>Windmill Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Digger (Remastered).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Digger (Remastered).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Dreams (21st).zip</path>
		<name>Pinball Dreams</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first in a line of pinball games from 21st Century and Digital Illusions, with four tables covering themes such as the wild west for Steel Wheel, space rockets for Ignition, a haunted graveyard for Nightmare and pop music for Beat Box.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Illusions Canada</developer>
		<publisher>21st Century Entertainment Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pinball Dreams (21st).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pinball Dreams (21st).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Fantasies (21st).zip</path>
		<name>Pinball Fantasies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After the success of Pinball Dreams on several systems, a sequel featuring four new tables was created. The gameplay is much the same as the first game, with realistic physics, multi-player options and a high score table to aim for. The tables are Partyland, Speed Devils, Billion Dollar Gameshow and Stones 'n' Bones, taking in a funfair, racing cars, a tacky game-show, and a graveyard. Each one has a range of ramps, combos, light sequences and targets to shoot, as well as general themes which are less influenced by real tables than those in Pinball Dreams.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Illusions Canada</developer>
		<publisher>21st Century Entertainment Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pinball Fantasies (21st).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pinball Fantasies (21st).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Absolute Zero (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Absolute Zero</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the 24th century, on the frozen Jovian moon of Europa, earth has established a colony to extract water from the moon. One of the mining facilities accidentally discovers on their excavations members of a long-buried alien race. The creatures, now awake, slaughter all the miners and destroy the moon's capital city. It's up to you now to defend what's left of the colony and eliminate the aliens, or at least hold them off until help arrives.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Domark</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Absolute Zero (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Absolute Zero (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sim Farm.zip</path>
		<name>SimFarm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take control and manage a virtual farm, buying and selling lifestock and planting and maintaning crops. There is a changing weather system and realistic seasons important to the running of your farm.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Leaping Lizard Software, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Maxis Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Sim Farm.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sim Farm.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bedlam 2 - Absolute Bedlam (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Bedlam 2: Absolute Bedlam</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It is half a year after the happenings in Bedlam where Major Kern defeated evil biomechs. Now they are back under the name Biomex and have important facilities under their control. Of course this has the consequence that the player uses Major Kern's combat robot to kill them all.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mirage Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Bedlam 2 - Absolute Bedlam (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bedlam 2 - Absolute Bedlam (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DOOM II (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Doom II: Hell on Earth</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this sequel to the original Doom, you play the same hero - the last remaining space marine. After having single-handedly saved Mars from demonic threat, you return to Earth, only to find out that the demons have already invaded it, killed most of its inhabitants or possessed them. It's your task to bring down the force field around the last operational star port to allow the remnants of mankind to escape to the stars. Doom II looks and plays very similarly to its predecessor, utilizing the same 3D graphical engine with 2D sprites for enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19941010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/DOOM II (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DOOM II (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Keeper (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Dungeon Keeper</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dungeon Keeper takes real-time strategy into a fantasy setting. You command a dungeon and its hellish minions, and must take them to glory against the hated good guys. You must use your gold to build a fortress and weapons to attack. As well as being able to rotate the 3D view, and control the light source, you can enter the direct viewpoints of your men, to see life through their eyes (one character's mode goes into black and white for this).</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dungeon Keeper (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dungeon Keeper (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eradicator (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Eradicator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Three distinct characters are on offer in this shoot 'em up - choose from Kamchak the lizard or humans Dan and Eleena. The game's path varies depending on which character you choose. The planet Ioxia is vital to your society, as nowhere else provides the vital element Mazrium. However, its long dormant alien forces have been woken up, and must be destroyed by a one-man army. You must fly into the Citadel to destroy its power source. Eradicator combines pure action and puzzle solving, with 1st-person and 3rd-person views to switch between. There are 20 different weapons, with the missiles you control after launching perhaps the most unusual. The single-player levels plus five more are all available for multi-player action.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Accolade</developer>
		<publisher>Accolade</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Eradicator (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Eradicator (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Extreme Assault (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Extreme Assault</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Extreme Assault is an arcade shooting game in which the player takes control of two different vehicles: a fictional Sioux AH-23 Attack Helicopter and a T1 assault tank. Using these vehicles the player must fight alien forces who have set up secret operations on Earth. Players can blast their way through completely 3D environments through various different missions. There's little story, but lots of action. The player can blow up pretty much anything. There's multiple difficulty levels and the player can select between multiple camera angles to behold the carnage.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blue Byte</developer>
		<publisher>Blue Byte</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Extreme Assault (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Extreme Assault (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jetpack.zip</path>
		<name>Jetpack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are an explorer trying to gather green gems from more than 100 small dungeons. You have a jetpack and an electric tazer, phaser, whatever. Your jetpack consumes fuel and extra fuel can be found over the map. You can also pick up enemy freezers and invulnerability powerups. Your tazer thing can cut through some materials to get through the level successfully, but it cannot hurt enemies. You can also use teleporters and ladders. Ice and grass can hinder your progress.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Adam Pedersen</developer>
		<publisher>Adept Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Jetpack.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jetpack.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Screamer 2 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Screamer 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to Screamer, an arcade-style racing game. This sequel features an improved graphic engine (SVGA) and new cars and tracks. The graphic engine was quite amazing when it was new, especially the nice track details like the cows and horses or the helicopters were nice to look at. The soundtrack consists of Techno CDA tracks.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Screamer 2 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Screamer 2 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Syndicate Wars (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Syndicate Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the sequel to the dark isometric action / strategy game Syndicate, you control either Eurocorp Syndicate or Church of the New Epoch. These two sinister forces are battling for world domination. You must help them dominate the world across 60 violent missions spread through 30 cities - you receive e-mails containing the mission plans. After selecting a squad of four men from your roster, you direct them through the rotatable 3D city views, shooting foes as the situation dictates. Nuclear grenades and psycho gas are among the new weapons. Tubes, a monorail system and unimpeded Antigrav vehicles give a futuristic feel to travel. In the PC version, 8-player battles over modem and network are available.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Syndicate Wars (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Syndicate Wars (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Theme Hospital (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Theme Hospital</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Theme Hospital is a level-based hospital management simulation where players have to start on an empty building, and then assemble rooms with all kinds of material, from desks and file cabinets for the general diagnosis to the expensive ultra-scanners and x-rays to diagnose such bizarre diseases such as Bloaty Head, Slack Songue or Alien DNA, and treat them with with even more bizarre machines like an Head Inflator or a DNA fixer.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Theme Hospital (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Theme Hospital (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ARSENAL Taste the Power (1998).zip</path>
		<name>A·R·S·E·N·A·L: Taste the Power</name>
		<sortname>Arsenal</sortname>
		<desc>A·R·S·E·N·A·L: Taste the Power is a shareware real-time strategy game that is in many aspects similar to Command &amp; Conquer. Gameplay elements include base construction, resource gathering and large-scale combat with ground, naval and air units. The game also introduces several unique elements to the genre: for example, all vehicles consume fuel, and the players need to maintain a supply network of gasoline trucks to keep their forces operational. Units also gain experience in combat, and this places an emphasis on micromanagement, encouraging the player to protect and repair damaged units, rather than rely on waves of expendable forces.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>TACTICAL Soft Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>TACTICAL Soft Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/ARSENAL Taste the Power (1998).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ARSENAL Taste the Power (1998).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Odyssey (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Alien Odyssey</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player takes the role of a humanoid stranded on an alien planet, who quickly becomes involved in a war between the planet's natives and the Dak, who want to invade the whole place. The only chance to escape the planet is to help these guys thwart the invasion.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>Philips Interactive Media</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Alien Odyssey (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien Odyssey (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Anvil of Dawn (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Anvil of Dawn</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Anvil of Dawn is a role-playing game featuring pseudo-3D dungeons similar to those of Eye of the Beholder, but with solo gameplay and action-oriented combat reminiscent of Ultima Underworld games. The player controls a single hero (can be chosen between two female, two male and one lizard character) on a quest to destroy an evil warlord. The dungeons lead the protagonist through varied places like castles or shipwrecks. The game requires the hero to overcome two basic obstacles: combat and the exploration of maze-like dungeons with occasional puzzles (mostly based on switches and inventory items). During battles, the player simply needs to select a weapon or spell and click on the enemy to use it..</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamForge Intertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>New World Computing's</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Anvil of Dawn (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Anvil of Dawn (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Commander Keen - Keen Dreams (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Commander Keen: Keen Dreams</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Having defeated the Grand Intellect in Invasion of the Vorticons and saved the Earth, eight-year-old child genius Billy Blaze is still forced by his parents to eat his vegetables at dinner. After being sent to bed, he falls asleep and wakes up in his pajamas in bed on top of a hill. Giant helmet-wearing potato men tell him that their king Boobus Tuber has brought him to their land with his Dream Machine, and Keen is now his slave. Keen puts on his Commander Keen helmet and defeats the vegetables, but finds that his raygun is now out of charge.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Commander Keen - Keen Dreams (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Commander Keen - Keen Dreams (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima VIII - Pagan (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima VIII: Pagan</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ultima VIII: Pagan begins where Ultima VII, Part Two: Serpent Isle ended. The Guardian banishes the player, the Avatar, to the land of Pagan, a world under his control. Stranded in this unknown land, without his companions to help him, his goal is to find a way back to Britannia. The Avatar has to confront four Titans in this world who are embodiments of the four elements. He has to master different styles of magic and fight many opponents on his way.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima VIII - Pagan (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima VIII - Pagan (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Bugs (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Battle Bugs</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A very unique real-time strategy game. It's only semi-real-time, because it's possible to pause the action at any moment. The player commands 22 different insects in a long campaign (56 missions) against the computer-AI or a human opponent.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epyx</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battle Bugs (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battle Bugs (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Corridor 7 - Alien Invasion (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Corridor 7: Alien Invasion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2012 it was finally possible to send a space ship to Mars. The scientists returned with a small object of unknown origin, which was supposed to be a proof for the existence of life on the planet. The object was taken to a special underground research facility and secured in its lowest labs, down ''Corridor 7''. Exposed to gamma radiation, the mysterious object caused a portal to appear, which connected two worlds. The Alien invasion began. It's time for you, a brave Special Forces agent, to descend to Corridor 7, where the fate of humanity must be decided.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capstone Software</developer>
		<publisher>Capstone Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Corridor 7 - Alien Invasion (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Corridor 7 - Alien Invasion (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crisis in the Kremlin (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Crisis in the Kremlin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of the few political sims available, take over the Kremlin as one of the three Russian leaders (Ligachov, Yeltsin, or Gorbachov), determine your foreign and domestic policies, and react to the crises that happens (like the Chernobyl crisis). Keep yourself in office by keeping both the Nationalists and the Reformists in line. Can you do better than Gorbachov himself?</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Spectrum Holobyte</developer>
		<publisher>Spectrum Holobyte</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Crisis in the Kremlin (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crisis in the Kremlin (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dominus (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Dominus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are an Overlord in the employ of an aged King who has long since tired of battling. Protection and control of the kingdom, its resources, treasures and its force of monster are your obligations.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>U.S. Gold</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dominus (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dominus (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Corruption (1988).zip</path>
		<name>Corruption</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Corruption is an interactive fiction game by Magnetic Scrolls released in 1988. In this game, a successful stockbroker suddenly finds himself embroiled in a world of crime and danger.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Magnetic Scrolls</developer>
		<publisher>Rainbird Software</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Corruption (1988).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Corruption (1988).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of Thunder (1993).zip</path>
		<name>God of Thunder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You're in a role of mighty Thor. You use your hammer to solving the problems, and dealing with beasts. It's a nice game, with a slightly noticeable story, but better any than none. You will automatically talk to other characters if you bump into them. If you accidentaly kill 'em, you can go a screen out, and then back, and they'll still be alive. You'll need to pick the keys along the trip, and unlocking many doors. It's a great and not big platform/top-down adventure that looks lot alike some old arcade Amiga game.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Adept Software</developer>
		<publisher>Software Creations</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/God of Thunder (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/God of Thunder (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gold of the Americas - The Conquest of the New World (1989).zip</path>
		<name>Gold of the Americas: The Conquest of the New World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Subtitled ''Conquest Of The New World''. A four player strategy game in which you took the role of either England, France, Spain or Portugal and set about exploring and conquering the New World: America. This game was historically accurate so if you want to win, best be Spain :-). You had to look after your colonies, explore unknown regions and invade other players territory.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SSG Strategic Studies Group</developer>
		<publisher>SSG Strategic Studies Group</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gold of the Americas - The Conquest of the New World (1989).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gold of the Americas - The Conquest of the New World (1989).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hi-Octane (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Hi-Octane</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A futuristic racing game with hover cars, in the same line as Wipeout, using a modified version of the Magic Carpet 2 engine. Gameplay takes a straightforward approach, with the directional keys controlling the steering and throttle, and three keys to fire the minigun, missiles or charge the booster. While the minigun has unlimited ammo, both fuel, armour and missiles must be replenished by passing through some marked areas or picking up powerups in the track or by left destroyed opponents.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hi-Octane (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hi-Octane (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic Pockets (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Magic Pockets</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Magic Pockets, players control the cool Bitmap Kid who has deep pockets that can store virtually anything. Bitmap Kid's mission is to get back his toys that were stolen by some creatures.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>The Bitmap Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Magic Pockets (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Magic Pockets (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moonbase (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Moonbase</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players assume the role of manager and must build then expand their moonbase, balancing the production of essentials such as air and power in order to keep the base running within a budget.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Wesson International</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Moonbase (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Moonbase (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mystic Towers (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Mystic Towers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Each tower consists of 45 rooms (5 floors with 9 rooms each), 15 monsters, and 1 monster generator. In each tower, Baldric must defeat all the monsters, destroy the monster generator, and obtain the Large Red Tower Key that opens the tower entrance.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Animation F/X</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mystic Towers (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mystic Towers (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pizza Tycoon (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Pizza Tycoon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pizza Tycoon is a strategy game where you are an aspiring pizza chef, who wants to start the best pizza chain in the world. You begin by choosing a character you want to be (they differ in appearance and abilities, but the most important factor is the amount of money they have at the start).</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Cybernetic Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pizza Tycoon (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pizza Tycoon (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Realms of the Haunting (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Realms of the Haunting</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Realms of the Haunting is a very interesting combination of first-person shooter and three-dimensional adventure game with quite a bit of live-action Full Motion Video thrown in to boot. Navigation through the game world is done through a FPS interface very similar to Doom, however there's also a free-floating cursor controlled by the mouse which you can use to interact with the various objects around you.There's also an inventory system and quite a few object related puzzles. The game has standard Doom-ish combat against a variety of monsters, however the combat is placed at intervals rather than throughout the game, and the emphasis is more on exploration and atmosphere.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Realms of the Haunting (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Realms of the Haunting (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Return to Zork (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Return to Zork</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are standing behind the white house. There is something in the mailbox. A video message from a wizard informing you that you are the sweepstakes winner to the Valley of the Sparrows... right now, by magic flight. Upon arriving at this mysterious place however, not everything is as it should be. There's nobody to meet you and those who you do come across don't seem to have any knowledge about a sweepstakes. It looks like this is a private vacation and you'll need to find your own way through this land.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Infocom</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Return to Zork (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Return to Zork (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ScubaVenture The Search For Pirate's Treasure (1993).zip</path>
		<name>ScubaVenture: The Search for Pirate's Treasure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player character dives in the Caribbean sea to search the sunken wreck of the Barbarosa to search for treasure and uncover the mystery being disappearing explorers.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>	Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Softdisk</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/ScubaVenture The Search For Pirate's Treasure (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ScubaVenture The Search For Pirate's Treasure (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stellar 7 (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Stellar 7</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player's tank, the Raven, has a front-facing cannon with an unlimited supply of bullets. The cannon can fire up to two shots at a time. The tank also has a cloaking device that, when triggered, would render it invisible to enemies for about a minute. Gauges on the right side of the screen indicate the amount of shields and power remaining. The tank starts with enough power to cloak twice, and power slowly trickles away as the time passes.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>	Damon Slye</developer>
		<publisher>Software Entertainment Company</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stellar 7 (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stellar 7 (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Domain (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Ultimate Domain</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ultimate Domain is a game of kingdom building set in the mythical land of Genesia. The game has an isometric view point, and allows you to watch as your people work, play, and suffer, in real time. You must build up your kingdoms infrastructure, grow food, mine minerals, produce building materials, conduct research, and create armies. You may engage in diplomacy with your neighbors, but eventually conquest will become essential for expansion.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>The Software Toolworks</developer>
		<publisher>Micro?ds</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultimate Domain (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultimate Domain (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Whiplash (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Whiplash</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Whiplash is a fast-paced racing game where you choose from eight different cars and race on over sixteen different tracks to brave death-defying loops and corkscrews in stunt racing. The different players are organized in teams of two cars each. The aim is of course to reach the finish line first, but on harder difficulty levels opponents can also be killed by repeatedly bumping into them. The damage is visible, with dents and smoke. Each track has a pit stop where cars stand still to be repaired, but they can be pushed out of the area.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Whiplash (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Whiplash (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Munchers - The Challenge Continues (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Super Munchers: The Challenge Continues...</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Munchers is a trivia action game. The player moves their muncher around a grid and eats words that fit a given clue or category. Incorrect words and a variety of critters get in the way.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>MECC</developer>
		<publisher>MECC</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Munchers - The Challenge Continues (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Munchers - The Challenge Continues (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystal Caves.zip</path>
		<name>Crystal Caves Volume 1: Troubles with Twibbles</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Twibbles are the hottest new pet in the galaxy, so Mylo hopes to earn enough crystals to buy a twibble farm. He succeeds and buys his farm. However, twibbles breed so quickly that the market is soon over-saturated, and Mylo is stuck with a planet overrun with twibbles.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910301T133934</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Crystal Caves.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crystal Caves.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyberia (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Cyberia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2027 the world is controlled by two rival super-powers, the western-bloc Free World Alliance and the east-bloc Cartel. Transmissions from an FWA spy reveal the location of a secret multi-national labratory deep within Siberia, the ''Cyberia Complex'', where a mysterious weapon is being developed. FWA leader Devlin frees a cyber-hacker named Zak from prison and sends him to infiltrate the complex and discover the true nature of the Cyberia weapon.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xatrix</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Cyberia (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cyberia (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dark Legions (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Dark Legions</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Dark Legions, the balance of power in the dark realm of Tahr Carog is broken. One of the two twin power orbs is lost, and the realm is in chaos. As the holder of one of the orbs, you must combat your opponent - the holder of the second power orb - until one of you loses his orb, and the other prevails. The holder of the two orbs will be granted immense power and immortality, so make sure you select and utilize your forces wisely.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Silicon Knights</developer>
		<publisher>Strategic Simulations</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dark Legions (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dark Legions (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Defcon 5 (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Defcon 5: Peace Has a Price</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player takes the role of a DOD operative who must use the BMD(Ballistic Missile Defense System) to protect the United States. This system is composed of ground-based, land-launched, and space-based system components. The goal is to destroy, defeat, confound, or destabilize incoming ballistic missiles.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Cosmi Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Cosmi Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Defcon 5 (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Defcon 5 (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragonsphere (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Dragonsphere</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A graphic adventure in the classic third-person Lucasarts and Sierra style. The fantasy plot involves a king who learns that an evil sorcerer, magically imprisoned 20 years ago, is about to break free from the spell, and embarks on a quest to destroy the sorcerer before he manages to regain his powers.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T134719</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dragonsphere (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragonsphere (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dune (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Dune</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the legendary Frank Herbert novel of the same name and visually inspired by the 1984 David Lynch movie, Dune is a strategy-adventure hybrid where the player takes the role of young Paul Atreides, the son of Duke Leto. The Emperor Shaddam Corrino IV has given the Atreides House the rights to manage the extraction of the most precious substance in the entire universe - the Melange, commonly known as Spice in the desolate desert planet Arrakis (Dune), the only place in the universe capable of producing the substance. While everything indicates the offer is a trap orchestrated by their enemies the Harkonnen, the Atreides family agrees on moving, as he who controls the spice, controls the universe.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cryo Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dune (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dune (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dune 2 - The Building of a Dynasty (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Dune II: The Building of a Dynasty</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The planet Arrakis (also known as Dune for its sandy landscape) is the only place in the known universe where Melange (more commonly known as the Spice) can be found. The Spice is the basis of interstellar travel and thus the standard of the Imperial economy. To increase productivity, The Padishah Emperor has invited three powerful Houses (Harkonnen, Atreides and Ordos) to compete against one another economically and bring up spice production. Competition among these houses begins peacefully but soon turns ugly as they battle each other with armed troops, advanced weaponry, and spies. The planet itself is also hostile, with dangerous sandworms inhabiting the spice fields.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dune 2 - The Building of a Dynasty (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dune 2 - The Building of a Dynasty (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FIFA Soccer 96 (1995).zip</path>
		<name>FIFA Soccer 96</name>
		<sortname>Fifa 96</sortname>
		<desc>Aiming to be the first football simulation that is realistic in the true sense of the word, FIFA Soccer 96 was extremely popular at the time of release. It was hailed as the first really successful FIFA release, and opened the way for yearly revisions of the concept.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Extended Play Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/FIFA Soccer 96 (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/FIFA Soccer 96 (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jazz Jackrabbit CD-ROM (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Jazz Jackrabbit</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jazz Jackrabbit is a video game trilogy featuring the eponymous character of Jazz Jackrabbit, a green anthropomorphic hare, who fights with his turtle nemesis.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic MegaGames, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Epic MegaGames, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Jazz Jackrabbit CD-ROM (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jazz Jackrabbit CD-ROM (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pirates! Gold (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Pirates! Gold</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pirates! Gold features Super VGA graphics including hand-painted screens, and a more-detailed playing environment than the original. The update also includes 3-D modeled ship and flag animations, and graphic depictions of items that were menu choices in the original game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Pirates! Gold (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pirates! Gold (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pro Pinball - Timeshock! (V1.07).zip</path>
		<name>Pro Pinball: Timeshock!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Prepare yourself for total assault of a multi-layered adventure in vision and sound through four different time zones. Experience gleaming Silicon Graphics that test your capabilities to the limit. Pro Pinball- Timshock! Brings you full 3D pinball table on screen with a specially recorded soundtrack by Bruce Foxton and Jake Burns of Stiff Little Fingers. The table is so detailed you'll even think you can see your reflection in the careering ball and gleaming metal fittings. This is the most complex, rewarding, frustrating and entertaining experience ever.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19970930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cunning Developments</developer>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pro Pinball - Timeshock! (V1.07).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pro Pinball - Timeshock! (V1.07).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ShadowCaster (1993).zip</path>
		<name>ShadowCaster</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Kirt, one of the last shapeshifters on earth. As the game begins, you learn from your grandfather that your race, the shapeshifters, was almost killed off in a massive civil war centuries ago. Because this war displeased the gods, the gift of "morphing" was taken away and "The People," as they were called, began a slow decline into ruin. The ShadowCaster game engine, a successor of the Wolfenstein 3D engine and a predecessor of the Doom engine was written by id Software's John Carmack and licensed to Raven Software.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>ORIGIN Systems, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/ShadowCaster (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ShadowCaster (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Goose Warrior.zip</path>
		<name>Stargoose Warrior</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Stargoose Warrior a top-down space shooter in which you move through a semi-3D environment shooting rounds and missiles at your enemies. Occasionally, the player can enter a tunnel and collect upgrades (ammo, shield or fuel) by climbing the walls of the tunnel to run into powerups.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Logotron Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>Logotron</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Star Goose Warrior.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Goose Warrior.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dyna Blaster.zip</path>
		<name>Dyna Blaster</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The black spaceman kidnapped Bomberman's beloved and brought her to his chambers in the castle, far beyond his reach, over the rivers, forest and mountains. Bomberman's job is to save her, battling the sea of the enemies, with only bombs at his disposal. The range of Bomberman's bomb explosions can be upgraded with time, but if he dies, the range resets back to the minimum range and Bomberman loses his previous skills. Some updates can make Bomberman walk through the walls, increase his speed, and give him some other assets to aid him in his quest to save the woman he loves.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dyna Blaster.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dyna Blaster.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terra Nova - Strike Force Centauri (1996).zip</path>
		<name>TerraNova: Strike Force Centauri</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Strike Force Centauri, the premier Strike Team on Alpha Centauri, was founded to combat pirates. As Nikola ap Io, you'll be leading them into combat. But the pirates are, too, well-armed, and the Terra Hegemony may be involved. When the covert action turns overt and a full-out assault is mounted by the Hegemony upon Alpha Centauri. All that stands in the way is SFC.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Looking Glass Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Looking Glass Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Terra Nova - Strike Force Centauri (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Terra Nova - Strike Force Centauri (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./the incredible machine 2.zip</path>
		<name>Incredible Machine 2, The</name>
		<sortname>Incredible Machine 2</sortname>
		<desc>This game involves puzzle solving, while creating wacky machines. Each level of the game contains a machine designed to do a specific task. The only problem is, there are parts missing, and it is your job to figure out where to put what in order to get the machine to work. The game features many wacky machine parts, including cats, super balls, lava lamps, flashlights, can openers, monkeys on treadmills, and many more wacky parts to get your machine working. The game also comes with an editor to let you design your own unique machines from scratch. These can either be for fun, or you can set it so that the person playing has to fill in the missing parts, just like in the campaign.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sierra On-Line</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/the incredible machine 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/the incredible machine 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Incredible Machine, The (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Incredible Machine, The</name>
		<sortname>Incredible Machine 1</sortname>
		<desc>The Incredible Machine is a series of video games that were originally designed and coded by Kevin Ryan and produced by Jeff Tunnell, the now-defunct Jeff Tunnell Productions, and published by Dynamix; the 1993 through 1995 versions had the same development team.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931201T140631</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>Sierra Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Incredible Machine, The (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Incredible Machine, The (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tyrian (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Tyrian</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tyrian is a shoot 'em up with a complex plot. You play the role of Trent Hawkings, this galaxy's ace solo fighter-pilot, whose luck forces him to save the galaxy, one time after another. Again and again, Trent must fight off MicroSol, a company with the evil intent of taking over the galaxy.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Eclipse Software</developer>
		<publisher>Epic MegaGames, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tyrian (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tyrian (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret Agent Mission 2.zip</path>
		<name>Secret Agent: Mission 2: Kill Again Island</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Agent 006, you are the world's only hope: the terrorist organization known as the D.V.S. has captured the blueprints to a new, powerful weapon known as the ''Red Rock Rover''. Your mission is to infiltrate an island occupied by the D.V.S. and retrieve the first part of the blueprints.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Secret Agent Mission 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret Agent Mission 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret Agent Mission 3.zip</path>
		<name>Secret Agent: Mission 3: Dr. No Body</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Agent 006, you are the world's only hope: the terrorist organization known as the D.V.S. has captured the blueprints to a new, powerful weapon known as the ''Red Rock Rover''. Your mission is to infiltrate an island occupied by the D.V.S. and retrieve the first part of the blueprints.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Secret Agent Mission 3.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret Agent Mission 3.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Carnage (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Alien Carnage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alien Carnage (also known as Halloween Harry) is a follow-up to the 1985 game Halloween Harry, created for the Microbee System by John Passfield in 1985, but it has very little in common with the original game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931010T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interactive Binary Illusions</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Alien Carnage (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien Carnage (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Manager 97-98 (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Championship Manager Season 97/98</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This was the final update to Championship Manager 2, and it was fully debugged and had the AI tidied up in several areas. The team and player data was updated for the 97/98 season, meaning that Michael Owen has emerged at Liverpool and Emmanuel Petit has joined Arsenal, for example. Nine different leagues are included, and up to 3 of these can be played at once on 16 Megabyte machines. As a result of this, more teams and players are included in the game system than ever, making for a more realistic player-signing challenge. A full data editor is included for the first time.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Sports Interactive Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Championship Manager 97-98 (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Championship Manager 97-98 (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Challenge Of The Ancient Empires.zip</path>
		<name>Challenge of the Ancient Empires!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Challenge of the Ancient Empires!, also known as "Super Solvers: Ancient Empires!" is an educational computer game created by The Learning Company in 1990.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T133458</releasedate>
		<developer>The Learning Company</developer>
		<publisher />
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Challenge Of The Ancient Empires.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Challenge Of The Ancient Empires.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Aladdin (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Aladdin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Aladdin, baffle the guards in the streets of Agrabah. Elude the tempting traps in the Cave of Wonders, and the dangers of the Sultan's Palace. Ride the magic carpet through breathtaking skies. Then challenge the evil Jafar to a duel of swords and magic!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Disney's Aladdin (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Disney's Aladdin (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frontier - Elite 2 (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Elite II: Frontier</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Elite II: Frontier is, of course, the sequel to Elite and it continues in much the same way. You have a ship and limited funds, and nowhere to go but out into space. Trade, fight, hunt criminals, work for the various governments, anything goes in Frontier. There are few, if any, limits on what you can do or where you can go. And Frontier's universe (with approx. 100,000,000,000 planets and moons) is so big you'll never see the end of it.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>GameTek</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Frontier - Elite 2 (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Frontier - Elite 2 (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Realms of Chaos (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Realms of Chaos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Realms of Chaos is one of the many action 3D Realms made back in the days they called themselves Apogee.Endrick, the warrior, and Elandra, the sorceress, have to travel through 26 levels, split into 3 'episodes' to find the source of what's corrupting the land of Mysteria. Endrick uses his sword fight enemies in close combat, and Elandra uses a supply of gems to blast them with fireballs from a distance.You can switch between characters at any time, but they both share their own health bars, and if one dies, you'll still need to restart the level.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Apogee Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Realms of Chaos (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Realms of Chaos (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./War Planets - Age of Chaos (1997).zip</path>
		<name>War Planets: Age of Chaos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Don Diego Vega has a secret identity - that of Zorro, a masked swordsman who has sworn to protect the innocents of California, at the time a Spanish colony. Among the powerful and corrupted men there is Don Cortez, who hopes to gain even more power by discovering an ancient treasure. Honoring his word, Zorro sets out to stop the Cortez, alone against nearly impossible odds.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Trendmasters, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Trendmasters, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/War Planets - Age of Chaos (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/War Planets - Age of Chaos (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cannon Fodder (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Cannon Fodder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Guide a team of up to four soldiers through 72 levels of combat in this innovative top-down action/strategy hybrid, best thought of as Lemmings crossed with Commando crossed with Dune 2. The characters are controlled indirectly using the mouse, as you activate each soldier or group of them by highlighting them, click the left button to move them to a particular spot, and the right button for them to fire guns at an enemy. You can also pick up grenades, which can be used to destroy groups of enemies or buildings (by pressing both buttons at once).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sensible Software</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Cannon Fodder (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cannon Fodder (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./CyClones (1994).zip</path>
		<name>CyClones</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Legions of alien Cybernetic Clones (''CyClones'') have devastated the Earth. Humanity's only hope lies with Havoc, himself a cybernetic warrior that had been manipulated by the CyClones to do their evil bidding. Havoc must fight the CyClones without mercy, protecting the Earth and avenging his own past.CyClones is a first-person shooter in which the player controls Havoc, exploring maze-like environments and blasting hostile aliens with a variety of firearms. The game is notable for pioneering the use of mouse control in games of its genre, allowing the player to aim independently of movement and move the aiming cursor to any part of the screen.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Raven Software</developer>
		<publisher>Strategic Simulations</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/CyClones (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/CyClones (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FIFA Soccer 97 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>FIFA 97</name>
		<sortname>Fifa 97</sortname>
		<desc>This iteration of the FIFA lineage includes commentary from John Motson with summaries from Andy Gray, with the between-match sections covered by Des Lynam. All player moves are from David Ginola using the MotionBlending technology. Full interactive replays are included. You can play a league or cup tournament, and practice your skills before playing. The game can be tailored to action or simulation style, with fouls, injuries and offsides available to toggle on or off. This version also includes a 6 vs 6 indoor play mode, and various multiplayer options.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/FIFA Soccer 97 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/FIFA Soccer 97 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fuzzy's World of Miniature Space Golf (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Fuzzy's World of Miniature Space Golf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Do you want to play Space golf? It sounds really amazing. If your answer is yes, probably this game is your only option which has a miniature shape in "zany" scenarios.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fuzzy's World of Miniature Space Golf (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fuzzy's World of Miniature Space Golf (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmo's Cosmic Adventure - Forbidden Planet (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Cosmo's Cosmic Adventure: Forbidden Planet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cosmo’s Cosmic Adventure is a side-scrolling platform game developed and published by Apogee Software and released for DOS in 1992. The game has many references to another Apogee title, Duke Nukem (one of my favorites), throughout.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cosmo's Cosmic Adventure - Forbidden Planet (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cosmo's Cosmic Adventure - Forbidden Planet (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F Godmom (1991).zip</path>
		<name>F. Godmom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>All the fairy godmothers are captured, and only you are left. You have to free them, by collecting all the tokens on a screen, grabbing the key and going to the exit, to the next challenge. You'll also have to survive the monsters, and for this you have only one weapon: a magic wand that can be used to transform objects (wall to ladder, ladder to wall, etc.)</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Soggybread Software</developer>
		<publisher>Soggybread Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/F Godmom (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F Godmom (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Once Upon a Forest (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Once Upon a Forest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lots of games are made from movies and also movies made from games, neither often turn out very well in the translation though. Once upon a forest was first made as a movie but I never saw it so I can't really judge it. The game is about a number of forest creatures who are called the furlings, one day they go into the forest and the youngest of them eats a poisoned mushroom. There is a cure but unfortunately the herbs are far away and it's a long and dangerous road. The three furlings decide to go and find the herbs to save their friend and this is where your adventure starts.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Sanctuary Woods</developer>
		<publisher>Sanctuary Woods</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Once Upon a Forest (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Once Upon a Forest (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chex Quest 2 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Chex Quest 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chex Quest 2 was made in 1997, a year after Chex Quest. You could only find this on chexquest.com when it was first released. It is not there anymore, but you can find it on many Chex Quest fan sites. The basic gameplay is the same as the first Chex Quest game. It is an add-on to the original, as the first Chex Quest is required to play it.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Café</developer>
		<publisher>Ralston Foods, Inc</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Chex Quest 2 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chex Quest 2 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chex Quest 3 (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Chex Quest 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chex Quest 3 is the newest edition to Chex Quest, created by original Digital Café team member Charles Jacobi. Only one map was planned originally, but Charles got more into making his map, and he announced in June 2008 that he was creating a full sequel, with much cheering by fans. It also includes improved versions of Chex Quest and Chex Quest 2.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Café</developer>
		<publisher>Ralston Foods, Inc</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Chex Quest 3 (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chex Quest 3 (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dig It! (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Dig It!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dig It! is a platform game. In it, you take the role of Dug Kewl, who returns home one day to find that his wife has been taken by the Supreme Spurkasaur. Using his trusty drill and gun, Dug must travel through four worlds rescue his beloved Dugette before it is too late.Each world in the game is made up of levels. In each level, Dug must find the place marked with an X and dig down to reach the next level. On the way he will encounter dragons, giant snails, armoured hedgehogs and all kinds of monsters to kill as well as plenty of treasure to collect. Dug can also dig in certain unmarked places, which will transport him to secret areas with plenty of treasure.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Pixel Painters Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Pixel Painters Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dig It! (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dig It! (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords of Midnight (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Lords of Midnight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lords of Midnight - also known as Lords of Midnight III: The Citadel - is the third game in the Lords of Midnight series, and a direct sequel to Doomdark's Revenge. The story begins with Luxor the Moonprince (an old man by now) trying to obtain the legendary Eye of the Moon. However, during his quest he is captured by Boroth Wolfheart and imprisoned. His son Morkin must rescue him and find a way to defeat the forces of evil.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Lords of Midnight (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lords of Midnight (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Seal Team (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Seal Team</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Seal Team simulates American operations in the Vietnam war. Missions include Patrol (kill enemies), Ambush (kill enemies), Demolition (building or well), Rescue (friendlies), Recover (certain object), Snatch (capture enemy leader), and Observe (call in the fire support teams). The player controls a single character giving orders to the others, with his statistics improving as the game progresses. True to the danger of Vietnam, you can run into traps like tripwire, panji stake pits, and more. As point man, you'll need to ''mark'' those so the follow-up don't run into the trap. Seal Team is one of the few games in which you get to see the ''riverine'' attack boats, including the Swift and PBR's.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Andre Gagnon</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Seal Team (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Seal Team (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starlord (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Starlord</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Starlord is a game of exploration and conquest from Mike Singleton, the author of the similarly-focused Midwinter and The Lords of Midnight. As the title implies, Starlord is set in a science-fiction world, as opposed to the fantasy universes of those previous games. Your family are Starlords of a single planet, but seek dominance of a vast space consisting of 1000 individually-ruled planets. If you are to come out on top you will have to manage resources across each of your starbases, using revenue to ensure enough fuel, food and minerals are available. Trade with other leaders and form tactical agreements. To actually take over planets, you will have to lead your ships into space combat, which is played out in multiple-view 3D.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Maelstrom Games</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Starlord (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Starlord (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scorched Earth (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Scorched Earth</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's all-out war in Scorched Earth, a simple, yet exciting artillery combat game! You and up to nine friends can duke it out on hills and in valleys as you nuke each other into submission in this turn-based tank battle. At the start of each round, each player purchases their weaponry, and if they choose, shields and parachutes for defense and safety from long drops. Then it's off to battle! Aim your cannon, taking note of trajectory and wind, and fire off your weapons in attempt to take out the opposition. Most of the options are very intuitive, and you can begin playing with only a little bit of information. The variety of weapons is the real highlight of Scorched Earth.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Freeware</developer>
		<publisher>Freeware</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-10</players>
		<image>./boxart/Scorched Earth (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Scorched Earth (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sid Meier's Civilization (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Civilization</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Civilization is a turn-based single- or multiplayer strategy game. The player takes on the role of the ruler of a civilization, starting with only one settler unit and one warrior, and attempts to build an empire in competition with one to eleven other civilizations. The game requires a fair amount of micromanagement (although less than any of the simulation games). Along with the larger tasks of exploration, warfare and diplomacy, the player has to make decisions about where to build new cities, which improvements or units to build in each city, which advances in knowledge should be sought (and at what rate), and how to transform the land surrounding the cities for maximum benefit.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sid Meier's Civilization (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sid Meier's Civilization (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sid Meier's Railroad Tycoon Deluxe (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Railroad Tycoon Deluxe</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The deluxe version of Railroad Tycoon adds VGA graphics and new continents South America and Africa, and 11 new trains.It also adds new historical periods: two more for the Eastern and Western United States, and one more for Europe.It takes into account drastically falling stock prices to improve the depth of the economic model.Train Bandits were included in the North American scenarios, which attempt to prey on mail cargoes</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MPS Labs</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sid Meier's Railroad Tycoon Deluxe (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sid Meier's Railroad Tycoon Deluxe (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starflight (1986).zip</path>
		<name>Starflight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc />
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Starflight (1986).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Starflight (1986).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starflight 2 - Trade Routes of the Cloud Nebula (1989).zip</path>
		<name>Starflight 2: Trade Routes of the Cloud Nebula</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>L'ultime génération dans l'exploration spatiale. Les Spemin, ces "Blobs" du cosmos, sont devenus la race la plus redoutée de la galaxie. Vous et votre équipe devez découvrir pourquoi. Suivez donc les routes commerciales interstellaires vers de nouveaux mondes, de nouvelles espèces et de nouvelles technologies dans une quête pour découvrir les mystères enveloppés dans le passé. -Plus de 500 planètes. 30 races extraterrestres. -Vaisseau puissant avec de nouvelles armes et technologies: modules de saut dans l'hyper-espace, scanner système, "Pods Blasto", sondes psychiques et plus encore.... -Aucune expérience dans Starflight 1 nécessaire. -Totale liberté de jeu! Scénario ouvert et intrigues secondaires.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Starflight 2 - Trade Routes of the Cloud Nebula (1989).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Starflight 2 - Trade Routes of the Cloud Nebula (1989).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima III - Exodus (1983).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima III: Exodus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After the defeat of the evil wizard Mondain and his mistress Minax in the previous two Ultimas, peace has returned to the land of Sorsaria. Times passes and eventually geological disruptions and a resurgence of the monster populace occur, and it is soon learned that Mondain and Minax had conceived a child named Exodus before their death. Now that child has become an adult with the power to avenge the death of his parents. Obviously, it falls upon the hero from Earth to find and stop him. The third title in the Ultima series was the first to feature a party of adventurers instead of a single player character.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Origin Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima III - Exodus (1983).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima III - Exodus (1983).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima IV - Quest of the Avatar (1985).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima IV: Quest of the Avatar</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The fourth game in the Ultima series features an improved game engine, with color graphics and enhanced character interaction: the player can have conversations with non-playable characters by typing names of various topics. However, the main difference between Ultima IV and its predecessors in the series (as well as other role-playing games) lies in the game's objectives and the ways to fulfill them. Instead of building up a character by any means possible in order to face a villain in the end of the game, in Ultima IV the player is trying to become the Avatar, a role model for people. This means upholding the Eight Virtues, basically trying to become a better person.</desc>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Origin Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima IV - Quest of the Avatar (1985).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima IV - Quest of the Avatar (1985).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wing Commander (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Wing Commander</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Confederation have been at war with the Kilrathi for the past 20 years, and you're just now joining the Vega campaign. You're a 2nd Lieutenant just out of the Academy, with some good work under your belt. You're posted to Tiger's Claw, the flagship of the Confederation Fleet. Will you help the Confederation to victory, or go down in infamy? Wing Commander is a space combat simulator interspersed with shipboard dialogs. Onboard the ship, you can save/load game, visit the bar to get the latest gossip, or go on to the next mission briefing, and the 3D space combat part. The 3D space combat has you sitting in the cockpit, where you control the craft like roll, turn, up/down, afterburner, as well as fire guns and launch missiles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Origin Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wing Commander (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wing Commander (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Action Soccer (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Action Soccer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Action soccer is a quick and uncomplicated soccer game with two different graphic styles (2D overview and 3D isometric). The 16 teams have 6 skills like speed, strength, shotpower etc.. There are no things like offside, fatigue or tactic. You can play a friendly game, the UBI-Cup, a championship or a tournament. In few options you can change the weather (sun, night, rain, snow) or little tactic (offense, defense, normal). Worth mentioning is also the funny audio-commentary from Jonathan Pearce and the editor.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Ludi Media</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Action Soccer (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Action Soccer (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Softporn Adventure (1991).zip</path>
		<name>Softporn Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Softporn Adventure is a comedic, adult-oriented adventure game, originally written by Chuck Benton for Apple II and became the inspiration for the animated Leisure Suit Larry series. Players must type the verb and the noun to do different actions and finally break virginity of protagonist. The player's name is not yet Larry, but the plot of the game is very similar to Leisure Suit Larry in the Land of the Lounge Lizards. The player has to collect items to win over women in creative ways.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Sierra On-Line</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Softporn Adventure (1991).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Softporn Adventure (1991).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Master II - The Legend of Skullkeep (1994).zip</path>
		<name>Dungeon Master II: The Legend of Skullkeep</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dungeon Master II: The Legend of Skullkeep is a role-playing game in which you play Thoram Zed, who must enter Skullkeep Castle to kill the infamous Dragoth. Access to the castle requiring the four keys of destiny, the player must first worry about finding these before starting his quest. To do this, gather a team of four fighters and carry out a number of missions.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FTL</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dungeon Master II - The Legend of Skullkeep (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dungeon Master II - The Legend of Skullkeep (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./FX Fighter (1995).zip</path>
		<name>FX Fighter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>FX Fighter is a 3D fighting game similar to Virtua Fighter by SEGA. You choose one of the eight comic book style characters to become the greatest fighter in the universe.Each character has its own special / hidden moves as well as a planet of their own housing the gruesome challenges with 3rd-person flying camera perspectives...</desc>
		<releasedate>19950624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>GTE Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/FX Fighter (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/FX Fighter (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gender Wars (1996).zip</path>
		<name>Gender Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After eons of fighting between the genders, men and women have broken into separate factions, each using genetic engineering to create new followers, and waging terrible war upon each other. Upon selecting the side you wish to play (depicted as either clueless blondes who can't drive, or beer-swigging lazy oafs), you select a team of 4 for your missions, arm them up with guns and other assorted weaponry, and wreak havoc on the 'enemy' in this isometric Syndicate-like game. Progress through the levels to the final conflict, collecting tanks and other assorted 'powerups' along the way, and watching the humourous cutscenes as you go.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SCi Games</developer>
		<publisher>GT Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Gender Wars (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gender Wars (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heroes of Might and Magic (1995).zip</path>
		<name>Heroes of Might and Magic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Heroes of Might and Magic is a turn-based strategy game in which the player takes on the role of one of four different heroes: the warlock, sorceress, barbarian, or knight. As the hero the player must build up his or her castle by adding different buildings to earn different units to strengthen the hero's army with. Units include dragons, cyclopes, phoenixes, paladins, and many more fantasy creatures. Bulidings and units cost money and resources. Buildings can also be upgraded to unlock new unit types. Another aspect of the game is exploring the world and discovering treasures, spells, mines to gather resources, nomad camps, magic lamps, ultimate artifacts, and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New World Computing's</developer>
		<publisher>New World Computing's</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Heroes of Might and Magic (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Heroes of Might and Magic (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heroes of Might and Magic II (Deluxe Edition) (1998).zip</path>
		<name>Heroes of Might and Magic II: The Succession Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Heroes of Might and Magic II is a fantasy role-playing game which takes place in the land of Enroth, a place of magic. There are a multitude of creature types, from griffins to rocs, golems to pikemen, unicorns to hydras, and four different dragons. Each castle type has six different creatures, from the weak to the strong. There are six castle types, each corresponding to a hero class: Knight, Sorceress, Wizard (Good side), Barbarian, Necromancer and Warlock (Evil side). There are also six different types of neutral creatures you can recruit in special structures scattered about the maps. Compared to the first game, this sequel has larger and more interactive combat screens.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New World Computing's</developer>
		<publisher>3DO</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<image>./boxart/Heroes of Might and Magic II (Deluxe Edition) (1998).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Heroes of Might and Magic II (Deluxe Edition) (1998).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metaltech Earthsiege (1994).zip</path>
		<name>MetalTech EarthSiege</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Command heavily-armed HERCs against relentless automated Cybrids (Cyborg Hybrids; intelligent creatures designed by mankind, who rebelled against us) in this MechWarrior-ish first-person simulation. Earthsiege is not a product of FASA's BattleTech universe (as the MechWarrior games are), though the resemblances are too close for legal comfort. You control your HERC in 45 missions on varied terrain ranging from slaughter to escort to protection. Note that the game should ideally be controlled by more than just the keyboard for best play value.Full Motion Video clips from your commander detail your missions while keeping you in touch with the bigger picture as the war develops.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dynamix</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra On-Line</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metaltech Earthsiege (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metaltech Earthsiege (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NASCAR Racing (1994).zip</path>
		<name>NASCAR Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Papyrus' third racing game, the focus is moved from open-wheeled cars (IndyCar Racing) to closed-cockpit Nascar stock cars. 640x480 is the highest resolution on offer, on the CD-ROM version. Nascar Racing is a detailed simulation with realistic car models, accurate controls and room for a distinct racing style. Nine tracks are featured, the Watkins Glen road course alongside oval racing. You have full control over the car's set up and paint job. To reach a wide audience, various driving aids are available, such as auto-shifting and auto-braking. Races can be fine-tuned with the amount of laps. One of the notable features is drafting, by which you can position your car just inches off the rear of competitors in front of you.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Papyrus Design Group, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/NASCAR Racing (1994).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NASCAR Racing (1994).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pool of Radiance (1988).zip</path>
		<name>Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Pool of Radiance</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You and and your party first help the city of Phlan defeat the evils that threaten it, then search for the legendary Pool of Radiance. The first in a series of successful ''gold box'' AD&amp;D games for SSI, you create your party and maneuver it through 1st-perspective dungeons and overhead-view turn-based sequences.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Strategic Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Strategic Simulations</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pool of Radiance (1988).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pool of Radiance (1988).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Populous (1989).zip</path>
		<name>Populous</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play a god, gaming against other gods in a celestial game of conquest. To win, you must help your chosen people take over the world and wipe out the vermin who worship that other god. Each god starts out with a single human, dumped into the middle of the wilderness. Sometimes there is inhabitable land in sight, sometimes not. To get win, you must change the landscape, creating flat land for your followers to build on. The more followers you have you have, the more powerful you will be, so take care of them. Build as fast as you can, because the other god is doing the same. When you have enough followers, you can make the leader of your people into a hero.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Populous (1989).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Populous (1989).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PowerMonger (1992).zip</path>
		<name>PowerMonger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Powermonger takes the basic design and concepts of Bullfrog's previous game Populous, and places it in a war context. The game cast the player as a dispossessed warlord plundering his way through 195 territories on the way to world conquest. Several other leaders have the same goal. The gameworld is now made up of polygons, so the view can be rotated and moved with greater freedom than Populous. Trade, diplomacy, inventions, and scorched earth invasions all play a key role in how the player progressed through the game. Two-player games via modem links are available on computer versions.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/PowerMonger (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/PowerMonger (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret of the Silver Blades (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Secret of the Silver Blades</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The heroes from Pool of Radiance and Curse of the Azure Bonds return once again. This time, they arrive naked via a magical well inside a frozen town wishing for heroes to help them. The party once again attempts to save a town under siege (once re-equipped) and struggles to learn the secret of the Silver Blades The gameplay is quite similar to that of the previous Gold Box games. Following the AD&amp;D rules of role-playing, the player creates a party of characters (up to the maximum of six). Exploration takes place in pseudo-3D environments, from first-person view. Battles (random as well as pre-set) take the player-controlled and enemy party to a top-down battle screen.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Strategic Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Strategic Simulations</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Secret of the Silver Blades (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret of the Silver Blades (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assault Trooper (1997).zip</path>
		<name>Assault Trooper</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Assault Trooper is an isometric shooter game with tactical and stealth elements. The player controls a commando (no details are given on the government or organisation he belongs to) on clandestine solo assignments in various hot spots of the world. Missions include rescue, document retrieval, destruction of military targets, sabotage and assassinations. The ten available regions have five missions each that are gradually unlocked as more assignments are completed.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Juha Kauppinen</developer>
		<publisher>Spectrum Pacific Publishing</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Assault Trooper (1997).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Assault Trooper (1997).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima V - Warriors of Destiny (1988).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima V: Warriors of Destiny</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Avatar, the embodiment of the Eight Virtues and the hero of Britannia, is called back to deal with a grave threat. Lord British, the country's benevolent monarch, has disappeared, and a man named Blackthorn has usurped his throne. The tyrant rules the land by enforcing the virtues upon the will of the people, corrupting their meaning in the process. His fundamentalist visions led him to create a police state, where failure to adhere to the virtues is punishable by death. Behind Blackthorn are the three Shadowlords, anti-thesis to the three principles of Truth, Love, and Courage.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima V - Warriors of Destiny (1988).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima V - Warriors of Destiny (1988).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima VI - The False Prophet (1990).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima VI: The False Prophet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the first Ultima game to be created first for the PC and then converted later to other home computer systems rather than the other way around. Because of this, the game is larger and richer in its graphical environment and interactivity. In this conclusion to the Second Trilogy, you, the Avatar, are summoned back to save Britannia from the Gargoyles, a strange race of beings who have taken control of the Eight Shrines of Virtue. Conceived to be evil by the people of Britannia, the Gargoyles are discovered to be struggling for survival against ancient forces you had not imagined. You must help the Gargoyle race by learning their culture, language and vocabulary.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Origin Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Origin Systems</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima VI - The False Prophet (1990).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima VI - The False Prophet (1990).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima VII Part 1 - The Black Gate + Forge of Virtue (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima VII: Part One: The Black Gate &amp; Forge of Virtue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Even today Ultima VII is still considered one of the greatest roleplaying games ever made. The game begins when you, the Avatar, are summoned after receiving a taunting message from a being known as the Guardian. Upon arriving, the Avatar is confronted by the scene of a brutal murder. As you begin to investigate, it becomes clear that all is not as it should be in Britannia. Magic is dying, mages are affected by a strange madness, and despite your previous adventures people have forgotten who you are. Many are now captivated by virtuous and benevolent organization known as The Fellowship, who is perhaps not as they seem.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Origin Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima VII Part 1 - The Black Gate + Forge of Virtue (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima VII Part 1 - The Black Gate + Forge of Virtue (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima VII Part 2 - Serpent Isle + The Silver Seed (1993).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima VII: Part Two: Serpent Isle &amp; The Silver Seed</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The events of the game take place eighteen months after those described in Ultima VII: The Black Gate. Batlin, the leader of the Fellowship has disappeared, as well as Iolo's wife Gwenno. A map is found that points to the Serpent Isle where the Guardian is still planning to destroy Britannia. Lord British sends the Avatar and his companions to this new land. Once there, the Avatar discovers that a great imbalance is upon the isle and it is up to him to fix it. To do so, he must learn the philosophies of the original inhabitants of this land, who worshipped giant serpents symbolizing the principles of Order, Chaos and Balance.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima VII Part 2 - Serpent Isle + The Silver Seed (1993).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima VII Part 2 - Serpent Isle + The Silver Seed (1993).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1830 Railroads and Robber Barons (1995).zip</path>
		<name>1830: Railroads &amp; Robber Barons</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on Avalon Hill's board game of the same name, 1830 is a railroad empire building game that is along the same lines (although a different style of gameplay) as the much more famous Railroad Tycoon.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>SimTex, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Avalon Hill</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/1830 Railroads and Robber Barons (1995).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1830 Railroads and Robber Barons (1995).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Rally Fever - Born on the Road (1996).zip</path>
		<name>World Rally Fever: Born on the Road</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>World Rally Fever: Born on the Road is a racing game with simple driving controls and no realistic simulated physics. The emphasis is on speed and arcade-like gameplay; for this end there are power-ups and the cars' ability to jump at the press of a button.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/World Rally Fever - Born on the Road (1996).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/World Rally Fever - Born on the Road (1996).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wolfenstein 3D (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Wolfenstein 3D</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first three episodes of the game focus on William "B.J." Blazkowicz's attempts to escape from Castle Wolfenstein and overthrow the Nazi regime. In the first episode, Escape from Castle Wolfenstein, B.J., an Allied spy, has been captured while trying to find the plans for Operation Eisenfaust, and was imprisoned in Castle Wolfenstein. Initially armed only with a knife and a Walther P38 (obtained by overpowering the guard in his cell), B.J. tries to escape the castle prison. Taking on SS guards, he eventually finds himself face to face with head prison guard Hans Grosse.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>Apogee Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Wolfenstein 3D (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wolfenstein 3D (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Chess Enhanced (1992).zip</path>
		<name>Battle Chess: Enhanced</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This version of Battle Chess, while retaining the gameplay of the original release, features improved 256-color VGA graphics as well as new visual effects and animations. In addition, it has a symphonic soundtrack in redbook (CD audio) format.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battle Chess Enhanced (1992).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battle Chess Enhanced (1992).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>