<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>PC Engine CD-Rom</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Explorer II [U][SCD][TGXCD1034][Hudson Soft][1993][PCE][thx-1138-darkwater].chd</path>
		<name>Dungeon Explorer II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This CD sequel to Dungeon Explorer plays exactly the same as the first game. You chose your character from a variety of fantasy stereotypes and set forth in a Gauntlet-esque adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dungeon Explorer II [U][SCD][TGXCD1034][Hudson Soft][1993][PCE][thx-1138-darkwater].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dungeon Explorer II [U][SCD][TGXCD1034][Hudson Soft][1993][PCE][thx-1138-darkwater].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynastic Hero [U][SCD][TGXCD1053][Westone][1993][PCE][rigg].chd</path>
		<name>Dynastic Hero, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Dynastic Hero is a slightly re-branded version of Wonder Boy in Monster World for the Turbo Duo.The game features palette-swapped visuals, new insect-themed graphics for main characters (and insects' natural predators as bosses), a Red Book audio soundtrack which is completely different from the Wonder Boy original, and anime-style cutscenes at the intro and ending. Shion was renamed Dyna and was modeled after a Hercules Beetle, and the final boss was changed to a giant lizard king. An English-language version was also produced, but both were built off of the Japanese version of Wonder Boy in Monster World. They feature the same difficulty and mechanics as the Japanese original.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dynastic Hero [U][SCD][TGXCD1053][Westone][1993][PCE][rigg].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dynastic Hero [U][SCD][TGXCD1053][Westone][1993][PCE][rigg].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vasteel 2 (Japan) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Vasteel 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Vasteel 2 is formally a sequel to Vasteel; it is also set in the eponymous fictional, futuristic solar system and deals primarily with strategic battles between robots. However, its story is not directly connected with that of the predecessor. The main hero is a young boy named Voice Knuckles, who enjoys a peaceful life with his mother and his girlfriend Diggy. But the cruel Emperor Agares attacks his planet and destroys Voice's home, killing his mother in the process. The boy swears revenge. Aided by his girlfriend and his friends, he assembles a rebel army from fighters who navigate giant robots, and is determined to defeat Agares at all costs.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940708T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HuneX Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Human</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vasteel 2 (Japan) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vasteel 2 (Japan) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmic Fantasy 2 (Un-Worked Designs).chd</path>
		<name>Cosmic Fantasy 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Van is a young boy who lives on the planet Idea, a place where technology has not yet reached a high level. One day his sweetheart Laura gets kidnapped by an unknown villain. Van soon discovers that Laura possesses mysterious powers that may grant immortality to the one who marries her. That is exactly what the evil wizard Galam has in mind. Van sets off to rescue Laura, on a quest that involves intergalactic journeys and travel through time.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cosmic Fantasy 2 (Un-Worked Designs).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cosmic Fantasy 2 (Un-Worked Designs).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys IV - The Dawn of Ys (English Text + Dub patched).chd</path>
		<name>Ys IV: The Dawn of Ys</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As the game begins, Adol and his friend return to the town of Minea, where the first game began. The evil Lord Darm has been defeated, and it's time to relax and spend some time with friends - but not for long. A new evil is rising, and Adol decides to set sail for the overseas land of Celceta to investigate these occurrences.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ys IV - The Dawn of Ys (English Text + Dub patched).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ys IV - The Dawn of Ys (English Text + Dub patched).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games, allowing Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions. Beside changing the battle system, the game's perspective switches to a side-scrolling view, as opposed to the top-down one of the previous games. Adol also has the ability to jump now. New to the series is the use of magical rings, which give Adol different powering-up abilities such as healing and shielding. The game also uses various key items found along the way to solve minor puzzles and progress the story.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./In Magical Adventure - Fray CD - Xak Gaiden (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Fray in Magical Adventure CD: Xak Gaiden</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This version of Fray in Magical Adventure differs from the original MSX and subsequent computer releases in several ways. It retains the major events of the story and gameplay mechanics; even though it has more detailed graphics, it still looks too similarly to the original release to be qualified as a remake. The major difference is in the layout of locations and enemies. Some levels are entirely different, even when they are composed of the same elements.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Micro Cabin Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Micro Cabin Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/In Magical Adventure - Fray CD - Xak Gaiden (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/In Magical Adventure - Fray CD - Xak Gaiden (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shape Shifter [U][SCD][TGXCD1021][ICOM Simulations][1992][PCE][japman].chd</path>
		<name>Shape Shifter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Dark Ones have captured the Ring of Five and imprisoned the wizards that guard it. A barbarian named Lykos has the power to transform into different creatures. He needs to rescue the wizards and the Ring of Five from the Dark Ones before they invade his home, Krellion. Shape Shifter is a side-scrolling action game with platforming and light role-playing elements. Much of the game consists of traversing hostile areas, fighting regular enemies on the way and defeating bosses.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shape Shifter [U][SCD][TGXCD1021][ICOM Simulations][1992][PCE][japman].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shape Shifter [U][SCD][TGXCD1021][ICOM Simulations][1992][PCE][japman].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sylphia_(NTSC-J)_[THCD3001].chd</path>
		<name>Sylphia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sylphia is set in an environment inspired by the Greek mythology. The heroine of the game was a fearless maiden who tried to protect her home town from the onslaught of monsters. But even her power was no enough, and she was slain. Touched by her sacrifice, the goddess Athena revived her as a flying demi-goddess. Restored to new life, Sylphia can now unleash her wrath upon the monsters and their supporters. Despite its theme and setting, Sylphia plays like a vertically scrolling shooter.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Tonkin House</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sylphia_(NTSC-J)_[THCD3001].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sylphia_(NTSC-J)_[THCD3001].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valis III [U][CD][TGXCD1024][Telenet Japan][1992][PCE].chd</path>
		<name>Varisu Surī: Valis III</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After Yuko has defeated the evil Rogles, peace descended upon Earth and the magical world of Vecanti. But a new threat has arisen: an enigmatic man named Glames from the Dark World, possessor of a sword named Leethus, is planning to conquer both Earth and Vecanti, convinced that there is no other way to save his world from imminent destruction. A young girl from the Dark World named Cham escapes from Glames, and asks Yuko to help her stop him with the aid of her Valis sword. Like its predecessors in the series.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Valis III [U][CD][TGXCD1024][Telenet Japan][1992][PCE].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Valis III [U][CD][TGXCD1024][Telenet Japan][1992][PCE].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vasteel (Japan) (Rev 10).chd</path>
		<name>Vasteel</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The governing planet of the Vasteel Solar System is called Belose. Emperors of the Faracia dynasty have been ruling the planet for hundreds of years. However, the last emperor turned out to be rather unpopular with the people, and they began talking about changing the government system. Unexpectedly, the emperor becomes gravely ill and dies soon thereafter. His elder son, Faliall, is proclaimed the heir. However, Faliall's younger brother, Stefan, cares for the wishes of the simple folk, and is willing to change things. Hence, the bloody war between the two brothers for power and justice begins.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19901220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Working Designs</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vasteel (Japan) (Rev 10).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vasteel (Japan) (Rev 10).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Parodier (Japan) (Rev 2).chd</path>
		<name>Star Parodier</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Move fast and blast! It's a nonstop explosion of fire power and you're streaking through space, right in the middle of it! The Brains Cult you once defeated is back, badder than ever. But your finger's on the trigger of an incredible new techno-attack! Scorch the Scorpion with a nuclear a sting. Fire your heat-seeking sidewinders. Then power-up to launch your doomsday Super Bomb! Blow those Brains out and save the galaxy. Then challenge your friends with a special competition time mode to prove who the Super Star really is!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inter State</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Parodier (Japan) (Rev 2).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Parodier (Japan) (Rev 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./L-Dis_(NTSC-J)_[NSCD0005].chd</path>
		<name>L-Dis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One day during a school break, a boy and a girl met in the yard and started drawing monsters and mechanical devices on the wall. Suddenly, a mysterious vessel appeared and swallowed the girl. All the creatures drawn by the children became alive - but so did a little fighter plane, which the boy immediately boards and goes up towards the skies, searching for the girl. L-DIS is a horizontally scrolling shoot-em-up with cartoon-like visuals and humorous overtones. The player can choose between three different weapon setups in the beginning. Power-ups are obtained by shooting little winged yellow creatures encountered in the stages.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910405T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dual Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/L-Dis_(NTSC-J)_[NSCD0005].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/L-Dis_(NTSC-J)_[NSCD0005].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type Complete CD (Japan) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>R·Type Complete CD</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>R·Type Complete CD combines part I and part II of the japanese PC Engine HuCard releases. It also adds remixed music, fully voiced cut scenes, an extra boss fight, and some other minor changes. An alien race called the Bydo attacks humanity without mercy. The prototype space fighter R-9 must stop the Bydo and save the human race.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/R-Type Complete CD (Japan) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R-Type Complete CD (Japan) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Seirei_Senshi_Spriggan_(NTSC-J)_[NXCD1004].chd</path>
		<name>Seirei Senshi Spriggan</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Another top-down shooter from Compile staged in a fantasy world that mingles traditional sci-fi elements with a feudal Japan setting. As the game starts a struggle for total control over elemental powers is about to begin between two warring nations. As the best mecha pilot in the good guy's army it's your task to repel the invasion and win the war by dealing with the enemy armada in standard shooter fashion. But surprise surprise! You won't be alone this time, as other AI-controlled mecha pilots will join you in the fray at key moments.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Seirei_Senshi_Spriggan_(NTSC-J)_[NXCD1004].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Seirei_Senshi_Spriggan_(NTSC-J)_[NXCD1004].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puyo_Puyo_CD_Tsuu_(NTSC-J)_[NIPR-1001].chd</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo Tsū</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The follow-up to Puyo Puyo is, like its predecessor, a falling block game in which the goal is to combine four or more blocks (Puyos) of the same color, which then disappear. The remaining Puyos will then fall down and can produce combos which can cause special blocks (Nuisance Puyos, that can only be destroyed by eliminating adjacent Puyos) to appear on the enemy's field. This game includes a story mode, in which Arle (the main character) fights against computer enemies, a vs player mode, a four player mode (SNES only), and an endless mode (SNES only).</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Puyo_Puyo_CD_Tsuu_(NTSC-J)_[NIPR-1001].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Puyo_Puyo_CD_Tsuu_(NTSC-J)_[NIPR-1001].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rally Championship (Japan) (FABT).chd</path>
		<name>Rally Championship</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rally Championship is a top-down racing game. The player can choose to control real rally cars: Toyota Celica, Nissan Pulsar, Lancia Delta, and others. There are three modes in the game: time attack, high speed rally, and "adventure mode", which takes the player through a championship in Senegal. Each mode allows the player to select a car and customize its steering, gears, brakes, etc. Car controls are fairly simple, with one button assigned to accelerating and another to applying brakes.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>P's PSYTEC Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Intec Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rally Championship (Japan) (FABT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rally Championship (Japan) (FABT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Chiki Chiki Boys</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This platform-based action game is set in the land of Alurea. The idyllic life of the Alurean people was shattered when the King is killed by a dragon, and a range of nasties inhabit the lands. Fortunately his twin sons have come to the rescue, and you must take control of one or the other to put the world right.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chiki Chiki Boys (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Down Load 2 - Remaster (Hack).chd</path>
		<name>Download 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Download 2 is an horizontal shooter. Nec Avenue certainly acknowledged that the game's best asset was the unique and innovative ability to jack-in and dive into computerized cyber-space worlds. This sequel follows the same formula but also features probably one of most electrifying storyline ever written for a video game. The brain of Adolf Hitler has been digitized inside a computer mainframe by terrorists and Syd, an elite cyber-diver and protagonist of the game, embarks on a perilous journey to stop and destroy the incoming threat. On board his ship and helped by the cute Deva, Syd flies through nine enemy infested areas and dives into abstract and challenging cyber worlds.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlfaSystem Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Down Load 2 - Remaster (Hack).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Down Load 2 - Remaster (Hack).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Slayer - The Legend of Heroes (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Slayer: The Legend of Heroes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Slayer: The Legend of Heroes is a RPG for PC Engine. You play as Prince Selios/Logan. During a test intended to make you a warrior, the kingdom of your father is attacked by savage monsters. Betrayed on all sides by your former allies, you must recruit companions to liberate your country.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Slayer - The Legend of Heroes (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Slayer - The Legend of Heroes (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Exile (Un-Worked Designs).chd</path>
		<name>Exile</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Exile concerns the desert adventures of Sadler, the great hero whose revolt years before led to the downfall of a powerful empire. Recently, however, peace was broken in Sadler's home country, as the rival Luciel empire has been launching attacks on the Village of Dunes. Exile is a hybrid action/role-playing game. Travel and exploration occurs in the traditional overhead view of RPGs, while the battles and dungeons are side-scrolling mazes, similar to Wanderers from Ys. Characters gain experience and levels, buy equipment, and use magic.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Working Designs</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Exile (Un-Worked Designs).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Exile (Un-Worked Designs).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Faussete Amour (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Fausseté Amour</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A young girl named Koruku lived in her home village, enjoying a peaceful life with her sister and her friends. But it all changed when an evil demon known as the Goatbone appeared. With his powers of mind control and shape-shifting, he possessed Koruku's friends, turning them into terrifying monsters, kidnapped her sister, and burnt down the village. A mysterious old man approaches the desperate Koruku and bestows her with a wonderful armor, weapon, and magic powers. The young girl is ready to venture into Goatbone's lair and liberate her sister. but will she be able to defeat her own friends who now obey the word of their dark master?</desc>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AIM</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Faussete Amour (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Faussete Amour (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pop'n Magic (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Pop'n Magic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A static screen action game in the style of Bubble Bobble or Don Doko Don, Pop 'n Magic allows you to trap enemies by firing your wand at them, then pick them up and throw them across the screen to destroy them. The bubbles they are trapped in are specific colours and care must be taken not to throw two of the same colour together as this will release the (now quite upset) creatures inside.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920724T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riot</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pop'n Magic (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pop'n Magic (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Splash Lake (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Splash Lake</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Splash Lake is an action strategy puzzle game. Each round consists of a single screen play area composed of tiles suspended over a lake. You control an Ostrich that can crack the tiles and cause them to fall into the water. Your goal is to use this ability to make all the bad guys on the screen fall into the water. The game features more than 60 levels, a simultaneous two-player mode, and humorous cutscenes every 10 levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bits Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Splash Lake (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Splash Lake (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strider Hiryuu (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Sutoraidā Hiryū</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 2048 AD. In Russia, the evil Grand Master Meio has begun his insane plot to take over the universe. A lone figure drops from a stealth glider into Meio's base. He is Hiryu, Super A-Class Strider. His mission is to defeat the Grand Master and put an end to his plotting once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Strider Hiryuu (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Strider Hiryuu (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Heroes 2 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>World Heroes 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The time-traveling tournament fighters are back! The original eight characters from the previous game return, along with six new characters hand-picked from several different eras and locations all through time. Who or what is behind this new tournament? In order to find that out, the strongest fighter must defeat all the opponents, win the title, and face the one who has all the answers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ADK Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/World Heroes 2 (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/World Heroes 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nexzr_(NTSC-J)_[NXCD2014].chd</path>
		<name>Nexzr</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2012 an alien armada attacked the Earth. Two young pilots were in the midst of a battle, and one of them, a lovely young woman, was killed. Three years later, the surviving pilot finally got a chance to avenge her death. Navigating a powerful new fighter ship named "Slasher", the pilot ventured into space, ready to bring destruction to those who took so much away from him. Nexzr is a vertically scrolling shoot-em-up similar to Super Star Soldier.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inter State</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nexzr_(NTSC-J)_[NXCD2014].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nexzr_(NTSC-J)_[NXCD2014].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Raiden (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Raiden</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A conversion of the classic arcade shoot 'em up, Raiden follows the conventions of the genre with coloured power up pods that give different weapons when collected.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Seibu Kaihatsu</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Raiden (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Raiden (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Avenger (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Avenger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A devastating atomic war wiped out the biggest cities on the Earth and most of its population. Anarchy reigned, different military organizations fighting each other in a new war for dominance. One of such organizations eventually seized control of the planet, establishing itself as a tyrannic government and using advanced technology for military purposes. Only a lone pilot can save humanity from their clutches.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Avenger (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Avenger (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beyond Shadowgate (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Beyond Shadowgate</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is a sequel to the adventure game Shadowgate. You control Prince Eric, the descendant of the hero of the first game. You return to your home country, only to discover that your father was murdered. You should become the new king, but the minister of the late king has other plans, frames you for killing your own father, and throws you into jail, where your adventure begins.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Turbo Technologies, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Icom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Beyond Shadowgate (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Beyond Shadowgate (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Godzilla (Audio Track Restore).chd</path>
		<name>Godzilla</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This interpretation of the famous giant monster from the Japanese cinematic industry takes form of a fighting game, only instead of the usual brave martial artists the players control horrifying monsters from the traditional Toho lineage: the titular beast itself, Rodan, Anguirus, Ghidorah, and others. The game has two modes: Normal and Vs. The latter is essentially a two-player mode, which allows the players to engage in giant monster battles in a variety of scenarios. Most of the monsters, however, are locked in the Vs. mode before the player has completed the Normal mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Toho Company</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Godzilla (Audio Track Restore).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Godzilla (Audio Track Restore).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Motteke Tamago (T-En).chd</path>
		<name>Motteke Tamago</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Motteke Tamago was included in the second volume of the Super PC Engine Fan Deluxe magazine. It is an action game similar in concept to Bomberman. The game consists of three "worlds", each with ten screens; on every screen, four ducks are competing against each other in collecting eggs and delivering their babies home. The ducks can be controlled by human players or by computer AI. Eggs are being dropped into the maze-like stage; the goal is to collect as many of them as possible. Once collected, an egg follows the duck, and after a while a baby would hatch and return home safely.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19970416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naxat Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Tokuma Shoten</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Motteke Tamago (T-En).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Motteke Tamago (T-En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman - Panic Bomber (Japan) (FAAT).chd</path>
		<name>Bomberman: Panic Bomber</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Panic Bomber is a falling block puzzle game, somewhat reminiscent of Puyo Puyo games: instead of Tetris-like abstract blocks, little colored heads are falling down and must be arranged in rows of three (vertically or horizontally), by rotating them and matching them with other heads of the same color. In this case, the heads clearly belong to the titular character of the Bomberman series.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19941222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bomberman - Panic Bomber (Japan) (FAAT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bomberman - Panic Bomber (Japan) (FAAT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton - Remaster (Hack).chd</path>
		<name>Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams plays in a similar way to other scrolling shooter video games such as R-Type. What distinguishes Cotton: Fantastic Night Dreams from other games of a similar ilk is its bright colourful graphics and its lead character, Cotton. The game also takes place in a fantasy dream-like world instead of space like many other shooting games. The game can be compared to other fantasy Shoot 'em up games like Parodius. It bears most similarities in style to the Chariot game on Three Wonders. The player controls Cotton, a young witch on a broomstick. The player must blast various monsters and avoid being shot. The player can collect power-ups to enhance their weaponry and unleash a more powerful attack on the enemy.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton - Remaster (Hack).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton - Remaster (Hack).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hellfire S - The Another Story (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Hellfire S: The Another Story</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hellfire S is a Shoot-'Em-Up game, developed by Bits Laboratory and published by NEC International, which was released in Japan in 1991.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hellfire S - The Another Story (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hellfire S - The Another Story (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ImageFight II - Operation Deepstriker (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Image Flight II: Operation Deepstriker</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Image Flight II: Operation Deepstriker is a sequel for the PC Engine Super CD-ROM exclusively to Japan. This game is a lost jewel of Irem, and they really put love in this game. It features a good storyline, new enemies, upgrades of past ones and a few new arsenal.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/ImageFight II - Operation Deepstriker (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ImageFight II - Operation Deepstriker (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mad_Stalker_-_Full_Metal_Force_(NTSC-J)_[HECD4009].chd</path>
		<name>Mad Stalker: Full Metal Force</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mad Stalker: Full Metal Force is a Japanese beat 'em up video game originally produced by Fill-in-Cafe and published and distributed by FamilySoft for the Sharp X68000. The music was composed by Keishi Yonao.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19940915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fill in Café</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mad_Stalker_-_Full_Metal_Force_(NTSC-J)_[HECD4009].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mad_Stalker_-_Full_Metal_Force_(NTSC-J)_[HECD4009].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Might and Magic III - Isles of Terra [U][SCD][TGXCD1047][New World Computing][1993][PCE][thx-1138-darkwater].chd</path>
		<name>Might and Magic III: Isles of Terra</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Emerging from the depths of the nebulous void, there came four lords. To each lord, a dominion: fire, water, air, and earth. But each lord lusted for more - to be the ultimate ruler of the void. The four lords of the elements descended into a hideous conflict that unleashed a raging storm.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>New World Computing's</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Might and Magic III - Isles of Terra [U][SCD][TGXCD1047][New World Computing][1993][PCE][thx-1138-darkwater].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Might and Magic III - Isles of Terra [U][SCD][TGXCD1047][New World Computing][1993][PCE][thx-1138-darkwater].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Air Zonk - Rockabilly-Paradise (USA).chd</path>
		<name>CD Denjin: Rockabilly Tengoku</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After the success of PC Denjin, our hero leaps onto CD with a whole new game and a whole new soundtrack. Flying over the various landscapes (you get to choose which order to play the first four levels in), you come up against tidal waves, giant robots and a general array of nasty but cute bad guys as you would expect. The plants from the original PC Kid games are still here to provide such joys as extra firepower, fountains of smiley faces or the tiny-denjin which makes dodging bullets that little bit easier. Another handy little trick is that your boots also pack a punch, so backing into an enemy is more likely to dispose of them than do you any permanent damage.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Air Zonk - Rockabilly-Paradise (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Air Zonk - Rockabilly-Paradise (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeon Master - Theron's Quest [U][SCD][TGXCD1041][FTL Games][1993][PCE][xeno-nec archives].chd</path>
		<name>Dungeon Master: Theron's Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Terrifyingly brutal beasts! Monstrous mazes! Treacherous pits of evil! The adventure of a lifetime is here. Theron's Quest!! The Monastery at Ya-Brodin has fallen to the Cult of Deaths and the Brotherhood of Enlightenment, the true keepers of Magic, have been slaughtered. The Seven Great Treasures now lie in the hands of foul beings who will stop at nothing to hold onto their massive powers. But Theron, with a courage beyond belief, has decided to seek out the Cult of Deaths and win back the Treasures. If he succeeds, he will become a High Lord. If not, the land will see eternal darkness.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FTL Games</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dungeon Master - Theron's Quest [U][SCD][TGXCD1041][FTL Games][1993][PCE][xeno-nec archives].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dungeon Master - Theron's Quest [U][SCD][TGXCD1041][FTL Games][1993][PCE][xeno-nec archives].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kaizou_Choujin_Shubibinman_3_-_Ikai_no_Princess_(NTSC-J)_[NSCD2010].chd</path>
		<name>Kaizō Chōjin Shubibinman 3: Ikai no Princess</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Third game in the Shubibinman series of action platformers. Cyborgs Tasuke and Kyapiko have taken a vacation from all their robot-bashing when they receive a plea for help from the princess of an alien world, naturally our heroes accept and make the journey to outer space, where more robot-bashing adventures await. The game plays like a standard action side-scroller in which you must clear each stage of all enemies using your attacks and make your way to the end-level boss, kick his metallic behind and advance to the next stage.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kaizou_Choujin_Shubibinman_3_-_Ikai_no_Princess_(NTSC-J)_[NSCD2010].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kaizou_Choujin_Shubibinman_3_-_Ikai_no_Princess_(NTSC-J)_[NSCD2010].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tengai_Makyou_-_Kabuki_Ittouryoudan_(NTSC-J)_[HCD5070].chd</path>
		<name>Tengai Makyō: Kabuki Ittou Ryoudan</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tengai Makyō: Kabuki Ittou Ryoudan is a 2D-versus fighting game who's roster includes characters from Tengai Makyou II: Manjimaru and Tengai Makyou: Fuun Kabuki Den. Red Company along with A.I. Co. developed Kabuki Ittou Ryoudan and the game was released in Japan for the PC-Engine CD by Hudson in 1995. The title was also included in a PlayStation Portable compilation pack in 2008 called Tengai Makyou Collection that contained ports of all of the PC-Engine entries in the Tengai Makyou series.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tengai_Makyou_-_Kabuki_Ittouryoudan_(NTSC-J)_[HCD5070].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tengai_Makyou_-_Kabuki_Ittouryoudan_(NTSC-J)_[HCD5070].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Downtown Nekketsu Monogatari (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Downtown Nekketsu Monogatari</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Brothers Ryuichi and Ryuji arrive at the Reihou Academy, After a short amount of time, nearby schools have begun fallen under the control of Ryuichi and Ryuji, who rumor has it have dubbed themselves the Double Dragons.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Downtown Nekketsu Monogatari (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Downtown Nekketsu Monogatari (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gate of Thunder - Remaster (Hack).chd</path>
		<name>Gate of Thunder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A side-scrolling shoot-'em-up, Gate of Thunder asks players to take control of the space-craft "Hunting Dog". You fly left-to-right mostly, with occasional vertically-scrolling sections, and use several different weapon styles to defeat your many foes. Along with Esty in her ship the "Wild Cat", you must defeat the forces of General Don Jingi, who has plans of taking energy from the star of Aries.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gate of Thunder - Remaster (Hack).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gate of Thunder - Remaster (Hack).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lords of Thunder (Sega CD OST).chd</path>
		<name>Lords of Thunder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the once peaceful land of Mistral, legend holds of a brave knight named Drak who has sealed an evil god named Deoric beneath the six continents of the land. However, peace never lasts. The Garuda Empire has invaded the lands of Mistral, and the six Dark Generals, led by Sornbul, have conquered the continents. Sornbul's ambition is nothing less than to resurrect Deoric and plunge the land into chaos. Duran, descendant of Drak, is the only one who can stop the Garuda Empire's mad plan, and with the power of Drak's mystic armors, he heads off to stop Sornbul at any cost.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lords of Thunder (Sega CD OST).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lords of Thunder (Sega CD OST).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Asuka 120% Maxima - Burning Fest. Maxima (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Asuka 120% Maxima Burning Fest.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Welcome to the "Ryouran Private School for Women" which educates the daughters of the upper echelons of society. Here, the high class clubs annually hold a martial arts tournament: the "Club Rivalry Budget Contest Mega Fight." Each character employs a different fighting style; techniques are unique to each club.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950728T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fill in Café</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Asuka 120% Maxima - Burning Fest. Maxima (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Asuka 120% Maxima - Burning Fest. Maxima (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TV Show, The (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>TV Show, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The TV Show is a humorous overhead action game similar to Bomberman in concept. The game consists of a scenario mode (single-player) and a versus mode (up to four players). Both modes offer seven characters to choose from. The characters are comically-themed and include a hyperactive schoolgirl, an armored ninja, and others. There is no real storyline behind these characters; each comes with a short introduction sequence that invariably leads to their admittance to an alien-organized TV show, where they have to defeat enemies and retrieve prizes.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Right Stuff Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Right Stuff Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/TV Show, The (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/TV Show, The (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys Book I &amp; II [U][CD][TGXCD1002][Falcom][1990][PCE].chd</path>
		<name>Ys: Book I &amp; II</name>
		<sortname>Ys 1</sortname>
		<desc>The players controls a young red-haired hero named Adol Christin, whose task is to find the six books of Ys, an ancient paradise-like land that mysteriously disappeared long time ago. It is said that whoever possesses the six books can gain access into Ys. In the first game, Adol is on the quest to find the books and to enter Ys. The second game takes place in Ys itself, and Adol must defeat an even greater evil and liberate the land.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19890101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ys Book I &amp; II [U][CD][TGXCD1002][Falcom][1990][PCE].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ys Book I &amp; II [U][CD][TGXCD1002][Falcom][1990][PCE].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ginga_Fukei_Densetsu_-_Sapphire_(NTSC-J)_[HCD5080].chd</path>
		<name>Ginga Fukei Densetsu Sapphire</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the future, time travel became a regular commodity. Criminal organizations began using advanced science in order to escape into different time periods to avoid capture. To counter that, a special police unit called "Burning Rabbits" was formed, consisting of four young ladies who bravely pilot their fighter craft through time and space. Ginga Fukei Densetsu: Sapphire is a vertically-scrolling shoot-em-up.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19951124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CAProduction co., ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ginga_Fukei_Densetsu_-_Sapphire_(NTSC-J)_[HCD5080].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ginga_Fukei_Densetsu_-_Sapphire_(NTSC-J)_[HCD5080].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psychic Storm (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Psychic Storm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Psychic Storm is a vertically scrolling shoot-em-up in which the player takes the role of four characters who must protect Neo Hong Kong City from an assault by vicious insectoid aliens. The player can select any of the four characters before each stage. The characters are distinguished by the unique attacks of their ships: Alex uses a vulcan gun, Charr has short-ranged "psychic" beam, Joe has a slow, yet powerful Hell Flame attack, and Nastasia uses ion laser. Each character can also acquire additional weapons by picking regular power-ups.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AlfaSystem Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Shin-Nihon Laser Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Psychic Storm (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Psychic Storm (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Rondo of Blood (T-En + English PSP Audio v1.01).chd</path>
		<name>Akumajō Dracula X: Chi no Rondo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the days of old, the people thrived on peace and prosperity. Indeed, fears of unrest were not among their thoughts but, ever-present, beneath the veneer of tranquility, evil lurks. Evil, which spurns prosperity and disdains peace. Gather they did, those who wished to summon the powers of darkness and cleanse the decadence of the world. And, with smiling countenance, they anxiously awaited the coming of their era. A hundred years had past, and he was resurrected. Able to become bat, wolf, or mist at will, he lived in the night. He drank the blood of young maidens and lived an eternal life. The lord of Castlevania, the god of evil, Count Dracula was reborn.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Rondo of Blood (T-En + English PSP Audio v1.01).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Rondo of Blood (T-En + English PSP Audio v1.01).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; TheMajinZenki v1.1] [Honorifics].chd</path>
		<name>Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon</name>
		<desc>Sailor Moon was the title of a video game released in Japan in 1994 for the PC-Engine console. The game was an interactive story, including characters and voice actors from the anime as well as some original characters. The songs "Koisuru Otome wa Makenai" and "Onaji Hoshi ni Umareta Futari Dakara" were written specifically for this game. A shortened version of each song appeared in the game, while full versions were available on the single "Sailor Moon: PC Engine Theme Songs".</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; TheMajinZenki v1.1] [Honorifics].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bishoujo Senshi Sailor Moon (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; TheMajinZenki v1.1] [Honorifics].mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19940805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Banpresto</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220209T170019</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaxy Fraulein Yuna (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; Mafoo343 v1.1] [n].chd</path>
		<name>Ginga Ojōsama Densetsu Yuna</name>
		<sortname>Galaxy Fraulein Yuna</sortname>
		<desc>Yuna Kagurazaka is a somewhat ditzy 16-year old girl. After winning a "Galactic Bish?jo Contest" (Galaxy Fräulein Contest, similar to Idol contests), she becomes "The Savior of Light", a magical girl charged with defending the universe from evil. Galaxy Fräulein Yuna is digital comic game (visual novel type). The game has no game over (can infinitely continue) or bad ending, similar to story-telling digital comic books or interactive movies. Move somewhere, talk with somebody, then fight against the 13 Fräuleins of Darkness... Combat scenes are played out in turn-based RPG style, but there is no EXP or items ? only attack or defence.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Galaxy Fraulein Yuna (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; Mafoo343 v1.1] [n].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Galaxy Fraulein Yuna (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; Mafoo343 v1.1] [n].mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19921023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220209T170043</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaxy Fraulein Yuna 2 - The Eternal Princess (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; Mafoo343 &amp; TheMajinZenki v1.0] [n].chd</path>
		<name>Galaxy Fraulein Yuna 2: Eternal Princess, The</name>
		<sortname>Galaxy Fraulein Yuna 2</sortname>
		<desc>This is the second game in the series about the school girl Yuna Kagurazaka, who fights crime in cosmic battles. Eien no Princess continues the story of the first game. Yuna has defeated the 13 Servants of Darkness, and their leader Lia has become a friend, fighting crime on her own in a superhero TV show. Life seems to continue normally, the only trouble being Erika, a snotty high school girl who sees herself as Yuna's biggest rival. She challenges Yuna to a fight, but both are spotted by the titular starship "Eternal Princess", commanded by the pretty Princess Mirage, whose task is to stop violence in the whole galaxy. What begins as a misunderstanding ends as a serious threat to the Earth...</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Galaxy Fraulein Yuna 2 - The Eternal Princess (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; Mafoo343 &amp; TheMajinZenki v1.0] [n].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Galaxy Fraulein Yuna 2 - The Eternal Princess (Japan) [T-En by Supper &amp; Mafoo343 &amp; TheMajinZenki v1.0] [n].mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19950630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220209T170058</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sorcery Saga I - The Fiery Kindergarten Graduation (Japan) [T-En by LIPEMCO! Translations v1.0] [n].chd</path>
		<name>Sorcery Saga I: Fiery Kindergarten Graduation, The</name>
		<desc>In this game, you play a young apprentice sorceress named Arle. She studies at a magic school, and is about to take her most important examination: go to the Tower of Satan, defeat the enemies and overcome all the obstacles on the way using her magic power! Mad? Monogatari I is a role-playing game. Featuring characters from the Puyo Puyo games, it is set in a 3D dungeon which you explore from first-person perspective. Combat takes place on a side-scrolling screen, and is a mixture of turn-based and real-time styles. Enemies attack you even if you wait, but you have time to perform your moves. You should hold down buttons and press direction arrows to execute various magic spells.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Sorcery Saga I - The Fiery Kindergarten Graduation (Japan) [T-En by LIPEMCO! Translations v1.0] [n].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sorcery Saga I - The Fiery Kindergarten Graduation (Japan) [T-En by LIPEMCO! Translations v1.0] [n].mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19961213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220209T170127</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Startling Odyssey II - Maryuu Sensou (Japan) [T-En by TruMisery v20100331].chd</path>
		<name>Startling Odyssey II - Maryuu Sensou  </name>
		<desc>A mad scientist named Dr. Killbait succeeded in resurrecting one of the eight ancient dragons, endangering the country of Hyneld. The captain of the king's knights, Robin Solford, witnesses the dragon's attack on the castle. His two comrades are killed, and the princess Patricia, Robin's adoptive sister, is nowhere to be seen. Robin is determined to find Patricia and stop Dr. Killbait, and begins to wander around the world, hoping to find friends who will help him on his perilous journey. Startling Odyssey II: Mary? Sens? is not a sequel, but a prequel to the first game, Robin Solford being the father of the previous game's hero.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Startling Odyssey II - Maryuu Sensou (Japan) [T-En by TruMisery v20100331].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Startling Odyssey II - Maryuu Sensou (Japan) [T-En by TruMisery v20100331].mp4</video>
		<releasedate>19941021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>RayForce Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>RayForce Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220209T170143</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xak III - The Eternal Recurrence (Japan) [T-En by NightWolve v1.00].chd</path>
		<name>Xak III: Eternal Recurrence, The</name>
		<desc>The great hero Latok, the descendant of the war god Duel, has returned to his hometown Fearless, where he lives peacefully with his mother. But one day, a messenger brings terrible news: the castle of Farland was attacked, the king, the princess, and countless soldiers brutally slain. Zomu Dizae, the third and the final demon commander of the dark world Zekisis (Latok has defeated the other two, Badu and Gospel), has arrived. He is aided by the treacherous Necromancer, who turned the soldiers of Farland into monsters. Will Latok be able to defeat the evil once again?</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Xak III - The Eternal Recurrence (Japan) [T-En by NightWolve v1.00].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Xak III - The Eternal Recurrence (Japan) [T-En by NightWolve v1.00].mp4</video>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Microcabin</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220209T170200</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk III - Bonk's Big Adventure (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bonk III: Bonk's Big Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bonk is back! And he's bigger and better than ever! Use your head (literally) to traverse 6 wild locations- including a forest grove, an antartic ice prison and more! Chomp on blue miracle candy to grow to gigantic proportions and break right through large obstacles. Chomp red candy to shrink to microscopic size and slip right under narrow cracks to discover secret items! Catch the magic flower in each stage to be transported to a bonus round- where you can score more points and earn bonus men! On your way, you will defeat menacing bosses that include acrobatic dinosaur, a sneaky squid and other! Are you ready to save the world, little cave dude!?</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bonk III - Bonk's Big Adventure (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bonk III - Bonk's Big Adventure (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Buster Bros. (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Buster Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your goal is to destroy the balloons which bounce around the playfield. To accomplish this, you can shoot hooks which travel upwards, and blow up any balloon they touch. Depending on their size, they either split on two smaller ones, or evaporate if they're at their minimum size. Apart from balloons, some levels also have barriers that have to be destroyed with your hooks, since they often block your access to balloons. There are also some barriers which cannot ever be destroyed. Your character has the ability to climb ladders, but cannot jump.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mitchell Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Buster Bros. (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Buster Bros. (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forgotten Worlds (USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>Forgotten Worlds</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Forgotten Worlds features two characters known as The Nameless Ones, who both look like Arnold Schwarzenegger, one even has a mohawk. It's their job to rid the planet of the attacking aliens. Guiding your character around the screen as they fly with jet-packs, guns on full auto, you control a satellite which you rotate around your character for the direction in which your gun is firing. At the end of each level is a boss which needs to be killed to progress. Enemies that have been killed drop money. At the end of every level is a shop where you can buy weapons, armour, items and first-aid packs.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Forgotten Worlds (USA) (En,Ja).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Forgotten Worlds (USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./J. B. Harold Murder Club (USA) (En,Ja).chd</path>
		<name>J. B. Harold Murder Club</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Murder Club is an adventure game with simulation elements. The player controls the private detective J.B. Harold, who must investigate the murder of a wealthy businessman named Bill Robbins and bring the murderer to court. The player has to do all the work a real detective would do: find clues, gather evidence, interrogate suspects, establish the motive for the crime ? and in the end, make sure the case will stand up in the court.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riverhillsoft</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/J. B. Harold Murder Club (USA) (En,Ja).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/J. B. Harold Murder Club (USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Monster Lair (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Monster Lair</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Feeling more like the first Wonder Boy than the second, Monster Lair is a fast-paced auto scrolling platform game. The levels are split into two stages, the first being a platform stage, the second a shoot 'em up stage which ends in a boss. During the game your energy counts down, so you must keep picking up fruit to replenish yourself. There are a variety of weapons to collect - lasers, spread shots, spinning shields and so on, but these are also on a timer and do not last long, so weapon switching is frequent to avoid being left with your basic short range sword shot. The game is single or two player simultaneous.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Monster Lair (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Monster Lair (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>While the Sultan of Persia is fighting a war in a foreign country, his Grand Vizier Jaffar orchestrates a coup d'état. His way to the throne lies through the Sultan's lovely daughter. Jaffar kidnaps her and threatens to kill her if she refuses to marry him. Meanwhile, the man the Princess loves is thrown into the dungeon. He has only one hour to escape from his prison, defeat the guards on his way, and stop Jaffar before the terrible marriage takes place. Prince of Persia is a 2D platformer that is commonly regarded as a progenitor of the cinematic platform genre.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19911108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Riverhillsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Prince of Persia (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Prince of Persia (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow of the Beast (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Shadow of the Beast</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>While very young, Aarbron was kidnapped and enslaved by the Priests of the Beast Lord. He grew up on drugs made to destroy his own will and turn him into the Beast Messenger, a powerful creature serving Maletoth, The Beast Lord himself. He did his job, until one day he noticed a man about to be sacrificed in a ritual, his face triggering ancient memories. As the sacrificial knife descended into the man's body, Aarbron recognizes his father's face. As his father dies in the altar, memories of his childhood and tormented past at the hands of the Beast Lord emerged, and as feelings of hate over his captors took over him, he swore revenge and fled the temple, knowing the road to avenge his father and redemption would be hard.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadow of the Beast (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadow of the Beast (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective - Volume 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective - Volume 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>"What they said about Sherlock I, you'll say about Sherlock II"...reads the advert in the box, based on the nice critics about Volume I. - The same video technology (this is 1992), keeps offering true interactive environment: actually letting you "feel" the traffic in the streets of the old London? - The same structure brings a familiar look, inviting to channel all attention to the task of solving mysteries: your intelligence, skills and patience are required to find clues by listening to people, observing details, or even reading the London Times - but don't let yourself be misguided by a wrong hint. - The same number of cases: 3 But, each situation is completely different: ?The Two Lions? involving the murder of circus lions, ?</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930528T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective - Volume 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective - Volume 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this game, the player is cast into the roles of Sherlock Holmes, the greatest fictional detective of all times, and his friend and partner Dr. Watson, as they have to investigate and successfully solve three criminal cases: The Mummy's Curse deals with the horrifying death of three men, which were apparently murdered by an ancient mummy; The Mystified Murderess involves a woman who has been convicted for murdering her beloved one, but cannot seem to recall anything of what had happened to her; The Tin Soldier concerns the murder of an old general, whose past must be investigated in order to find the killer.Sherlock Holmes: Consulting Detective can be described as a hybrid of adventure game and simulation.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19910726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Victor Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sherlock Holmes - Consulting Detective (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan) (Rev 4).chd</path>
		<name>Monster Lair</name>
		<desc>Feeling more like the first Wonder Boy than the second, Monster Lair is a fast-paced auto scrolling platform game. The levels are split into two stages, the first being a platform stage, the second a shoot 'em up stage which ends in a boss. During the game your energy counts down, so you must keep picking up fruit to replenish yourself. There are a variety of weapons to collect - lasers, spread shots, spinning shields and so on, but these are also on a timer and do not last long, so weapon switching is frequent to avoid being left with your basic short range sword shot.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan) (Rev 4).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wonder Boy III - Monster Lair (Japan) (Rev 4).mp4</video>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220210T143732</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advanced V.G. (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Advanced V.G.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The story of Advanced V.G. follows a similar template as those of the previous Variable Geo games: the strongest young women in the country hold a tournament, which is sponsored by various restaurant chains, which in turn ask the competing girls to pose as waitresses working in said restaurants, for promotional purposes. The girls of the Jahana group who starred in the previous games return, with the new main protagonist being the young martial artist Yuka Takeuchi, who has been training in a secluded forest area before joining the competition. Like its predecessors, Advanced V.G. is a fighting game, with the basic "kick" and "punch" moves, while the various special attacks are executed by pressing combinations of buttons.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GIGA</developer>
		<publisher>Technical Group Laboratory, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Advanced V.G. (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Advanced V.G. (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ai Chou Aniki (Japan) (SADS).chd</path>
		<name>Ai Chou Aniki</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the first Cho Aniki (Super Big Brother) game, this is very Japanese in its bizarreness. It's a shoot ?em up, with the player taking the role of an almost nude muscle-man (Adon) or his brother (Samson) in a 2 player game. Their main weapon is a ball of energy that grows over a hole in their heads and shoots out towards any advancing enemies. Other, more powerful shots are achieved by a combination of back-forward-fire, down-up-fire etc on the pad. Through the levels you will encounter all manner of nasties out to get you, but you are aided by a woman in blue that flies around and drops power-ups conveniently for you. Also, levels vary from the standard left-to-right to vertically scrolling.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ai Chou Aniki (Japan) (SADS).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ai Chou Aniki (Japan) (SADS).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Brandish (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Brandish</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once there was a prosperous kingdom, which was protected by a tower, where a mighty dragon was living. The people of the kingdom were secure with such a guardian. But one man wanted the dragon's power for something else, and this man was the king. He went to the tower and tried to kill the dragon, in order to rob his power. But the dragon's fury turned the king into a horrible creature, a demon, and his evil essence made his entire kingdom sink deep under the earth. Many years have passed, and now you take control of a traveler named Varik (Ares in the Japanese version). A young woman accuses him of killing her teacher, and in a desperate fight they both fall underground, to where the lost kingdom was buried.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940617T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Brandish (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Brandish (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cardangels (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Cardangels</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Asano family possessed a heirloom known as the Sorcerer's Trump. In the year 1984, however, it was stolen under mysterious circumstances. Seventeen years later, Sayaka, the young heiress of the Asano family, forms a group together with her friends Miki and Kyoko, and the three begin looking for the lost treasure. Heist after heist goes by unsuccessfully. Eventually, the girls organize a TV show, challenging dubious personalities to card games, hoping to find the Sorcerer's Trump in process. Cardangels is a card game in which the player takes the roles of the three friends, playing cards against young, attractive female opponents.</desc>
		<rating>0.2</rating>
		<releasedate>19941209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fujicom</developer>
		<publisher>Fujicom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cardangels (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cardangels (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chou Aniki (Japan) (FAAT, FACT).chd</path>
		<name>Chou Aniki</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The odd world in this shooter made for quite the conversation piece in its day. Players control either Idaten or Benten, celestial warriors out to bring an end to the tyrannical rule of the emperor of Planet Builder, who holds muscular prowess to be the supreme virtue of the universe. Aided by able-bodied muscle-head options Adon and Samson, they must battle to defeat the emperors army across five stages. Use the buttons to fire away and lay into the Builder forces! Power up your character and options with protein from defeated enemies to have them "bulk up" with a yell, and take their macho battle to the next level!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>NCS Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chou Aniki (Japan) (FAAT, FACT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chou Aniki (Japan) (FAAT, FACT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chou Jikuu Yousai Macross 2036 (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Chou Jikuu Yousai Macross 2036</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Macross 2036 is a horizontally scrolling shooter set in the universe of the Macross anime series. The player takes control of one of the series' minor characters, the female pilot Mylene Jenius, who navigates the space fighter Veritech, fighting against ships and robotic soldiers of the alien Zentradi race. The player-controlled space ship is equipped with a vulcan gun (which can be upgraded with power-ups) and bombs, which are released simultaneously. Another button controls a special weapon, which the player can purchase for points (awarded for defeating enemies) between stages.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920403T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NCS Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chou Jikuu Yousai Macross 2036 (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chou Jikuu Yousai Macross 2036 (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Far East of Eden - Tengai Makyou - Ziria (Japan) (Rev 7).chd</path>
		<name>Far East of Eden: Tengai Makyou - Ziria</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Long time ago, humans lived in a paradise, the Garden of Eden. But the brave and audacious members of the Fire Clan were banned from Eden, and had to seek shelter on the Earth. They built their own paradise - the land they later called Jipang. However, the evil demon lord Masakado wanted to destroy Jipang, and the Fire Clan fought and defeated him. Now, many years later, a young thief named Ziria learns that he is a descendant of the Fire Clan. He must now find the other members, and prevent the resurrection of Masakado by his followers. Loosely based on the Japanese folk tale of the ninja Jiraiya, Tengai Maky?: Ziria was the first role-playing game released on a CD ROM;</desc>
		<releasedate>19890630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Far East of Eden - Tengai Makyou - Ziria (Japan) (Rev 7).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Far East of Eden - Tengai Makyou - Ziria (Japan) (Rev 7).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Garou Densetsu Special (Japan) (FABT).chd</path>
		<name>Garou Densetsu Special</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fatal Fury Special is an improved version of SNK's 2D one-on-one fighter Fatal Fury 2. The objective is to win the tournament by defeating all other fighters including end boss Wolfgang Krauser. Fatal Fury Special features a fairly large selection of fighters that includes: The eight regular fighters from Fatal Fury 2: Terry Bogard, Andy Bogard, Joe Higashi, Kim Kaphwan, Jubei Yamada, Cheng Sinzan, Mai Shiranui and Big Bear. The four bosses from Fatal Fury 2: Billy Kane, Axel Hawk, Lawrence Blood and Wolfgang Krauser (this time they're all immediately playable). Three characters returning from the first Fatal Fury: Duck King, Tung Fu Rue and Geese Howard (the end boss from Fatal Fury).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Garou Densetsu Special (Japan) (FABT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Garou Densetsu Special (Japan) (FABT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goetzendiener (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Goetzendiener</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Demon God has abducted the princess Misa, intending to sacrifice her in order to restore his power. The king has sent an army to rescue his daughter, led by a knight who was carrying the legendary Sword of the Valiant. All the soldiers were killed by the minions of the Demon God, and only the brave knight survived. But as he delivered the fatal blow to the Demon God, he was himself mortally wounded by him. The princess Misa has no other choice but to take the Sword of the Valiant and to find a way to escape from the Demon God's dungeon, full of deadly traps and enemies...</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19941125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gainax Co., Ltd., Studio Alex, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Goetzendiener (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Goetzendiener (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius II - Gofer no Yabou (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Gradius II: Gofer no Yabou</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gradius II is a sequel to Gradius and Life Force, and is a horizontal space shooter composed of seven levels. Like in its predecessor, it is possible to collect power-ups from enemies and choose which type to use and when. This time, this system is enhanced with the option of choosing between four different power-up sequences, allowing the player to use different types of weapons against enemies. There is also the possibility to gain options, which are mysterious balls of fire that follows the player-controlled spaceship closely and mimic all its movements (including shots). While the player only could have two of them in the NES version of Gradius, it is now possible in all versions to have up to four.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19921218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gradius II - Gofer no Yabou (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gradius II - Gofer no Yabou (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hihou Densetsu - Chris no Bouken (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Hihou Densetsu: Chris no Bouken</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A scientist named Arnold Steiner researches the ancient civilization of Indios in Central America. However, following a breakthrough discovery, Steiner mysteriously disappears. His daughter Chris travels to Central America in search of her father, and steps into an intimidating world of monsters and conspiracies. Hih? Densetsu: Chris no B?ken is a platformer. Chris is armed with a dagger and cannot use any other weapons or gadgets to protect herself. However, the dagger can be upgraded by collecting colored orbs dropped by enemies. Depending on their combination, the dagger can be used as a long-ranged weapon, firing projectiles or acting as a boomerang. The protagonist's health is measured with hearts;</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Pack In Video</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hihou Densetsu - Chris no Bouken (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hihou Densetsu - Chris no Bouken (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mugen Senshi Valis - The Legend of a Fantasm Soldier (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Mugen Senshi Valis: The Legend of a Fantasm Soldier</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Yuko Ahso is an ordinary Japanese teenager with an ordinary life - until one day she is attacked by a monster on the street. Out of nowhere, a sword appears in her hands. She fights the monsters who have suddenly invaded the city, and is summoned to the parallel world known as Vecanti, which is ruled by a cruel tyrant named Rogles, whose actions disrupt the balance of the the worlds. Wielding the legendary Valis sword, Yuko must defeat Rogles and restore the balance. Valis has the same story and basic genre (platform action) as the original first game in the series; however, it is a different game with different locations, regular enemies and bosses, new cutscenes, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920319T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Riot</developer>
		<publisher>Telenet</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mugen Senshi Valis - The Legend of a Fantasm Soldier (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mugen Senshi Valis - The Legend of a Fantasm Soldier (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ookami-teki Monshou - Crest of Wolf (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ookami-teki Monshou: Crest of Wolf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The police is afraid to deal with a criminal organization known as the Dragon Zone. Street punks and leaders of Chinese crime syndicates dominate the area where its headquarters are supposedly located. The young fighter Hawk has his own score to settle with the Dragon Zone: they have kidnapped his girlfriend Candy. Together with his friend, the punk Tony, Hawk enters the dangerous districts and is determined to rescue his sweetheart and put an end to the organization. Riot Zone (Crest of Wolf in Japan) is a rather simple brawler in which the player can choose to control either Hawk or Tony. Hawk is faster, but doesn't hit quite as hard as Tony.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19930226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ookami-teki Monshou - Crest of Wolf (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ookami-teki Monshou - Crest of Wolf (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ryuuko no Ken (Japan) (En,Ja,Es) (FABT).chd</path>
		<name>Ryuuko no Ken</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Yuri Sakazaki has been kidnapped! Her big brother Ryo Sakazaki and Robert Garcia, his best friend, go search for her on the streets of South Town. As they go deeper and deeper they will find clues as to who ordered the kidnapping, the Sakazaki family's relation to the mob, and a person from their past. The gameplay differs from most fighting games. In this game, you have a Spirit meter. A Spirit meter is in the game and will decrease as you perform special moves. It can be recharged, but doing so leaves you open to attack. When your health is almost gone, you can perform a secret combination that will unleash a deadly attack on your opponent - provided you have a full Spirit meter.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19940326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ryuuko no Ken (Japan) (En,Ja,Es) (FABT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ryuuko no Ken (Japan) (En,Ja,Es) (FABT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spriggan Mark 2 - Re Terraform Project (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Spriggan Mark 2: Re Terraform Project</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once again get to pilot a mecha in a war between two opposing armies, in Spriggan mark 2: Re-Terraform Project, this time to decide the fate of a distant colony in outer space. As in the first game, other AI-controlled mechas join in the fight and even talk to the protagonist with full voice-overs to advance the plot. The color-coding weapon system of the original is gone, replaced with a standard collectible power-up system. No options are available to watch the player character's back, but it is possible to change the direction the player-controlled mecha faces, allowing the player to deal with threats from behind.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spriggan Mark 2 - Re Terraform Project (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spriggan Mark 2 - Re Terraform Project (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Summer Carnival '92 - Alzadick (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Summer Carnival '92: Alzadick</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After the legendary Recca on Famicom, Naxat Soft comes back, this time on PC Engine, for a new Summer Carnival. For those who don't know what the Summer Carnival is, it is the equivalent of the Hudson Caravan Stage. These contests allowed players from all over Japan to compete and win prizes. The principle is simple: play during a defined time in order to make the most points possible. In this case, what better than a good old shoot'em up! Alzadick makes full use of the principle of the timed game... So much so that one wonders why it could be marketed... Maybe only to allow players to train for the tournament.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920717T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naxat Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Naxat Soft</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Summer Carnival '92 - Alzadick (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Summer Carnival '92 - Alzadick (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Darius (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Darius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Darius is a port of Darius for the PC Engine CD-ROM, and the only attempt at an accurate port of the game for many years; it even uses recordings of music and sound effects straight from the arcade PCB! Its other claim to fame is the introduction of all 26 bosses from the original draft for Darius, some of which were earlier seen on promotional material.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Darius (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Darius (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Darius II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Darius II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Darius II is a updated Darius II released for the TurboGrafx-CD featuring an entirely new set of bosses, major changes to levels, and a fully arranged soundtrack including new songs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Darius II (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Darius II (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ane-san (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Ane-san</name>
		<desc>The two sisters, Ai and Yuuko, have taken different paths in life. Yuuko has been taken away by a mysterious gang. Ai is determined to save her from the clutches of crime. In a seemingly all-female city overrun by insane workers, biker gangs, and assorted criminals, Ai and her friends Chika and Makoto decide to work together in order to restore the world to normality again. Ane-san is what is commonly called beat-'em-up, i.e. a fighting game that allows limited movement through side-scrolling environment. The player can choose to control a variety of female fighters. In the beginning, only Ai, Chika, and Makoto are selectable. Ai is the all-around balanced character, Chika is fast and fragile, while Makoto is very strong, but slow.</desc>
		<image>./boxart/Ane-san (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ane-san (Japan).mp4</video>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC</developer>
		<publisher>NEC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220222T091525</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
