<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Nintendo 64</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev 1).v64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Banjo-Kazooie's fairy tale back story is reminiscent of Snow White's. A gnarled, ugly witch named Gruntilda asks her magical cauldron who is the fairest of them all. Of course, the pot's answer doesn't please the hag-- he singles out Banjo's sister, Tooty. When Tooty turns up missing, Banjo and his birdie buddy Kazooie set out to find her. The worlds in Banjo-Kazooie are gigantic, and chock full of crazy items to collect. Musical Notes, Puzzle Pieces ("Jiggies"), Mumbo Tokens, and Jinjoes are just some of the swag that Banjo must stuff in his backpack to complete his adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Banjo-Kazooie (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Tooie (USA).v64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Tooie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After two years under the rock, Gruntilda is finally set free from her death bed by her two sisters. As nothing but a skeleton, Grunty and her sisters plan a way of curing her looks by sucking the life out of the land so as to restore her body to its old self. On hearing this news, our two champs Banjo and Kazooie with the aid of Mumbo set out to stop the evil plan and seek revenge for the passing away of Bottles the mole.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Banjo-Tooie (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Banjo-Tooie (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blast Corps (U) (V1.1) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Blast Corps</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Get out of the way! A nuclear missile carrier is out of control on a one way-set path, and unless that path is cleared, it will explode as soon as it makes contact with anything, destroying the world. It is up to you to clear the path so that nothing gets in the way of the Carrier.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19970324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blast Corps (U) (V1.1) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blast Corps (U) (V1.1) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Body Harvest (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Body Harvest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 2050 AD, the earth has been taken over by horrible aliens, who long ago planted the humans there to later devour, and the last remains of humanity are working on a desperate plan - to send a genetically engineered soldier back into the past, and help hold back the invasion. But, as the final preparations for this Alpha Command operation are underway, alarms light up in the orbital control-station where the last humans hide the aliens are back for dinner.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Body Harvest (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Body Harvest (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Conker's Bad Fur Day</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Unlike every other Nintendo game ever made, Conker sees his first outing on the N64 with a mature audience in mind. But don't let the violence get in your way of playing this title, which is much like other Rare platformers including Banjo-Kazooie, with a twist. In this case, Conker has had one hell of a night, and when he wakes up not only does he have a huge hangover, but something just doesn't feel right. So it's up to Conker and his many skills to clean things up.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Rareware</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA).v64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>K. Rool has kidnapped the Kongs! Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Ponytail Twirl. Even rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your objective is to restore a run-down farm that you've inherited from your grandfather, who has died recently. In the village many people help you out on your long journey. During this time you can attend festivals, race in horse races, farm, tend to your livestock, add to your house, get married, or maybe even have a child. There are 5 beautiful women to be chosen from, each having their own jobs and personalities. At the end the player's parents come by and rate them after 2 and a half years of performance. The option then exists either to keep going or stop there. The real question is if you're up for the challenge.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pack In Video</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Harvest Moon 64 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Harvest Moon 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Force Gemini (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Jet Force Gemini</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Twins Juno and Vela, and their dog Lupus, are Jet Force Gemini, intergalactic police. Their mission? Stop the evil space bug, Mizar, from his goal of galactic conquest with his seemingly-infinite army of Drones. They'll have to stop along multiple planets along the way, and assisting King Jeff and rescuing his subjects, the Tribals.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jet Force Gemini (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jet Force Gemini (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Micro Machines 64 Turbo (USA).n64</path>
		<name>Micro Machines 64 Turbo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>With a quirky mix of toy car racers and sophisticated gameplay, Micro Machines 64 Turbo guarantees to be a refreshing addition to the stable of standard racing games. The wide variety of vehicles featured includes Formula 1 racers, speed boats, monster trucks, tanks, and ice cream trucks. Choose from 25 whimsical tracks, which run the gamut from a kitchen table to a chemistry lab, each including the appropriate props to match the d¿cor. Such detail rich touches keep this game interesting, even to the most jaded gamer. Belying the kiddie car appearance, the game requires you to plan strategically if you want to emerge the winner, making good use of the weapons at your disposal.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/Micro Machines 64 Turbo (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Micro Machines 64 Turbo (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pilotwings 64 (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Pilotwings 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>PilotWings 64 is the update to the original PilotWings for SNES. The gameplay is somewhere between a flight simulation and an action/arcade experience. Players start with a limited number of craft and earn access to other craft and bonuses upon successful completion of set criteria.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pilotwings 64 (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pilotwings 64 (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpaceStation Silicon Valley (USA).z64</path>
		<name>SpaceStation Silicon Valley</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Long ago, scientists created a living space station, full of animals. After its launch into space, the station vanished, never to be seen again.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/SpaceStation Silicon Valley (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SpaceStation Silicon Valley (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev 1).v64</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Lylat system has been invaded! Join Fox McCloud and his Star Fox team as they fight to save the galaxy from the clutches of the evil Andross. Travel to many different 3-D worlds. Battle the enemy in the air and on the ground and listen in as Fox McCloud interacts with a cast of characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Fox 64 (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 (USA).v64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3-D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive sound track, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis - Bowser, King of the Koopas!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario 64 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 (USA).v64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Eight familiar faces, including Mario, Bowser and Yoshi, on four progressively tougher four-track circuits. Wide curves and gentle banks mark the Mushroom Cup tracks. Your commute gets notably tougher on the Flower Cup, though. The player will have to dodge semis rumbling on Toad's Turnpike and bounding boulders on fogbound Choco Mountain! Star Cup tracks range from the icy surfaces of Sherbet Land to the lava lakes of Bowser's Castle. The true test of karting competence, though, comes on the four tracks in Special Cup.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Kart 64 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Kart 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev A).z64</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's an island takeover when the evil space wizard, Wizpig, discovers Tiger Island! After the islands prized racetracks become sealed up, Timber Tiger contacts his friend Diddy Kong to help him reclaim the racetracks and save the island before his parents return. Along for the ride are the Kremling spy Krunch, Bumper Badger, Banjo (prior to meeting Kazooie in Banjo-Kazooie), pre-sweary Conker, Tiptup Turtle, and Pipsy Mouse.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19971124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev A).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Diddy Kong Racing (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Kirby 64: The Crystal Shards</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dart past enemies, soar the skies and swim the depths of the ocean as Kirby takes on Dark Matter in an all-new adventure. Inhale, exhale and swallow your enemies, then copy and combine their abilities and use them as your own! Team up with familiar friends and foes - like Waddle Dee and King Dedede - as you travel through dreamy worlds in search of the lost Crystal Shards.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby 64 - The Crystal Shards (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocket - Robot on Wheels (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Rocket: Robot on Wheels</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Whoopie World, the greatest amusement park ever, is ready to open, but second-banana park mascot, Jojo the Raccoon, has gone nuts. He's taken over the park! Can Rocket, the most advanced amusement park robot ever, save the day? Rocket's a one wheel wonder with double-jump booster rockets and 7 cool cars to drive. He's got a tractor beam that can pick up almost anything, swing from ledges, trees, even toss freeze &amp; smash objects. Rocket's got the moves &amp; he's got the tools to make things right.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sucker Punch Productions</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA) (Rev 1).v64</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Rogue Squadron</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fly against the evil Empire! As Luke Skywalker, co-founder of the Rebel Alliance's elite Rogue Squadron, you must combat the evil Galactic Empire! Engage in intense, fast-paced planetary air-to-ground and air-to-air missions - dogfights, search and destroy, reconnaissance, bombing runs, rescue assignments and more! Pilot X-wings, Y-wings, A-wings, V-wings and Snowspeeders with powerful weapons in over 15 missions battling TIE fighters, TIE bombers, Imperial shuttles, AT-AT walkers, AT-STs and other challenging foes.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Rogue Squadron (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snowboard Kids (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Snowboard Kids</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A racing game where you control one of five cutesy snowboarders competing against each other. Being a snowboarding game, each track is a downhill slalom with a ski lift at the bottom which takes you back to the start for however many laps a track has.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Snowboard Kids (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Snowboard Kids (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 (USA) (Rev A).z64</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ready or not, the terror of Resident Evil 2 is here. In chapter one, the case of the disastrous T-virus outbreak--a mutagenic toxin designed for biological weapons--was eventually closed but the experiments were far from over. Control the destiny of Leon Kennedy or Claire Redfield as their nightmare begins when a biotech terror runs rampant in Raccoon City. Relentless zombies and hideous monsters are all out for a taste of your blood. If the suspense doesn't kill you, something else will.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Resident Evil 2 (USA) (Rev A).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Resident Evil 2 (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Superstar Soccer 2000 (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>International Superstar Soccer 2000</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The undisputed king of football returns, experience the new Career Mode, bring youngsters through the ranks to create individual star players. Smoother animations and gameplay. ISS 2000 is the choice of champions and nothing gets as close to the beautiful game.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCEO</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/International Superstar Soccer 2000 (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/International Superstar Soccer 2000 (USA) (En,Es) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario and a range of well known Nintendo characters, including Yoshi, Bowser, Luigi, and Wario return for some more party action. The second edition includes 5 new boards, each with a specific theme, such as Space Land, Western Land, Horror Land, and Mystery Land. Each board includes unique attributes in relation to the theme, but the main goal is the same: complete the board game over a certain amount of moves and be the player to have the most coins and/or stars at the end.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Party 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Party 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Choose your favourite Nintendo character and take to the world of tennis. Game types include ring shot (where you must shoot the ball through golden hoops that are suspended above the play area, gaining bonus points as you play), bomb tennis (simply put Tennis with Bombs) and Piranha Challenge (much like the tennis machines which chuck balls at you, but in this case they are replaced with Piranha plants). Of course, there is your normal tournament mode, with up to 4 players in on the action, and some crazy arenas, especially Bowser's Castle, which is suspended above a lava pit.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Tennis (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Tennis (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey's Speedway USA (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Disney's Mickey's Speedway USA</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Weasels have kidnapped Pluto while he was wearing his diamond collar! All that was left of him was a ransom note showing the Weasels driving him away in a van. Mickey rounds up all of his friends (and even Pete wants to get in on the action!), and Professor Von Drake soups up their race cars so that they can catch up with the Weasels as they go on a cross-country tour of the United States. The Weasels have also stolen four parts of the Professor's top-secret racer, and hidden them in four of the tracks. Once players find all these pieces, they can catch up with the Weasels in the final showdown.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Rareware</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mickey's Speedway USA (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mickey's Speedway USA (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Snap (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Pokémon Snap</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Professor has asked you to capture the Wild Pokemon of Pokémon island on film! Tour the island in your ZERO-ONE vehicle and snap pictures of Pokémon in their natural habitat. Wild Pokémon are often camera-shy, so you'll have to use special items to bring them out in the open. Only the best shots will do for the Professor's Pokémon Report, so sharpen your photography skills and get ready to SNAP!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon Snap (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon Snap (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet Legends (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Gauntlet Legends</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sumner's brother Garm releases Skorne from the Underworld. Sumner has summoned the four mighty heroes (a warrior, a valkyrie, a wizard, and an archer) to stop Skorne from taking over the land. They must travel to the four realms of the land and free them from Skorne's four guardians. Once the guardians are destroyed, their keys unlock a desecrated temple, where the heroes battle Skorne. After facing defeat, however, Skorne flees back to the Underworld. The heroes must then find the 13 runestones that will open the Underworld, where they face Skorne again and destroy him for good.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gauntlet Legends (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gauntlet Legends (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev 1).v64</path>
		<name>WWF No Mercy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The last wrestling title made by the team of THQ and AKI allows players to compete for 7 different WWF Titles with each belt getting its own unique story. Stories can be replayed, allowing players to defend their title in a storyline. Upon successful completion of a story mode, players will unlock the title they were competing for in Exhibition mode where titles can be won and defended as the players see fit.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AKI Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WWF No Mercy (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros. (USA).v64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Smash Brothers takes familiar Nintendo characters such as Mario, Kirby and Donkey Kong, and puts them into battle! There are 8 fully-interactive landscapes, with one for each character and noticeable links to their games. Controls are analogue-based, with different moves executed depending on the direction and how firmly the stick is pressed. Items like baseball bats, Bob-ombs, and healing items drop into the arenas at random, aiding any nearby characters than can make use of them. The game uses a fixed viewpoint which scrolls, although characters are rendered in 3D.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Smash Bros. (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Smash Bros. (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1080 TenEighty Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).n64</path>
		<name>1080° TenEighty Snowboarding</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>1080° Snowboarding is a snowboard racing game. The player will find 6 downhill slopes and a half-pipe as courses, several characters to choose from, and be able to perform more than 25 tricks. After choosing a character and a board among the available eight, the player can compete in a variety of events.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/1080 TenEighty Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1080 TenEighty Snowboarding (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero X (USA).v64</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Famed SNES racer F-Zero got this N64 update. Gameplay remains essentially unchanged, race in a futuristic racing tournament on tracks levitated miles up in the air, against a selection of devious opponents.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/F-Zero X (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F-Zero X (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye 007 (USA).v64</path>
		<name>GoldenEye 007</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The name is Bond. James Bond. The famous hero of Ian Fleming's novels returns in this first-person shooter, which is based on the movie of the same name. Agent 007 and his friend Alec Trevalyan (a.k.a. Agent 006) were sent to Soviet Union on a secret mission. But everything goes wrong, James Bond barely escapes, and his friend is presumed dead.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/GoldenEye 007 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/GoldenEye 007 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev 1).v64</path>
		<name>Perfect Dark</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Joanna Dark is an agent for the Carrington Institute, a secret organization funded by anonymous sources and dedicated to protecting the world. Through their highly trained operatives and special devices (gadgets), Carrington keeps an eye on terrorists, world powers, and strange happenings. The speed in which the dataDyne corporation has established itself through the development of new technologies is starting to worry the institute. So when Carrington receives a message from Dr. Caroll, a scientist wishing to escape dataDyne, they send their best agent, Joanna, to infiltrate the company headquarters.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Perfect Dark (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wave Race 64 (USA) (Rev A).z64</path>
		<name>Wave Race 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wave Race 64 is sure to provide some of the most exciting racing you've ever experienced. Feel the pounding and crashing of the waves as you accelerate into straight-aways, whip around the marker buoys and go airborne on the jump ramps. Don't race alone - challenge a friend! Take control in three different modes of play - Championship, Time Trials and Stunt Mode. Nine challenging courses set in exotic locales - race conditions change and the wave action responds to the way both you and your opponents race!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wave Race 64 (USA) (Rev A).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wave Race 64 (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WCW-nWo Revenge (USA).n64</path>
		<name>WCW/nWo Revenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>WCW/nWo Revenge is the much anticipated sequel to THQ's smash "WCW Vs NWO: World Tour". With greatly improved graphics, animation, roster, control and much anticipated 40 man 'battle royal', Revenge is a definite step up over it's predecessor. Take control of one of 50 WCW wrestlers (and 10+ fictional wrestlers) such as Sting or Hollywood Hogan and battle through for any of the 5 different title belts with full statistical tracking of wins/losses/draws and new replay mode you can gloat in your victory or powerful move over and over again.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik</developer>
		<publisher>Asmik</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/WCW-nWo Revenge (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WCW-nWo Revenge (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beetle Adventure Racing! (USA) (En,Fr,De).z64</path>
		<name>Beetle Adventure Racing!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take control of a collection of the latest Volkswagen Beetle "2.0" models (from street type to off-road designs) and race across varying road types that will test your speed and endurance (each track taking up to 4 minutes to complete from one end to another). Find shortcuts or use nitro boosts to get to the end first in order to move on to the next track. If the computer AI is to easy for you, battle against a friend in two player race mode. Up to 4 people can also play a special Battle Mode challenge, with added abilities including weapons (from mines and rockets to magical elements) while collecting the flag and finding the exit.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradigm Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Beetle Adventure Racing! (USA) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Beetle Adventure Racing! (USA) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Doom 64 (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Doom 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>DOOM 64 picks up where all the other DOOM games left off. After tearing through space, hell, and wherever else in the previous games, the Space Marine thought that the threat of the demons was finally past. Of course, one survived, and it is currently reanimating all of the fallen monsters in a last-ditch attempt to revitalize their evil mission. The player's task is to finally rid the universe of all the crazy hellions, from the dead guy with the pistol to the rocket-spewing Cyberdemon.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Doom 64 (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Doom 64 (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Superstar Soccer 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>International Superstar Soccer 64</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>ISS64 offers all of the style and grace you expect in a game of Soccer, the World Game. There are six game modes to play, including the usual 1-4 player exhibition modes and training. International Cup has you competing against a range of teams from around the world for the International Cup; World League is a series of 70 matches against every team from around the world. You can also play a penalty shoot-out competition with up to 4 players, or attempt to complete certain scenario games (where each game is setup with a specific goal, for example scoring a goal within a givin time limit, or stoping the opposing team from scoring, etc.)</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCEO</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/International Superstar Soccer 64 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/International Superstar Soccer 64 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Golf (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Golf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Forget buying expensive golf gear--Mario brings the game to you. Mario Golf features four complete 18-hole courses, 11 golfers, and precise play control. Create your own golfer and build up his or her experience and skill levels by competing in various tournaments and head-to-head matches. The more you play, the stronger and more accurate your golfer becomes. There are many different modes of play in Mario Golf, including a wide variety of minigames designed to challenge even the most level-headed swingers.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990726T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Golf (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Golf (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You know Mario can jump. You know he can kick Bowser's tail from here to the moon, but we bet you didn't realize that Mario is the biggest party animal on the face of the Earth. Nintendo is throwing the most insane bash to ever hit the N64, and you're invited. For the first time, you'll catch a glimpse of how Mario celebrates all of the victories he's had over the years. Mario Party is unlike any other game for the N64, and it just might be the best party game to ever hit the system. Mario Party is designed for 1 to 4 players, but it's not really a party unless you're playing with your pals. The festivities are based on a board game format, right down to the fact that players must roll a die to determine how many spaces to move.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Party (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Party (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 3 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The series continues with a set of 70 new mini-games. Play in the new single-player Story mode, or bring in some friends for Party mode. Four player games and a new two player mode are also available for play. In Battle Royale mode (four player), you race around different boards to earn the most stars and coins. At the end of each round, you face it off in one of the mini-games, which can be chicken chases, snowball fights, or various other competitions. Duel mode allows play between just two people. You still race around the board, but mini-games are only played when you land on a specific square. Another play change is the addition of another character for your team, allowing tag team-style action in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010507T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Party 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Party 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Ogre Battle 64: Person of Lordly Caliber</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Holy Lodis Empire is planning the domination of the entire continent of Zeteginia! It is up to you to raise the flag of revolution and rid the land of the Lodis threat. Make decisions in real-time and take control of numerous characters to prove victorious on the battlefield and regain freedom for all people!</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20001007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario pals around in an all-new action adventure! Mario's back in his first adventure since Super Mario 64, and this time, Bowser's bent on preventing a storybook ending. When Princess Peach is kidnapped, Mario plots to rescue the seven Star Spirits and rid the Mushroom Kingdom of Koopa's cruel cohorts. As he travels from the tropical jungles of Lavalava Island to the frosty heights of Shiver Mountain, he'll meet up with seven all-new companions... and he'll need help from each one or there'll be no happily ever after.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Paper Mario (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Paper Mario (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Pokémon Stadium 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hundreds of Pokémon in Three-mendous 3-D! What's sweeter than victory in a Pokémon battle! Victory in a 3-D arena on the N64?! Set your strategy and stand back while your Pokémon battle it out. You can even set the Pokémon you've trained--fully rendered in 3-D and ready for battle!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2 - The Great Escape (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).z64</path>
		<name>Rayman 2: The Great Escape</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Enter a massive 3-D action adventure of amazing beauty and challenge. The pirate terror has enslaved the world and only Rayman's speed, agility, and magical powers can save all. Race and battle across 45 intricately designed areas - rainforests, jungles, narrow canyon passes, even into the mighty pirate ship itself.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rayman 2 - The Great Escape (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rayman 2 - The Great Escape (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./San Francisco Rush 2049 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>San Francisco Rush 2049</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Unlike the previous San Francisco Rush titles, this racing game is set in the future. The same rules apply though, get to the finish before everyone else while avoiding massive crashes and taking as many shortcuts as possible. Along with the usual race style, you now have the ability to fly, allowing you even more speed, stunts and shortcuts to the finish line. While the tracks themselves include moving ramps and switches to other shortcuts. Modes include time trials, stunt mode including unique track designs to get the most out of your stunts, and a four player 'Battlematch' mode that adds weapons to the action.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/San Francisco Rush 2049 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/San Francisco Rush 2049 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I: Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Join Jedi-to-be Anakin Skywalker in the Star Wars race of your life! Relive all the thrills and excitement of the Podracer sequence from Star Wars: Episode I. Hang on tight - with afterburners on, Podracers max out at a simulated 600 mph! Race in furious competition against more than 21 opponents! Take on over 21 tracks in 8 unique worlds. Avoid hazards such as methane lakes, meteor showers and Tusken Raiders! Featuring spectacular 3D environments!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19990519T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater is a skateboarding simulation in which you control a famous skate star around 3D environments. Each game area contains a plethora of objects like ramps, rails, and half-pipes which can be used to perform tricks. Each trick you perform earns you more points for your score. The game is divided into two types of levels. In the first, you skate around locations like a mall, a city street, or a warehouse. In each of these areas, there are 5 goals for the you to complete. Some goals involve obtaining a high score, others smashing objects, and some collecting objects. For every goal you complete, you earn a video tape. By collecting enough video tapes, you unlock levels and skateboards for you to use.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge Of Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the award winning PSX and N64 title, Tony Hawk 2 adds heaps of new tricks, as well as those from the original, and a complete roster of all the greatest skaters worldwide. Fly through some of the greatest skate parks in the world, or create your own, and share them with your mates. You can also create your own skater, with a choice of clothing and official skateboards. Improved graphics and a choice of alternative or hip-hop music add to the endless options and full on action.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge Of Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tony Hawk returns with an all new line-up of skaters, an all new line-up of parks to crash through, and a whole new level of graphics. The line-up of street and vert riders include Elissa Steamer, Jamie Thomas, Steve Caballero, Rune Glifberg, Geoff Rowley, Andrew Reynolds, Rodney Mullen, Eric Koston, Chad Muska, Bucky Lasek and Bam Margera from MTV's Jackass (and Tony Hawk, of course). The create a skater mode returns, allowing for even further levels of options for your character, like adding glasses and tatoos to changing the colour of the knee and elbow pads or even the hair.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20020820T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Edge Of Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok 2 - Seeds of Evil (USA) (Rev 1).z64</path>
		<name>Turok 2: Seeds of Evil</name>
		<sortname>Turok 2</sortname>
		<desc>Only evil this dark could bring him back. Only a game this big can do him justice. Turok 2: Seeds of Evil! Pick off distant enemies with deadly sniper weapons, and enjoy ferocious multi-player deathmatches!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Turok 2 - Seeds of Evil (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Turok 2 - Seeds of Evil (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF WrestleMania 2000 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>WWF WrestleMania 2000</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>WWF Wrestlemania 2000 is THQ's first WWF licenced game after making two previous WCW titles. Wrestlemania 2K picks up where WCW/NWO Revenge left off. The graphics are by far superior as well is the animation. Wrestlemania 2K adds three highly sort after features: Cage match, custom entrances and Create A Wrestler feature. Wrestlemania 2K features more than 50 real WWF stars as well as the option for 16 custom wrestlers. All the wrestlers come with their real-life theme music, entrance videos (made into slide shows) and entrance performances.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AKI Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/WWF WrestleMania 2000 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WWF WrestleMania 2000 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok - Rage Wars (U) (V1.1) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Turok: Rage Wars</name>
		<sortname>Turok 1</sortname>
		<desc>Since time began, Turok has maintained the balance between good and evil with the Light Burden. A vessel that holds the power of creation. Now, fierce wars are fought for control. You must prove yourself worthy to wield the Light Burden. You must relive the challenge of your ancestors and survive the RAGE WARS! Featuring brutal heart-pounding deathmatches, lethal weapons with unimaginable power, and 8 savage game modes, including co-op mission-based gameplay, Team Bloodlust, Frag Tag and more!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Turok - Rage Wars (U) (V1.1) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Turok - Rage Wars (U) (V1.1) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (U) [!].z64</path>
		<name>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion</name>
		<sortname>Turok 3</sortname>
		<desc>Older than time itself, a savage cosmic entity called Oblivion exists only to devour everything in its path. Two new Turok warriors, Danielle and Joseph Fireseed must face this evil. The heritage of Turok and all humankind depends on them. Join the legacy. Over 24 upgradable weapons to battle 40 new and original enemies! Intense multiplayer action - over 8 modes and 48 maps!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (U) [!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (U) [!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev 2).v64</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: Ocorina of Time, The</name>
		<sortname>Legend of Zelda 1</sortname>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule. He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce. As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf's evil schemes. Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora's Domain.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev 2).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA) (Rev 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).v64</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask, The</name>
		<sortname>Legend of Zelda 2</sortname>
		<desc>Thrown into a parallel world by the mischievous actions of a possessed Skull Kid, Link finds a land in grave danger. The dark power of a relic called Majora's Mask has wreaked havoc on the citizens of Termina, but their most urgent problem is a suicidal moon crashing toward the world. Link has only 72 hours to find a way to stop its descent.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tsumi to Batsu - Hoshi no Keishousha (Japan).z64</path>
		<name>Sin And Punishment</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rogue mutants, named Lufian were originally bred to manage food production in the overpopulated and resource scarce Earth, but they've revolted against their human masters. The army has been soundly defeated, and now it's up to two teenage heroes, 14-year-old Saki Amamiya and 15-year-old Airan Jo to save the day. As the story advances, the heroes find out the Lufian's true intention and that the mutants could jeopardize the future of Earth!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tsumi to Batsu - Hoshi no Keishousha (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tsumi to Batsu - Hoshi no Keishousha (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>