<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>NES</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Gear</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Near the end of the 20th century, a small fortified nation named Outer Heaven (founded by a mysterious war hero whose name and identity are shrouded in secrecy) is threatening the nations of the "West" with the development of a new prototype weapon named Metal Gear, a walking tank which is capable of launching nuclear warheads from anywhere on the globe. As FOX-HOUND's (an elite black ops unit) newest recruit, going by the codename of Solid Snake, your mission is to infiltrate Outer Heaven and rescue your missing comrade, Grey Fox.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metal Gear (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metal Gear (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Storm (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Storm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Metal Storm is an action game in which the player takes control of the giant mecha M-308 Gunner in order to put a stop to a malfunctioning computer menace. To save it from becoming another generic action game, innovation is shown through fast paced gameplay and the "gravity flip" ability, which enables the character to freely switch between moving along the floor or ceiling. While the game is only seven levels long, the difficulty ramps up quickly, so mastery of the gravity technique and memorization of the levels become absolute necessities for survival.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19910202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tamtex</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metal Storm (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metal Storm (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ninja Gaiden begins with a cinematic animation in which 2 ninjas duel to the death; one goes down. It is revealed that the doomed ninja is the father of Ryu Hayabusa. When Ryu learns of this, he embarks on a quest to find out who killed his father and why. This quest takes him to America to find an archaeologist with whom Ryu's father was working. From there, Ryu becomes embroiled in an evil, supernatural conspiracy involving a villain named Jaquio who has plans to use an ancient castle and some relics to unleash a terrifying evil upon the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ninja Gaiden (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ninja Gaiden (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./North and South (USA).zip</path>
		<name>North and South</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the Belgian comic book, "Les Tuniques Bleues", this strategy game allows you to replay the American Civil War from both the North and the South sides. In the strategy part of the game, you can move your troops on a map of the US. If two opposing armies enter the same state, the battle is played out in an action sequence. Additional action sequences must be accomplished when capturing an enemy fort or train.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/North and South (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/North and South (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pipe Dream (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pipe Dream</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Each level of this abstract puzzler challenges the player to set up a network of pipes to allow an unspecified substance known as 'flooz' to flow through as many of those as possible. The pieces are offered in random order, and there are seven different types - straight lines going horizontally or vertically, corners rotating in each of the four directions, and cross-over pieces which carry the flooz straight across horizontally and vertically.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Assembly Line, The</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet Proof Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pipe Dream (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pipe Dream (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rygar (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Rygar</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A hero has arrived to defeat the forces of evil in the land of Argool, and you are this hero. Do you have what it takes? This game was one of the first adventures to hit the NES and the remarkable aspect on top of this was the multiple viewpoints the games offers. When you are in an action zone, the game is a side-scrolling action game; however, then you are travelling between zones, the game takes on an overhead view that can also lead to combat situations.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rygar (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rygar (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shatterhand (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shatterhand</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Shatterhand is an action game with eight-direction scrolling. You control Shatterhand in his quest to find and defeat General Grover, leader of the Metal Command. Through the game you’ll encounter all kinds of mechanical and biomechanical creatures. Shatterhand’s primary weapon is his cybernetic fists and therefore most enemies must be defeated by punching them. Additional help can be given from any of the eight hovering satellite robots, each of which has it’s own weapon that fires automatically when Shatterhand throws a punch.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shatterhand (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shatterhand (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Dodge Ball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Dodge Ball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This ain't elementary school and it sure as heck ain't gym class. This is Super Dodge Ball. Control your team of six players to pummel the opposing team into submission using only the ball and your team's unique skills. Each player has his own special attacks and each team has their own unique attributes. Play the World Cup mode and take on teams from around the world to claim the championship. You play as the star USA team and must work your way through teams from countries such as England, Iceland, Japan, and more to finally take on the current ruling world champions, the Soviet Union.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Million</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Dodge Ball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Dodge Ball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tecmo Bowl (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Bowl</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The most popular American football game to hit the NES console, Tecmo Bowl pits the player vs. the computer in 11 game single-elimination playoff action, or you can go head-to-head with a human opponent in action or coach mode. There are 12 teams of real NFL players (circa 1988) to choose from, but don't look for official NFL team logos or mascots like Bears or Dolphins--Tecmo Bowl has the NFLPA but not the NFL license.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tecmo Bowl (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tecmo Bowl (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>With April O'Neil held hostage by The Shredder's thugs, Bebop and Rocksteady, once again, it's up to the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles to come to her rescue! Play as all four of the turtle heroes, rescue April, and then rescue your sensei Splinter from Mecha-Turtles clutches than go after The Shredder deep in the bowels of The Technodrome itself.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19890602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II - The Arcade Game (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II: The Arcade Game</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>April O'Neil, the reporter friend of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, is kidnapped by the villainous Shredder and his two goons, Bebop and Rocksteady. The four ninja turtles: Raphael, Michelangelo, Donatello and Leonardo fight their way through hordes of Foot Soldiers in order to rescue April. They battle familiar foes such as the mad scientist Baxter Stockman, General Traag from Dimension X and the evil alien brain Krang, up to the final showdown with Shredder himself.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19901202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II - The Arcade Game (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II - The Arcade Game (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Willow (USA).zip</path>
		<name>W·I·L·L·O·W</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>W·I·L·L·O·W is an action RPG based on the movie with the same name. The player assumes the role of Willow, the chosen one who must restore human form to the benevolent sorceress Fin Raziel and destroy the evil sorceress, Bavmorda. While the game follows the movie's plot somewhat most of the time, it also expands on it and introduces characters, races and enemies not found in the movie. Gameplay is similar to other action RPGs and The Legend of Zelda. Willow is seen from a top down perspective and all enemies are visible on screen. Slaying enemies will give Willow experience points, which will eventually lead to him increasing his stats automatically.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Willow (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Willow (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Track &amp; Field (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Track &amp; Field</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Track &amp; Field is a sports game that allows the player to have an experience based around the Summer Olympic Games. It is based on an arcade game of the same name. Events include 100 meter dash, hammer throw, the long jump and the 110 meter hurdles. The MSX version replaces the hurdles with a 400 meter dash.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Track &amp; Field (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Track &amp; Field (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pro Wrestling (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Pro Wrestling</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pro Wrestling is an action wrestling game for one or two players. By using different controller combinations you can perform a wide variety of moves to try and beat your opponent in a 5 minute match. In the one player version, you need to fight your way to first place (but the game will be over if you fall below 6th place). There are seven different wrestlers to fight before you can be declared the Video Wrestling Association champion!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19870301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pro Wrestling (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pro Wrestling (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spy vs Spy (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Spy vs Spy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>M.A.D. magazine’s comic strip of the same name comes to life in this game which was designed for one or two players. The innovative split-screen shows both spies at the same time. Play with a friend or against the machine. The black crow and the white crow are out to beat each other before the time bell rings. Find the needed objects by digging through drawers, closets and furniture in the house. Foil your opponent by setting creative booby traps in the various rooms (a bomb in a dresser drawer, for instance). Fights ensue when both spies enter the same room.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19860426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>First Star Software</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spy vs Spy (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spy vs Spy (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III - The Manhattan Project (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III: The Manhattan Project</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This was the last side-scrolling Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles game for NES. It followed the highly acclaimed Turtles II over a year later and, unlike its predecessor, doesn't have an Arcade counterpart. The third game in the series is basically the same as the second. The story and the stages are different, of course, but it doesn't really matter. Choose your favourite turtle and kill as many Foot Clan soldiers as you can, fight the bosses and reach Shredder in a Double Dragon-styled game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III - The Manhattan Project (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles III - The Manhattan Project (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zanac (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Zanac</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Zanac is a 2D shoot them up game. You are flying fighter model Zanac, a ship built by 256 Riot Fleet as man's last hope against total annihilation. On board are special weapons to help you blast your way through twelve screens of enemy creatures and destroy the system's home base. Zanac is divided into 12 "areas", which look like planets. The various locations range from deserts to jungles and from oceans to industrial zones, featuring many different types of enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19871201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pony Canyon</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zanac (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zanac (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! (Japan, USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mike Tyson's Punch-Out is one of the most popular and biggest selling video games of all time. Step into the ring as Little Mac, a 17-year-old fighter from the Bronx, ranked number three in the minor circuit. Your goal is to work your way up through the rankings so that you can challenge Mike Tyson, Kid Dynamite, in a dream fight.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19871115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! (Japan, USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!! (Japan, USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightshade (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nightshade</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sutekh has gotten rid of local superhero Vortex, and now Metro City is in the hands of crime. You are Nightshade - the superhero that nobody knows - and your goal is to stop the evil doers, including main villain Sutekh. Nightshade is a humorous adventure game, with a menu that allows the protagonist to perform various actions, such as look, take, talk, etc. Also included are some one-on-one fight scenes, which differ from the standard controls and in which Nightshade is able to jump, kick, punch and duck.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nightshade (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nightshade (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden II - The Dark Sword of Chaos (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden II: The Dark Sword of Chaos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A year after the events of the original Ninja Gaiden, a new villain named Ashtar receives word of Jaquio's defeat. Ashtar uses this opportunity to hatch a new plan to plunge the world into darkness. The ninja, Ryu Hayabusa, hits the trail to destroy all.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19900501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ninja Gaiden II - The Dark Sword of Chaos (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ninja Gaiden II - The Dark Sword of Chaos (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pirates! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pirates!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take on the life of a buccaneer in the golden age of Caribbean Piracy! This game lets you choose from 6 different "ages" (for example, "The Silver Empire" from 1560-1600, "War For Profit" from 1640-1660, etc.), one of 4 nationalities (English, French, Dutch, Spanish), 4 difficulty levels, and one of 5 special abilities.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultra Games</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pirates! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pirates! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Punch-Out!! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Punch-Out!!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>"Punch-Out!! featuring Mr. Dream" is the reedition of the previous version "Mike Tyson's Punch-Out!!". Contrary to popular belief, Tyson was not removed because of his rape conviction (which did not occur until a year after the changeover), but because his contract expired. Since he had lost the title to James "Buster" Douglas by that point.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Punch-Out!! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Punch-Out!! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R.C. Pro-Am (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>R.C. Pro-Am</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Guide your radio controlled car to victory in this racing game. You have to beat your 3 opponents on 32 tracks while avoiding obstacles like water and oil puddles and collecting bonus items like better engines and tires. You can also collect a variety of weapons to blast your opponents out of the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/R.C. Pro-Am (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R.C. Pro-Am (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rad Racer (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rad Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rad Racer is an arcade style 3-D racing game. The object of the game is to race to the goal within the given time limit. Along each course are several checkpoints which will increase the amount of time you have to reach the final destination. There are eight different stages with increasingly difficult roads, changing weather conditions, and a variety of opponents who tend to get in the way. Included with the game is an optional pair of red-blue 3-D glasses which can be used to give the game an even more 3-D appearance.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19871001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rad Racer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rad Racer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Islands (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rainbow Islands</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sequel to Bubble Bobble, Rainbow Islands sees Bub and Bob (in 2 player mode), who are now curiously small boys rather than dinosaurs, attempting to rid the Rainbow Islands of bad guys. Using the power to cast rainbows, trapping anything underneath, the boys must ascend vertically 4 levels each island, with a big, bad boss at the end of each. By trapping beasts under your rainbows, then jumping on them to break them you can collect seven different colored gems, and there are also power-ups for extra speed and rainbows.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rainbow Islands (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rainbow Islands (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./River City Ransom (USA).zip</path>
		<name>River City Ransom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil Slick has kidnapped Ryan's girlfriend and taken over the high school. The player is cast as either Ryan or Alex (second player) and has to fight his way through River City's merciless gangs before confronting Slick and freeing his girl. River City Ransom is a side-scrolling beat-em-up similar to Double Dragon. The player, or players, travel through the locations of River City, encountering various gangs along the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/River City Ransom (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/River City Ransom (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rockin' Kats (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rockin' Kats</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Willy is a young jazz cat who goes by the name of "The Rockin' Kat". His girlfriend, Jill, was kidnapped by Mugsy, the local crime boss. In this side scrolling game, you must help Rockin' Kat Willy to save his girlfriend through 7 stages. Each stage is a TV show broadcast through different channels of a TV set, and you must thus choose which channel you want to play. Through the channels Willy it will be sent to different themed shows such as western movies, gangster movies, etc, as well as some bonus channels.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19921119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rockin' Kats (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rockin' Kats (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snake Rattle n Roll (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Snake, Rattle 'n Roll</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Snake, Rattle 'n Roll is an isometric 3D platformer. The object of each level is to eat as many Nibbley Pibblies (round creatures of various colours) as possible to make your snake heavy. Once it's heavy enough, you must stand on the scales in the level, and if you're heavy enough, the door will open and you can make your way to the exit.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Snake Rattle n Roll (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Snake Rattle n Roll (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Snow Brothers (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Snow Brothers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Nick and Tom are two Princes living the dream with two beautiful princesses. When suddenly the evil King Scorch freezes Prince Nick and Tom and kidnaps the Princesses. Now Nick and Tom find themselves with abilities dealing with snow and ice. These two Snow Brothers will need to hunt down the evil King Scorch and rescue the princesses.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toaplan</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Snow Brothers (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Snow Brothers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super C (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super C</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The alien Red Falcon is back, and planning on taking over the planet Earth. Now it's up to Scorpion and Mad Dog to battle through five levels and save the planet. Based on the arcade game, Super C is the sequel to Contra. Gameplay is a combination of side scrolling/platform and top down view. There is a wide variety of enemies to defeat, starting with earthly locations, and progressing to more alien. To help out, weapon upgrades can be found as the game progresses. Two players can play simultaneously, or one player can attempt to take on Red Falcon himself.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super C (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super C (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Turrican (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Super Turrican</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Like other entries in the series, Super Turrican for the NES is a side-scrolling platformer in which players explore large levels filled with enemies items and secret areas. Three different, upgradable weapons are available: multiple (spreadshot), laser and rebound. Holding down the fire button activates a rotatable laser that is useful for discovering hidden power-up capsules. Despite carrying the same name as one of its big brothers, Super Turrican for the NES is based on Turrican and Turrican II.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rainbow Arts (Softgold)</developer>
		<publisher>Imagineer</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Turrican (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Turrican (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris (USA) (Tengen) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris: The Soviet Mind Game</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Almost everyone agrees that Tengen's version of the game was far superior to Nintendo's, even including a two-player mode which Nintendo's version sorely lacked. Today, the game known as Tengen Tetris is a rare title to have in your collection, but it's a worthwhile play. After all, Tetris is one of the classic games not only on the NES, but of all-time.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tetris (USA) (Tengen) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tetris (USA) (Tengen) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bugs Bunny Birthday Blowout, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Bugs Bunny Birthday Blowout</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Bugs Bunny Birthday Blowout takes place as Bugs is invited to his 50th birthday. Because some of the other Warner Bros. toons weren't invited (including Wile E. Coyote), they decided to stop Bugs from going to this party. A Warner Bros licensed game.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19900902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bugs Bunny Birthday Blowout, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bugs Bunny Birthday Blowout, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vice - Project Doom (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Vice: Project Doom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Quinn Hart and his partner, Detective Reese of the VICE squad both work to stop the trafficking of illegal substances. But something new has appeared on the scene, a neon gel with great addictive properties. During investigations as to the origin of the gel, Reese mysteriously disappears and leaves Hart without a lead. Time passes and Hart becomes romantically involved with his new partner, Christy, as he continues trying to track down the gel. But Hart is about to get a brand new lead Vice.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vice - Project Doom (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vice - Project Doom (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solomon's Key (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Solomon's Key</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Solomon's Key is a platform game with both action and strategy elements. On each level your goal is to retrieve a key which can then be used to unlock the exit. To help out, you have a magic wand which can be used to create and destroy blocks (though some blocks can't be destroyed). In order to reach the key you will need carefully to arrange the blocks on the screen so you can jump your way around safely. Wandering around each level are a variety of enemies which will cause you to lose a life if you're caught.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Solomon's Key (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Solomon's Key (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the future city of Monsteropolis, the use of robot labour has helped civilization grow more than ever before. At the forefront of this technology is Dr. Light and his assistant Dr. Wily, who are commissioned to build six robots to handle a variety of specific tasks. They are named Bombman, Gutsman, Iceman, Cutman, Elecman, and Fireman in reference to their individual prime functions. Dr. Wily, however, has bigger plans and chooses to take control of the robots and let loose destruction in a bid for world control. Dr. Light fights back with the best tool he has, an experimental human-like robot, Rock aka Mega Man, who had been tested to perform cleaning duties.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19871201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After defeating Dr. Light's six robots that were reprogrammed by the villainous Dr. Wily in Mega Man, it seemed like the world was safe. But it was not to be. Dr. Wily has escaped from prison and is madder than ever, this time creating eight new Robot Masters of his own to take over the world and crush Mega Man! Is the world doomed?</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>"Calling Mega Man! Calling Mega Man! Come in please!" This is a traditional action-platformer: you jump from brick to brick while avoiding pits and shooting robots. It's quite similar, in all respects, to other Mega Man games; however, this is the first time that you get a sidekick. It's also the first time you're allowed to slide instead of merely walking. Also, there is a mysterious character called Protoman who may or may not be your friend. Rush is your dog who helps out by offering other modes of transportation when you need it.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 4 (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 4</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Mega Man 4, Dr. Wily is declared as having been killed by the explosion of Gamma. A year passes and Rock, Roll, and Dr. Light are living in peace. But soon, the peace is broken by a new threat. A supposed colleague of Dr. Light's, the mysterious Dr. Cossack, has sent out eight of his own Robot Masters to find Mega Man, whom Cossack blames for the kidnapping of his daughter. Mega Man, hoping to clear his name, sets out to find Dr. Cossack, this time armed with a powerful new weapon: the Rock Buster!! Rockman must now battle with Cossack's fiendish Robot Masters and find Cossack's daughter before it's too late!.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man 4 (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man 4 (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 5 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 5</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dr. Cossack, humbled by his defeat and his allowing of Dr. Wily to influence his ways, decides to help Dr. Light by providing him and Rockman with tools and weapons to help foil Dr. Wily for good. All seems calm and peaceful until a sudden rampage breaks out, and the cause is found to be a group of robots, led by a mysterious figure. As Dr. Light begins to investigate this rampage and attempts to find a way to stop it, he is kidnapped by the leader of the robots. Rockman hurries to save Dr. Light, but is too late.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man 5 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man 5 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 6 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 6</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mega Man 6, the whole world is alive and buzzing with word of the 1st Annual Robot Design Contest. Hundreds of robot designers from all corners of the globe enter their most powerful robots into the contest in hopes of taking home the ultimate prize. The sponsor of the contest, the mysterious Mr. X, suddenly declares that he has decided on winners and takes 8 of the Robot Masters for his own purpose, taking over the world!! Rockman confronts him and demands an explanation, and what Mr. X replies with shocks him. Mr. X declares to Rockman that he had been using Dr. Wily as a puppet the entire time.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man 6 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man 6 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ufouria - The Saga (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>U·four·ia: The Saga</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You must explore the world on which you and three other friends crash landed. As you encounter the new characters you must fight them to make them recover their memory. Once you have recovered all 3 other characters you are then searching for Temple Keys which will lead back to your homeworld of Ufouria. The world in which you interact is free form, meaning that you can wander around as you please. To get to new areas you will need to get power-ups and/or new characters with their own abilities. Character switching is done as needed, not defined by levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ufouria - The Saga (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ufouria - The Saga (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Over Horizon (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Over Horizon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Over Horizon is a side-scrolling shooter in which the player has to guide a spaceship through various levels and destroy numerous enemies. The ship's weapons can be fired in tow directions and defeated enemies sometimes drop power-ups that equip the ship with different weapons and up to two options. There are three different weapons in addition to the standard shot: Laser, homing missiles and bombs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hot-B</developer>
		<publisher>Hot-B</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Over Horizon (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Over Horizon (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solstice - The Quest for the Staff of Demnos (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Solstice: The Quest for the Staff of Demnos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Princess Eleanor has been captured by the evil mage Morbius and is somewhere in the fortress of Kastlerock. You play the part of Shadax, who must now rescue the Princess by searching the fortress for the six pieces of the magical Staff of Demnos and use it to defeat Morbius. Solstice is a combination of a puzzle/adventure and action game played from an isometric 3-D point of view. There are numerous rooms to explore in the fortress, many with dangerous, evil creatures wandering about and traps and obstacles to get past. Along the way there are magic potions, keys, and many other items to find which help you get past the creatures as well as reach new parts of the fortress.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Solstice - The Quest for the Staff of Demnos (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Solstice - The Quest for the Staff of Demnos (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./StarTropics (USA).zip</path>
		<name>StarTropics</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In StarTropics, you play the part of Michael Jones. Mike's uncle (Dr. Jones, a famous archaeologist) is on C-Island looking for some lost ruins and has invited Mike to come visit him. However, shortly after arriving on the island Mike learns from Chief Coralcola that Dr. Jones has recently been abducted! Now it is up to Mike to locate Dr. Jones and find out why he was abducted. StarTropics is a combination of an adventure and action game played from an overhead point of view. Starting out with just an island yo-yo, Mike will need to search the island for Dr. Jones.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/StarTropics (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/StarTropics (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda II - The Adventure of Link (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Zelda II: The Adventure of Link</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The land of Hyrule is in chaos. As Link, you'll be sent on a treacherous journey to return six precious Crystals to their origins in six stone statues. Only by defeating the guardians of the six palaces will you gain passage to the seventh palace, take on the ultimate challenge that awaits you, and wake the Princess Zelda from her sleeping spell. On your way, helpful villagers you encounter will offer clues and secret messages invaluable in your quest. As you guide Link through the levels of Hyrule, close-ups and overviews will enhance your video vision. Are you up to the challenge?</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zelda II - The Adventure of Link (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zelda II - The Adventure of Link (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonderland Dizzy (Europe) (En,Fr,Es,Nl,Pt,Pl) (2015) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Wonderland Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wonderland Dizzy For NES HERE AT LAST - its only taken Codemasters (aherm) 20 years to get this bad boy developed and released, well technically NOT Codemasterr. While the original game series, which included the first game, its sequels Treasure Island Dizzy and Fantasy World Dizzy, was developed by twins Andrew and Philip Oliver, future sequels came under the wings of Big Red Software. However, the lads didn't just stop with those three Dizzy games, they were also working on a fourth and final game by the name of Wonderland Dizzy which unfortunately was never released. This game was supposed to be released for NES in 1993.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20150101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Andrew Joseph</developer>
		<publisher>The Oliver Twins</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wonderland Dizzy (Europe) (En,Fr,Es,Nl,Pt,Pl) (2015) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wonderland Dizzy (Europe) (En,Fr,Es,Nl,Pt,Pl) (2015) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mystery World Dizzy (Europe) (En,Pt,Pl) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Mystery World Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A Nintendo Entertainment System version of Fantasy World Dizzy titled Mystery World Dizzy was developed in April 1993 but was not released until 24 years later in April 2017. It's available free on the official Dizzy website.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Oliver Twins</developer>
		<publisher>The Oliver Twins</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mystery World Dizzy (Europe) (En,Pt,Pl) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mystery World Dizzy (Europe) (En,Pt,Pl) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guardian Legend, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Guardian Legend</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the far future, Earth is a peaceful place with very few worries. To ensure it stays that way, a top secret project was authorized: the creation of the guardian suit. It's a suit of flight armor that allows the guardian to survive any environment. It's a good thing too, because a giant space station is spotted on a collision course with Earth. You take the role of the guardian. Your mission is to activate the station's self-destruct and destroy it before it collides with Earth.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Guardian Legend, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Guardian Legend, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tom &amp; Jerry - The Ultimate Game of Cat and Mouse! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tom &amp; Jerry: The Ultimate Game of Cat and Mouse!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game plays very similar to Chip &amp; Dale's Rescue Rangers. Tom has mouse-napped Jerry's nephew Tuffy and locked him in a trunk in the attic. You and your furry little buddy Jerry must dash, jump, and climb from the basement up through every level of the house to rescue him in time. Jerry's main defense is his unlimited supply of marbles. Pick up other items such as bubble gum, meat cleaver, cups of water, moth balls, hammer, invisible ink and drill to overcome the enemies and obstacles in your way. Make sure you outwit Tom whenever he appears.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>HiTech Software</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tom &amp; Jerry - The Ultimate Game of Cat and Mouse! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tom &amp; Jerry - The Ultimate Game of Cat and Mouse! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Micro Machines (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Micro Machines</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Choose your vehicle and go! Feel the power, feel the traction - excellent! Performance sports cars, Formula One racing cars, Power boats, Combat Monster trucks &amp; Turbo Wheels. Absolutely Brilliant!!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camerica</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Micro Machines (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Micro Machines (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fantastic Adventures of Dizzy, The (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>The Fantastic Adventures of Dizzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil wizard Zaks casts a spell on the Yolkfolk and kidnaps Dizzy's girlfriend Daisy. It is up to Dizzy to undo Zak's doings and rescue Daisy from the castle in the clouds.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>The Oliver Twins</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fantastic Adventures of Dizzy, The (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fantastic Adventures of Dizzy, The (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solomon's Key 2 (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Solomon's Key 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The peaceful island Coolmint is attacked by flame monsters sent by the evil wizard Druidle. The queen of the winter fairies chooses the novice wizard Dana to drive back the monsters. Fire 'n Ice is a puzzle game seen from a side-view perspective. The goal in each level is to extinguish all flames by pushing or dropping blocks onto them. The player takes control of Dana who can create or destroy ice blocks, climb blocks and push loose blocks.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Solomon's Key 2 (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Solomon's Key 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Blade (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Power Blade</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It is the year 2191, and Earth's blissful existence was governed by a master computer. Then suddenly, its master control program malfunctioned, and people panicked ensuring total chaos. Secret Agent Nova is called in to locate agents located in six sectors. These agents hold an ID card which Nova must acquire to gain access to the security room within each sector. There, he must defeat the guards and obtain secret tape units, and if Nova obtains six of these, he will be able to gain entry to the control center and defeat the guard to destroy the computer and restore order to society.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Power Blade (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Power Blade (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Spy Hunter (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Spy Hunter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2525, things are a mess. politically. Terrorists led by someone named "X" want to attack the United Nations. The CIA is in charge of discouraging the attacks. To that end, and since all of their best agents have failed the task, they send out an unofficial agent -- you, the Super Spy Hunter.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Spy Hunter (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Spy Hunter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xexyz (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Xexyz</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's the year 2777. Due to nuclear wars and natural disasters, Earth's population has decreased dramatically and only five island are left, forming the nation of Xexyz. In Xexyz, humans, spirits and faeries have lived peacefully for centuries under the reign of King Xeu Star. One day, Xexyz is attacked by Goruza who murders the king, builds mechanical castles on each island and captures the queen of each island. You play a soldier named Apollo who wants to put an end to Goruza's reign.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Xexyz (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Xexyz (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Ghostbusters II (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>New Ghostbusters II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>New Ghostbusters II follows loosely the original Ivan Reitman's film plot. You start out by selecting two ghostbusters out of five (The 5th one is Louis Tully). The first, player controlled buster will use proton pack and second, controlled by AI, uses the trap where ghosts end up, after been freezed by using the proton pack. Player controlled buster can get hurt, if touched by a ghost, while AI buster can't.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19901226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/New Ghostbusters II (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/New Ghostbusters II (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magic of Scheherazade, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Magic of Scheherazade</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil wizard Sabaron summoned a horde of demons to invade Arabia. One brave magician tried to fight Sabaron, but was trapped in the holes of time. This magician is you. Traveling through different time periods, you'll have to stop Sabaron's evil plans and to rescue the beautiful princess Scheherazade he kidnapped.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Magic of Scheherazade, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Magic of Scheherazade, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario's Woods (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Wario's Woods</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wario's Woods is a puzzle game similar to Tetris or Columns, but with a twist. Instead of directly controlling the monsters and bombs that are falling down, the player controls Toad who has to carry around stacks of monsters and bombs and to combine them in the right way. One bomb plus at least two monsters of the same color have to be combined to make them disappear. If five or more objects are cleared at the same time, a diamond will appear. Destroying the diamond will clear all monsters of the diamond's color.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wario's Woods (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wario's Woods (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>These Tiny Toons have big problems. That's right. The arch enemy of Acme Acres, Montana Max, has kidnapped the ever-so-popular Babs Bunny. Now the furry female's fate rests in the paws of Buster Bunny and his crime fighting pals - Dizzy Devil, Furrball and Plucky Duck. Four kooky buddies with their own special talent. Buster can bounce over bad guys with the best of them. Furrball uses his feline claws to climb walls. Dizzy Devil prefers to spin through them. And Plucky can glide through the air and swim like a fish.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tiny Toon Adventures (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tiny Toon Adventures (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Man (USA) (Namco).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board. Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde). One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man. Pac-Man can turn the tables on his pursuers by eating of the four Energizers located within the maze. During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pac-Man (USA) (Namco).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pac-Man (USA) (Namco).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Warrior is the first famous console RPG. You assume the role of a descendant of Erdrick, a brave warrior of the past. Once upon a time, Erdrick defeated the evil Dragonlord with the help of the Ball of Light. Now, Dragonlord stole the Ball of Light, and your mission is to recover it and to restore peace in the world. In Dragon Warrior, you move your character around in a top-down world. In cities and palaces you can talk to people, rest in inns and buy stuff in shops. There's a variety of weapons, equipment and armor to buy. When wandering around in the wilderness, you occasionally encounter enemies, and fight them from 1st person perspective.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Warrior (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Warrior (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Warrior II is an early top-down RPG that expands and improves on its predecessor, Dragon Warrior. Taking the role of a descendant of Erdrick, the player once again ventures forth in an effort to save the world. Unlike the first game, Dragon Warrior II allows the player to join forces with two other characters, a magic-using princess and a wizard-warrior prince. Also including expanded monster battles involving up to 6 creatures and a much larger world, Dragon Warrior II is an important step in the evolution of the Dragon Warrior series.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Warrior II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Warrior II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior III (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior III</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Warrior III is the concluding game of the first Dragon Quest/Dragon Warrior trilogy, and its story takes us back to the time period of the legendary Erdrick (also known as Loto), the ancestor of the first game's hero. You are the son of a powerful warrior Ortega, skillful in physical combat and spellcasting. Your father went out to fight the evil Baramos, who is responsible for the appearance of monsters in your region, and never returned. You are sent by the king on a quest to continue your father's brave deeds and to defeat Baramos.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Warrior III (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Warrior III (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Warrior IV (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Warrior IV</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Warrior IV, the fourth volume in the Dragon Warrior series (and the last on the NES), once again took the elements of the previous games and expanded them into a five chapter saga of epic proportions. The first four chapters are played from the viewpoint of one character per chapter, who will all meet up in the fifth chapter. From a soldier to a merchant, the game weaves an intriguing story that ties all four characters together in the end.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Warrior IV (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Warrior IV (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deja Vu (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Déjà Vu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Déjà Vu was the first game ever made by ICOM, the makers of such famous adventure games as Shadowgate and Uninvited. It featured mouse support, a multi-window interface, and bitmapped graphics at a time when text-based interactive fiction was the norm.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Seika Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Deja Vu (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Deja Vu (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike (Japan, USA).zip</path>
		<name>Excitebike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Race by yourself against the clock or compete with other motocross riders on 5 tracks full of long straights, large jumps and obstacles to win the Excitebike championship. Create your own tracks by placing jumps and obstacles of all different sizes and shapes on the track and choosing how many laps each race will have, then race against the clock or other riders to see how your track fares in competition.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19851018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Excitebike (Japan, USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Excitebike (Japan, USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-117A Stealth Fighter (USA).zip</path>
		<name>F-117A Stealth Fighter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>F-117A Stealth Fighter is a flight simulator where the player is in the cockpit of the game's eponymous jet fighter. The game revolves around flying solo punitive strike missions against various rogue nations. For example, the first mission has the player launching from a base in Sicily to strike targets in Libya. Watch out for enemy jets, of course. The 8-bit NES's input capabilities are a bit limited so this flight simulator depends on many button combinations in order to carry out various complicated actions.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MicroProse</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/F-117A Stealth Fighter (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F-117A Stealth Fighter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Faria - A World of Mystery &amp; Danger! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Faria: A World of Mystery &amp; Danger!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It was a stormy night. Cold wind raged, and rain poured over the country. The wise men understood at once: the prophecy has become reality. The spell of the Legendary Sword was lifted. Fast-forward to three months later. You are a nameless young adventurer, looking for some action. Your first task is, you guessed it, to rescue a princess. After the king gives you this assignment, you are free to roam about the world, visiting dangerous caves and towers, and fulfilling ancient prophecies.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>NEXOFT Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Faria - A World of Mystery &amp; Danger! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Faria - A World of Mystery &amp; Danger! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Faxanadu (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Faxanadu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This 2D platformer has elements of role-playing and adventure in addition to side-scrolling action. The story is a classic one of good versus evil. Disaster strikes the once peaceful Elf town of Eolis. The sky rains meteorites upon the World Tree - wild animals and evil monsters terrorize the citizens - the water supply from the wells is dwindling - plants are withering - people are dying. Only you can restore peace to the land by conquering the Evil One, who lives in the Evil Place. There are many places you must visit during your quest including the medieval town, where you begin, country villages, fortresses, caves, and gloomy bogs - each with its own ambiance and musical score.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Faxanadu (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Faxanadu (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fester's Quest (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Fester's Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Uncle Fester was out one night, moonbathing in the yard of the Addams Family property one day when suddenly, out of the sky, a UFO descended and started beaming alien creatures to the planet. Grabbing his gun, Fester sets off to stop the aliens and slay their boss creatures, encountering other Addams Family members along the way who will aid him.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19890901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fester's Quest (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fester's Quest (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hironobu Sakaguchi's Final Fantasy the first of one of the longest role-playing game series known to mankind. Final Fantasy is the game for the NES console that started it all. The world is veiled in darkness. Winds don't blow, the seas are stormy, and the earth rots. All people can hope for is that the ancient prophecy will be finally fulfilled. "When the world is veiled in darkness, four warriors will come" And indeed, they come - the four characters you have previously chosen. Their first quest is to free a princess from the evil Garland, and then the real journey begins.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Galaga - Demons of Death (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Galaga: Demons of Death</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Galaga is a vertical arcade shooter from Namco. You control a space fighter at the bottom of the screen, scrolling left and right in order to avoid oncoming bombs and kamikaze attacks from alien invaders--and to fire your own missiles to fight back! There are an infinite number of stages to progress through. Every third level is a "challenge stage" in which you have a free chance to shoot as many aliens as possible and rack up bonus points. Certain aliens have tractor beams they can use to capture one of your ships. If that wasn't your last "life," you can try to shoot that alien down and recapture your ship, giving you two ships at once and doubling your firepower.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Galaga - Demons of Death (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Galaga - Demons of Death (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gargoyle's Quest II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gargoyles's Quest II </name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As in its predecessor, gameplay in Gargoyle's Quest II is divided into an adventure-like and an action part. During the adventure parts, Firebrand explores a world map and several villages from a top-down perspective, talking to his fellow ghouls and zombies to advance the story or receive important items. Action parts are seen from a side-scrolling perspective. In these parts of the game, Firebrand has the ability to jump, cling to walls, fly for a limited amount of time and shoot fireballs at his enemies. As the game progresses, Firebrand becomes more and more powerful, receiving items that improve his agility, armor or attack power.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gargoyle's Quest II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gargoyle's Quest II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghosts'n Goblins (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ghosts'n Goblins</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ghosts'n Goblins is a sideways scrolling action platformer spread over six levels, each of which must be completed within three minutes (or a life is lost), taking in forest, village, mountain and cavern settings with increasing difficulty. Arthur the brave knight must rescue his beloved Princess from the Demon King Astaroth and his forces - amongst them are the various undead (ghosts, zombies), bats, ogres and goblins. Other challenges include moving platforms, ladders and water/fire hazards. As in most games in this genre, the player can pick up power-ups such as daggers and bombs during the course of the game, giving the player greater firepower.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19861102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ghosts'n Goblins (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ghosts'n Goblins (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gradius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The people of Gradius are in trouble. The ameoboid Bacterions have launched an all out attack against the planet, and it's up to you to fly into battle and save them. Along the way you'll be able to power up your ship with hyper speed, force fields, lasers, missiles, double beam cannons and more to help you battle. Based on the arcade game, Gradius is a side scrolling shooter. Shooting certain enemies will leave a power up pod behind which can be collected to add more power to your ship. Each level features a wide variety of enemies trying to stop you, with a large boss at the end. Gameplay is for one player or two players alternating.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19861202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gradius (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gradius (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gremlins 2 - The New Batch (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gremlins 2: The New Batch</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Gizmo, you must reach the Gremlin Control Centre to wipe them out. This is an isometric action game differing from the Elite title. You can gain items such as a bow and arrow and matches after each level to help. Mr Wing's Shop also contains many goodies, so watch out for its door magically appearing. Hazards include spiders, electrified wires, ground-mounted hazards, and a boss at the end of each level.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19901001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gremlins 2 - The New Batch (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gremlins 2 - The New Batch (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guerrilla War (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Guerrilla War</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A tropical island (specified as Cuba in the Japanese original) is being oppressed by a dictator, but fortunately one or two brave US soldiers (Ernesto "Che" Guevara in the Japanese version) are on hand to restore justice. March through the rivers, swamps and forests to overthrow the dictator (specified as Batista in Japan) in this evolution of the Commando style.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Guerrilla War (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Guerrilla War (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun Nac (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gun·Nac</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A Galactic Federation starfighter is sent off to destroy an alien armada (led by giant robotic rabbits this time around -- an unusually whimsical theme in keeping with the contemporary Parodius) threatening to collapse your system's sun into a supernova.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gun Nac (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gun Nac (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heavy Barrel (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Heavy Barrel</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Heavy Barrel is a shooter with a top-down view similar to Commando and Ikari Warriors. Terrorists have seized the underground control complex of a nuclear missile site. It is up to the player to infiltrate the installation and eliminate the leader of the terrorist army before they can launch the missiles. To stop the terrorists you will need the powerful weapon Heavy Barrel. The problem is that the weapon still is in the installation. Before the fortress fell the weapon was taken apart and locked in six different storage lockers. To defeat the terrorists you must collect all keys and reassemble the weapon. The game supports co-op for two players.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Heavy Barrel (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Heavy Barrel (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ikari Warriors (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Ikari Warriors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A conversion of the arcade game, Ikari Warriors is a vertically scrolling action game. One or two players fight their way through a variety of terrain, such as jungles, rivers, and ruins. Along the way different weapons can be found, including machine guns, grenades, and rocket launchers.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19890810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ikari Warriors (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ikari Warriors (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Isolated Warrior (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Isolated Warrior</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Max Maverick is the last surviving member of his planet's special forces following a devastating alien invasion. Far from being discouraged, Max takes it upon himself to wipe out the alien menace single-handedly. Isolated Warrior is a constantly-moving shoot-em-up, or shmup, where the hero is always walking or flying forward from an isometric overhead perspective. The hero has a basic laser gun to start with but collects powerups that can allow the gun to fire in multiple directions.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NTVIC</developer>
		<publisher>Vap Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Isolated Warrior (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Isolated Warrior (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jackal (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Jackal</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The enemy army has captured too many of your forces. Being held in P.O.W. camps, these soldiers are effectively out of the war unless some kind of rescue operation can be mounted. Heavy Forces are too slow and visible to be of any use, but perhaps something smaller and lighter may make it in where larger forces would fail. A small jeep, maybe two, crewed by about 4 people minimal enough not to represent too much of a loss and yet suitable enough to aid in rescue. But of course, if these brave men want to succeed AND come back alive; they'll need to fight like animals, they'll need to fight like jackals. Jackal is an overhead view jeep game for up to 2 players.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jackal (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jackal (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Journey to Silius (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Journey to Silius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 0373 in the new space age calendar. The earth's population is growing rapidly, and people are now forced to start space colonies. Jay McCray is among those leaving earth and heading to the colony in the Silius solar system. Unfortunately, terrorists have destroyed a research colony there. Jay's father was killed in this attack, and now Jay vows to destroy the terrorists responsible and to continue the research his father was working on.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Journey to Silius (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Journey to Silius (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kabuki Quantum Fighter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this futuristic platform game, a computer virus has affected the Earth's defense systems. A lone warrior is transferred into digital data and sent inside the mainframe, where he becomes a Kabuki warrior. Gameplay is similar to other ninja-platformers (such as Ninja Gaiden) but with some interesting modifications, such as using your long red hair as a whip to attack enemies!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kabuki - Quantum Fighter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kickle Cubicle (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kickle Cubicle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kickle Cubicle is a Lolo type sliding puzzle game where the Wicked Wizard King covered the kingdom with ice and hid the people and palaces deep within the ice. Armed with his freezing breath, Kickle sets out to save his friends and attempts to rescue the kingdom from this puzzling predicament of perpetual winter. Each level has a fixed time limit and enemies that will try and block your progress. The four lands (Garden, Fruit, Cake and Toy) have 17 or 18 puzzles in each.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kickle Cubicle (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kickle Cubicle (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid Icarus (USA, Europe) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Kid Icarus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Far away in peaceful Angel Land lived a young angel warrior named Pit, who has been given the task of defeating the monstrous Medusa, who wishes to destroy Angel Land and all of the people, and she has started by kidnapping Palutena, the Princess of Angel Land. Young Pit must rescue the Princess and restore peace to Angel Land. He will travel from the deep caverns of the Underworld to Medusa's palace in the sky on his journey, and deadly monsters will attack him every step of the way. But he has the power of the Gods on his side! A powerful bow and arrows, Water of Life, and Angel Feathers will assist Pit on his quest to destroy Medusa and save the princess!.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19861219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kid Icarus (USA, Europe) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kid Icarus (USA, Europe) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kings of the Beach - Professional Beach Volleyball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kings of the Beach: Professional Beach Volleyball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kings of the Beach is a two on two beach volleyball game. You must quickly move your team about on the sand performing serves, thumps, and spikes to not only out-perform but also out-smart the opposing team. There are 15 levels and 20 challengers to beat, on famous beaches like Rio, Hawaii and Sydney, in order to be crowned King of the Beach. Both cooperative and competitive multiplayer (non-networked) are also supported.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kings of the Beach - Professional Beach Volleyball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kings of the Beach - Professional Beach Volleyball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Adventure (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Dream Spring, the source of all dreams, has dried up, causing all the dreams of Dream Land to disappear. Now it's up to Kirby to rescue Dream Land! Kirby's Adventure is an action/adventure side scrolling platform game. As the pink puffball Kirby you will explore numerous, colorful lands with a variety of enemies to defeat. To help out on his journey, Kirby has the ability to eat enemies and spit them out as projectiles. With certain enemies Kirby can capture their abilities and e.g. gain a sword, shoot lasers, or even fly around the level. There are seven different stages, each broken up into multiple levels, and sometimes also containing a couple of bonus mini-games.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby's Adventure (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby's Adventure (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kiwi Kraze - A Bird-Brained Adventure! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kiwi Kraze: A Bird-Brained Adventure!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One day, a kiwi tribe was having fun and games outside the zoo, only to be kidnapped by the evil-minded Leopard Seal, who plans to sell them at the black market. Fortunately, during the kidnapping process, Tiki, leader of the tribe, managed to escape the sack, and her job is to rescue Phee-Phee and the other kiwis scattered around New Zealand, and are held in cages in various locations that include Auckland, Rotorua, Waitomo Caves, Strait Cook, and Mt. Cook. If Tiki doesn't rescue a kiwi in a limited amount of time, the devil will appear and try to kill her. When Tiki reaches the outskirts of each city, except Strait Cook, there is a boss waiting to meet Tiki, and kill her by using their own choice of weapons.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19910301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kiwi Kraze - A Bird-Brained Adventure! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kiwi Kraze - A Bird-Brained Adventure! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In one of the darkest times in the Kingdom of Hyrule, a young, pointy-eared boy named Link takes on an epic quest to restore the fragmented Triforce of Wisdom and save the Princess Zelda from the clutches of the evil, power-hungry Ganon. The Legend of Zelda for the NES marks the first action-adventure title of the popular Nintendo series. Players must make their way through the various forests, graveyards, plains, and deserts of the Overworld to find the secret entrances of the eight dungeons in an attempt to piece together the broken Triforce. Once all pieces are joined, Link will be able to gain entry to Death Mountain, home of Ganon, and prison of Princess Zelda.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legendary Wings (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Legendary Wings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A heroic figure from ancient times thrust into a strange futuristic world, you must fight your way through six levels to defeat "The Devil" and save the day. The primary gameplay mode is a top-down, vertical-scrolling shooter similar to Xevious and Capcom's own 1943. Your main weapon is used to attack flying enemies, and your secondary missile weapon is used to attack fixed placement, land-based enemies. Numerous powerups are available along the way, and these both improve your weapons and your resistance to damage (every "upgrade" is worth a free hit from enemies without dying).</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19880702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legendary Wings (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legendary Wings (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Life Force (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Life Force</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a distant part of the universe, an alien creature called Zelos was born. As he grew so did his appetite, and soon he began devouring galaxies, planets, and stars by the hundreds. Now your planet has appeared in Zelos' path, and it is up to you and a partner to fly into battle to save your world. Life Force is an action packed shooter based on the arcade game. There are six levels which alternate between side and vertical scrolling, each of them ending with a powerful guardian. Throughout the game, destroying certain enemies will release power ups which can be used to equip your ship with more powerful weapons, extra speed, and shields. Gameplay is for one player or two players simultaneously.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19880801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Life Force (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Life Force (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Nemo - The Dream Master (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Little Nemo: The Dream Master</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on a comic strip for the 1940's, Nemo is a young boy from London summoned to the kingdom of Slumberland, a fantasy realm filled with strange creatures and dream-like locations. You soon learn that the King of Slumberland has been kidnapped by the Prince of Nightmares, and you are requested to save him by Princess Camille. Using your only weapon, a sack of candy, you stun enemies and lull friendly animals into helping you through levels like the Mushroom Forest and Train Land. This platformer featured licensed characters and artwork from the comic, along with using the animals, such as apes and moles, to traverse through the different terrain.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Little Nemo - The Dream Master (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Samson (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Little Samson</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ta-Keed, the Prince of Darkness, has managed to escape from his supernatural penitentiary where he has had centuries to plot exactly how he will take revenge on those that locked him away. Emperor Hans sends his troops to deal with this threat, but they are no match for the ultimate evil one. As an alternative, the emperor summons the bearers of 4 Magical Bells. These 4 adventurers must make their way to the castle and work as a team if they are to destroy Ta-Keed. The first part of Little Samson has each of the 4 characters journeying from his or her home land to the emperor's palace. This gives the player an opportunity to explore that character's unique abilities which will be essential throughout the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Sur de Wave</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Little Samson (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Little Samson (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maniac Mansion (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Maniac Mansion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Edison mansion has always been a creepy old house on the edge of town. There have been rumors of strange experiments going on and of odd creatures living amongst the Edison family. There is even a story that a meteorite once crashed near the home nearly 20 years ago. More immediately, a girl named Sandy has gone missing from the local highschool and her boyfriend Dave swears that he saw Dr. Fred abducting her. Dave knows that he cannot do it alone and will need help from two other students if he has any hope of infiltrating the mansion and rescuing Sandy.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Realtime Associates</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Maniac Mansion (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Maniac Mansion (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mappy-Land (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mappy-Land</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mappy the mouse has a girlfriend named Mapica. In order to please his girlfriend, Mappy goes on a mission to collect gifts for his significant other. Unfortunately the boss cat Nyamco and his legion of pink cats want to track Mappy down so they can make a meal out of him. The goal of the game is to collect 6 of 1 item in each stage without getting eaten by a cat. The items you collect (either pieces of cheese, wedding rings, christmas trees, or baseballs) vary depending on what stage your playing. There are also stage specific items in the background that will help you defeat your feline adversaries.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19861126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taxan USA Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mappy-Land (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mappy-Land (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marble Madness (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Marble Madness</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A port of the arcade game. The idea is deceptively simple: Guide a marble down a path without hitting any obstacles or straying off the course. The game is viewed from an isometric perspective, which makes it harder to stay focused on the direction the ball is to follow. There are tight corridors to follow and enemies to avoid.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milton Bradley Co.</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Marble Madness (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Marble Madness (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eliminator Boat Duel (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Eliminator Boat Duel</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Eliminator Boat Duel is a ruthless one on one boat racing game that can either be played against the computer or a human opponent. The races take place in such settings as open water, the bayou, and even industrial water districts. Each boat race consists of several sections. First, there is the starting line -- where you can expect a $2000 fine for a false start.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19911102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electro Brain Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Eliminator Boat Duel (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Eliminator Boat Duel (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gumshoe (USA, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Gumshoe</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your daughter, Jennifer, has been kidnapped! You have to help Mr. Stevenson who is on a mission to rescue her. Throughout the levels there are five diamonds you must collect which are needed to complete the final level and rescue Jennifer, with plenty of obstacles and enemies to get in the way. During the game Mr. Stevenson continuously walks to the right and you have to use the light gun to save him from any obstacles blocking his path. Some obstacles can be destroyed with the light gun, others Mr. Stevenson will need to jump over (shooting him with the light gun will cause him to jump.).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gumshoe (USA, Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gumshoe (USA, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gyromite ~ Gyro (World).zip</path>
		<name>Gyromite</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Gyromite, you need to help a mad scientist deactivate all of the dynamite in his laboratory before time runs out! ROB the robot will assist you in this game by moving the red and blue pillars blocking the way. Just in case finding your way through the laboratory wasn't enough, be sure to watch out for the deadly Smicks who wander about trying to prevent success of your mission. If you find a radish, pick it up and feed it to the Smicks so you can safely get past them. There is also a second game variation where you need to clear the way for a sleepwalking mad scientist so he can get home safely.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gyromite ~ Gyro (World).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gyromite ~ Gyro (World).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jackie Chan and his twin sister Josephine were great kung fu fighters in China and trained under a great master. One day when Jackie and Josephine were out walking, the Master's great enemy, The Sorcerer appeared. The Sorcerer had come to rule over China and knew the twins would stand in his way, so he cast a spell to make Josephine disappear. Now it's up to Jackie Chan to follow after the Sorcerer and battle his minions in order to rescue his sister and save China.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jackie Chan's Action Kung Fu (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Bros. (World).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario and Luigi are doing some underground plumbing when all sorts of weird creatures come flying out of the pipes. Turtles, crabs - even fighterflies - attack the helpless Mario Bros. It's up to you to kick, punch, and knock out these sewer pests before time runs out! But beware. Just when you think you got rid of them, they come back for more! Play against the computer, or with a friend - either way, this is one underground classic you'll want to play time and time again!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Bros. (World).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Bros. (World).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mendel Palace (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mendel Palace</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Mendel Palace, you are Bun-Bun and you have to rescue your girlfriend Candy, who has fallen asleep and is now trapped in her dream. To progress, you have to go through various areas that feature dolls as enemies. Games are played on a board of 7x5 sliding tiles, using an overhead view. By sliding floor tiles, you'll be able to put them off balance and make the crash in the wall, leading to their destruction.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mendel Palace (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mendel Palace (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mighty Final Fight (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mighty Final Fight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Capcom's only 8-bit port of the Final Fight series, Mighty Final Fight follows the storyline and characters of the first Final Fight game. Mayor of Metro City Mike Haggar, his ninja friend Guy and his daughter's boyfriend, Cody learn that Haggar's daughter, Jessica, has been kidnapped by the Mad Gear Gang whose leader has fallen in love with her, and also wants the meddling Mike Haggar to leave town. Now it's personal! Choosing one of the three fighters, the player embarks on a beat-em-up quest through the streets of Metro City.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mighty Final Fight (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mighty Final Fight (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man (USA) (Tengen) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 1982, a sequel to the incredibly popular Pac-Man was introduced in the form of his girlfriend, Ms. Pac-Man. This sequel continued on the "eat the dots/avoid the ghosts" gameplay of the original game, but added new features to keep the title fresh. Like her boyfriend, Ms. Pac-Man attempts to clear four various and challenging mazes filled with dots and ever-moving bouncing fruit while avoiding Inky, Blinky, Pinky and Sue, each with their own personalities and tactics. One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Ms. Pac-Man.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ms. Pac-Man (USA) (Tengen) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ms. Pac-Man (USA) (Tengen) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NES Open Tournament Golf (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NES Open: Tournament Golf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In NES Open Tournament Golf, you can play a round of golf on one of three different courses. One or two players can play in the U.S., Japan, or the U.K. and choose a stroke or match play game. Gameplay is from two point of views, starting with an overhead view allowing you to set up the shot and choose a club, then switching to a 3-D point of view. Hitting the ball uses the common power meter where tapping the button starts the meter, tap the button a second time to select the amount of power in the shot, then tap the button a third time to select the amount of slice or hook.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/NES Open Tournament Golf (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NES Open Tournament Golf (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Quest (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pinball Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Billed as a pinball role-playing game, though the term is used loosely, as you only earn gold to buy stoppers and more powerful flippers. Actually, there are four different modes of play. The RPG-mode has six, multi-screen pinball tables, where you use your flippers to knock the pinball into enemies, find keys, and eventually rescue Princess Bali. The other modes, POP!POP!, Viva Golf, and Circus, are each specialized multi-screen pinball tables involving sports, golf, and the circus. The latter has a slot machine and a bonus game in which you throw balls at animals to save the girl they are chasing.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pinball Quest (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pinball Quest (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Popeye (World) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Popeye</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Popeye is a conversion of the arcade action/platform game. As Popeye, you are trying to win Olive Oyl's love! She is at the top of the screen dropping tokens of her love, and you need to collect them before they hit the ground. After you have collected the required number of items, you can move on to the next, more difficult level.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19830715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Popeye (World) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Popeye (World) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Many growing seasons ago, the Salad Kingdom was a peaceful land. But one day, minister Pumpkin betrayed king Broccoli, kidnapped princess Tomato, stole the royal Turnip Emblem, and took them to his castle in Zucchini mountains. He sent his cruel Farmies to terrorize the Salad Kingdom. Shortly thereafter, the king died, unable to recover from the loss of his beautiful daughter. But he promised you, the brave Sir Cucumber, the princess' hand and the entire kingdom, if you save the beautiful Tomato from the clutches of the evil Pumpkin.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Princess Tomato in the Salad Kingdom (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rodland (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Rodland</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Taking a rather literal view of the term 'slap-stick humour', Rodland features two fairies called Tam and Rit, whose mission is to rescue their mum who's been captured and taken to a castle. There are 40 screens to clear, all full of baddies, who are disposed of by grabbing them with a stick, and flipping them from side to side to inflict damage. The hits needn't all be inflicted at the same time, as it's possible to release them to move them out of the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rodland (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rodland (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rush'n Attack (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rush'n Attack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Depending on which title you use, and how you interpret it, this game is about a guy who a)rushes in before attacking b)attacks Russians (this was the mid-80s, when the US helped bin Laden do the same), or c)wears a rather goofy hat. One way or another, this arcade conversion arms you with a knife.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rush'n Attack (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rush'n Attack (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./S.C.A.T. - Special Cybernetic Attack Team (USA).zip</path>
		<name>S.C.A.T.: Special Cybernetic Attack Team</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a humorous take on the eighties' sci-fi judgment day films, you either play Arnold or Sigourney in a mission to save the world. The year is 2029 and an alien invasion, led by Supreme Commander Vile Malmort, threatens the earth.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/S.C.A.T. - Special Cybernetic Attack Team (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/S.C.A.T. - Special Cybernetic Attack Team (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowgate (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shadowgate</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Using the same graphical interface as Deja Vu, Shadowgate is an adventure game set in a fantasy world. Players take the part of an adventurer sent to the ancient keep of Shadowgate on a quest to find a mystic artifact known as the Staff of Ages and stop the evil Warlock Lord from summoning a horrific demon known as the Behemoth. However Shadowgate has become infested with the Warlock Lord's demonic minions, not to mention the castle's still functional booby-traps.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ICOM Simulations</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadowgate (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadowgate (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skate or Die (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Skate or Die</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Skate or Die incorporates five distinct styles of skating, which can be attempted individually or in turn. You skate around a menu room to choose which one to attempt. Before taking off you can visit Rodney's skate shop to buy equipment.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Ultra Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/Skate or Die (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Skate or Die (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Super Bowl</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tecmo Super Bowl is the follow-up to the NES football arcade/simulation Tecmo Bowl. While the basic gameplay of the original is intact, a host of new features and improvements have been added.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19911202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This version of Tetris is one of many conversions of the famous block-stacking game, as well as the best-known (but not the only) version on Nintendo's first home console. The goal is to place pieces made up of four tiles in a ten-by-twenty well, organizing them into complete rows, which disappear. As rows are cleared, the pace of the game increases, and the game ends if the stack reaches the top of the well.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19891101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HiTech Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tetris (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tetris (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Marlin, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Blue Marlin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Blue Marlin is a big, strong, quick fish with a long nose. To catch such a fish is the dream of any fisherman. A great fishing competition begins this summer in Florida and Hawaii. You are invited to participate in it. Will you be able to demonstrate your fisherman skills and win the competition?</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920702T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hot-B</developer>
		<publisher>Hot-B</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blue Marlin, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blue Marlin, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goonies II, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Goonies II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a movie released in the 1980s, a group of youngsters formed a special gang and called themselves The Goonies. Nintendo banked upon the movie’s popularity by releasing several games using the characters and music from it, including the theme song by Cyndi Lauper. This is their second game on NES, The Goonies being released only for the Famicom system outside the United States.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19871102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Goonies II, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Goonies II, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Karate Kid, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Karate Kid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the 1986 John G. Avildsen film, The Karate Kid 2. The Karate Kid is a beat'em up game where the player, as Daniel Larusso, must go through some stages (including bonus ones) from the karate competition to the final battle in Okinawa against Chozen.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>19871101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LJN</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Karate Kid, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Karate Kid, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mafat Conspiracy, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Mafat Conspiracy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play as Golgo 13 aka Duke Togo, ace sharpshooter and assassin. Based off a character of various manga comics, Golgo is a down-to-business man at the end of a gun. Stuck in the world of espionage among such groups as the FBI and the CIA, Golgo is constantly in mortal danger, and a lethal weapon in his own right.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokai Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Tokai Engineering</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mafat Conspiracy, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mafat Conspiracy, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Stuntman, The (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>The Ultimate Stuntman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dr. Evil has kidnapped the scientist Jenny Aykroyd and it's the Ultimate Stuntman's job to rescue her. Ultimate Stuntman must fight through 7 worlds with 4 stages each and then through the final world which consists of 3 stages. The game has a variety of different gameplay types. The stages go in the order of an overhead view stage, a side-scrolling stage, a climbing stage with the Android boss, and then a bomb disposal stage.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Codemasters</developer>
		<publisher>Camerica</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultimate Stuntman, The (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultimate Stuntman, The (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wizards &amp; Warriors (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Wizards &amp; Warriors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Kuros, a powerful knight who enter the woods of Elrond. Legend says that a powerful wizard named Malkil has has gone completely mad during his years and turned his powerful magic to the dark side. Malkil has his base on the castle IronSpire where he has imprisoned a young and beautiful princess. It is up to Kuros to save the princess once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19871201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wizards &amp; Warriors (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wizards &amp; Warriors (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Cookie (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Yoshi's Cookie is a fast-paced puzzle game that can be enjoyed by everyone as it is easy to play, but challenging to complete. To play, you move the randomly placed cookies into rows and columns of cookies with similar patterns. When you successfully assemble a row or column of the same cookies, the line will disappear, and you can begin on a new row or column. The "Yoshi" cookie is very special in both the 1-player and the 2-player game. Since the Yoshi Cookie is the key to both games, you must use it wisely.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Yoshi's Cookie (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Yoshi's Cookie (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ice Hockey (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ice Hockey</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ice Hockey is an action game for one or two players. Start of by selecting a team and customizing your players. Each team member can be one of three player types: small and skinny (very fast, but not good at checking or shooting), very large (slow, but with a strong body check and outstanding shooting strength) or average (medium speed, with average checking and shooting strength). After the teams are set up, it's time to play some ice hockey!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ice Hockey (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ice Hockey (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ice Climber (USA, Europe, Korea).zip</path>
		<name>Ice Climber</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Ice Climber one or two players need to climb their way to the top of 32 different mountains. Each mountain is broken up into eight levels of platforms along with a bonus stage at the top. Attempting to stop you from making upward progress are different creatures ranging from polar bears to condors as well as treacherous landscapes with falling icicles, moving platforms, and icy floors. To help out, your only weapon is a mallet which can be used to knock out enemies as well as bust away bricks in the platforms to give you some room to jump up to the next level. When you finally reach the top, it's time to move on to the next, more difficult level.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19850130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ice Climber (USA, Europe, Korea).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ice Climber (USA, Europe, Korea).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bowser is back, and along with the Bowser kids, he's out to spoil Mario's day once again. This time, along with nabbing the Princess, the Bowser crew have also taken the magic wands from the Kings of each land and turned them into creatures. It's up to Mario and Luigi to get back the magic wands, defeat Bowser, and save the Princess all before the day is done.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19900212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Bros. 3 (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R.C. Pro-Am II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>R.C. Pro-Am II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This second Pro-Am racing game for NES introduces some innovations compared to its predecessor. Once again, you have to bring your red radio-controlled car to victory, score points, hit turbo speed lines, and leave no chance to your blue, green, and yellow adversaries. But you can also upgrade your engine and tires - if you can afford it, which means you'll have to think seriously about gathering those dollar signs scattered on the track. The tracks themselves have more variety, some have unusual enemies (little planes bombing you from above), and more kinds of obstacles.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/R.C. Pro-Am II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R.C. Pro-Am II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dusty Diamond's All-Star Softball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dusty Diamond's All-Star Softball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>All weekend ballplayers know softball's no joke, but that doesn't mean you can't have a little fun with it. And when you step up to the plate in this cart you'll find the wackiest bunch of players to ever hit a softball diamond!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tonkin House</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dusty Diamond's All-Star Softball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dusty Diamond's All-Star Softball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Felix the Cat (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Felix the Cat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Felix the Cat is a platformer based on the famous cartoon character.The Professor has kidnapped Kitty, Felix girlfriend, trying to exchange her for Felix' magic bag. Naturally, Felix is not going to let himself be blackmailed, and instead sets out to free Kitty.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Felix the Cat (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Felix the Cat (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gun.Smoke (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gun.Smoke</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gun.Smoke is a top-down scrolling shooter that casts the gamer as a lone gunman, out to save the gold rush town of Hicksville from a fearsome group of bandits known as the Wingates. Each level has a particular target enemy, although his or her henchmen must also be taken out.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gun.Smoke (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gun.Smoke (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./KickMaster (USA).zip</path>
		<name>KickMaster</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil wizard Belzed and his forces have attacked the kingdom of Lowrel, killed its king and queen and kidnapped princess Silphee. Players take control of aspiring martial artist Thonolan who sets out to rescue Silphee and defeat Belzed. Kick Master is a side-scrolling platformer in which enemies are defeated by using various kicks and spells. Defeated enemies drop three items that refill Thoalon's health or magic, grant an extra life, damage him or increase his experience. When Thoalan gains a level, his maximum MP is increased and he learns new kicks, such as sliding, flying, roundhouse or butterfly kicks. Along the way, he can also pick up different spells that damage his enemies, protect him or refill his health.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/KickMaster (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/KickMaster (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Micro Mages (World) (Aftermarket) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Micro Mages</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Slip into your wizard robes and enter the Demon Fortress, home of great treasure and ghastly creatures alike. Shoot and wall-jump your way up the fortress's towers and battle the evil bosses lurking at the top.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20190430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Morphcat Games</developer>
		<publisher>Morphcat Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Micro Mages (World) (Aftermarket) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Micro Mages (World) (Aftermarket) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nebs 'n Debs (World) (Aftermarket) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Nebs 'n Debs</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Run, jump, and dash your way through 12 levels as you search for the missing parts of Debs's ship to escape the hostile alien planet Vespasian 7MV!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20180101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dullahan Software</developer>
		<publisher>Broke Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nebs 'n Debs (World) (Aftermarket) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nebs 'n Debs (World) (Aftermarket) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nintendo World Cup (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nintendo World Cup</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This soccer game was made at the time when Nintendo introduced their four player adapter, and was probably made for the four playing purpose. This is shown clearly when you choose to play 2 or more players. Then you can choose between many different ground layers, like ice, grass and stone, which adds to the replayability.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nintendo World Cup (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nintendo World Cup (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Man Championship Edition (USA, Europe) (Namco Museum Archives Vol 1) (Aftermarket).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Man Championship Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Like the original Pac-Man, the basic game play of Pac-Man Championship Edition consists entirely of navigating Pac-Man through a maze, eating dots, power pellets and bonus items (such as fruits, keys, and other objects), and avoiding the four ghosts that roam the maze as well. If Pac-Man is caught by a ghost, the player loses a life. Eating a power pellet causes the ghosts to turn blue, allowing Pac-Man to eat them and send them back to their home, where they re-emerge in their original form.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20200618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>M2</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pac-Man Championship Edition (USA, Europe) (Namco Museum Archives Vol 1) (Aftermarket).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pac-Man Championship Edition (USA, Europe) (Namco Museum Archives Vol 1) (Aftermarket).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panic Restaurant (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Panic Restaurant</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Panic Restaurant is a side-scrolling platform game where you play as chef Cookie. The rival chef Ohdove has taken over his restaurant and it's up to Cookie to reclaim it. It is a fairly basic platform game. You run and jump, and enemies are placed all around to try and stop you. The entire game, backgrounds, enemies and bosses, is food-themed. You encounter things such as sausages, microwave ovens, onions and hamburgers on your way through the restaurant. To your help you always have a frying pan to beat the enemies with, and you can also find other items, such as a spoon, and plates to throw at the enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EIM</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Panic Restaurant (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Panic Restaurant (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Blade 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Power Blade 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Christmas Eve, 2200. The Delta Foundation has just finished the development of a cyborg unit which represents a new generation of fighting robots. They want to sell it to the government's department of defense as it would pose a threat to the security of the nation if it is sold to a foreign country. They have asked the president, who is actually an alien from outer space, to consider their offer and respond in one week. The government takes this matter very seriously, and assigns Nova to destroy the Delta Foundation. Unfortunately, the government cannot be involved in the event that something might happen to him.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Power Blade 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Power Blade 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puzznic (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Puzznic</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The challenge in each level of Puzznic is to maneuvre a selection of blocks into place so as to clear them all, by making them make contact with blocks of the same design. You control a cross-hair, which can move a block left or right, which can cause it to fall if there is no block under the space it would occupy.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Puzznic (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Puzznic (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret Ties (USA) (Proto).zip</path>
		<name>Secret Ties</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Secret Ties is a planned video game adaptation of Master Thief Sugar, a manga created by Takao Saito, who also made Golgo 13. Game was finished but never released. music is good! it plays much like Ninja Gaidan. Very fast pace. You can climb walls, jump kick, punch, A lot of fun.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokai Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Tokai Engineering</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Secret Ties (USA) (Proto).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret Ties (USA) (Proto).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Spike V'Ball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Spike V'Ball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bump, Set, Spike, Kabooom!! Warm up with a few exercise games then face contenders in the American Circuit. For the ultimate challenge play against the best in the World Cup.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Spike V'Ball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Spike V'Ball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle of Olympus, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Battle of Olympus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is much like Zelda II: The Adventure of Link turned into ancient Greece. You play as Orpheus, whose girlfriend, Helene, has been kidnapped by the demonic ruler of the netherworld called Hades. So begins the journey. Just like in Zelda II, there is a top-down map of Greece with towns and other locations to explore. Each of these has side-scrolling sections in which Orpheus fights his way through the minions of Hades. There are various items one must get to continue to the next location, including swords, shields and crystals. There are three fragments of love hidden around; Orpheus has to find them before he can enter Tartarus and fight Hades to save his beloved Helene.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19891202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infinity Ward</developer>
		<publisher>Broderbund Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battle of Olympus, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battle of Olympus, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lone Ranger, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Lone Ranger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the early 1880's in Texas, a man has returned to bring justice to the outlaw who murdered his brother and his former comrades, the Texas Rangers. His name is the Lone Ranger. The outlaw, whose name is Butch Cavendish, has now kidnapped the President. The time has come for the masked man to begin his journey of adventure for the purpose of safely rescuing the President and avenging the deaths of his brother and former comrades.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lone Ranger, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lone Ranger, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Young Indiana Jones Chronicles, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>The Young Indiana Jones Chronicles</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Young Indiana Jones Chronicles is based on the television series of the same name, which is in turn based on the Lucas/Spielberg movie franchise starring Harrison Ford. In this game, a young Indiana Jones embarks on globetrotting adventures in which he gathers treasure and fights for what is good and right. The game features side-scrolling action where young Indy trots along the ground, jumps, crawls flat, and can collect and wield a variety of weapons against copious enemies in the game. Indy starts with a whip and can find such weapons as throwing knives, grenades, pistols, rifles, and others. He can also collect hat powerups which allow him to sustain more damage.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Young Indiana Jones Chronicles, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Young Indiana Jones Chronicles, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Time Diver - Eon Man (USA) (Proto).zip</path>
		<name>Time Diver: Eon Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Earth, 60 years into the future. The world is virtually crime free thanks to the Clear System invented by Kane Nelson, scientist extraordinaire. That is, until a secret organization called Romedrux decides to challenge the system by unleashing a plague of crime. In order for them to succeed, they'll need to prevent the Clear System from ever being invented, and that means eliminating Kane or his ancestors. Los Angeles, 1993. Dan Nelson thought he was an ordinary student living in LA until the day he found himself under attack by Romedrux warriors. During the attack, Dan learns about his future son, Kane, and vows to protect his family past, present, and future. It's a race through time in this new sci-fi thriller from Taito!</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Time Diver - Eon Man (USA) (Proto).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Time Diver - Eon Man (USA) (Proto).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wacky Races (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Wacky Races</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Despite what the name implies, Wacky Races for NES is not a racing game, and has nothing to do with the other games bearing the same name but the license. In this game, the player takes control of Muttley, the grumbling, but loyal dog from the popular Hanna-Barbera cartoon. His master Dastardly sends his on three different missions, each taking place in a different location, which in its turn is divided into smaller levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19920501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wacky Races (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wacky Races (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hammerin' Harry (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Hammerin' Harry</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the peaceful town of Carpentersville, some workers known as The Rusty Nailers decide to bulldoze a house that belongs to Harry. Harry is certainly not happy with this, and goes on a rampage, destroying workers that get in his way. As Harry, you can destroy workers in one of two ways: you can smash them when one of them gets near them, or you can pound the ground, and by doing this, you will send shockwaves in both directions.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hammerin' Harry (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hammerin' Harry (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parodius (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Parodius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is mostly the parody of Gradius (Nemesis on some systems), with some flavor from other shoot-em-ups, like Twinbee. The series is available on numerous platforms. The game is a right-to-left scrolling shoot-em-up. You can choose from 4 different flying creatures, with different weapons. You must finish 7 stages, each having a boss at the end. You may start at either one, but must complete every level to advance to the final stage.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Palcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Parodius (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Parodius (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Get'Em Gary (Second Dimension) (2016).nes</path>
		<name>Get 'Em Gary</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The neighborhood ruffian has gone on a rampage and started destroying the buildings in Westspring Manor. Equipped with the Mystical Squeegee of Maintenance, Gary is the only one who can repair the carnage caused by Rusty. Can you repair the windows and close the shutters before time runs out?</desc>
		<releasedate>20160101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Second Dimension</developer>
		<publisher>Quiquopro Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Get'Em Gary (Second Dimension) (2016).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Get'Em Gary (Second Dimension) (2016).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twin Dragons (NESDev Compo Edition) (Glutock) (2016).nes</path>
		<name>Twin Dragons</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>On a far away island, Dinky and Minky, the Twin Dragons, live on top of a mountain with their parents, waiting for their new sibling to hatch out. One day, while their parents went hunting, the sorcerer of the neighboring remote tribe's village decided to steal the egg in order to increase his power. Help Dinky and Minky on their fantastic journey to rescue the Precious !</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Antoine Gohin</developer>
		<publisher>Broke Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Twin Dragons (NESDev Compo Edition) (Glutock) (2016).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Twin Dragons (NESDev Compo Edition) (Glutock) (2016).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Spirit: The New Legend</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Galda has decided to attack earth and it is up to you to stop him. Galda has taken Iris, the sister of Lace captive. You are Lace who, taking his father's sword, goes off to defeat Galda.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Spirit - The New Legend (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Flintstones: The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak!, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fred and Barney are searching for their children, Pebbles and Bam-Bam who got lost. When they finally find them, a volcanic eruption blocks their way and so they start going all the way around the mountain to find out why this happened and of course to save their children.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Flintstones, The - The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Flintstones, The - The Surprise at Dinosaur Peak! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor (USA).zip</path>
		<name>G.I. Joe: The Atlantis Factor</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cobra, the evil villain, previous encounter with G.I. Joe ended with Cobra's base been destroyed (as played in G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero). But this time Cobra has unlocked the secret of Atlantis. Using an ancient power source Cobra has managed to raise Atlantis out of the bottom of the ocean and now is rebuilding his forces set to destroy the world. It is up to General Hawk and his friends, all part of the Joe Team, to save the day again.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19920302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/G.I. Joe - The Atlantis Factor (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golgo_13_-_Top_Secret_Episode_U_.7z</path>
		<name>Golgo 13: Top Secret Episode</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The greatest assassin for hire in the world. A vial of the deadliest biological weapon known to man, codenamed "Cassandra G.", has been stolen and you need to recover it before someone uses it on the unsuspecting world. This is a traditionial side-scrolling game that uses a third-person view in cutscenes.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokai Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Tokai Engineering</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Golgo_13_-_Top_Secret_Episode_U_.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Golgo_13_-_Top_Secret_Episode_U_.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solar Jetman - Hunt for the Golden Warpship (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Solar Jetman: Hunt for the Golden Warpship</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The golden warpship was once the most powerful ship in the galactic fleet. But the ship was captured by aliens, and its parts scattered throughout twelve different worlds. On each world deadly aliens, booby traps, black holes, and extreme gravitational forces guard the parts. It is now up to Solar Jetman to land on each of the worlds and retrieve all the parts so the golden warpship may be reassembled.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Solar Jetman - Hunt for the Golden Warpship (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Solar Jetman - Hunt for the Golden Warpship (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Splatterhouse - Wanpaku Graffiti (World) (Namcot Collection, Namco Museum Archives Vol 1).zip</path>
		<name>Supurattāhausu: Wanpaku Gurafiti</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wanpaku Graffiti is the first Splatterhouse game to appear on a home console. It is not clear how it fits in the series' timeline, but it starts with Jennifer mourning over Rick's grave (her boyfriend). Lightning strikes his grave and he is resurrected. Before she can rejoice, another bolt strikes the grave next to him and a jack-o-lantern appears. This pumpkin king kidnaps Jennifer and Rick barely has the time to wipe off the dust from his clothes before he sets off to rescue his girlfriend.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Splatterhouse - Wanpaku Graffiti (World) (Namcot Collection, Namco Museum Archives Vol 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Splatterhouse - Wanpaku Graffiti (World) (Namcot Collection, Namco Museum Archives Vol 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. - Cooperative two-player (Super Mario Bros. modification) (1.0).nes</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. (2 Players)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Mario Bros. (2 Players) - The Princess has been kidnapped by the evil Bowser, and it is up to Mario and brother Luigi to save the day. The first ever platform adventure for the Mario Brothers has the player exploring level after level, with Bowser to contend with as the end of level boss. Power-ups include the Super Mushroom, which increases Mario's size and power, the fire flower, allowing him to shoot fireballs at enemies, and the ever important starman for a short burst of invincibility.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Bros. - Cooperative two-player (Super Mario Bros. modification) (1.0).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Bros. - Cooperative two-player (Super Mario Bros. modification) (1.0).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Town &amp; Country Surf Designs - Thrilla's Surfari (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Thrilla's Surfari</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In order to restore his immortal powers, Wazula, an evil Kahuna, is ordered to travel to Hawaii to kidnap Barbi Bikini. Barbi Bikini happens to be Thrilla Gorilla's girlfriend so now he's off to Africa so he can rescue her.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Town &amp; Country Surf Designs - Thrilla's Surfari (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Town &amp; Country Surf Designs - Thrilla's Surfari (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Champ (USA).zip</path>
		<name>World Champ: Super Boxing Great Fight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>World Champ is a boxing game that has many similarities to Data East's Ring King. You can play a one player "Ranking" mode, where you can build your boxer's stats up while climbing the ladder to eventually challenge for a championship in one of the four weight classes. There is also a two player vs. mode where you and a friend can square off. A tournament mode allows up to 8 players participate in a bracketed tournament. Gameplay consists of each boxer moving around the ring trying to land jabs, hooks, and uppercuts. The goal is to either knock your opponent out for a 10-count or have the most points on the scorecard at the end of the allotted amount of rounds.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19910401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pixel</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/World Champ (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/World Champ (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wurm - Journey to the Center of the Earth! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Wurm: Journey to the Center of the Earth!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 1999, the world is suddenly facing intensive natural disasters. Scientists are perplexed and decide that research on the inside of the earth is needed. To this end, an underground vehicle is constructed to explore the underworld. They call it the VZR, but the crew know it more commonly as a Wurm. Four different Wurms have already been dispatched and mysteriously disappeared, so a fifth Wurm vehicle is ready to launch crewed by the best and the brightest. Crew Chief Moby has been chosen to lead the mission, even though she has lost both her love and father on previous Wurm missions.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cyclone System</developer>
		<publisher>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wurm - Journey to the Center of the Earth! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wurm - Journey to the Center of the Earth! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zoda's Revenge - StarTropics II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>StarTropics II: Zoda's Revenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Mike Jones, the main character in the game. One day at Dr. Jones' office, the Oxford Wonder Word is opened and while saying the magic words; a time rift opens up and you fall in. This game is a journey through time and space, going through 8 different time shifts, and meeting some of the historical figures from the past. Your mission is to get the mystical tetrads that are located in these time periods. You run into the alien creature Zoda who is out to steal and destroy the tetrads.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zoda's Revenge - StarTropics II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zoda's Revenge - StarTropics II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. (World).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Princess has been kidnapped by the evil Bowser, and it is up to Mario and brother Luigi to save the day. The first ever platform adventure for the Mario Brothers has the player exploring level after level, with Bowser to contend with as the end of level boss. Power-ups include the Super Mushroom, which increases Mario's size and power, the fire flower, allowing him to shoot fireballs at enemies, and the ever important starman for a short burst of invincibility.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19850913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Bros. (World).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Bros. (World).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./G.I. Joe - A Real American Hero (USA).zip</path>
		<name>G.I. Joe: A Real American Hero</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>G.I Joe is a side-scrolling action game where you can select 3 out of a possible 5 characters to complete a mission. Each level is in three main parts: The fight into the mission zone, the mission zone, and the escape from the mission zone. The stages where you fight into and escape from the mission zone are straightforward action – just fight your way to the end of the stage, and defeat the stage boss.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Taxan USA Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/G.I. Joe - A Real American Hero (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/G.I. Joe - A Real American Hero (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Enter the world of off-road racing as 4 vehicles will face each other, on a series of tracks which are based around flipped and reversed versions of a core selection. Fame, glory and bikini clad women await your victories and the taste of dirt awaits if you fail. Let a computer car beat you and you lose one of your 3 credits.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Leland Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden III - The Ancient Ship of Doom (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden III: The Ancient Ship of Doom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the third entry in the series of fast-paced ninja action games, and is the last game in the series to be released on the Nintendo Entertainment System. Some time has passed since the defeat of Ashtar and the resurrected Jaquio, and Irene Lew has received a new mission to complete. She is to observe a strange factory that has been constructed recently for an unknown purpose, and investigate it. She proceeds to reconnoiter it, but is intercepted and apparently assassinated by her friend Ryu Hayabusa except it isn't Ryu. It is an imposter. The real Ryu, angered over her death, and the subsequent false accusation that he murdered her, continues her mission and proceeds to investigate the factory.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ninja Gaiden III - The Ancient Ship of Doom (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ninja Gaiden III - The Ancient Ship of Doom (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metroid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the future, the Galactic Federation and the pirates of planet Zebes are at war. Pirates have stolen an unknown life-form, recently discovered on the planet SR388. The life-form, designated "Metroid", is in a state of suspended animation and, according to analysis, was the cause of the complete destruction of SR388. If the Metroid ever got loose, the alien could destroy countless other systems. It is up to the space bounty hunter Samus Aran to land on Zebes and find her way through the perilous terrains of Brinstar and Norfair.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19860801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metroid (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metroid (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./EarthBound Beginnings (USA, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>EarthBound Beginnings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Earthbound Beginnings is a Japanese-style RPG set in modern times. Combat system is similar to Dragon Warrior: the player-controlled party encounters random enemies and bosses, and fights them in turn-based combat viewed from first-person perspective. Instead of magic, the characters can use special psychic powers called PSI.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ape, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/EarthBound Beginnings (USA, Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/EarthBound Beginnings (USA, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Formula One - Built to Win (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Formula One: Built to Win</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Formula One: Born To Win is a career racing game. The player begins with a Mini Cooper and claws up the ranks of the racing circuit starting with the lowest ranked races in the eastern part of the United States. By winning races, the player can upgrade parts on the Mini and have a better shot at more races. Win enough races and eventually earn the opportunity to race using faster cars. The other cars available in the game are the Vector W2, Ferrari F40, and of course, the Formula 1. The first races take place in New York City, Detroit, and Miami. The other locales to visit are Yellowstone, Denver, Dallas, Las Vegas, Los Angeles, San Francisco, and finally Hawaii.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Winky Soft</developer>
		<publisher>SETA Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Formula One - Built to Win (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Formula One - Built to Win (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gaplus (World) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Gaplus</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gaplus is a sequel to Galaga and has similar gameplay. The player controls a spaceship, that can now move vertically (limited to halfway up the screen, much like Atari's Centipede) as well as horizontally, and shoots at swarms of incoming insect-like aliens which fly in formation above it and swoop down to attack it in a kamikaze-like dive. In this sequel, the level starts over if the player gets killed before all the enemies have come in. When all enemies are killed, the player moves on to the next level.</desc>
		<releasedate>20200618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gaplus (World) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gaplus (World) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jay and Silent Bob - Mall Brawl (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Jay and Silent Bob: Mall Brawl</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Play as Jay and Silent Bob in a retro 8-bit sidescrolling brawler solo or with a friend. Pummel enemies with hard-hitting combos, dash attacks, and elbow drops as well as a random assortment of weapons as you battle your way out of the mall and back to the Quickstop.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20200101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interabang Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interabang Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jay and Silent Bob - Mall Brawl (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jay and Silent Bob - Mall Brawl (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Noah's Ark (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Noah's Ark</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Noah has been commanded by God to put two of each animal aboard his ark to save them from the flood. However unhappy people from around the world have captured different animal species, preventing Noah from doing his job. Noah will need to visit these different locations and free the animals from the people holding them captive.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Source Research &amp; Development Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Noah's Ark (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Noah's Ark (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paperboy (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Paperboy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, the object of Paperboy is to deliver papers to your customers while inflicting as much damage as possible to the houses of your non-customers. To make things more difficult, numerous obstacles get in your way including construction workers, rogue tires, skateboarders, dogs and cats, cars, and even the occasional tornado.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Paperboy (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Paperboy (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rampart (USA) (Jaleco).zip</path>
		<name>Rampart</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The objective is brutally simple: engage your enemy in an all-out exchange of cannonfire, then assess the damage and rebuild your castle. But the reality of RAMPART is far more complex. The key to victory lies in how quickly you can pick up the pieces and redesign, refortify, and extend your walls before the next battle begins. Whether you're facing an onslaught from the computer's armada, or pitting your castle cannons against another player's, there's only one way out. Defend or perish.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rampart (USA) (Jaleco).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rampart (USA) (Jaleco).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rollie (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Rollie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rollie and Lorrie are on a mission to save their forest, Paradise Gorge. Their goal is to defeat the brats and bullies who have seized power in the midst of an unstable ecosystem precipitated by a sudden overpopulation of snakes. They aim to lead as examples, to show how sharing and sacrifice are rewarding, and that rampant self-serving brutality perpetuates destruction.</desc>
		<releasedate>20200102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chris Lincoln</developer>
		<publisher>Chris Lincoln</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rollie (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rollie (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Slalom (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Slalom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Slalom you need to ski down different trails and beat the clock to move on to the next of the 24 trails. Other skiers, trees, snowmen, sledders, and moguls will get in your way and slow you down if you crash into them. Slalom flags are located throughout the trails, and skiing on the wrong side of these will cause your player to snowplow momentarily and lose speed, so to get the best times you need to make sure none of the flags are missed.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19870801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Slalom (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Slalom (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Starship Hector (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Starship Hector</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A top-down/side-scrolling sci-fi shooter in which you take control of a small starfighter as you make your way through an alien planet with your objective being to destroy all enemy forces. Your ship is equipped with both a standard laser and an independently fired ground weapon, which you must coordinate to defeat ground and aerial enemies. A shield bar keeps track of your damage and you can replenish it by defeating certain enemies, but otherwise its just you, your ship and several stages of alien enemies that alternate between top-down and side-scrolling perspectives.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Starship Hector (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Starship Hector (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter 2010: The Final Fight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player is Ken, the hero of the Street Fighter series. It's been 25 years since he last participated in a fighting tournament. He has become a scientist and has developed a powerful medicine together with his friend Troy. But an unknown fiend breaks into his laboratory, kills Troy, and steals the invention. It's time to recall the good old days and to embark on a quest for revenge!</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter 2010 - The Final Fight (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Strider (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Strider</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Striders are a global organization of infiltration specialists who work to combat villainy and keep the world safe. From their orbital space station, the Blue Dragon, they are able to quickly reach anywhere in the world. Hiryu is one of the top striders. He is given the task by Vice-Director Matic, of finding another captured strider, Kain. But rather than mount a rescue, Hiryu is told his assignment is to kill Kain. Hiryu questions these orders and travels to Kain's last known location to try to find him.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Strider (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Strider (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bat Puncher (USA) (Unl) (Demo).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bat Puncher</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Bat Puncher is an original homebrew game for the NES console. Explore the dark caverns of a mysterious planet and find out about the plague that threatens Earth.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20110101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Morphcat Games</developer>
		<publisher>Morphcat Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Bat Puncher (USA) (Unl) (Demo).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Bat Puncher (USA) (Unl) (Demo).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tecmo World Cup Soccer (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo World Cup Soccer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tecmo World Cup Soccer is a NES conversion of the arcade original Tehkan World Cup. At its base, it is a simple soccer game with an overhead view. Only one mode (World Cup) is available, playable by either one player against the computer AI or two players against each other. Any of the sixteen available national teams can be selected by the player; the opponent cannot be chosen manually if controlled by the AI. The game itself allows only basic moves such as passing, shooting, and side-sliding during defense. There is no team management or strategy available, and no options for game rules and conditions.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19901207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tecmo World Cup Soccer (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tecmo World Cup Soccer (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toki (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Toki</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The hero of the game is a young jungle-man named Toki. One day the evil wizard Dr. Stark kidnaps his girlfriend Wanda. When Toki tries to save her, he is turned into a monkey! Now Toki has to find Dr. Stark in his palace, to rescue Wanda, and to become a human being again! It is a platform game with a lot of various levels: jungle, underwater, volcanic caves, on the ice. Toki's only weapons are spitting on the enemies or jumping on them and crashing them. There are many possibilities to upgrade his spitting "weapon" for example, if he finds an upgrade, he can spit fireballs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tad Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Toki (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Toki (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Track &amp; Field II (USA) (Rev A).zip</path>
		<name>Track &amp; Field II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Track &amp; Field II is a game that allows the player to have an experience based around the Summer Olympic games. Playable events include fencing, the triple jump, swimming, diving, skeet shooting, pole vaulting, Tae Kwon Do, hammer throwing, canoing, archery, hurdles, and the horizontal bar.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Track &amp; Field II (USA) (Rev A).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Track &amp; Field II (USA) (Rev A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trophy (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Trophy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Trophy, you must navigate challenging environmental obstacles and terrain, such as water, snow, moving platforms, and even zero gravity. Collect power-ups and upgrade Trophy's health and weapon systems, all while battling enemies throughout the levels. Be prepared, though, as at the end of each level you will have to square off against one of the largest bosses ever seen on the NES!</desc>
		<releasedate>20201201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>E.B.D. Holland</developer>
		<publisher>E.B.D. Holland</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Trophy (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Trophy (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultima - Quest of the Avatar (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ultima: Quest of the Avatar</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Following the defeat of the evil triad in the previous three Ultima games, the world of Sosaria changed beyond recognition: continents rose and sank, and new cities were built, heralding the advent of a different civilization. Unified by the reign of the benevolent monarch Lord British, the new world was renamed Britannia. Lord British wished to base people's well-being on the ethical principles of Truth, Love, and Courage, proclaiming the Eight Virtues (Honesty, Compassion, Valor, Justice, Sacrifice, Honor, Spirituality, and Humility) as the ideal everyone should strive for.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>FCI</developer>
		<publisher>FCI</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultima - Quest of the Avatar (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultima - Quest of the Avatar (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Whomp 'Em (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Whomp 'Em</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Whomp 'Em tells the tale of a little Native American Indian named Soaring Eagle who is on a quest to fill his magic pouch with totems. These totems are guarded by fearsome bosses at the end of different environments spread throughout the land. Each totem gives Soaring Eagle a new power to help him complete his journey.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Whomp 'Em (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Whomp 'Em (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombie Nation (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Zombie Nation</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 1999 a mysterious object crashes into the desert and a mysterious creature, Darc Seed appears. Using magnetic powers, he soon turns the people of the United States into zombies and exerts influence over various weapons and objects. Among the weapons Darc Seed claims is the legendary samurai sword, Shura. When the great head of the samurai, Namakubi hears about this, he sets out for the United States to defeat Darc Seed and reclaim the sword.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze</developer>
		<publisher>Meldac</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zombie Nation (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zombie Nation (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (USA).zip</path>
		<name>P.O.W.: Prisoners of War</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The enemy is unstoppable. They maintain vigilant guard over their front lines! The only way to defeat them is to get behind their lines. But how? By allowing a soldier to get captured, perhaps he could escape and single-handedly defeat the enemy forces in his way. In P.O.W., the player is a soldier who has been imprisoned in a Prisoner of War camp and must escape. In order to accomplish this, he must defeat a variety of enemies. The foes will attack you hand-to-hand, with knives, guns, and from helicopters. Boss enemies will guard the end of each level.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19890901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/P.O.W. - Prisoners of War (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kung Fu (Japan, USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kung Fu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You'll need lightning fast reactions to knock out the Knife Thrower, stop the Stick Fighter, and trip up the evil Tom Tom Brothers in this action-packed martial arts contest! Are you sure you're tough enough? Because it'll take all your strength and skill to master the moves in KUNG FU, beat your opponents, and rescue the fair Sylvia who's held captive on the top floor! The action is non-stop, and just when you think you've got your enemies licked there's always a Giant, a Snake, or a fire-breathing Dragon to contend with in KUNG FU!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19851002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kung Fu (Japan, USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kung Fu (Japan, USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gauntlet II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, Gauntlet II is very similar to the original. Up to four players (a wizard, a warrior, an elf, and a valkyrie) make their way through various mazes, collect treasures and magic potions, and fend off assorted creatures and ghosts.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gauntlet II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gauntlet II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gauntlet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gauntlet, the original arcade smash hit, is a fighting game where you choose a character and let rip into the hordes of enemies that assault you on you way to the end of the level. One or two players must make their way through 100 levels of mayhem and magic.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19850101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tengen</developer>
		<publisher>Tengen</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gauntlet (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gauntlet (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jaws (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Jaws</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Loosely based on the fourth movie "Jaws: the Revenge", players take control of a ship to sail the ocean in the search for the killer shark. Along the way, the ship will stop to allow a diver to swim out and kill baby sharks, jellyfish and manta rays to find conch shells. The conch shells are used to buy upgrades for the boat. Extra conch shells can be earned in bonus rounds where a sea plane flies over the water to bomb jellyfish (think the bonus rounds of Galaga with reversed perspective).</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19871101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westone</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jaws (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jaws (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of many different titles based on Steven Spielberg's 1993 dinosaur thriller, the version for NES and Game Boy is a top-down action game with exploration elements. Playing as Dr. Alan Grant, the player must work through six levels by completing certain objectives including rescuing the kids Tim and Lex, restoring power, destroying Raptor nests and finally getting off the dinosaur-infested island. To advance in a level, a number of dinosaur eggs scattered over the area must be collected or destroyed.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jurassic Park (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jurassic Park (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TaleSpin (USA).zip</path>
		<name>TaleSpin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the Disney cartoon Talespin. Baloo's airline cargo company, Higher for Hire, makes deliveries all around the world. The air pirates, lead by the daring Don Karnage have increased their attacks against air travel. In order to foil the plans of the pirates, Baloo trades in his normal plane for a "Mini Sea Duck", designed to fly more maneuverably.To get his cargo delivered on time, Baloo must fly over many dangerous areas, and also pick up any cargo stolen or scattered by the air pirates. Eventually, the fortress of the air pirates themselves must be destroyed for air travel to remain safe and profitable.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/TaleSpin (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/TaleSpin (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Gun (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Top Gun</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Top Gun is loosely based on the film of the same name. It is an action game in which the player controls an F-14 Tomcat fighter through four different missions. The action is seen from a first-person cockpit view. Depending on the mission, different kinds of targets must be destroyed. There are always enemy aircraft, but some missions include sea and ground targets as well. Two weapons are available: machine guns (with unlimited ammunition) and missiles. The player can choose from three types of missiles before a mission: the more powerful ones can only be carried in lower quantities.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19871102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Top Gun (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Top Gun (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hatris (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Hatris</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Hatris, the falling blocks of Tetris are replaced by falling hats which are top hats, cowboy hats, baseball caps, derbys, party hats and crowns. The setting is a hat factory, where hats are dropped down from a conveyor belt two at a time and must be stacked on one of six mannequin heads. Once five hats of the same kind have been stacked on top of each other, they fall down onto another conveyor belt below and are shipped out of the factory, rewarding the player with a cash bonus.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900706T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet Proof Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hatris (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hatris (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Simpsons, The - Bart vs. the World (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Simpsons: Bart vs. the World, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Krusty the clown appears in the beginning of the game and presents a menu with five games to play (one of which is not available from the start): A jump-and-run game, where Bart must find an exit on a ship, while enemies fire at him and try to prevent him from reaching the exit; a card game, where you have five tries to find hidden cards on a board; a simple jigsaw puzzle; a series of trivia questions concerning the Simpsons; and finally, a platform-skateboard game (available only after you have completed the ship level).</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19911201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Simpsons, The - Bart vs. the World (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Simpsons, The - Bart vs. the World (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Bros. 2 (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One night Mario has a strange dream, where he opens a door to another world filled with even stranger creatures and lands then those in his last adventure against Bowser. Amazingly, the next day, Mario, Luigi, Toad, and the Princess stumble upon a cave, which leads to the world that was in Mario's dream. Subcon, the land of dreams, is under an evil spell thanks to Wart, so Mario and the gang must save the day.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19890428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Bros. 2 (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Bros. 2 (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of the Wizard (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Legacy of the Wizard</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Long ago, an evil dragon named Keela was imprisoned inside a magical dungeon. However time has passed and the magic that sealed the dragon away is weakening. The Drasle family decides that it's time to destroy the dragon once and for all. However only one weapon is capable of doing this, the Dragon Slayer, which is itself sealed away by four magical crowns. The Drasle family decides to take on this quest, and will use every member of the family in order to accomplish it.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Broderbund Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nihon Falcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Legacy of the Wizard (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legacy of the Wizard (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lizard (Rainwarrior) (2018).nes</path>
		<name>Lizard</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Choose your lizard carefully. You can find six different ones scattered across the land, each with its own special ability. You'll need these abilities as you make your difficult journey through many dangerous places. Carefully hop your way to the top of an active volcano. Surf down a surging river. Swim an underwater lake. Ascend a snowy mountaintop. What kind of strange creatures will you meet? Can you unravel the mysteries of Lizard?</desc>
		<releasedate>20180101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Brad Smith </developer>
		<publisher>Brad Smith </publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Lizard (Rainwarrior) (2018).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lizard (Rainwarrior) (2018).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mad Wizard, The - A Candelabra Chronicle (Sly Dog Studios) (2015).nes</path>
		<name>Mad Wizard: A Candelabra Chronicle, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil summoner Amondus from The Order of the Talon has taken over Prim, Hekl's once happy homeland. And nothing drives a wizard more crazy than having their territory trampled on!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20180101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retrozone</developer>
		<publisher>Sly Dog Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Mad Wizard, The - A Candelabra Chronicle (Sly Dog Studios) (2015).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mad Wizard, The - A Candelabra Chronicle (Sly Dog Studios) (2015).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project Blue (NESDev Compo Edition) (Toggle Switch &amp; Frankengraphics) (2017).nes</path>
		<name>Project Blue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the dystopian wasteland of Neo Hong Kong, help Blue escape from the evil clutches of the Omnicorp conglomerate. Avoid robots, lasers, pools of toxic waste, and more as you fight your way out of a research facility and exact revenge upon your captors.</desc>
		<releasedate>20190101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toggleswitch</developer>
		<publisher>Broke Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Project Blue (NESDev Compo Edition) (Toggle Switch &amp; Frankengraphics) (2017).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Project Blue (NESDev Compo Edition) (Toggle Switch &amp; Frankengraphics) (2017).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quest Forge by Order of Kings (Ludosity) (2015).nes</path>
		<name>Quest Forge by Order of Kings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Sir Nils, knight of the castle Axvald, and the king needs your help. The world orb has been stolen and the demon gate can now be opened. By the orders of the king, you have to stop whoever is plotting to unleash evil on these lands.</desc>
		<releasedate>20150101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ludosity</developer>
		<publisher>Ludosity</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Quest Forge by Order of Kings (Ludosity) (2015).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Quest Forge by Order of Kings (Ludosity) (2015).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R.B.I. Baseball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>R.B.I. Baseball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Here's the baseball action that started it all - the one, the only, the original RBI. With permission from the Major League Players Association, this game uses the names and likenesses of real baseball players. This means the ten different teams in the Tengen league can have lineups that include baseball stars of the time; such as Reggie Jackson, Fernando Valenzuela, and Willie McGee. Stats and abilities have been structured to give each player strengths and weaknesses he had in the 1986 and 1987 seasons. You'll have to use your knowledge of real players and teams to manage your lineup effectively.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19880101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/R.B.I. Baseball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R.B.I. Baseball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Haunted Halloween 85.zip</path>
		<name>Haunted: Halloween '85</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Haunted: Halloween '85 is a new NES homebrew game featuring side-scrolling, platforming, beat 'em up action! It was originally released on cartridge in October of 2015 for the original Nintendo.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retrotainment Games</developer>
		<publisher>Retrotainment Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Haunted Halloween 85.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Haunted Halloween 85.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Haunted Halloween 86.zip</path>
		<name>Haunted Halloween '86: The Curse of Possum Hollow</name>
		<sortname>Haunted: Halloween '86</sortname>
		<desc>The year is 1986 and the town of Possum Hollow is under siege again. Harry has summoned a new pack of haunted henchmen from the depths to rise up and take control on the most evil of nights, Halloween Night.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mega Cat Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Mega Cat Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Haunted Halloween 86.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Haunted Halloween 86.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow of the Ninja (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shadow of the Ninja</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the 21st century, the evil Emperor Garuda has taken over the city of New York, killing many of its inhabitants. You play as either Hayate or Kaede, two ninjas who are attempting to free the city from Garuda's control.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19901202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadow of the Ninja (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadow of the Ninja (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legends of Owlia (Gradual Games) (2016).nes</path>
		<name>The Legends of Owlia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Legends of Owlia is Gradual Games' second release for the NES. It is an action-adventure game inspired by StarTropics, Crystalis, and the Legend of Zelda.</desc>
		<releasedate>20160601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gradual Games</developer>
		<publisher>Gradual Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Legends of Owlia (Gradual Games) (2016).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legends of Owlia (Gradual Games) (2016).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1943 - The Battle of Midway (USA).zip</path>
		<name>1943: The Battle of Midway</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to 1942, which is still a vertically scrolling shooter, has the player once again fighting over the clouds during the second world war, this time in an intense battle just off the coast of Midway islands. Updates to the gameplay include an energy bar, which can be run down by either being hit from incoming fire or using a special weapon. The energy bar can be replenished by picking up power-ups, while special weapons (lightning, cyclones and waves) can knock down all fighters on the screen at the time.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19881002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/1943 - The Battle of Midway (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1943 - The Battle of Midway (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3-D WorldRunner (USA).zip</path>
		<name>3-D WorldRunner</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Somewhere in a place known as Solar System #517, the evil Grax and his horde of Serpentbeasts are terrorizing the people of the eight worlds. A hero is needed who can run and jump. Jump between worlds, in fact. That hero is the WorldRunner.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19870901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/3-D WorldRunner (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3-D WorldRunner (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./David Crane's A Boy and His Blob - Trouble on Blobolonia (USA).zip</path>
		<name>A Boy and His Blob: Trouble on Blobolonia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blob has come from the distant planet Blobolonia in search of an earth boy to help him save his world. Join him on this fantastic adventure in mysterious caverns beneath the earth searching for treasure. then travel to Blobolonia to battle the evil emperor. Discover Blob's amazing appetite for jellybeans and the different transformations that occur with each flavor. Learn to use these shapes to overcome even the most outrageous obstacles.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineering</developer>
		<publisher>Absolute Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/David Crane's A Boy and His Blob - Trouble on Blobolonia (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/David Crane's A Boy and His Blob - Trouble on Blobolonia (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightmare on Elm Street, A (USA).zip</path>
		<name>A Nightmare on Elm Street</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The classic horror series casts the player as a teen searching the houses on Elm Street for Freddy Krueger's bones. Once they are all collected, they must be thrown into the high school furnace to destroy Freddy once and for all (a plot similar to 1987's A Nightmare on Elm Street 3: Dream Warriors).</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19901002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nightmare on Elm Street, A (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nightmare on Elm Street, A (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Abadox - The Deadly Inner War (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Abadox: The Deadly Inner War</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Somewhere in the galaxy, a huge alien space creature known as Parasitis travels between realms digesting it's pray. It's latest victim is the planet Abadox which is now consumed by the alien entity. However, in order to digest this planet, Parasitis has had to assume to form of the planet itself. Abadox's starfleet, the World Alive Force (WAF) uses this time to launch an all out assault on the alien lifeform, of which you are a single soldier.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Abadox - The Deadly Inner War (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Abadox - The Deadly Inner War (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the South Pacific, Master Higgins lives peacefully wearing only a grass skirt and a cap. That is until the Evil Witch Doctor decides to capture the Princess Leilani and hold her as his own. It's up to Master Higgins to gather throwing axes, fireballs and skateboards in order to aid his noble quest. The game is a side scroller, Master Higgins moves across the screen from left to right and finds his power-ups in giant eggs. This includes a skateboard which results in a great speed enhancement - until Master Higgins gets hit and loses his power. If he is not on a skateboard a hit means instant death.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19880902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventure Island (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventure Island (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island II</name>
		<sortname>Adventure Island 2</sortname>
		<desc>In Adventure Island II: Aliens in Paradise the player takes the role of Master Higgins who has to save his cavegirl from aliens which also want to dominate the Earth. The basic gameplay elements are the same as in its predecessor Adventure Island: Master Higgins walks through the levels while fighting against various enemies. One hit results in his untimely death unless he carries one of the various power ups, e.g. weapons or a skateboard which improves his speed. He also needs to collect food to fill up his steadily decreasing starvation bar - death awaits if it hits zero.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19910202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventure Island II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventure Island II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventure Island 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventure Island 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your girlfriend is once again kidnapped by aliens, and you have to rescue her, forcing your way through various levels. The gameplay and the design haven't much changed since Adventure Island II: there is a world map, you can choose items before starting a level, the levels themselves are quite short (unlike Adventure Island, where each large level contained several stages). You perform standard "adventure island" activities: ride various types of dinosaurs, throw boomerangs at snails, birds, snakes, and skulls, collect grapes and apples, jump over stones, and of course, ride your old trusty skateboard.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventure Island 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventure Island 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Dino Riki (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Dino Riki</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Somewhere in the land of dinosaurs, a hero known as Dino-Riki sets out to battle against the beasts of the ancient times and prove man's right to survival amongst evolution. You control Dino-Riki from a top-down perspective as the screen scrolls towards the top. Dino Riki must shoot the enemies in his way as well as leap over pits and avoid obstacles. His chances improve when he obtains weapon power-ups such as fireballs or boomerangs. Angel Wings also help and let Dino Riki fly above the ground. At the end of each level, Dino-Riki faces off against a boss creature.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19890902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventures of Dino Riki (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventures of Dino Riki (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Lolo (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Lolo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The lovely princess Lala was kidnapped by the Evil Demons of the Empire. You are Lolo, a round ball-like creature (just like the princess herself), and your mission is to sneak into the empire castle and to liberate the princess. Adventures of Lolo is a puzzle game, and each level is a castle room. The goal in each room is to collect all the hearts. It is not always easy, because some hearts are blocked by enemies who will shoot you when you cross their path horizontally or vertically (or both).</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventures of Lolo (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventures of Lolo (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Lolo 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Lolo 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Adventures of Lolo 2 is a sequel to Adventures of Lolo (NES). Once again, the brave blue ball-like Lolo has to save the princess from the evil demons, who kidnapped her and imprisoned her in a high tower. Solve puzzles to proceed from room to room. Push tiles, eat hearts, turn green dragons into white eggs, and protect yourself from enemies firing at you and chasing you all over the room.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventures of Lolo 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventures of Lolo 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Lolo 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Lolo 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This time, Lolo has a red friend who will do for him some of the work. Unlike the two previous Lolo games, here you can wander around a world map and enter different locations in a non-linear fashion. However, some of the locations remain blocked until you find a key after completing another level. The gameplay is very similar to the one of the two previous games. You have to collect all the hearts in each room. Enemies will prevent you from doing that, and others will appear once you have eaten all the hearts and are hurrying towards the exit. The puzzles involve mostly pushing things to prevent enemies from stopping you.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Adventures of Lolo 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventures of Lolo 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Air Fortress (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Air Fortress</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Federation of Intergalactic Powers is under threat by gigantic fortress spaceships which have suddenly appeared and destroyed nearby civilization. When conventional defense tactics fail, the Federation looks to find a specially selected person, Hal Bailman and equip him with a special "Lightship". His mission will to be to fly through the defenses of the eight known Air Fortresses and dock at the airlock. Then he must travel through the fortress in only a spacesuit to find and destroy the central core. Once the central core is destroyed, Hal must then quickly find the emergency lightship and escape before the fortress explodes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Air Fortress (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Air Fortress (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kid_Dracula_USA_Europe_Castlevania_Anniversary_Collection.zip</path>
		<name>Akumajō Special: Boku Dracula-kun</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Akumajō Special: Boku Dracula-kun Kid is an unusual side-scroller from Konami. It's a parody of the company's popular Castlevania series. Instead of playing as a member of the Belmont family, you play as young Kid Dracula. You have been woken up from your sleep by the evil demon Garamos, who's been wrecking havoc in Dracula's Castle. It's up to you to stop him by traveling across several different locations, including Dracula's Castle, New York, the Sea, and Egypt!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19901019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Kid_Dracula_USA_Europe_Castlevania_Anniversary_Collection.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kid_Dracula_USA_Europe_Castlevania_Anniversary_Collection.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Archon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Archon: The Light and the Dark</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A chess board is lined with trolls, wizards, knights and other magical beings. Just another strategy game? Don't count on it. When you challenge a square held by the enemy, the board explodes into a battlefield. Your strategic skills on the game board will determine your fate in battle as you take on your opponent in a heartpounding duel to the death.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Free Fall Associates</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Archon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Archon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assimilate (RetroUSB) (2012).nes</path>
		<name>Assimilate!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Assimilate! itself is a very simple retro-style game, in the mold of the NES's earliest titles which were mostly ports from the arcades. You control an alien spaceship named Ossan. The goal of each level is to maneuver Ossan around a series of deadly projectiles and enemies while kidnapping and assimilating the humans below. Scoop up a human with your tractor beam and use one of four tools to convert them into your alien slave. Then, plant them back in the same building from which you picked them up without dropping them. The level is completed when you have assimilated 100% of the humans in the level.</desc>
		<releasedate>20120209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toggleswitch</developer>
		<publisher>Nessylum Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Assimilate (RetroUSB) (2012).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Assimilate (RetroUSB) (2012).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Astyanax (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Astyanax</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are Astyanax, a sixteen year old boy that has the same dream night after night: A princess, calling for help. One afternoon, you are summoned to the world of Remnia by Cutie, a pixie, to save the realm's princess. You are the chosen one mentioned by their prophecies! Yes, this is your typical fantasy story setting. You must save the realm from Blackhorn's evil horde! Along the way you'll find powerups that will make you stronger, and upgrade your weapon; and you can also unleash magical attacks that hit all enemies on the screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Astyanax (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Astyanax (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bad Dudes (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bad Dudes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This six-level action game was converted from a Data East coin-op. The gameplay involving beating a succession of guys to complete the level, then an end-of-level bad guy. The action takes place on two different levels of the screen, which can be jumped across or navigated using ladders. Moves such as punches and kicks are on offer. The control method makes jumping sideways quite tricky.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bad Dudes (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bad Dudes (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bad News Baseball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bad News Baseball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Welcome to the world of Bad News Baseball, a place where rabbits serve as umpires, home runs escape the earth's atmosphere, and batters are knocked unconscious when they make an out.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bad News Baseball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bad News Baseball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Balloon Fight (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Balloon Fight</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Balloon Fight you need to fly around with the aid of two balloons and try to pop your opponents balloons before they pop yours. Landing on top of your opponents will cause their balloon to pop and they will use a parachute to fall to safety. You then need to destroy the fallen opponent by running into it before it can blow up a new balloon and rejoin the battle. Should both of your balloons get popped, you will fall into the water below and lose a life. There is also a second game variation called "balloon trip" where you need to collect as many balloons as possible while avoiding the ocean below and lightning which forms maze like walls.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19860602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Balloon Fight (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Balloon Fight (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Baseball Stars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This NES version of Baseball Stars is the very first game in SNK's popular series. It is also the most comprehensive game in the series. You can create, name, upgrade, and manage your own team, as well as customize the team's logo and colors. You can also change the stats of each individual player by paying him or her more money (earned from winning games). There are eight already-created gimmick teams that you can also play with, including the American Dreams, Lovely Ladies, and the Ghastly Monsters. You can set up a custom league which will keep complete stats on all players in the league. All games are played in the famous SNK Stadium.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19890701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Baseball Stars (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Baseball Stars (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Baseball Stars II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Baseball Stars II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The second in the Baseball Stars series, Baseball Stars 2 was done by Romstar. Contains a more polished baseball game at the expense of a few of the customizing features that the first Baseball Stars had. The returning features include a create-a-team mode, upgrading and hiring/firing players, and league mode. Missing features removed for this game include renaming players, renaming teams, and females are no longer present. This sequel contains 12 pre-made teams and 6 slots for user created teams. There are four selectable stadiums to play in this time around.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pixel</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Baseball Stars II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Baseball Stars II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bases Loaded (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bases Loaded</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bases Loaded is a baseball action game for one or two players featuring a large variety of options and realistic graphics and sound. You can select from twelve different teams and choose a lineup for each team. Each team has 30 players with different characteristics to learn. During gameplay you can control all of the positions in the field and pitch everything from a fast ball to curve ball. When at bat you can try to hit a homerun, bunt, or steal bases. Play can be a single game or a complete pennant.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19880701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bases Loaded (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bases Loaded (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - Return of the Joker (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Batman: Return of the Joker</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Joker lives again in SunSoft's sequel to their NES original. The Joker has somehow managed to escape from Arkham Asylum once again, and Batman must fight him across seven stages to restore peace to Gotham City. Batman carries a gauntlet shooting basic bullets by default. This can be upgraded with weapon powerups located in boxes throughout the level, giving access to homing and energy weapons. Every upgrade weapon can be charged up for a secondary attack, different for each weapon. Batman also has a slide useful against most enemies and some bosses.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19911202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Batman - Return of the Joker (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman - Return of the Joker (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Video Game (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Batman: The Video Game</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The NES version of Batman: The Video Game is loosely based on the 1989 movie. It is a side-scrolling game, with a blue dressed Batman fighting enemies such as robots, jet-packed soldiers, ninjas and mutants. The game consists in five levels somewhat related to the movie: Gotham City streets (with Killer Moth as the final boss), AXIS Chemical Factory (with Machine Intelligence System as boss), Underground Conduit (with Electrocutioner as boss), the Laboratory Ruins (the Dual-Container Alarm as boss) and Gotham's Cathedral (with Firebug as boss) where Batman finally faces the Joker. Before each level, a cutscene with scenes from the movie is displayed.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Batman - The Video Game (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman - The Video Game (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Kid - Fortress of Peril.zip</path>
		<name>Battle Kid: Fortress Of Peril</name>
		<sortname>Battle Kid 1</sortname>
		<desc>Battle Kid: Fortress Of Peril is a homebrew 2D platform video game, released in February 2010 for the Nintendo Entertainment System, created by American developer Sivak Games, and published through Retrozone with the cover art designed by Larry Bundy Jr. Unlike most games in the modern era, Battle Kid is available for purchase only on a physical NES cartridge. While there has been a demand for a downloadable version, the developer has stated that the game is currently not planned to be released on any other formats due to a contract with Retrozone.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20100222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sivak Games</developer>
		<publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Battle Kid - Fortress of Peril.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battle Kid - Fortress of Peril.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battle Kid 2 - Mountain of Torment (USA) (V1.000) (Aftermarket).zip</path>
		<name>Battle Kid 2: Mountain of Torment</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Battle Kid 2: Mountain of Torment is a homebrew developed for Sivak Games that mixes the concepts of “I Wanna Be The Guy” (for the design of the hero and his pistol and for the “Die and Retry” mechanics), and Mega Man (for the boss battles) . The hero dies as soon as he is hit, but the player has infinite continues. There are 500 rooms, 30 different types of enemies and multiple difficulty options. The second opus added new features like new types of ice block, enemies and mud, an improved "Wall-Grip", a death counter and an introduction level.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20121215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sivak Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sivak Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Battle Kid 2 - Mountain of Torment (USA) (V1.000) (Aftermarket).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battle Kid 2 - Mountain of Torment (USA) (V1.000) (Aftermarket).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Dark Queen has attacked and kidnapped (toadnapped?) your best buddy.. To make matters worse, she nabbed the best looking girl around! So, what will you do? Cry? Whimper? Hide? Call the Starcops? NO! Cause you're a Battletoad! Battletoads don't cry, hide or call for help! And they certainly don't whimper! They get MAD then they get EVEN! So grab your blaster, hop on the Toadster and go get 'em! You will control a battletoad through various levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battletoads (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battletoads (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Earth is under fire by Colossus, a battleship the size of a city. Using powerful laser cannons, it has destroyed most of Earth's defence forces, while its many troops clean up the rest of the planet. All expect for 5 warriors. The Battletoads, who are well aware of evil forces in the galaxy, join forces with Billy and Jimmy Lee from Double Dragon to defend Earth from the deadly ship and its troops. Using a range of special moves you must fight your way through the streets into the heart of the ship and destroy it.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bee 52 (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Bee 52</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are bee number 52, and you need to collect enough honey every day to fill your quota. But the backyard can be a dangerous place for a bee! Spiders, grasshoppers, assorted bugs, and even lawn sprinklers are all over the place and try to stop bee 52 from reaching the many flowers where honey can be collected. Even after collecting honey, you may need to defend your nest against ants who will try to sneek in and steal honey from you.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camerica</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bee 52 (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bee 52 (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bio Force Ape (Japan) (En) (Proto).zip</path>
		<name>Bio Force Ape</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bio Force Ape allows you to play as a pet chimpanzee who must rescue his family by taking the mysterious Bio Force serum and mutating into a pro wrestler. It was the recipient of an extremely positive profile in Nintendo Power - "extremely positive" being NP's default setting back in the day - but then vanished, presumably never to be seen again. Last week, though, the archivists at Lost Levels not only acquired the long-lost prototype cartridge, but uploaded a playable version of it to the Internet.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Lost Levels</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Bio Force Ape (Japan) (En) (Proto).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bio Force Ape (Japan) (En) (Proto).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bionic Commando (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bionic Commando</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play a soldier with a bionic arm that extends and contracts. Your arm allows you to grab on to fixed objects to swing around and climb up levels -- no jumping allowed! The arm also grabs opponents and pull them towards you. Your mission is to infiltrate the enemy fortress, find your missing comrade, "Super Joe", and take out the evil leader, "Generalissimo Kilt", of the invading force that has been attacking your people for the last 2 years.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19881202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Bionic Commando (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bionic Commando (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Black Box Challenge (Sly Dog Studios) (2017).nes</path>
		<name>Black Box Challenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Can you brave the sewers in your quest? Can you overcome the heat of the desert and the unknown paths through the junkyard? Will you be able to stand the spookiness of an actual pirate ship? Find out in Black Box Challenge, a brand-new RPG for the NES, and prove to the Evil Overlord that you are a worthy collector!</desc>
		<releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sly Dog Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Hagen’s Alley</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Black Box Challenge (Sly Dog Studios) (2017).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Black Box Challenge (Sly Dog Studios) (2017).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blades of Steel (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Blades of Steel</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, Blades of Steel is a hockey arcade action game (gameplay doesn't require the need to worry about statistics or provide the ability to customize teams.) Two players can play against each other, or one player against the computer. In one player mode there are single game and tournament mode options. From time to time a fight may break out, which will provide a close up view of the two players. The player has control during the miniature fight game sequence, with the loser having to spend time in the penalty box.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19881202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blades of Steel (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blades of Steel (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blaster Master (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Blaster Master</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The classic story of a boy and his frog who runs away, becomes radioactive and jumps into a hole. More importantly however, it's the story about a boy who finds a fully functional battletank, SOFIA the 3rd, and goes adventuring around the underground. His mission to find new weapons and add-on parts to the battletank which will in turn allow him to explore more areas until eventually he finds that freedom-loving mutant frog. And while he's down there he might as well defeat the Evil Plutonium Boss who wishes to threaten the Earth.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19881101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Blaster Master (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blaster Master (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bomberman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bomberman was a robot in a bomb making factory who longed for his freedom. Rumors circulated that escaping to the surface would allow the robot to become human. Getting out would be the trick. Each room is inhabited by monsters that must be neutralized and the exit itself hidden underneath bricks.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Bomberman (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bomberman (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bomberman II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Our hero the white Bomberman (Bomberman Shiro) was walking down the street one day when he witnessed a robbery. It was black Bomberman (Bomberman Kuro) who was the robber. But Black Bomberman knocked White Bomberman to the ground, and than left the money so that he would be framed. Now Bomberman has been taken to jail and must fight his way out of this place using the only method he knows: explosive bombs. Bomberman is the second Bomberman game in the series and plays similar to the first, only all gameplay has been reduced to a single screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bomberman II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bomberman II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bonk's Adventure (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bonk's Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Prehistoric platform game where you are in control of a baby and have to guide him through the levels avoiding all manner of strange nasties. The game is very similar to every other platform game you have ever played, but it does have its own unique features such as the ability to climb vertical walls with your teeth and do a diving head butt from a jump. Power ups come in the form of lumps of meat and give extra speed and invulnerability in the later stages. If you have ever played chuck rock then you know what to expect from this, a bog standard platform game with a prehistoric theme.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Red Company</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Bonk's Adventure (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bonk's Adventure (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boulder Dash (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Boulder Dash</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You're Rockford and have to dig through monster infested caves in search of diamonds. In each level you must collect a certain number of these diamonds, in order to open a portal to the next stage. Enemies can be squashed by falling boulders, which are released when the ground below them is removed or they are pushed onto empty ground, but be careful because these can also squash you. In later levels, difficulty is increased by many puzzle elements and shorter time limits.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SAS Sakata</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Boulder Dash (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Boulder Dash (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bubble Bobble is the story of two humans, Bub and Bob who wander into the mysterious cave of monsters and magically turn into dinosaurs. The only way to transform back is to reach the end of the cave</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19881101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bubble Bobble (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bubble Bobble (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bubble Bobble Part 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bubble Bobble Part 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cubby and Rubby, descendants of Bub and Bob from the original Bubble Bobble, must rescue their friend Judy, who has been kidnapped by the evil Skull Brothers! The game plays much like the original game: You use a dinosaur that spits bubbles at their enemies, trapping them until you touch the bubbles to make them pop and defeat the trapped enemies. But Cubby and Rubby have two skills their ancestors did not: by holding down the attack button, they can float upwards - and by releasing it, they'll fire several bubbles at once. They can also pick up special items that increase their points, speed and attack power. This game features 80 levels, all-new enemies, and bonus mini-games.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ITL</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bubble Bobble Part 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bubble Bobble Part 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bucky O'Hare (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bucky O'Hare</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Captain Bucky O'Hare and his loyal crew; Blinky, Deadeye, Jenny and Willy, fight to save the Aniverse from the scourge of the Toad Armada. That is until Bucky's ship is attacked and his crew taken prisoner. Now a lone bunny on a mission, Bucky must fight to rescue his comrades from four hostile planets and then confront the Air Marshall on his flagship. Buck O'Hare is a side-scroller game based off of the cartoon of the same name. Bucky's main abilities are a jump and a blaster weapon, which he can charge up to make an even more powerful jump. Life and Weapon bars are displayed at the bottom of the screen. Bucky can obtain new weapons throughout the game from his crew members.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Bucky O'Hare (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bucky O'Hare (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Burai Fighter (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Burai Fighter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Burai, a race of evil super-brain aliens, have launched their plan to conquer the universe with their army of half-organic, half-robot creatures -- the robo-mutants. It's up to you to stop them! Strap on your jet pack, and get ready to become the ultimate Burai Fighter.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taxan USA Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Taxan USA Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Burai Fighter (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Burai Fighter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BurgerTime (USA).zip</path>
		<name>BurgerTime</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As Chef Peter Pepper, you must fend off the Food Foes while making perfect burgers! Use pinches of pepper to stun Mr. Hot Dog, Mr. Egg and Mr. Pickle, or lure them onto or under burger buns, lettuce, cheese or tomatoes to escape their clutches! Making perfect burgers gets progressively tougher through the six screens of BurgerTime!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19851127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/BurgerTime (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/BurgerTime (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Captain Skyhawk (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Captain Skyhawk</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Earth has been invaded by aliens and it is up to you to stop them. Piloting a plane through several levels, you must blow up enemy artillery and planes before taking on one of four large bases. The action is from a top down perspective, but the landscape is 3D rather than flat as in similar games. Your plane can be upgraded at space stations between levels, and you even have to accurately pilot your plane into the space station. After successfully completing all the levels you have to destroy the final alien boss.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940524T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Milton Bradley Co.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Captain Skyhawk (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Captain Skyhawk (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Every hundred years, the dark vampire known as Dracula resurrects and terrorizes the land. A vampire hunter named Simon Belmont bravely ventures into the Count's mansion in order to defeat him. Along the way he'll have to defeat skeletons, bats, fishmen, medusa heads and other evil creatures.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania II: Simon's Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Castlevania II: Simon's Quest is the second one of three Castlevania games released on the NES. After the vampire killer Simon Belmont destroyed Count Dracula in the original Castlevania (1987), an evil curse possessed him. The only way Simon can break the count's curse is to find five of Dracula's body parts (which are mysteriously strewn throughout Transylvania) and burn them. Unlike most of the other Castlevania games, Simon's Quest does not feature the traditional stages but allows you to freely roam the land of Transylvania in the style of Nintendo's Metroid. In several towns Simon can talk with NPC's and buy items in shops, adding a touch of role-playing.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania II - Simon's Quest (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania III: Dracula's Curse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Taking place 100 years before the events of Castlevania 1 and Castlevania 2, Dracula the Vampire has risen up to threaten the small village of Warakiya. Citizens who had banished the Belmont family now beg for Trevor Belmont's help in slaying Dracula. In his strange castle, Dracula has been assembling a massive army of undead creatures to sweep the Earth clean of life and bring everlasting darkness. Trevor agrees to help and equips his family's hereditary whip, the "Vampire Slayer", in order to destroy Dracula.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania III - Dracula's Curse (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Clash at Demonhead (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Clash at Demonhead</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Professor Plum and his designs for the "doomsday device", DEAD END have been taken by the diabolical LAWBREAKERS - a sinister group dedicated to the destruction of mankind. It's only a matter of time before the device is assembled and the final countdown begins. As Sergeant Billy "Big Bang" Blitz of the special Assault Brigade for Real Emergencies(S.A.B.R.E) your mission is to foil the LAWBREAKERS plan. To do this, you must find the shortest route to the summit of Demonhead mountain, where the professor is being held. Rescue the professor and save the world from total destruction.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokai Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Tokai Engineering</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Clash at Demonhead (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Clash at Demonhead (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cobra Triangle (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Cobra Triangle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Cobra Triangle is a single-player boat-racing game that lets you do more than race. It borrows the power-up system from the shoot 'em up genre but keeps the emphasis more on maneuvering than shooting. Since you have a health meter with a dozen bars in it, it's not that important to dodge bullets unless your health is really low, but you should try not to run into too many walls. In order to get very far you need to make use of your power-ups which are TURBO for better acceleration; FIRE for increased firepower; SPEED for increased top-speed; MISSILE for firing missiles as well as bullets; and FORCE which makes you fire tons of missiles and also makes you invincible for a limited time.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19891025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Cobra Triangle (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cobra Triangle (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Code Name - Viper (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Code Name: Viper</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set against the backdrop of the war on drugs from the late 1980s/early 1990s, Code Name: Viper directly confronts the drug cartel at their bases in South America. You play an American secret agent who must infiltrate the cartel drug bases and mansions, free hostages and informants, and piece together clues about who the kingpin is-- and inevitably bring him down. Equip yourself with a progressively more powerful arsenal as the game progresses in standard NES side-scroller fashion.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19900301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Code Name - Viper (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Code Name - Viper (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conquest of the Crystal Palace (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Conquest of the Crystal Palace</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Long ago the Crystal Palace was a thriving kingdom, however the evil war spirit Zaras appeared one day and brought destruction to the lands! The people of the Crystal Palace left as Zaras and his henchman took over, changing the kingdom into a maze of many dangers. You control Farron, the hero of the story who needs to enter the Crystal Palace and destroy the bad guys in order to restore peace. The game is an action platform game that scrolls both horizontally and vertically. On each of five stages you'll need to fight various enemies throughout the varied terrain, and finally defeat the boss at the end.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19901101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Asmik</developer>
		<publisher>Quest</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Conquest of the Crystal Palace (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Conquest of the Crystal Palace (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Contra</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2631, a small meteorite has fallen into the Galuga archipelago, located 20km northeast off the coast of New Zealand. Two years later, a terrorist group known as Red Falcon has seized the island in preparation for an alien invasion. The earth's marines sent two members of their elite Contra unit, Bill Rizer and Lance Bean, to neutralize the terrorists. As either, Bill (player 1) or Lance (player 2), the player must get to the end of each stage, shooting everything in sight, while avoiding enemy fire themselves. The player can upgrade their standard-issue rifle into one of four different weapons, including the powerful spread shot.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19880202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Contra (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Contra (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cowboy Kid (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Cowboy Kid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this game you play the role of a young gunslinger who travels the land fighting baddies and playing mini games. The main game play involves you moving around the towns horizontally collecting gold by hitting chest whilst at the same time killing the bad guys before they kill you. There is also an RPG element to it where you have to visit people in the towns in order to proceed like at the very beginning where you need to first acquire a knife and you are then able to smash the chest and get money in order to buy a key which in turn allows you to enter the Sheriffs building. Once you are made sheriff you can go to various towns hunting down an outlaw for the bounty money.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Romstar Incorporated</developer>
		<publisher>Romstar Incorporated</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cowboy Kid (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cowboy Kid (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cowlitz Gamers 2nd Adventure (Cowlitz Gamers for Kids) (2017).nes</path>
		<name>Cowlits Gamers' 2nd Adventure, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Cowlitz Gamers' Adventure 2 is a new arcade-style cooperative platformer game for the NES. In it, you help Kaylee and her brother, Justice, collect gold and diamonds from dangerous mines and a treacherous tower.</desc>
		<releasedate>20170101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Lukasz Kur &amp; M-Tee</developer>
		<publisher>Cowlitz Gamers for Kids</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cowlitz Gamers 2nd Adventure (Cowlitz Gamers for Kids) (2017).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cowlitz Gamers 2nd Adventure (Cowlitz Gamers for Kids) (2017).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash 'n' the Boys - Street Challenge (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Crash 'n' the Boys: Street Challenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Crash 'n' the Boys: Street Challenge features the same basic gameplay engine and mechanics found in the rest of the Kunio/Nekketsu High games. The player controls a character in side-scrolling levels and try to defeat opponents using an arsenal of attacks and special moves. Unique to this game is that in order to clear the five stages, the player must also accomplish a series of sport-themed objectives. There is a throwing event, a golfing event, swimming, jumping, and all-out fighting events, all with unique twists inspired by the street/gangs theme of the game (e.g. the jumping event involves jumping across the rooftops in the city).</desc>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crash 'n' the Boys - Street Challenge (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crash 'n' the Boys - Street Challenge (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crystalis (USA, Europe) (SNK 40th Anniversary Collection).zip</path>
		<name>Crystalis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>October 1st, 1997 is known as END DAY. A great war encircles the globe and brings about an end to civilization. The surviving humans concluded that they could never repeat their mistakes and build a great tower in the sky to watch over the world and act accordingly to combat "evil". One hundred years have passed since then and a hidden cryogenic chamber in the mountains springs to life.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19900701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Crystalis (USA, Europe) (SNK 40th Anniversary Collection).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crystalis (USA, Europe) (SNK 40th Anniversary Collection).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyber Stadium Series - Base Wars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Cyber Stadium Series: Base Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the 24th century, the game of Baseball is very different. Tired of paying huge players salaries, the team owners got together one weekend and came up with a bold new idea, Robots. Indeed they renamed their league the Cyber League and stocked it with four robot types; Cyborg, Tank, Floater or Motorcycle, to play. On an orbital stadium in space, these robots all play a slightly different variation of the baseball rules. Hitting the ball and catching pop-flys and making home runs are all the same, but when the call of a play is in dispute, there are no base referees; the robots engage in a one-on-one battle using any weaponry they're carrying.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cyber Stadium Series - Base Wars (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cyber Stadium Series - Base Wars (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Danny Sullivan's Indy Heat (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Danny Sullivan's Indy Heat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Danny Sullivan, 1988 IndyCar champion and winner of the classic 'Spin &amp; Win' Indianapolis 500 in 1985, put his name to this Super Sprint style racing game. There are 4 cars in each race, 1 or 2 player options, and 9 tracks to race on, with the Tradewest Speed Bowl the ultimate target, and is much longer but with double points (it's essentially a substitute for the licensed-elsewhere Indianapolis 500, which did pay double the usual level of IndyCar championship points for many years). The player has limited fuel, and will run slowly if supplies run out, and the car can be damaged, although both are repairable in the pits.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Leland Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Danny Sullivan's Indy Heat (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Danny Sullivan's Indy Heat (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Desert Commander (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Desert Commander</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Somewhere in a nameless desert, two opposing nameless armies take to the battlefield to destroy the other. Through the strategy of their commanders and the diversity of their units, each side seeks to gain the advantage over the other. There are 5 campaigns total and can be played either VS the computer or a second player.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19890602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Desert Commander (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Desert Commander (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Devil World (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Devil World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Devil World is a scrolling maze game, strikingly similar to the classic Pac-Man, only with an undeniable religious bent. Collect dots in an automatically-scrolling maze directed by the devil himself, use crosses to power up and destroy his minions, and be careful not to get crushed by the walls. After collecting all the dots, you must collect bibles to seal up the source of the enemies and make the devil temporarily retreat. After this, there is a timed bonus stage where the player can control the scrolling, then the next round starts the cycle over from the beginning.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19870715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Devil World (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Devil World (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dig Dug II - Trouble in Paradise (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dig Dug II: Trouble in Paradise</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It is Dig Dug's job to protect 72 different tropical islands from his arch rivals, Pooka and the fire breathing Fygar. Played from an overhead point of view, Dig Dug now has two weapons at his disposal; the first is an air pump and the second is a drill. The pump can be used to inflate and destroy the enemies the same as in the original Dig Dug. At various locations on the islands are stakes, and when the drill is used near a stake a crack will form.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19891201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dig Dug II - Trouble in Paradise (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dig Dug II - Trouble in Paradise (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chip 'n Dale - Rescue Rangers (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Chip 'n Dale: Rescue Rangers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The rescue rangers are tiny heroes. Consisting of two chipmunks, two mice and a fly these heroes may be small but there's no case too big for them to take on. This game starts out simply enough, with a mission to rescue a small kitten, but soon escalates into a wider plot that pits the rescue rangers against their arch-nemesis, the feline kingpin, Fat Cat.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19900601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chip 'n Dale - Rescue Rangers (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chip 'n Dale - Rescue Rangers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chip 'n Dale - Rescue Rangers 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Chip 'n Dale: Rescue Rangers 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Following the first Rescue Rangers game, the Rangers' overcame the plot of their arch-nemesis Fatcat, and locked him up in the prison/pound. However, Fatcat's henchmen have sprung him from prison by blimp. Suddenly a television news anchor is reporting that there is a bomb threat in a local restaurant. The Rescue Rangers take it upon themselves to save the day only to learn that the whole bomb scare was a diversion in order to allow Fatcat to steal an artifact known as the Urn of the Pharoah. The team must track Fatcat and learn what he has in store for the stolen goods.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chip 'n Dale - Rescue Rangers 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chip 'n Dale - Rescue Rangers 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Darkwing Duck (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Darkwing Duck</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The kingpins of crime are at it again! The mysterious criminal organization F.O.W.L. has hatched a plan to take control of the peaceful city of St. Canard. Six of their most heinous henchmen are running rampant through the city and only the daring Darkwing Duck can bring them to justice! Join Darkwing as he explores the woods to weed out Bushroot's evil plan. Search the warehouses along the wharf for Mega Volt and pull the plug on an electrifying scheme.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Darkwing Duck (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Darkwing Duck (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DuckTales (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's DuckTales</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Duck Tales for NES is a traditional platform game in which the player takes the role of greedy Scrooge McDuck in search of treasures around the globe. He counts on his three nephews and on other Duck Tales characters to help him in his quest through inospit places such as the Amazononic forest, the African Mines, the Himalayas, Transylvania (where he meets Dracula Duck) and even the Moon. Each one of them reserves the old duck lots of adventure, different enemies and hidden rooms. The game features a 2D side-scrolling platform gameplay very similar to Mega Man. Graphics are colorful and cartoonish, music remembers players of the TV series and controls are very simple.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19890914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/DuckTales (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DuckTales (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./DuckTales 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's DuckTales 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Scrooge McDuck is hot on the trail of the richest adventure ever. Pieces to the map of the Lost Treasure of McDuck have been scattered across the globe, and Scrooge must find them before the greedy Flintheart Glomgold grabs them. It's going to be a race to the finish as both of them try to find the treasure and become the richest duck in the world! Join Scrooge and his nephews as they explore the ancient pyramids of Egypt and do battle with swash-buckling pirates in the Bermuda Triangle. Help them search the haunted halls of an ancient Scottish castle and scale the watery heights of Niagara Falls.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/DuckTales 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/DuckTales 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Duck Tales 2 Two-Players (Hack) v1.4a Ti.nes</path>
		<name>Disney's DuckTales 2 (2 Players)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>2 Player Hack, Scrooge McDuck is hot on the trail of the richest adventure ever. Pieces to the map of the Lost Treasure of McDuck have been scattered across the globe, and Scrooge must find them before the greedy Flintheart Glomgold grabs them. It's going to be a race to the finish as both of them try to find the treasure and become the richest duck in the world! Join Scrooge and his nephews as they explore the ancient pyramids of Egypt and do battle with swash-buckling pirates in the Bermuda Triangle. Help them search the haunted halls of an ancient Scottish castle and scale the watery heights of Niagara Falls.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Duck Tales 2 Two-Players (Hack) v1.4a Ti.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Duck Tales 2 Two-Players (Hack) v1.4a Ti.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Little Mermaid, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Little Mermaid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this version of Disney's The Little Mermaid you play as Ariel the mermaid. Ariel has already met Eric, and they plan to wed, but the sea-witch Ursala has taken control of the ocean! So Ariel (After explaining what's going on to Eric) becomes a mermaid once more and sets off to rescue the sea.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19910701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Little Mermaid, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Little Mermaid, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong (World) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Released in the arcades in 1981, Donkey Kong was not only Nintendo's first real smash hit for the company, but marked the introduction for two of their most popular mascots: Mario (originally "Jumpman") and Donkey Kong. Donkey Kong is a platform-action game that has Mario scale four different industrial themed levels (construction zone, cement factory, an elevator-themed level, and removing rivets from girders) in an attempt to save the damsel in distress, Pauline, from the big ape before the timer runs out. Once the rivets are removed from the final level, Donkey Kong falls, and the two lovers are reunited. From there, the levels start over at a higher difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong (World) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong (World) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Classics (USA, Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Classics</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Donkey Kong Classics features both the original Donkey Kong and Donkey Kong Jr. on a single cartridge. In Donkey Kong, you need to guide Mario safely up the scaffolding to rescue his girlfriend, Pauline. In Donkey Kong Jr., the roles are reversed; you control Jr. who needs to rescue his father, who has been captured by Mario.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19881001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong Classics (USA, Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong Classics (USA, Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Jr. (World) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Jr.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario has kidnapped Junior's Papa! Donkey Kong Jr. was originally released in the arcades in 1982 as a sequel to Donkey Kong. In this game, Mario plays the antagonist, finally having captured Donkey Kong, and has put the ape in a locked cage. As Donkey Kong Jr., players will have to make their way through four different levels (Vines, Springboard, Chains and Mario's Hideout) in an attempt to find keys to free the little monkey's Father. Along the way, Mario will send out Snapjaws, swooping purple birds, and electric sparks in an attempt to stop Junior. Junior can defend himself by dropping fruit found around the levels on the heads of his foes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19830715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong Jr. (World) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong Jr. (World) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in a post-apocalyptic New York, Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers trained in the fighting style of Sou-Setsu-Ken. Together, they manage a small martial arts training school, teaching their students in self-defense. One day, Billy's girlfriend, Marian, is kidnapped off the street by the "Black Warriors", a savage street gang led by a man named Willy. The Black Warriors demand the Lee brothers disclose their martial arts secrets in exchange for Marian's freedom. The Lee brothers set out on a rescue mission to crush the Black Warriors and save Marian.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19880602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Double Dragon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Double Dragon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon II - The Revenge (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon II: The Revenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The lovely Marian was rescued from the clutches of the Black Warriors gang by Billy &amp; Jimmy Lee in the first Double Dragon game, but now the gang has killed her in retaliation of their early defeat. The Dragons must now embark on a mission to avenge her death and defeat the Black Warriors for the second and final time.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19900101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Double Dragon II - The Revenge (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Double Dragon II - The Revenge (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Double Dragon III: The Sacred Stones</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The final game in the trilogy. Billy and Jimmy Lee are returning from martial arts training when their paths cross a fortune teller. She tells them of a great evil in Egypt, their strongest adversary yet, and how the Rosetta Stones can aid them.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Double Dragon III - The Sacred Stones (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Double Dribble (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Double Dribble</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the arcade game, Double Dribble is a basketball action game for one or two players. You can select different time limits for games, select teams, and begin playing! Gameplay is entirely action, so no time needs to be spent customizing the teams or with statistics. You control each player on the team one at a time (the player with or about to receive the ball will be human controlled, with the computer taking over the other players temporarily.) Some versions feature a small amount of digitized sound effects, and close ups of slam dunks.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19870901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Double Dribble (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Double Dribble (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dr. Mario (Japan, USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Dr. Mario</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this Tetris-style game, you play as Dr. Mario, who must drop differently coloured pills onto viruses to remove them from the bottle. Each pill is split into two, with each side a different colour. Match that colour to the colour of the virus, and it will be removed from the bottle. Included in the game is the normal mode, a time trial, and a two player battle mode to see who can remove the most viruses.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19900727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dr. Mario (Japan, USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dr. Mario (Japan, USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Fighter (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon Fighter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Dragon Fighter the protagonist is a fighter who can turn into a dragon. In this side-scrolling action game the hero can walk, jump, and slash with his sword. He can also charge his sword to fire a magical projectile. The real power-up, however, is that he can transform into a flying dragon. When this happens, the game turns into a shmup-style game in which the scrolling moves at a constant rate and the dragon can shoot fireballs in a spread formation.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>SOFEL Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Fighter (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Fighter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>