<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Nintendo DS</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./0088 - Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Advance Wars: Dual Strike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Advance Wars, the award-winning turn-based strategy game, makes its debut on the Nintendo DS. Players lead their new Commanding Officers to fend off the Black Hole Army's latest invasion. With massive battles that sweep across both of the DS screens, Advance Wars: Dual Strike will change the face of war forever.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0088 - Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0088 - Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0771 - Age of Empires - The Age of Kings (Europe) (En,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Age of Empires: The Age of Kings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Age of Empires: The Age of Kings for the Nintendo DS is based on the best-selling PC RTS title of all time: Age of Empires II: The Age of Kings. Players command five different civilizations, build armies and take them on scores of campaigns. Boasting turn-based strategy game play, Age of Empires: The Age of Kings allows players to move from the Dark Ages through the Middle Ages with one goal in mind: domination of the known world.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0771 - Age of Empires - The Age of Kings (Europe) (En,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0771 - Age of Empires - The Age of Kings (Europe) (En,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4433 - Assassin's Creed II - Discovery (DSi Enhanced) (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Assassin's Creed II: Discovery</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Discover an untold chapter from the Assassin’s Creed II storyline. Follow Ezio as he travels to 15th century Spain to rescue fellow assassins being held under the guise of the Inquisition, only to uncover a Templar plot to sail west and discover the New World.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20091119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Griptonite Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4433 - Assassin's Creed II - Discovery (DSi Enhanced) (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4433 - Assassin's Creed II - Discovery (DSi Enhanced) (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0221 - Burnout Legends (U)(Mode 7).nds</path>
		<name>Burnout Legends</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The fastest, most dangerous racer on home consoles is now the fastest, most dangerous racer on the DS, with Burnout Legends. Taking the series' award-winning speed, action and attitude on the road, Burnout Legends combines the best moments in the franchise's history with exclusive features, gameplay and connectivity. The ultimate quick-hit of on-the-go gameplay, Burnout Legends includes tricked-out tracks from Burnout, Burnout 2: Point of Impact and Burnout 3: Takedown, updated for aggressive racing on the DS.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20051129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Impact</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0221 - Burnout Legends (U)(Mode 7).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0221 - Burnout Legends (U)(Mode 7).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1666 - Chessmaster - The Art of Learning (U)(Sir VG).nds</path>
		<name>Chessmaster: The Art of Learning</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chessmaster: The Art of Learning expands the scope of chess to include broader principles of learning. Josh Waitzkin's much-anticipated book The Art of Learning (Free Press) is designed to pave the road to successful long-term growth on and off the chessboard. Waitzkin then turns to the classics, introducing beginners to brilliant games from some of the most important players in the history of chess.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20071025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1666 - Chessmaster - The Art of Learning (U)(Sir VG).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1666 - Chessmaster - The Art of Learning (U)(Sir VG).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3055 - Chrono Trigger (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When a newly developed teleportation device malfunctions at the Millennial Fair, young Crono must travel through time to rescue his misfortunate companion from an intricate web of past and present perils. The swashbuckling adventure that ensues soon unveils an evil force set to destroy the world, triggering Crono's race against time to change the course of history and bring about a brighter future.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20081125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>KOCH Media</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3055 - Chrono Trigger (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3055 - Chrono Trigger (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1662 - Contra 4 (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Contra 4</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Contra 4 takes place two years after the events of Contra III: The Alien Wars. After saving earth from invasion by Red Falcon, Bill Rizer and Lance Bean are confronted with a new extraterrestrial menace: the terrifying Black Viper. Joined by hard-boiled mercenaries Mad Dog and Scorpion, the warriors must once again wage war against an entire army of invaders.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1662 - Contra 4 (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1662 - Contra 4 (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4166 - DiRT 2 (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Colin McRae: DiRT 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>DiRT 2 is set to take off-road racing games on DS to a new level. Features exciting action-sports attitude and takes players on a stunning World Tour. Influenced by the big-event atmosphere rally is showcased in at events like the X-Games, this global tour takes players to some of the most diverse and exotic real-world locations and offers a sensational line up of officially licensed rally and off-road vehicles.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebrand Games</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4166 - DiRT 2 (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4166 - DiRT 2 (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1548 - Front Mission (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Front Mission</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The story takes place on Huffman Island which is located in the neutral zone between two nations Oceania Community Union (O.C.U.) and the Unified Continental States (U.C.S.). In the year 2070, a war broke out between the two nations that lasted for two years before finally peace was achieved and the island was split in half, both sides being used for each nations base. In 2090, however, a U.C.S factory is mysteriously attacked, leading to another conflict.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1548 - Front Mission (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1548 - Front Mission (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Game Center CX Arino no Chousenjou 2 (English Patched v1.4).nds</path>
		<name>Game Center CX: Arino no Chousenjou 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The digital version of Game Master Arino returns, hurtling you back into the past once more. However, unlike the original Retro Game Challenge, this time, you'll be tackling games from all sorts of systems, including handhelds, 8-bit, 16-bit and disk systems too! Can you conquer them all? Once again, players must complete tasks in each game set by Game Master Arino to unlock more games with their own tasks.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indies Zero</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Game Center CX Arino no Chousenjou 2 (English Patched v1.4).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Game Center CX Arino no Chousenjou 2 (English Patched v1.4).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet (Prototype).nds</path>
		<name>Gauntlet</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gauntlet was a cancelled video game planned for release on the Nintendo DS system but never saw the light of the day. Is a hack and slash action game in a heroic fantasy universe. A remake of an 80's video game classic, Gauntlet brings new features: new 3D view, new attacks, new powers as well as several online multiplayer modes (cooperative or deathmatch). Play as Merlin, Thor, Questor or Thyra and explore the labyrinths of Gauntlet.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gauntlet (Prototype).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gauntlet (Prototype).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1745 - Geometry Wars - Galaxies (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Geometry Wars: Galaxies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>First acting as a bonus mini-game in Project Gotham Racing 2 on Xbox, Geometry Wars Galaxies is now a game in its own right on DS. On board your spacecraft, you have to face the hordes of geometric enemies that are constantly sweeping the playground. Old-fashioned shoot'em up, Geometry Wars Galaxies is a demanding title not to be put among all hands.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20071127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kuju Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1745 - Geometry Wars - Galaxies (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1745 - Geometry Wars - Galaxies (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5478_-_Ghost_Trick_-_Phantom_DetectiveUSA_NDS-XPA.nds</path>
		<name>Ghost Trick: Phantom Detective</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Ghost Trick Phantom Detective, players are transported into the spirit world of Sissel, a murder victim who has lost his memory and returned as a ghost to solve the mystery of his suspicious demise. As Sissel’s ghost it’s up to players to possess and manipulate items found in the real world to solve the captivating puzzles he encounters.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20110111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5478_-_Ghost_Trick_-_Phantom_DetectiveUSA_NDS-XPA.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5478_-_Ghost_Trick_-_Phantom_DetectiveUSA_NDS-XPA.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3517 - Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (US)(M5)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto: Chinatown Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Following his father’s murder, Huang Lee has a simple mission: deliver an ancient sword to his Uncle Kenny to ensure his family retains control of the Triad gangs of Liberty City. Huang is a spoiled rich kid who expects everything to run smoothly, but his trip does not go exactly as planned. After being robbed and left to die, he will search for honor, riches and revenge in the most dangerous and morally bankrupt city in the world. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3517 - Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (US)(M5)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3517 - Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (US)(M5)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3550 - Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure (US)(M5)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Henry Hatsworth in The Puzzling Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Meet Henry Hatsworth, a quirky, light-hearted character who players will guide on their journey through a new style of gaming adventure on their DS. In this two-in-one adventure, players will explore five exotic worlds, fight a variety of opponents, and venture through more than 30 levels, including nearly a dozen hidden levels while taking on outrageous world-ending bosses.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3550 - Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure (US)(M5)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3550 - Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure (US)(M5)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jump! Ultimate Stars (J) [English].nds</path>
		<name>Jump Ultimate Stars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jump Ultimate Stars is more or less an expanded version of the original game, Jump Super Stars. It features the same Super Smash Bros.-style fighting gameplay with a plethora of licensed manga characters, bringing in a wide variety of new franchises and characters. The roster has been expanded to more than 300 characters from 41 different manga titles. There is also Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection support, making global internet play a possibility.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20061123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ganbarion</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jump! Ultimate Stars (J) [English].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jump! Ultimate Stars (J) [English].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4225 - Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (US)(M2)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dive into the heart of the Kingdom Hearts storyline's biggest secrets. In Kingdom Hearts, Sora turned the Keyblade on himself in order to release Kairi's heart, but his heart was also released in the process. This brought about the creation of Roxas, Sora's Nobody. Unlike most Nobodies, however, Roxas has no memories of his past. He joins Organization XIII and slowly begins to discover the truth behind his existence and the Organization itself. He meets and befriends the fourteenth member of the Organization, who also has no recollection of her past.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>H.A.N.D</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4225 - Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (US)(M2)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4225 - Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (US)(M2)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5051 - LEGO Harry Potter - Years 1-4 (U)(BAHAMUT).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Harry Potter: Years 1-4</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>LEGO Harry Potter: Years 1-4 will give gamers the chance to experience the magic and adventure of Harry Potter in a uniquely LEGO way. Playing as Harry Potter, Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger, as well as more than 100 other favorite characters, gamers will have the opportunity to attend lessons, cast spells, mix potions, fly on broomsticks and complete tasks to earn rewards. Throughout the game, players will also have the freedom to explore iconic settings from the wizarding world including Hogwarts castle, Diagon Alley, the Forbidden Forest and the village of Hogsmeade.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>TT Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5051 - LEGO Harry Potter - Years 1-4 (U)(BAHAMUT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5051 - LEGO Harry Potter - Years 1-4 (U)(BAHAMUT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5880 - LEGO Harry Potter - Years 5-7 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Harry Potter: Years 5-7</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the last three Harry Potter books and final four films, LEGO Harry Potter: Years 5-7 takes players through Harry Potter's heroic adventures in the Muggle and wizarding worlds. From Privet Drive in Little Whinging to Diagon Alley, Hogsmeade and Hogwarts - plus new locations including Grimmauld Place, the Ministry of Magic, and Godric's Hollow - players will encounter new faces, new challenges and new magic, preparing them for the ultimate face-off against Lord Voldemort.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>TT Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5880 - LEGO Harry Potter - Years 5-7 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5880 - LEGO Harry Potter - Years 5-7 (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./6325 - LEGO Marvel Super Heroes Universe in Peril (U)(ABSTRAKT).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Marvel Super Heroes: Universe in Peril</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Features an original story crossing the entire Marvel Universe. Players take control of Iron Man, Spider-Man, the Hulk, Captain America, Wolverine and many more Marvel characters as they unite to stop Loki and a host of other Marvel villains from assembling a super-weapon capable of destroying the world. Players will chase down cosmic bricks as they travel across LEGO Manhattan and visit key locations from the Marvel Universe, such as Stark Tower, Asteroid M, a Hydra base and the X-Mansion.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20140218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>TT Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/6325 - LEGO Marvel Super Heroes Universe in Peril (U)(ABSTRAKT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/6325 - LEGO Marvel Super Heroes Universe in Peril (U)(ABSTRAKT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4414 - LEGO - Rock Band (US)(M6)(Venom).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Rock Band</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players will become rockers as they embark on a journey to stardom that the whole family can enjoy as they work their way through local venues, stadiums and fantasy locations on Earth and beyond, that mimic the imaginative settings that the LEGO world offers. Also continuing the LEGO “build-and-play” gaming experience, players will be able to create their own LEGO Rock Band style as they customize their minifigure avatars, band and entourage, including roadies, managers and crew.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20091126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4414 - LEGO - Rock Band (US)(M6)(Venom).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4414 - LEGO - Rock Band (US)(M6)(Venom).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0553 - LEGO Star Wars II - The Original Trilogy (U)(Legacy).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars II: The Original Trilogy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players navigate their way through familiar scenes of movies from the original Star Wars trilogy: A New Hope, The Empire Strikes Back, and Return of the Jedi. The difference here being that all the characters and sets are made entirely from LEGO, and the cutscenes (acted out by characters in amusing pantomime) and gameplay reflects this. Jedis can use The Force to shift blocks and make plants grow, normal characters can build certain blocks to make items, and droid characters can activate special locks.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20060913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0553 - LEGO Star Wars II - The Original Trilogy (U)(Legacy).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0553 - LEGO Star Wars II - The Original Trilogy (U)(Legacy).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./6116 - LEGO The Lord of the Rings (U)(EXiMiUS).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO The Lord of the Rings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players control a variety of characters using the control pad (as well as the 3DS Circle Pad) across several levels in an open-world environment, completing a set of quests along the way. Players also need to utilise special items like the Light of Eärendil, Elven rope and a wide arrange of weaponry to defeat several enemies (especially in the dark region of Mordor).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20121123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TT Fusion</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/6116 - LEGO The Lord of the Rings (U)(EXiMiUS).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/6116 - LEGO The Lord of the Rings (U)(EXiMiUS).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario_Kart_DS_USA_NDS-SCZ.nds</path>
		<name>Mario Kart DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An all-star cast that includes Mario, Luigi, Peach, Yoshi, Donkey Kong, Wario, Bowser and Toad will round out a truly all-star lineup of more than 30 courses drawn from every Mario Kart game. That's right – players will tour courses from Super Mario Kart, Mario Kart 64, Mario Kart: Super Circuit and Mario Kart: Double Dash!!, not to mention brand-new tracks and arenas. With all the crazy items and frantic speed players have come to expect, this game is a Mario Kart fan's dream. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario_Kart_DS_USA_NDS-SCZ.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario_Kart_DS_USA_NDS-SCZ.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0314 - Resident Evil - Deadly Silence (U)(WRG).nds</path>
		<name>Resident Evil: Deadly Silence</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Resident Evil: Deadly Silence brings the original PlayStation survival horror game, Resident Evil, to your Nintendo DS. You can play through the original game or in rebirth mode. Rebirth mode is essentially the same story but with new puzzles, monster placements, and touch-screen-specific minigames. You can also partake in a multiplayer match that challenges you and your opponents to complete a stretch of the game not only with the fastest time, but also with the most points, which are earned by killing enemies along the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20060207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0314 - Resident Evil - Deadly Silence (U)(WRG).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0314 - Resident Evil - Deadly Silence (U)(WRG).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3377 - Retro Game Challenge (US)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Game Center CX: Arino no Chousenjou</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Defeat the retro game challenges, or be trapped in the 80’s forever! The evil Game Master Arino has thrown you back in time – your only chance is to beat him at every classic gaming challenge he throws at you. Take on timeless 8-bit gameplay: classic space shooters, breakneck racing, ninja action and even epic RPG play. Experience a variety of fast-paced retro challenges, then unlock the complete games to enjoy in free play. Seek help from in-game magazines, filled with cheat codes to warp you to later levels, receive unlimited continues, and even become invincible!</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20090210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indies Zero</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3377 - Retro Game Challenge (US)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3377 - Retro Game Challenge (US)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0630 - Scurge - Hive (U)(Psyfer).nds</path>
		<name>Scurge: Hive</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When bounty hunter Jenosa Arma takes on a mission to investigate Planet Inos, a research center investigating an alien lifeform called Scurge, she gets more than she bargained for. While in orbit around the planet, she is attacked and quickly infected with the Scurge herself. Jenosa has no alternative but to land onto Inos, to investigate the Scurge and find a cure.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Southpeak Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Orbital Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0630 - Scurge - Hive (U)(Psyfer).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0630 - Scurge - Hive (U)(Psyfer).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1607 - Simpsons Game, The (U)(Micronauts).nds</path>
		<name>Simpsons Game, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Each of the Simpsons are playable in this sidescroller action game and feature their own wacky, special abilities. Homer can transform into a large blob and roll his way through levels. Bart can don a cowl and cape and become Bartman, using his slingshot and gliding ability to overcome the game's goons. Lisa can use an all-touchscreen Hand of Buddha to solve puzzles and remove obstacles from her path, and Marge can control mobs to overwhelm anyone who stands in her way.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20071030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amaze Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1607 - Simpsons Game, The (U)(Micronauts).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1607 - Simpsons Game, The (U)(Micronauts).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2980 - Tomb Raider - Underworld (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: Underworld</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Embark on a perilous journey around the world to uncover the secrets of a forgotten power that, if unleashed, could lay waste to all civilization. Experience a new level of challenge and choice in this epic tomb raiding adventure. For generations, stories have been told of the fearsome weapon of Thor, the Norse god of thunder. Legend holds that Thor’s hammer had the power to smash mountains into valleys and to destroy even the gods. For more than a thousand years it has existed only as a myth until now.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20081121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2980 - Tomb Raider - Underworld (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2980 - Tomb Raider - Underworld (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0174 - Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (U)(Mode 7).nds</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's American Sk8land</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Featuring a unique cell-shaded art style, players must prove themselves to Tony Hawk and other legendary pros as they undertake hundreds of skating goals set in seven popular areas of Los Angeles and restore the ultimate skate park, American SK8Land, to its former glory. The game challenges players to complete signature skate tricks that have been made popular by the Tony Hawk franchise, and also includes exclusive features such as wireless online multiplayer, voice in-game and touch-screen capabilities.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0174 - Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (U)(Mode 7).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0174 - Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (U)(Mode 7).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1479 - Animal Crossing - Wild World (v01) (U)(Independent).nds</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing: Wild World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wild World focuses on living in a remote village populated with anthropomorphic animals, where the player is encouraged to perform any number of tasks, such as collecting and planting. Like all Animal Crossing titles, the game is synced to the console's clock and calendar, allowing the game to be played in real-time, which affects the occurrence of in-game events based on the current time of day or season. Wild World also utilizes Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, which notably allows players to travel and visit the villages of other players via online play.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1479 - Animal Crossing - Wild World (v01) (U)(Independent).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1479 - Animal Crossing - Wild World (v01) (U)(Independent).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3430 - Bomberman 2 (EU)(M5)(EXiMiUS).nds</path>
		<name>Bomberman 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bomberman 2 marks the welcome return of Hudson Soft’s evergreen bomb-toting hero and will sees the popular franchise undergoing a visual make-over and a wealth of new elements to the gameplay. While the familiar basis of laying bombs to eradicate patrolling foes remains intact, Hudson Soft has expanded it across a more open format, creating a deeper title that maintains the addictive nature the series is famed for.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3430 - Bomberman 2 (EU)(M5)(EXiMiUS).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3430 - Bomberman 2 (EU)(M5)(EXiMiUS).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4564 - Dragon Ball Z - Attack of the Saiyans (USA) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball Z: Attack of the Saiyans</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Ball Z: Attack of the Saiyans is a role-playing game that starts before the 23rd World Martial Arts Tournament at the end of the Dragon Ball animé. The story covers the Saiyan saga of the series and events not originally told about Yamcha, Krillin and Tien. The combat system is turn-based and features an Active Guard system as well as a Sparking! gauge. Active Guard allows the player to reduce damage taken from an enemy and the Sparking! Gauge allows players to perform special Ki attacks or combination attacks.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20091030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Monolith Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4564 - Dragon Ball Z - Attack of the Saiyans (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4564 - Dragon Ball Z - Attack of the Saiyans (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon_Ball_Origins_2_USA_CLEAN_NDS_NukeThis.nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball: Origins 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Play as Goku and his friends in search of the seven mystical Dragon Balls! Jump into the world of Dragon Ball and play as Goku and his friends in search of the seven mystical Dragon Balls! Dragon Ball: Origins 2 is an all-new Action-Adeventure game encompassing Goku’s battle against the Red Ribbon Army featuring a humorous and memorable story taken from the original anime series. Battle alone or with a friend on Goku’s continuing quest with engaging controls and a fun mix of fierce fighting, dynamic action, exploration and puzzles!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100625T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Republic</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon_Ball_Origins_2_USA_CLEAN_NDS_NukeThis.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon_Ball_Origins_2_USA_CLEAN_NDS_NukeThis.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5075 - Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (U)(BAHAMUT).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies, players begin their adventure as guardian of a city who is sent to retrieve the fruits of a sacred tree that have the power to grant wishes. Players travel the world, conquer fearsome monsters and unravel an epic storyline. During their journey, players will encounter mighty opponents in fast-paced battles, and also interact with a colourful cast of characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./boxart/5075 - Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (U)(BAHAMUT).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5075 - Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (U)(BAHAMUT).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2691 - Ferrari Challenge - Trofeo Pirelli (U)(SQUiRE).nds</path>
		<name>Ferrari Challenge: Trofeo Pirelli</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Official licensed game of the Ferrari Challenge series. Up to 16 international racing circuits, plus additional unlockable content. All official teams and cars from the real-world the racing series, plus new downloadable teams, cars and content made available at the start of each new season. Lifelike vehicle simulation and handling dynamics. Realistic Ferrari race damage modeling and simulation. Unlock additional Ferrari cars including 360 Challenge, 355 Challenge, 348 Challenge and many other cars that have featured over the Ferrari Challenge weekends including the Ferrari FXX.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20071207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>System 3 Software</developer>
		<publisher>Deep Silver</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2691 - Ferrari Challenge - Trofeo Pirelli (U)(SQUiRE).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2691 - Ferrari Challenge - Trofeo Pirelli (U)(SQUiRE).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0344 - FIFA Street 2 (U)(Trashman).nds</path>
		<name>FIFA Street 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hit the streets and go one-on-one with the best Pro Players from around the world, or face real life street stars who have earned their legendary status in the underground arenas across the globe.. The Trick-Stick Weapon is your key to survival as you compete against the best; it comes equipped with a full arsenal of tricks including all new juggling moves. Using the right (analog) Trick-Stick in combination with the controller buttons you can select specific tricks to intimidate and disgrace your opponent.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20060302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0344 - FIFA Street 2 (U)(Trashman).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0344 - FIFA Street 2 (U)(Trashman).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2495 - Final Fantasy IV (U)(Independent).nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Final Fantasy IV, one of the highest rated adventure games of all time, makes an impressive return on Nintendo DS. With improved 3D graphics, fully-voiced dramatic cut-scenes, an inspiring remixed score and additional content never before seen, there has never been a better time to immerse yourself in this masterpiece of interactive storytelling. The gameplay benefits from all the Nintendo DS capabilities and allows for a deeper and richer experience of a tale of exceptional heroes, inevitable betrayal, unforeseen redemption, endless love and colossal magic.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2495 - Final Fantasy IV (U)(Independent).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2495 - Final Fantasy IV (U)(Independent).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2565 - GRID (U)(Micronauts).nds</path>
		<name>GRID</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>GRID is all about the race! GRID will take players to beautifully realised and dramatic race locations over three continents to compete in an unprecedented variety of racing events. Packed with the most powerful race cars – new and classic, circuit and drift – players will compete to conquer the most prestigious official race tracks and championships and then go beyond to compete in challenging city-based competitions, through to road events and urban street races.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20080805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebrand Games</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2565 - GRID (U)(Micronauts).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2565 - GRID (U)(Micronauts).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5527 - Jewel Master - Cradle of Athena (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Jewel Master: Cradle of Athena</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Follow the tracks of Hercules and recreate the glorious ancient world at the foot of the acropolis. Construct the Pergamon Alter, the famous Theater of Dionysus and countless other legendary buildings! In this one of a kind Match 3 Adventure, swap adjacent tiles so that rows of three or more of the same symbols emerge. By doing this, you will collect food, building resources, jewels and gold, as well as magical artifacts for your mission. Will the Goddess of Wisdom be merciful to you?</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20101005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Storm City Games</developer>
		<publisher>Storm City Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5527 - Jewel Master - Cradle of Athena (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5527 - Jewel Master - Cradle of Athena (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2696 - Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Kirby Super Star Ultra</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>With so many adventures waiting to be unlocked, there’ll never be a dull moment as you run, float, copy enemies and use Helpers to fight the likes of King Dedede and Meta Knight. On top of a slew of new adventures, the original modes found in the beloved Super NES® game, Kirby Super Star™, are all here with updated graphics and fully rendered movie scenes.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20080922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2696 - Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2696 - Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Phantom Hourglass (USA) - D-Pad Controls.nds</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The epic story of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker continues as Link finds himself lost and alone in unknown seas in a new adventure. Featuring intuitive touch-screen controls and innovative puzzles, The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass offers new challenges for fans of the series and an easy-to-grasp introduction for gamers new to The Legend of Zelda. But time grows short, and only the Phantom Hourglass can buy Link the minutes he'll need to survive. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Phantom Hourglass (USA) - D-Pad Controls.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The - Phantom Hourglass (USA) - D-Pad Controls.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (USA) - D-Pad Controls.nds</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>All Aboard for an Amazing New Adventure! The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks sets hero Link on a daring new adventure. The game provides players with a new story, more puzzles and even a new mode of transportation. In this game, Link voyages by train, which offers up new possibilities for problem-solving. The game has the same look and feel established in the hit Nintendo DS game The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20091211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (USA) - D-Pad Controls.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (USA) - D-Pad Controls.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3841 - Legendary Starfy, The (US)(1 Up).nds</path>
		<name>Legendary Starfy, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Nintendo's newest five-sided hero beneath Starfy's glamorous exterior pulses the heart of a true hero. He can handle anything anyone throws at him. Swift ocean currents, bottomless pits and hordes of enemies daunting for a lesser hero, but not Starfy, Nintendo's newest platforming sensation. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3841 - Legendary Starfy, The (US)(1 Up).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3841 - Legendary Starfy, The (US)(1 Up).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./6058 - LEGO Batman 2 - DC Super Heroes (U).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Batman 2: DC Super Heroes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>LEGO Batman 2: DC Super Heroes is an Action-Adeventure game set within the Batman universe, and filled with LEGO versions of heroes and villains from the Batman comic series, working together/against those from the Justice League comic series.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20120619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/6058 - LEGO Batman 2 - DC Super Heroes (U).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/6058 - LEGO Batman 2 - DC Super Heroes (U).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4491 - LEGO Indiana Jones 2 - The Adventure Continues (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Indiana Jones 2: The Adventure Continues</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The story of Kingdom of the Crystal Skull is retold in three acts of four chapters each, with comic-book-style cutscenes between levels. The levels themselves follow the usual LEGO game format: players control several characters and can switch between them at will. Different characters have different abilities which must be used in combination to overcome challenges and solve puzzles. For instance, Indy can use his whip, Marion and other female characters can cross special ledges and Indy's son Mutt can use his knife to cut ropes and can also climb walls.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20091120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4491 - LEGO Indiana Jones 2 - The Adventure Continues (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4491 - LEGO Indiana Jones 2 - The Adventure Continues (US)(M3)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1612 - LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga (U)(Micronauts).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars: The Complete Saga</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>From the Trade Federation's "negotiations" with Obi-Wan Kenobi and Qui-Gon Jinn in The Phantom Menace to the space battle above Endor in Return of the Jedi, The Complete Saga allows players to kick some brick through 36 Story Mode levels, including Episode II's newly added high-speed pursuit of bounty hunter Zam Wessell. Traveller's Tales has revamped levels from the original LEGO Star Wars to match the gameplay evolutions found in LEGO Star Wars II, and Prequel Trilogy characters can now be mixed and matched with those from the Original Trilogy - more than 160 in all.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1612 - LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga (U)(Micronauts).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1612 - LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga (U)(Micronauts).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3294 - Lord of the Rings - Conquest, The (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Lord of the Rings: Conquest, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in The Lord of the Rings universe of J.R.R. Tolkien as depicted by the Academy Award-winning films, players will finally fight the entirety of these epic battles any way they want. In addition to crusading as the heroic forces of good, for the first time ever in a The Lord of the Rings action title they'll conquer Middle-earth while playing as the legions of Saurons evil army, including Cave-trolls, Oliphaunts, the Balrog and Sauron himself.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20090113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Pandemic Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3294 - Lord of the Rings - Conquest, The (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3294 - Lord of the Rings - Conquest, The (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2982 - Metal Slug 7 (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 7</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Peregrine Falcon Strike Force, the Ikari Warriors, and the SPARROWS are once again on a search for General Morden and his army. Their mission is to catch General Morden and prevent his attempts at another coup d'état on the government. However, as soon as Morden was defeated, a strange army from the future came to his aid. Now, they must face Morden once again and this time, put a stop to his plans once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2982 - Metal Slug 7 (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2982 - Metal Slug 7 (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0142 - Metroid Prime Pinball (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime Pinball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Unleash Metroid pinball action across dual screens. Play Samus in Morph Ball form on different Metroid-themed tables in a classic pinball adventure. Samus Aran's entry into the bumper-and-flipper world is a sci-fi adventure that has her battling gigantic boss creatures and careening through all the classic Metroid® Prime regions, including Phendrana Drifts and Magmoor Caverns.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fuse Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0142 - Metroid Prime Pinball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0142 - Metroid Prime Pinball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5613_-_Monster_Tale_USA_NDS-LameFuck.nds</path>
		<name>Monster Tale</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A group of nasty kids have snuck into a secret world inhabited by monsters and enslaved them as their pets. This ragtag pack of kids is using the monsters to do all sorts of selfish, destructive things that will ultimately result in the downfall of the Monster World. That is, until little Ellie discovers the Monster World and befriends a mysterious young monster named Chomp. This dynamic duo sets out on a fantastic adventure where our Monster Tale begins.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20110330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DreamRift</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5613_-_Monster_Tale_USA_NDS-LameFuck.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5613_-_Monster_Tale_USA_NDS-LameFuck.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2595 - N+ (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>N+</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are a ninja! Use the included level editor to create your own crafty levels and upload/download them to test other ninja's skills. Run, jump, and wall-slide through hundreds of levels in pursuit of the ninja's ultimate goal; GOLD! Avoid deadly ninja-killing enemies as you make your way through each level. One moment of hesitation and you're history! Play head-to-head wirelessly with friends, or team up to clear levels cooperatively. Outwite and outrun deadly enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SilverBirch Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2595 - N+ (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2595 - N+ (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0647 - Need for Speed Carbon - Own The City (U)(Supremacy).nds</path>
		<name>Need for Speed: Carbon - Own the City</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You take the role of a novice street racer out to avenge the seemingly accidental death of your older brother. With the aid of his ex-girlfriend and a few friends you'll have to take on all the racing crews of the city to get your answers, who'll only answer to you once you beat them in racing duels. Winning also allows you to cash in points for new cars, upgrades and racing kits, which become essential for getting the edge over the competition.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Exient</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0647 - Need for Speed Carbon - Own The City (U)(Supremacy).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0647 - Need for Speed Carbon - Own The City (U)(Supremacy).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3015 - Need for Speed - Undercover (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Need for Speed: Undercover</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chase or be chased! You never thought it would turn out like this-an all-out chase where you’re the hunted. And the hunter. Now you must use all of your experience -and every ounce of skill- to infiltrate and take down a ruthless international crime syndicate, outrun the law, and unlock the truth that puts an end to this chase once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3015 - Need for Speed - Undercover (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3015 - Need for Speed - Undercover (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2504 - New International Track &amp; Field (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>New International Track &amp; Field</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>New International Track and Field has been specially developed for Nintendo DS and retains the ultra competitive multiplayer game play that made the original arcade game such a success, and also brings the Nintendo DS touch-screen and stylus into play. More than 20 athletic challenges await, spanning the 100m sprint, high jump, long jump, through to archery and skeet shooting, pole vaulting, javelin and rowing, amongst many others.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20080612T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sumo Digital</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2504 - New International Track &amp; Field (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2504 - New International Track &amp; Field (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New_Super_Mario_Bros_USA_NDS-pSyDS.nds</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bowser and Bowser Jr. have kidnapped Princess Peach again, and only Mario can save her. Jump, bounce and power-up through visually stunning side-scrolling worlds filled with Mushroom Kingdom madness. Mushrooms make Mario ultra-tiny or ultra-huge, and new items like the Blue Shell (which transforms Mario into a spinning shell that wipes out enemies) will keep players on their toes. The worlds are swarming with classic enemies like Goombas and Koopas, but watch out for new foes, big bosses and unbelievable challenges.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060515T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/New_Super_Mario_Bros_USA_NDS-pSyDS.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/New_Super_Mario_Bros_USA_NDS-pSyDS.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0127 - Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (U)(Legacy).nds</path>
		<name>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Not everyone is innocent until proven guilty! Players star as a defence attorney, who must prove his seemingly guilty client's innocence no matter how dire the circumstances may seem. The game presents twisting storylines and intriguing gameplay in a comical anime style. Players must collect evidence, weed through inconsistent testimonies, and overcome corrupt agendas to ensure that justice prevails. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0127 - Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (U)(Legacy).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0127 - Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (U)(Legacy).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5495 - Plants vs. Zombies (U).nds</path>
		<name>Plants vs. Zombies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Get ready to soil your plants! Stem a zombie attack in the fun-dead action hit — now on Nintendo DS! A mob of zombies is about to invade your home, and the only defense is your arsenal of home-guardin' plants. You'll have to think fast and plant faster as you zap zombies through day, night, fog, in the swimming pool and on the roof. Dig into five game modes and add to the action with four all-new mini-games. Take on a friend in Versus mode and choose your side. You can even make your own zombie creation with the Zombatar! The fun never dies!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>PopCap Games</developer>
		<publisher>PopCap Games</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5495 - Plants vs. Zombies (U).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5495 - Plants vs. Zombies (U).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_Black_Version_2_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Black Version 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your journey takes place in the Unova region two years after the events of Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version. You’ll start your adventure in Aspertia City, in the far southwest corner of the Unova region. Many things have changed in the region, including some extraordinary new places and people for you to discover. Plus, many of the returning characters from Pokémon Black Version have taken on new roles when you meet them. Look forward to uncovering the mystery of Black Kyurem somewhere in the Unova region.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20121012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_Black_Version_2_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_Black_Version_2_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0844 - Pro Evolution Soccer 6 (E)(Legacy).nds</path>
		<name>Pro Evolution Soccer 6</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The intelligence of players has seen a marked improvement. For example, players now make more realistic runs into space, often pointing where they would like the ball played. The physical aspect has also been beefed up, with strikers using their sheer presence to turn defenders and likewise, the defenders stepping a yard away to enable them to force players away from goal and not letting them spin into dangerous positions. New gameplay modes have been added and features like the much loved Master League mode also returns.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20070222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0844 - Pro Evolution Soccer 6 (E)(Legacy).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0844 - Pro Evolution Soccer 6 (E)(Legacy).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1476 - Race Driver - Create &amp; Race (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Race Driver: Create &amp; Race</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Race Driver: Create &amp; Race on DS is a racing game designed specifically for the small Nintendo notebook. Find 32 circuits, including the famous Silverstone circuit, 25 licensed vehicles and official drivers (Mika Hakkinen, Jean Alesi, Heinz-Harald Frentzen). Create the circuits of your dreams via the publisher and challenge up to 3 of your friends on a local network or via the Nintendo Wi-Fi connection.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Firebrand Games</developer>
		<publisher>Codemasters</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1476 - Race Driver - Create &amp; Race (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1476 - Race Driver - Create &amp; Race (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5574 - Radiant Historia (U)(LameFuck).nds</path>
		<name>Radiant Historia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the midst of an unending war for dominance between two super-powers, Special Intelligence Agent Stocke is assigned to a routine escort mission that goes horribly awry. However, wielding a mysterious book called the White Chronicle, Stocke discovers a way to travel to the intersection of time itself: Historia. With this power in his hands, he must travel back and forth through key events and an entirely alternate timeline to right the world's ill-fated course.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5574 - Radiant Historia (U)(LameFuck).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5574 - Radiant Historia (U)(LameFuck).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0017 - Ridge Racer DS (U)(Lube).nds</path>
		<name>Ridge Racer DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Experience the race of your life as Ridge Racer comes to Nintendo DS with all the fast-paced action of the original arcade legend. Compete in the Grand Prix mode against 11 computer-controlled cars to unlock all 20 circuits and the Car Attack mode, where you go head-to-head against an opponent in order to win new cars. Ridge Racer also offers a Quick Play mode for instant racing and a Time Attack mode. There are 32 playable cars in total, each car has its own unique statistics, so players can pick the car best suited to their driving style.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0017 - Ridge Racer DS (U)(Lube).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0017 - Ridge Racer DS (U)(Lube).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4584 - Scooby-Doo! - First Frights (US)(M5)(Suxxors).nds</path>
		<name>Scooby-Doo!: First Frights</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Scooby-Doo! First Frights is an action platform game that puts the player in the shoes of Mystery Inc. during some of their first mysteries. The gang explores spooky locales such as Rocky Bay, Keystone Castle, and others. The player has to collect clues, solve puzzles, and fend off creepy creatures. After collecting clues the player gets to choose who he or she thinks the villain behind each episode is. Correctly guessing grants an additional bonus item.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Torus Games</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4584 - Scooby-Doo! - First Frights (US)(M5)(Suxxors).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4584 - Scooby-Doo! - First Frights (US)(M5)(Suxxors).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5291 - Sims 3, The (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Sims 3, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In The Sims 3 for console and handheld, players will be able to create Sims with unique personalities, fulfill their desires or not, and control their lives within a living neighborhood. For the first time ever on the Nintendo DS, players can enjoy a complete life simulation as they guide their Sims through completing challenges to unlock additional items, new buildings and landmarks, and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20101028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5291 - Sims 3, The (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5291 - Sims 3, The (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solatorobo_Red_the_Hunter_USA_AP Patched.nds</path>
		<name>Solatorobo: Red the Hunter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in a steampunk fantasy world of floating sky islands populated by anthropomorphic dogs and cats dubbed "Caninu" and "Felineko" respectively, the game focuses on a canine freelance adventurer named Red Savarin who pilots a flying mecha. On a seemingly ordinary task to fetch a stolen file, he encounters a mysterious young Felineko named Elh, and becomes involved in a series of events that reveal the hidden truth of the origin of his world and those who live in it.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20101028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CyberConnect2</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Solatorobo_Red_the_Hunter_USA_AP Patched.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Solatorobo_Red_the_Hunter_USA_AP Patched.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0735 - Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin</name>
		<sortname>Castlevania 2</sortname>
		<desc>Created by Koji Igarashi, who devised the long-running series, Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin gives the player control of two different characters. The pair – vampire hunter Jonathan Morris and Charlotte Orlean, a young girl with magical abilities – must work to thwart a plan to resurrect Dracula's Castle and unleash a reign of evil upon the unsuspecting world, all within a new World War II setting.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0735 - Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0735 - Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Order of Ecclesia</name>
		<sortname>Castlevania 3</sortname>
		<desc>Following on the success of Dawn of Sorrow and Portrait of Ruin the legendary Castlevania series is back on the Nintendo DS. This time you play as a member of the Ecclesia, an organization that has sworn to defeat the evil forces of Dracula. Use the brand new Glyph attack system which has more than 100 different combinations to battle Dracula and his minions throughout 20 explorable areas. Take part in side quests and collect items to power up your character in the next great Castlevania game produced by Koji Igarashi.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0732 - Kirby - Squeak Squad (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Kirby: Squeak Squad</name>
		<sortname>Kirby 1</sortname>
		<desc>Kirby: Squeak Squad is a platform game for Nintendo DS. You play the famous and adorable Kirby, who can breathe in air to inflate like a balloon and thus cross the many levels of the game while gliding. The small creature is also able to swallow its enemies and take their strength, and must stop the "Squeak Squad", a group of malicious rodents.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0732 - Kirby - Squeak Squad (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0732 - Kirby - Squeak Squad (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2694 - LEGO Batman - The Videogame (U)(Micronauts).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Batman: The Videogame</name>
		<sortname>lego batman 1</sortname>
		<desc>A stampede of notorious criminals have busted out of Arkham Asylum, where Gotham City houses only the shadiest of characters. It's up to the famed Caped Crusader to sweep Gotham clean of criminal activity using everything at his disposal, including crime-fighting vehicles as well as several baddie-bashing bat gadgets.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2694 - LEGO Batman - The Videogame (U)(Micronauts).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2694 - LEGO Batman - The Videogame (U)(Micronauts).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2332 - LEGO Indiana Jones - The Original Adventures (U)(Micronauts).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Indiana Jones: The Original Adventures</name>
		<sortname>lego indiana 1</sortname>
		<desc>LEGO Indiana Jones: The Original Adventures takes the fun and creative construction of LEGO and combines it with the wits, daring and non-stop action from the original cinematic adventures that enthralled audiences everywhere (Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom and Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade). With a unique tongue-in-cheek take on the original adventures, LEGO Indiana Jones follows Dr. Jones escapades through the jungles of South America to the mountaintops of India.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2332 - LEGO Indiana Jones - The Original Adventures (U)(Micronauts).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2332 - LEGO Indiana Jones - The Original Adventures (U)(Micronauts).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MegaMan ZX (U)(Slot-2 Patch v1.0).nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man ZX</name>
		<sortname>mega man 1</sortname>
		<desc>In Mega Man ZX, players traverse an open map structure as they face various foes in order to acquire Biometals. The crystallized Biometal data collects at the weak points of bosses, so only by defeating them will players acquire the necessary substances to transform into different Models. The specific powers of each type will help access previously inaccessible areas and progress through the game. Each Model type offers distinct abilities including the ability to break walls, burn enemies with fire, dash through water and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Inti Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MegaMan ZX (U)(Slot-2 Patch v1.0).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MegaMan ZX (U)(Slot-2 Patch v1.0).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1549 - MegaMan ZX Advent (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man ZX Advent</name>
		<sortname>mega man 2</sortname>
		<desc>Grey was a Reploid found in a hidden factory in suspended animation, accidentally awakened during battle. Ashe was a human Hunter, chasing after treasures and bounties. After their encounter with the evil Prometheus, they were rescued and taken to a Hunter Base, where their first mission was to help transport a mysterious Biometal. With another attack on the train occurring during their mission, they attempt to protect it - the Biometal, Model A, fuses with them, allowing them to become a powerful Mega Man! But other people are after Model A as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1549 - MegaMan ZX Advent (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1549 - MegaMan ZX Advent (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4997 - MegaMan Zero Collection (U).nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero Collection</name>
		<sortname>mega man 3</sortname>
		<desc>The Mega Man Zero Collection is the ultimate collection of the single player, 2D platformer Mega Man Zero games. Designed to please both new and longtime fans of the series, the collection contains all four Mega Man Zero games, collected together on one Nintendo DS game cartridge. Together for the first time, this collection is the first opportunity DS player have had to play these classic games without the use of the GameBoy Advance (GBA) cartridge slot, and is the only opportunity DSi players have had to date.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20100608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4997 - MegaMan Zero Collection (U).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4997 - MegaMan Zero Collection (U).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0002 - Need for Speed - Underground 2 (U)(Trashman).nds</path>
		<name>Need for Speed: Underground 2</name>
		<sortname>need for speed 1</sortname>
		<desc>Welcome to the ultimate driving playground! Speed into the anything-goes world of Need for Speed: Underground 2 and dominate the tuner racing underground. In this first-ever Need for Speed title for the Nintendo DS, customize and build the ultimate tuner then push it to the limits the underground’s toughest tracks.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>20050510T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./boxart/0002 - Need for Speed - Underground 2 (U)(Trashman).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0002 - Need for Speed - Underground 2 (U)(Trashman).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_Pearl_USA_NDS-LGC.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Pearl Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 1</sortname>
		<desc>In the Sinnoh region, there are two Pokémon that symbolize the region. They appear in the Sinnoh region's myths and old folklore. One is called Dialga, and is said to have the power to control time. The other is called Palkia, who is said to have the ability to distort space. The sinister organization called Team Galactic is trying to rule the region by using the power of these two Pokémon. During the adventure, these two Pokémon, and Team Galactic, will intertwine into the story and lead players on a fantastic journey across the Sinnoh region.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_Pearl_USA_NDS-LGC.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_Pearl_USA_NDS-LGC.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_Diamond_USA_NDS-LGC.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Diamond Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 2</sortname>
		<desc>In the Sinnoh region, there are two Pokémon that symbolize the region. They appear in the Sinnoh region's myths and old folklore. One is called Dialga, and is said to have the power to control time. The other is called Palkia, who is said to have the ability to distort space. The sinister organization called Team Galactic is trying to rule the region by using the power of these two Pokémon. During the adventure, these two Pokémon, and Team Galactic, will intertwine into the story and lead players on a fantastic journey across the Sinnoh region.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_Diamond_USA_NDS-LGC.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_Diamond_USA_NDS-LGC.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./3541 - Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Platinum Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 3</sortname>
		<desc>A new world has appeared in the Sinnoh region: the mysterious new Distortion World, where the normal rules of Time and Space don't apply. Discover never-before-seen forms of powerful Pokémon. Beyond Time and Space lies a Pokémon unlike any other: Giratina Origin Forme. Players can witness an epic encounter between Legendary Pokémon. Travel across the Sinnoh region catching, training and battling with Pokémon.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/3541 - Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/3541 - Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4788 - Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon SoulSilver Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 4</sortname>
		<desc>Pokémon HeartGold Version and Pokémon SoulSilver Version return players to the scenic Johto region first introduced in the beloved original Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver games nearly a decade ago. The richly detailed adventure of Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver is now enhanced for the Nintendo DS with updated graphics and sound, as well as new touch-screen features and a host of surprises. Pokémon HeartGold Version and Pokémon SoulSilver Version bring dozens of Pokémon characters back into the limelight for a new Pokémon generation to catch, train and battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/4788 - Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4788 - Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_HeartGold_USA_USA_PROPER_NDS-NoGroup.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon HeartGold Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 5</sortname>
		<desc>Pokémon HeartGold Version and Pokémon SoulSilver Version return players to the scenic Johto region first introduced in the beloved original Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver games nearly a decade ago. The richly detailed adventure of Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver is now enhanced for the Nintendo DS with updated graphics and sound, as well as new touch-screen features and a host of surprises. Pokémon HeartGold Version and Pokémon SoulSilver Version bring dozens of Pokémon characters back into the limelight for a new Pokémon generation to catch, train and battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_HeartGold_USA_USA_PROPER_NDS-NoGroup.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_HeartGold_USA_USA_PROPER_NDS-NoGroup.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_White_Version_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon White Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 6</sortname>
		<desc>Pokémon White Version feature new Pokémon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokémon can only be caught in one version of the game. Pokémon White Version mark the first time in a Pokémon video game that the seasons will change in the game world. Certain Pokémon appear more frequently during different seasons, and players can only access some areas during a specific season. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_White_Version_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_White_Version_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_Black_Version_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Black Version</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 7</sortname>
		<desc>Pokémon Black Version feature new Pokémon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokémon can only be caught in one version of the game. Pokémon Black Version mark the first time in a Pokémon video game that the seasons will change in the game world. Certain Pokémon appear more frequently during different seasons, and players can only access some areas during a specific season. Note: may require using the microphone.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_Black_Version_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_Black_Version_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon_White_Version_2_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon White Version 2</name>
		<sortname>pokemon 8</sortname>
		<desc>Your journey takes place in the Unova region two years after the events of Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version. You’ll start your adventure in Aspertia City, in the far southwest corner of the Unova region. Many things have changed in the region, including some extraordinary new places and people for you to discover. Plus, many of the returning characters from Pokémon White Version have taken on new roles when you meet them. Look forward to uncovering the mystery of White Kyurem somewhere in the Unova region.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20121012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon_White_Version_2_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon_White_Version_2_PROPER_EUR_USA_NDS_DSi-EXiMiUS.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1444 - Sonic Rush Adventure (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sonic Rush Adventure will retain the DS action that fans loved so much from Sonic Rush, as well as providing a new high seas adventure where Sonic clashes with ruthless pirates. Players will set off from Windmill Village as Sonic and blast their way through seven action-packed and widely diverse levels. Sonic Rush Adventure will make full use of the DS Download Play feature and Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, which enables gamers to compete with friends in wireless racing and mission-based battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1444 - Sonic Rush Adventure (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1444 - Sonic Rush Adventure (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2821 - Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Spider-Man: Web of Shadows</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>New York City has been invaded by a vicious symbiote infection and only Spider-Man can save it. Experience an unprecedented level of game play choice, including for the first time, control over the game's direction and outcome. Choose how Spider-Man fights, which powers to upgrade, who in the Marvel universe to fight with or against &amp; the fate of NY City itself. Choose wisely.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/2821 - Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2821 - Spider-Man - Web of Shadows (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0076 - Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith (U)(WRG).nds</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the third episode of the Star Wars trilogy, Star Wars Episode III: Revenge of the Sith promises an authentic Jedi experience. The third-person action game follows Anakin Skywalker and Obi-Wan Kenobi as they fight enemies, learn new skills, and pull off combo moves. In multiplayer duels, you can fight against Darth Vader and other challenging enemies.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0076 - Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith (U)(WRG).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0076 - Star Wars Episode III - Revenge of the Sith (U)(WRG).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0366 - Tetris DS (U)(WRG).nds</path>
		<name>Tetris DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The long blue bar. The yellow block. And those darn zigzag things whose images stay on your brain. These familiar Tetris shapes started a generation of video game fans. Now Nintendo is putting a new spin on the classic with Tetris DS, available March 20 exclusively for Nintendo DS, which incorporates the use of Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection, Nintendo's wireless gaming service. Tetris DS builds on that emotional attachment by combining the original game with new types of game play that could only be possible on Nintendo DS.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/0366 - Tetris DS (U)(WRG).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0366 - Tetris DS (U)(WRG).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5670_-_TrackMania_Turbo_USA_NDS-EXiMiUS.nds</path>
		<name>TrackMania Turbo: Build to Race</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>TrackMania Turbo: Build to Race is the second TrackMania game released for the Nintendo DS. It features four environments lifted from previous TrackMania titles on PC: Stadium, Snow, Island and Coast, with Stadium being the only one that was present already in TrackMania DS. A total of 150 tracks are included, plus a track editor for which you gain pieces by progressing through the campaign. Online functions are also present for both multiplayer and track sharing.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20100916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Focus Home Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Firebrand Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5670_-_TrackMania_Turbo_USA_NDS-EXiMiUS.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5670_-_TrackMania_Turbo_USA_NDS-EXiMiUS.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5018 - Transformers War for Cybertron - Autobots (U).nds</path>
		<name>Transformers: War for Cybertron - Autobots</name>
		<sortname>transformers 2</sortname>
		<desc>Taking place on the Transformers home planet of Cybertron, Transformers: The War for Cybertron tells the story of the Transformers long before they came in contact with Earth, an event that had been previously explored in the games based on the 2007 and 2009 movies. In Transformers: War for Cybertron - Autobots players can play their favorite characters and fight as the ultimate weapon, transforming at any time between vehicle and robot and hitting enemies with futuristic firepower.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20100622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5018 - Transformers War for Cybertron - Autobots (U).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5018 - Transformers War for Cybertron - Autobots (U).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./6157 - Transformers Prime (U)(EXiMiUS).nds</path>
		<name>Transformers Prime: The Game</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Help Optimus Prime and the Autobots join forces with human friends Jack, Miko and Raf to save the Earth from Megatron and his new secret weapon. Play as one of your favorite Autobot characters as you battle through unique vistas around the world to help defeat the Decepticons. Continue the battle in Multiplayer Mode with 11 playable characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20121102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Altron</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/6157 - Transformers Prime (U)(EXiMiUS).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/6157 - Transformers Prime (U)(EXiMiUS).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1658 - Ultimate Mortal Kombat (U)(XenoPhobia).nds</path>
		<name>Ultimate Mortal Kombat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ultimate Mortal Kombat combines the best of all the Mortal Kombats into a single cartridge. 23 playable characters are immediately available, such as Reptile, Cyrax, Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Jax, Katana, Sonya, and more. There are two bosses that are unlockable, as well as additional characters. There is a variety of new levels, some of which are interactive. Characters can uppercut someone, causing them to hit the ground hard and crash through to the bottom floor, or they can knocked someone off a bridge, landing in a pit of spikes.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20071207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/1658 - Ultimate Mortal Kombat (U)(XenoPhobia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1658 - Ultimate Mortal Kombat (U)(XenoPhobia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5471_-_Zorro_-_Quest_for_Justice_USA_MULTi5_NDS-iND.nds</path>
		<name>Zorro: Quest for Justice</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Zorro to the rescue! Villains beware! The masked adventurer Zorro returns in this legendary adventure on Nintendo DS. Vanqish evil-doers with your razor -sharp sword and lightning wit!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Bros</developer>
		<publisher>Digital Bros</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/5471_-_Zorro_-_Quest_for_Justice_USA_MULTi5_NDS-iND.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5471_-_Zorro_-_Quest_for_Justice_USA_MULTi5_NDS-iND.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./5863 - Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).nds</path>
		<name>Aliens: Infestation</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Developed by WayForward in collaboration with Gearbox Software, Aliens: Infestation will pit players against the overwhelming Xenomorph hive using a vast selection of iconic weapons and tools from the series.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Wayforward</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/5863 - Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/5863 - Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0689 - Asphalt - Urban GT 2 (U)(Legacy).nds</path>
		<name>Asphalt 2: Urban GT</name>
		<sortname>asphalth 2</sortname>
		<desc>The sequel to Asphalt: Urban GT continues the fast-paced racing of the original game with various additions. Asphalt 2: Urban GT combines the virtues of both simulation and arcade racing for the Nintendo DS. Players will be in the driver’s seat while hitting the streets in a wide range of licensed high-performance cars and motorbikes on tracks from all over the world. Winning races, collecting prize money, and then purchasing new vehicles and/or tuning current ones are the key to success. Asphalt 2: Urban GT is a solid game for both sports car enthusiast and racing fans.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20061116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gameloft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/0689 - Asphalt - Urban GT 2 (U)(Legacy).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0689 - Asphalt - Urban GT 2 (U)(Legacy).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (U)(No-Touch v1.1).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow</name>
		<sortname>Castlevania 1</sortname>
		<desc>Set in the year 2036, the newest title in the series continues the storyline that first emerged in the critically acclaimed Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow for the GBA. While the new 2D side scrolling action game will contain all the classic gameplay that fans of the series have come to expect, Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow will also incorporate innovative gameplay elements that take full advantage of the portable system's powerful new technology.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (U)(No-Touch v1.1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (U)(No-Touch v1.1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./1538 - Power Rangers - Super Legends (U)(Micronauts).nds</path>
		<name>Power Rangers: Super Legends - 15th Anniversary</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Protect the world from evil villains, anywhere you go! The long-running, hit television show, "Power Rangers" now comes to the Nintendo DS in the all new game, Power Rangers: Super Legends. Playing as one of sixteen Rangers from the Mighty Morphin era to the current Operation Overdrive team, fans will travel across time and have the opportunity to unlock powerful special moves and devastating super attacks while battling hordes of henchmen and powerful bosses.</desc>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Handheld Games</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/1538 - Power Rangers - Super Legends (U)(Micronauts).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/1538 - Power Rangers - Super Legends (U)(Micronauts).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 DS (USA) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario, Luigi, and Wario have all gone to the Mushroom Palace for some of Princess Peach's famous home made cake. However, when they don't return its up to the heroic dino Yoshi to find out what's wrong. In this portable remake of the original Super Mario 64 You are able to play as different characters from the Mario franchise. Wario, Yoshi, Luigi, and of course Mario. Each character has different abilities to be made use of during the games expanded quest.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20041120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario 64 DS (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario 64 DS (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0681 - Final Fantasy III (U)(Psyfer).nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Final Fantasy III has been reborn, incorporating the latest in portable gaming technology. Using the features of the Nintendo DS to their fullest, FINAL FANTASY III features graphics that have been reworked and remodeled in 3D, while maintaining the mythical Final Fantasy look and feel. Raised as an orphan by Nina and Elder Topapa in the village of Ur, Luneth, his shy friend Arc, the rebellious Refia and the brave soldier Ingus are chosen as the Four Warriors of Light to send to restore balance to the crystals, and save the world from imminent destruction.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/0681 - Final Fantasy III (U)(Psyfer).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0681 - Final Fantasy III (U)(Psyfer).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./0216 - Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Partners In Time</name>
		<sortname>mario &amp; luigi 1</sortname>
		<desc>The famous Mario Brothers return in this sequel to the humorous Superstar Saga. In this adventure, Princess Peach takes a trip in a time machine, but when it returns, there's only a monster inside! The heroic brothers travel back in time only to discover that evil alien life forms known as the Shroobs have taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and no-one is safe! They soon meet up with their younger selves, and set out to stop the alien menace, not to mention rescue the Princess!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/0216 - Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/0216 - Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>