<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Nintendo DS</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance Wars - Days of Ruin (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Advance Wars: Days of Ruin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Days of Ruin takes place in an entirely new world where a large-scale meteor shower triggered massive global destruction that eradicated 90 percent of the population. After the catastrophe, the survivors have formed together into militaristic bands that are warring over the last remaining scraps of civilization. You'll take control of Will, a young military cadet (whose hair is admittedly just a little spiky) who quickly becomes embroiled in the conflict at the outset of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Advance Wars - Days of Ruin (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Advance Wars - Days of Ruin (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA, Australia).nds</path>
		<name>Advance Wars: Dual Strike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first entry of the long running Wars series for the Nintendo DS. This turn-based strategy game has you commanding an Allied Nations army against the vile Black Hole.Choose from a handful of COs (commanding officers), each with his own unique CO power</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA, Australia).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Advance Wars - Dual Strike (USA, Australia).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Animal Crossing - Wild World (USA) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Animal Crossing: Wild World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Animal Crossing: Wild World is a 2005 social simulation video game developed and published by Nintendo for the Nintendo DS handheld game console, and is the second game in the Animal Crossing series. Wild World focuses on living in a remote village populated with anthropomorphic animals, where the player is encouraged to perform any number of tasks, such as collecting and planting. Like all Animal Crossing titles, the game is synced to the console's clock and calendar, allowing the game to be played in real-time, which affects the occurrence of in-game events based on the current time of day or season.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20051205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Animal Crossing - Wild World (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Animal Crossing - Wild World (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bangai-O Spirits (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Bangai-O Spirits</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bangai-O Spirits is a handheld remake of the original, this version has the player take the role of two Bangai-O pilots, Riki and Mami, as they fly in an omni-directional path across environments, blasting away bad guys. The game is a mix of action, shooter and strategy, as the player can use ten different weapons (Napalm Missiles, Homing Missiles, Bounce Missiles, Break Missiles, Direct Missiles, Freeze, Reflect, Sword, Bat and Shield) with the ability to choose from two different Bangai-O suit classes, each with their own strengths and weakness. The main game is at the bottom of the dual-screen while the top is used for a map, so the player can track their place in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20080926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>D3 Publisher</developer>
		<publisher>Treasure</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bangai-O Spirits (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bangai-O Spirits (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The team that developed Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow returns to bring the sequel, CastleVania: Dawn of Sorrow, to the Nintendo DS. This time, you must infiltrate a castle belonging to a cult that is planning to resurrect Lord Dracula. Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow lets you defeat evil spirits using the "Magic Seal" system which utilizes the Nintendo DS touch screen. You can trade captured souls with other players using the wireless system as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Order of Ecclesia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Set in the early 19th century, this installment of the long running Castlevania series takes a slight departure from the typical series storyline. A secret monastic organization, Order of Ecclesia, is charged with finding alternative ways of combating the hordes of undead summoned by the ever-returning evil lord Dracula, as the Belmont clan has apparently gone into hiding. Shanoa, a young acolyte of the Order, is chosen for her extraordinary magical abilities to wield Dominus: the ultimate spell against evil. As she is about to complete the ritual to absorb Dominus a rogue acolyte named Albus steals the three tomes containing the spell. Shanoa is then dispatched to track down Albus and return him and the spell back to the Order.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Order of Ecclesia (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take control of two heroes, Jonathan Morris, a vampire killer and his close friend Charlotte Orlean, a girl with tremendous magical ability. Amidst the chaos of World War II, two mysterious sisters emerge, working to resurrect Dracula and David and Charlotte are all that stand in their way.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Portrait of Ruin (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger (Europe) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>What begins as a carefree day at the Millennial Fair for a young man named Crono turns into his ultimate adventure. When Crono meets a young girl named Marle, little does he realize that this young girl, his best friend Lucca's invention, and a mysterious pendant will thrust him into the ultimate trip through time and space, encountering new friends, defeating the forces of evil, and encountering the one who would destroy the flow of time. Chrono Trigger is a role-playing game, with the usual game mechanics fare for such: the player takes control of a variably large party, developing the combat skills of its members and managing their equipment.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>KOCH Media</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chrono Trigger (Europe) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chrono Trigger (Europe) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra 4 (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Contra 4</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Contra 4 for the Nintendo DS is a direct sequel to 1994 SNES Contra III: Alien Wars. Two years after the defeat of Red Falcon - the first wave of the alien colonization fleet, the main invading force Black Viper approaches Earth. The heroes of the original Contra series - Billy Rizer and Lance Bean as well as two newcomers - Mad Dog and Scorpion are now humanity's last line of defense against total annihilation. This installment of the long-running series adds dual screen gameplay, enabling the player a wider view, and a 2-player co-op mode via local Wi-Fi connection. Each player is now given two weapon slots which can be filled with any one of the game's many weapon power-ups and switched at will with a press of a shoulder button.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Contra 4 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Contra 4 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Heroes: Rocket Slime</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The peaceful land of Slimenia has been suddenly invaded by a mysterious cartel called "the Plob" who then proceed to kidnap all the slimes in the capital city of Boingburg. Our protagonist Rocket is the only slime left behind and must embark on a journey throughout Slimenia to save his friends and uncover the Plob's nefarious plot!Part of a series of Slime Mori Mori games in Japan Dragon Quest Heroes is full of adventure stages that take advantage of our hero's bouncing and stretching abilities as he works to solve the challenges of each area in the game and rescue his captured slime friends. Each adventure stage culminates in Rocket hopping aboard a colossal slime-shaped player-customizable war machines.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20060919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Quest Heroes - Rocket Slime (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IV: Chapters of the Chosen</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Legends of Zenithia starts here! A prestigious army captain, an adventurous princess, a humble merchant, two sisters, and you, the hero. Dive into this unique adventure, and discover the grand tale told through the experiences and emotions of characters from all walks of life.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arte Piazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Quest IV - Chapters of the Chosen (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Dragon Quest IX: Sentinels of the Starry Skies, players begin their adventure as a city guardian who is sent to retrieve a sacred trees fruits, which have the power to grant wishes. Players travel the world, conquer fearsome monsters and unravel an epic storyline. During their journey, players will encounter mighty opponents in fast-paced battles, and also interact with a colorful cast of characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100711T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Quest IX - Sentinels of the Starry Skies (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest V: Hand of the Heavenly Bride</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The legend of Zenithia continues! What begins as an innocent voyage of a boy traveling alongside his father develops into an eye-opening adventure that transcends generations. You - a hero in the making - determine your own path, choose your own wife and befriend a wagonload of quirky monsters along the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arte Piazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Quest V - Hand of the Heavenly Bride (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy - The 4 Heroes of Light (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy: The 4 Heroes of Light</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>With FINAL FANTASY: THE 4 HEROES OF LIGHT, the FINAL FANTASY series is rendered anew as an epic storybook adventure by the creators of the FINAL FANTASY III and FINAL FANTASY IV Nintendo DS remakes. Players will enter a beautiful fairy-tale world featuring illustrations and character designs by acclaimed character designer Akihiko Yoshida (FINAL FANTASY III for DS, FINAL FANTASY XII). Developed exclusively for Nintendo DS, this role-playing game is the first original FINAL FANTASY title for the platform. In the small kingdom of Horne, Brandt awakes on the morning of his 14th birthday. Today is the day he becomes an adult, and the custom of the realm says that he must go to the castle to present himself to the king.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Matrix Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy - The 4 Heroes of Light (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy - The 4 Heroes of Light (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy Tactics A2 - Grimoire of the Rift (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy Tactics A2: Grimoire of the Rift</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Embark on a journey through the vibrant world of Ivalice this summer with FINAL FANTASY TACTICS A2: Grimoire of the Rift. As the third entry in the Ivalice Alliance series, this follow-up to the 2003 Game Boy Advance release brings the popular tactical franchise to the Nintendo DS for the first time. FINAL FANTASY TACTICS A2: Grimoire of the Rift will introduce newcomers to an engaging turn-based, grid-oriented battle system as they make new discoveries alongside the hero in this lighthearted adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080624T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy Tactics A2 - Grimoire of the Rift (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy Tactics A2 - Grimoire of the Rift (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Emblem - Shadow Dragon (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A second retelling of the original Fire Emblem on the Famicom, Shadow Dragon utilises the Nintendo DS online options in a first for the long running Fire Emblem series. The game offers a graphical enhancement from Ankoku Ry? to Hikari no Ken and Monsh? no Nazo, which was the first remake of the original, as well as utilising the dual screens on the Nintendo DS to display the action and character stats simultaneously. The main story centres on prince Marth as he embarks on a quest to reconquer his home kingdom and rescue his kidnapped sister. Characters and chapters that were not present in the original have been introduced in this version, as well as some that were omitted for Fire Emblem: Monsh? no Nazo.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20090216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fire Emblem - Shadow Dragon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fire Emblem - Shadow Dragon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghost Trick - Phantom Detective (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Ghost Trick: Phantom Detective</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ghost Trick: Phantom Detective, known in Japan as simply Ghost Trick, is an adventure game developed by Capcom for the Nintendo DS. Ghost Trick's story centers on the recently deceased protagonist Sissel, and his ghost's struggle to discover who he was when he was alive and who killed him. The player assumes the role of this ghost, who has the ability to perform various Ghost Tricks to solve puzzles and navigate the world around him.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20110111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ghost Trick - Phantom Detective (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ghost Trick - Phantom Detective (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Sun - Dark Dawn (USA, Australia) (En,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Golden Sun: Dark Dawn</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After going dark six years ago, 2010 will see a new dawn. Golden Sun DS updates the popular portable Golden Sun role-playing series with an impressive graphical style. This installment follows the story of the previous heroes' descendants and immerses players into the magic of its adventure by pushing the boundaries of intuitive touch-screen controls.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Golden Sun - Dark Dawn (USA, Australia) (En,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Golden Sun - Dark Dawn (USA, Australia) (En,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto: Chinatown Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: Chinatown Wars is an entirely original entry into the critically acclaimed Grand Theft Auto series, and brings a new level of interactivity to its sprawling open environments. With the use of the DS touch screen, players navigate their way through the streets as they uncover the truth behind an epic tale of crime and corruption within the Triad crime syndicate, delivering the unprecedented amount of depth that has become a true trademark of the franchise.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090320T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hotel Dusk - Room 215 (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Hotel Dusk: Room 215</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Los Angeles, 1979. You are Kyle Hyde, an ex-cop turned salesman trying to track down a missing friend. Clues lead you to an eerie, old hotel rumored to have one very strange room - a room where wishes are granted. It's up to you to unravel the mystery in Hotel Dusk: Room 215, a gritty new graphic adventure for Nintendo DS. Players hold their DS like a book and use the touch screen to grill characters, search for clues and solve mystifying puzzles. Players follow the plot twists and turns as they hunt for their missing friend and investigate the mysteries of Hotel Dusk.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cing</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hotel Dusk - Room 215 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hotel Dusk - Room 215 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (USA) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Disney's Kingdom Hearts: 358/2 Days</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kingdom Hearts 358/2 Days revolves around Roxas, the "other" hero from Kingdom Hearts II. Players follow Roxas through his days among Organization XIII's ranks, unraveling the events that took place during the year that Sora was asleep, and ultimately revealing one of the Kingdom Hearts saga's most shocking secrets. Players and their friends will join Roxas, his friend Axel and the mysterious fourteenth member of Organization XIII on a journey across charming, vibrant worlds full of Square Enix's and Disney's beloved characters.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>H.A.N.D</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kingdom Hearts - 358-2 Days (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Mass Attack (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Kirby Mass Attack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kirby: Mass Attack is a single player Side-Scrolling, Real-Time Strategy game for Nintendo DS that features both new adventure, and a new gameplay mechanic uniquely suited to the Nintendo DS. Gameplay includes the ability and necessity of controlling multiple versions of Kirby simultaneously in order to defeat enemies, solve puzzles and complete challenges.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby Mass Attack (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby Mass Attack (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Kirby Super Star Ultra</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kirby's back with a bunch of fun adventures! Explore Dream Land and defeat King Dedede, tame the ferocious Dynablade, explore a huge cave, take part in a gluttonous race, vandalize Meta Knight's ship, the Halberd, explore the entire galaxy, and more! Kirby Super Star Ultra is an updated remake of Kirby Super Star, a popular SNES game which is broken up into seven main games. In addition to those previous games, Ultra includes five new games and three new sub-games. Listed are just some of the new ones: Revenge of the King: King Dedede wants a rematch! This game is a toughened up version of Spring Breeze, the opening game. The Arena: Every boss that Kirby has met throughout the game, one after the other! Try to beat them all!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20080922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby Super Star Ultra (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Window - The Secret of Cape West (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Last Window: The Secret of Cape West</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Los Angeles, 1955: A man has broken into a safe. A mysterious figure then enters the room, aims a gun at him, and fires. The victim collapses, dead. He drops a diamond which he removed from the safe, and a photograph of a man and a young boy lies next to it. 1967: A woman is slouched over a table, apparently dead, in a room in the Hotel Cape West. A man is seen leaving the room. 1980: Kyle Hyde wakes up in his car and speaks on the phone with Ed Vincent, his boss at Red Crown; Vincent fires Hyde for his negligence. He travels to the Cape West Apartments, where he lives. Just before he enters the building, he notices a mysterious woman wearing a hat and sunglasses.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20100917T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cing</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Last Window - The Secret of Cape West (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Last Window - The Secret of Cape West (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ride into adventure with Link and Princess Zelda. ? Wield weapons and solve puzzles, all with your stylus ? Duke it out with friends in multiplayer battle mode ? Link and Zelda adventure together for the first time The Legend of Zelda: Spirit Tracks sets hero Link on a daring new adventure. The game provides players with a new story, more puzzles and even a new mode of transportation. In this game, Link voyages by train, which offers up new possibilities for problem-solving.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20091211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The - Spirit Tracks (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario &amp; Luigi: Bowser's Inside Story is the third game in the Mario &amp; Luigi series of games. Players control Mario and Luigi simultaneously in the side-scrolling platform environment of Bowser's body, while also controlling the Koopa King himself in the top-down world of the Mushroom Kingdom. Similar to games like Earthbound, enemy encounters are seen as actual enemies that players can avoid or attempt to strike early. The actual battles are a combination of turn-based menu attacks, and timed reactions to enemies during battle. By watching the way an enemy reacts, you can anticipate their attack and avoid it or counterattack.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20091009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Alpha Dream</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario &amp; Luigi - Bowser's Inside Story (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Mario &amp; Luigi: Partners in Time</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The famous Mario Brothers return in this sequel to the humorous Superstar Saga. In this adventure, Princess Peach takes a trip in a time machine, but when it returns, there's only a monster inside! The heroic brothers travel back in time only to discover that evil alien life forms known as the Shroobs have taken over the Mushroom Kingdom, and no-one is safe! They soon meet up with their younger selves, and set out to stop the alien menace, not to mention rescue the Princess!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alpha Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario &amp; Luigi - Partners in Time (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Mario Kart DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario Kart DS is the continuation of the long running racing game series that began on the Super Nintendo. It features 16 new tracks as well as 16 tracks from the previous 4 games, with each set split up into the Nitro and Retro Grand Prix respectively. Eight racers are initially available, each with two go-karts to choose from. A number of characters and additional karts are also available to unlock. New items have been added to the arsenal, including a Blooper squid that squirts ink onto the screens of other players and a Bullet Bill power up that transforms the player into a giant, fast-travelling bullet on autopilot.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Kart DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Kart DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Mario Party DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>He's captured Mario and his friends in his pursuit of a crystal that the group collected when it fell from the sky, and he doesn't hesitate to shrink them to miniature size to get rid of them and get his hands on the other four crystals. The mini-heroes have to find the crystals before he does, making their way through giant environments filled with enormous creatures. The single-player campaign takes place in five different settings, each of them ending with a boss. As usual, players have to collect coins and stars, at the same time escaping dangers such as Piranha Plants and other classic creatures from the Mario universe.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20071119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Party DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Party DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man Zero Collection (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Mega Man Zero Collection</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mega Man Zero Collection is a set of all four games in the Mega Man Zero series on a single game cart. It includes: Mega Man Zero Mega Man Zero 2 Mega Man Zero 3 Mega Man Zero 4 In addition to the four games, Mega Man Zero Collection also features an art gallery with works from the games in the series. The e-Reader cards that were exclusive to the Japanese version of Mega Man Zero 3 and provided in-game enhancements are now discoverable throughout that game as collectibles. There is also the option to play through all four games in one continuous playthrough, rather than having to select each game individually. Finally, an included "Easy Mode" makes the game more accessible to those not used to the game's tough difficulty level.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20100608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man Zero Collection (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man Zero Collection (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Meteos (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Meteos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Designed by Masahiro Sakurai and produced by Tetsuya Mizuguchi, Meteos was the DS's second big-name puzzle game (after Polarium). Most of the game's action takes place on the bottom of the DS's two screens, where colored meteors plummet downwards towards a planet's atmosphere. There, they form columns that the user can manipulate with either the stylus or a combination of the D-pad and A button. When three or more meteors of the same color are arranged either vertically or horizontally, they "ignite" and rocket up towards the top screen. Rockets carry upwards any other metors that happen to be above them, and by stringing together several ignitions it is possible to lift many blocks at once.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Q Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Meteos (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Meteos (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime - Hunters (USA) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime: Hunters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An episode in the Metroid Prime series which started on the GameCube, this game takes place between Metroid Prime and Metroid Prime 2: Echoes. Interstellar bounty hunter Samus Aran is sent to the distant Alimbic Cluster by the Galactic Federation to investigate a message saying that the source of ultimate power lies in this desolate part of the galaxy, once home to an advanced culture. Samus is not alone, however. Other races have heard this mysterious message, too. Six other bounty hunters, each with unique characteristics, will do everything to get their hands on the Alimbic relics for their own reasons. The single-player mode is more focused on shooting than other Metroid games but also has puzzles in classic Metroid fashion.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metroid Prime - Hunters (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metroid Prime - Hunters (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Might &amp; Magic - Clash of Heroes (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Might &amp; Magic: Clash of Heroes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Might &amp; Magic: Clash of Heroes is a mix of a role-playing and puzzle-game on Nintendo DS. The title offers five types of heroes, with specific powers and units, as part of five scripted campaigns. The game also offers a Free mode which allows you to configure skirmishes, as well as a two player mode to face a friend.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20091201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capybara Games</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Might &amp; Magic - Clash of Heroes (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Might &amp; Magic - Clash of Heroes (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Mario Bros. (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In an all new 2D side-scrolling adventure, Mario and Luigi return after nearly fifteen years. The first traditional Mario Bros. game since Super Mario World. The character models are rendered in real time 3D, allowing for a far greater number of moves ever before seen in a Mario Bros. title. Also as the game is on DS, the touch screen allows players to store an additional power-up and view the distance still to go in a level.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/New Super Mario Bros. (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/New Super Mario Bros. (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nine Hours, Nine Persons, Nine Doors (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Nine Hours, Nine Persons, Nine Doors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Junpei, a fairly normal college student finds himself involved in a deadly conspiracy that he couldn't have possibly imagined. He awakes aboard an old passenger ferry, dazed and confused he stumbles around the room trying to reclaim his memories. First thing he noticed was a number roughly drawn on the cabin's door. A bright red number 5. Junpei's memory then returned and he remembered what happened right before becoming unconscious! A mysterious person with a gas mask crossed his mind. He remembered the haunting words he spoke, I'm gonna make you play the game, the Nonary Game' the game of life or death".</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20101116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Aksys Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Nine Hours, Nine Persons, Nine Doors (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nine Hours, Nine Persons, Nine Doors (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ookami Den (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Ōkamiden</name>
		<sortname>Okamiden</sortname>
		<desc>In a fitting reflection of the relationship shared with Amaterasu, the powerful sun goddess who embodied a wolf in Ōkami, the child deity Chibiterasu manifests in the form of a white wolf cub in Ōkamiden. The game is set nine months after the events of the previous game, and the young sun god is summoned to battle a sinister force that has drained the landscape of colour, leaving it withered and faded where once it was luminous with life. Ōkamiden shares many gameplay elements with its predecessor, including the paintbrush used as a weapon against enemies and for puzzle solving. Chibiterasu can also team up with various companions during the game for additional abilities.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ookami Den (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ookami Den (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney - Trials and Tribulations (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney: Trials and Tribulations</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Phoenix Wright is back as the third game in the popular Ace Attorney hand-held franchise comes to the WiiWare service. As Phoenix Wright, you'll play through five shocking new cases in first-person perspective. The game features two unique modes of play. In Investigations Mode you'll survey crime scenes, interview witnesses and gather evidence. You'll then present findings, listen to testimonials and examine witnesses in Court Mode. Trials AND Tribulations also includes the "Psyche-Lock" feature that allows Phoenix to use a line of questioning to reveal inconsistencies in witness testimony.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney - Trials and Tribulations (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney - Trials and Tribulations (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Not everyone is innocent until proven guilty! Players star as a defense attorney, who must prove his seemingly guilty client's innocence no matter how dire the circumstances may seem. The game presents twisting storylines and intriguing gameplay in a comical anime style. Players must collect evidence, weed through inconsistent testimonies, and overcome corrupt agendas to ensure that justice prevails.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Phoenix Wright - Ace Attorney (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Black Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: Black Version</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version feature new Pokémon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokémon can only be caught in one version of the game. For example, the Legendary Pokémon Reshiram can only be caught in Pokémon Black Version, while the Legendary Pokémon Zekrom can only be caught in Pokémon White Version. Additionally, the two games feature different areas for the first time in the series, with the game world of Pokémon Black Version featuring a unique metropolitan area called Black City, and a lush, green area named White Forest only found in Pokémon White Version.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20110306T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - Black Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - Black Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Black Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: Black Version 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Made for Nintendo DS, this game is a sequel to the fifth generation of Pokémon games, known as Pokémon Black &amp; Pokémon White. Return to the captivating Unova region two years after the events of the original Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version games -- the first time in the core Pokémon game series that a storyline has continued from one game to another. Players can explore new areas, discover Gyms with new leaders and see how everything has changed in the last two years.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20121012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - Black Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - Black Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - HeartGold Version (Europe).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: HeartGold Version</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pokémon HeartGold is an enhanced remake of one of the second installments in the Pokémon Main RPG Series, Pokémon Gold. Set in the region of Johto, the player controls a new Pokémon Trainer on his/her way to meet up with Pokémon Researcher Professor Elm at his lab to receive his/her first Pokémon. While running an errand for Elm, the player returns to find that a thief has stolen one of the professor's Pokémon . This event starts your quest to becoming a Pokémon master, leading you through the region of Johto and later Kanto, to battle the mysterious Team Rocket and capture all 493 Pokémon. Along with retaining most of the original game's features, HeartGold contains quite a few new updates.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - HeartGold Version (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - HeartGold Version (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: Platinum Version</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Together with Pokémon Diamond and Pokémon Pearl, this game is the 3rd games in the 4th generation of the Pokémon series. Set in a new region, Sinnoh, it includes 107 new Pokémon , bringing the total up to 493. Pokémon Platinum includes for the first time in the 4th generation, the Battle Frontier which can be played on and off-line, make Poffins on-line. Players can collect badges, challenge the Elite Four, and become the ultimate Pokémon master. The game continues the basic idea of previous Pokémon games - the player, a new trainer, sets out on a quest to catch every known Pokémon and defeat the Pokémon league.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20090322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - Platinum Version (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (Europe).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: SoulSilver Version</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pokémon HeartGold Version and Pokémon SoulSilver Version return players to the scenic Johto region first introduced in the beloved original Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver games nearly a decade ago. The richly detailed adventure of Pokémon Gold and Pokémon Silver is now enhanced for the Nintendo DS and Nintendo DSi systems with updated graphics and sound, as well as new touch-screen features and a host of surprises. Pokémon HeartGold Version and Pokémon SoulSilver Version bring dozens of Pokémon characters back into the limelight for a new Pokémon generation - and longtime fans - to catch, train and battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - SoulSilver Version (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - White Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: White Version</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version feature new Pokémon that players can catch, train and battle as they progress through the game, and some Pokémon can only be caught in one version of the game. For example, the Legendary Pokémon Reshiram can only be caught in Pokémon Black Version, while the Legendary Pokémon Zekrom can only be caught in Pokémon White Version. Additionally, the two games feature different areas for the first time in the series, with the game world of Pokémon Black Version featuring a unique metropolitan area called Black City, and a lush, green area named White Forest only found in Pokémon White Version.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - White Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - White Version (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - White Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon: White Version 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players must take on the role of a Pokémon Trainer in the Unova region. As they work to unravel the mystery behind Black Kyurem and White Kyurem, they'll need to face down opponents such as Gym Leaders and other Pokémon Trainers. The Unova region has changed and grown in the two years since the original Pokémon White Version game. The first areas players travel through are completely new, and some characters from the previous games have grown and moved into different roles.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20121007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon - White Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon - White Version 2 (USA, Europe) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Darkness (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Darkness</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this action-packed adventure, players journey as actual Pokémon through a fantastic land untouched by humans. Before the game starts, players take a test to help them figure out which of 16 Pokémon best represents their personalities. Players then experience their adventure through the eyes of a Pokémon as they explore the land and embark on an epic journey through time and darkness. They talk and team up with other Pokémon to set out on an epic voyage while navigating an endless array of randomly generated dungeons.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>PokÃ©mon Company</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Darkness (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Darkness (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Sky (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Sky</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Sky expands on the fun found in Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time and Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Darkness. Players become a Pokémon and team up with a partner Pokémon. Together the two set out on an adventure of exploration and discovery, ultimately saving the world from destruction. With additional Pokémon to become, new Special Episodes and enhanced communication features, this is a grand adventure with a moving story and stunning finale. This game is a great starting point for players to enter the world of Pokémon Mystery Dungeon and for returning players to discover even more secrets.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20091012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Sky (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Sky (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Time (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Mystery Dungeon: Explorers of Time</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this action-packed adventure, players journey as actual Pokémon through a fantastic land untouched by humans. Before the game starts, players take a test to help them figure out which of 16 Pokémon best represents their personalities. Players then experience their adventure through the eyes of a Pokémon as they explore the land and embark on an epic journey through time and darkness. They talk and team up with other Pokémon to set out on an epic voyage while navigating an endless array of randomly generated dungeons.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>PokÃ©mon Company</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Time (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon Mystery Dungeon - Explorers of Time (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Curious Village (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Curious Village</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After hearing about a strange inheritance dispute in the town of St. Mystere, Professor Layton and his young apprentice, Luke, travel there on behalf of Lady Dahlia, who has requested their presence to resolve the issue. However, it quickly becomes apparent that St. Mystere is quite strange... all the townsfolk seem to be obsessed with puzzles, and Baron Reinhold's fortune isn't the only secret that the town has hidden... Professor Layton and the Curious Village is a puzzle game which uses the works of Akira Tago, author of the Japanese series of Head Gymnastics books as its basis. As both Layton and Luke, players explore the town of St. Mystere screen by screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Professor Layton and the Curious Village (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Professor Layton and the Curious Village (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When Professor Layton and his assistant, Luke, receive a letter from the Professor's mentor, Dr. Andrew Schrader, Layton feels uneasy. The letter mentions that Schrader has acquired an elusive artifact called the Elysian Box - legend has it that anyone who tries to open it dies. The pair rush to Schrader's apartment, but it is too late - the box appears to have claimed another victim, and yet is missing. The only clue is a ticket for the luxurious Molentary Express, found in the apartment. Will Layton and Luke be able to solve this latest mystery? Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box is the sequel to Professor Layton and the Curious Village, taking place directly after the events of the first game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Professor Layton and the Diabolical Box (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Last Specter (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Last Specter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Three years before the events in the first game, Professor Layton receives a letter from his old schoolmate Clark Triton. It states that ?a mysterious giant shrouded in fog has been laying waste to our houses.? The professor heads to the town of Misthallery to investigate, and is joined by Emmy, his new assistant. What is the meaning of all the destruction, and is it related to the village?s folklore legend of a ?specter?? The unfolding story details how Professor Layton and his apprentice, Luke, met.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20111017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Professor Layton and the Last Specter (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Professor Layton and the Last Specter (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Professor Layton and the Unwound Future (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Professor Layton and the Unwound Future</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Professor Layton and his assistant Luke attend the unveiling of a new invention called a time machine. The Prime Minister of London is volunteered as a test subject, but the machine explodes and there is no trace of him. With the Prime Minister missing, London is in chaos! Shortly after these events, the puzzle-solving pair receive a letter, which has apparently been sent by Luke's future self, stating that London is in serious trouble. The Professor and Luke follow the directions in the letter, which leads them to their most exciting adventure yet... Professor Layton and the Unwound Future is the third installment in the Professor Layton series.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20100912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Professor Layton and the Unwound Future (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Professor Layton and the Unwound Future (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radiant Historia (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Radiant Historia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the midst of an unending war for dominance between two super-powers, Special Intelligence Agent Stocke is assigned to a routine escort mission that goes horribly awry...</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20110222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Radiant Historia (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Radiant Historia (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman DS (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Rayman DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The character with no arms and no legs makes his debut on the Nintendo DS. Rayman must defeat the pirates who have enslaved his world. As Rayman, you'll travel through magical worlds where you can explore waterfalls, sea caves, and pirate hideouts. Master Rayman's special moves to progress through each challenging level. The DS's bottom screen let you monitor your progress, track your lums, and keep an eye on Rayman's health.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DC Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rayman DS (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rayman DS (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scribblenauts (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).nds</path>
		<name>Scribblenauts</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Scribblenauts is a side-scrolling action game based on puzzles. The goal is to have the character Maxwell overcome obstacles by summoning objects based on a dictionary of more than 20.000 words, partly based on the concept of the real-life game Mad Libs. This is done by writing an object's name on the touchscreen, letter by letter. When the word is recognized, the object spawns in the world, where it can be manipulated or act on its own. This leads to an endless amount of possibilities to progress through the game. For instance, when an item needs to be retrieved from a tree, you could summon a ladder to get it out, a football to hit it, or just a helicopter or an albatross to fly over there.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>5th Cell</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Scribblenauts (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Scribblenauts (USA) (En,Fr,Es,Pt).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Shin Megami Tensei: Devil Survivor</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Devil Survivor is set in modern-day Tokyo and follows a 17-year-old student and his friends, who see an outbreak of demons with some of them becoming their allies. The Protagonist also finds he has the ability to see a person's remaining lifespan and decides to work to avoid as many deaths as possible. Devil Survivor is a tactical role-playing video game where the player and computer control a number of squads composed of one leader and two supporting characters. Between combat, the player can explore several districts in Tokyo to either advance the plot by speaking to specific characters, discover new information, or take part in "free battles".</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20090623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shin Megami Tensei - Devil Survivor (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Solatorobo - Red the Hunter (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Solatorobo: Red the Hunter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Get ready to suspend reality and be brought into a world of floating islands where personal robots are a necessity and pirates and vicious monsters roam the skies. You'll see many dogs and cats along the way, but don't expect your furry friends to be on all fours – they're anthropomorphs. With his cigarette-like bone sticking out of his mouth, Red Savarin, an overconfident teenager, and his specialized robot Dahak have made a name for themselves by taking on odd jobs. Red's curiosity gets the best of him when he comes across a mysterious medallion. Ruh-oh, strange artifacts? This can't be going anywhere good.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>CyberConnect2</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Solatorobo - Red the Hunter (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Solatorobo - Red the Hunter (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rush (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sonic's first outing on the Nintendo DS system features action in two screens with a story featuring Sonic getting involved in another one of Dr. Eggman's evil plots. A mysterious Emerald is left behind by Dr. Eggman, but an unfamiliar character makes off with it before Sonic can investigate! Sonic gives chase, and thus the adventure begins. Playable characters in the game are Sonic the Hedgehog and new character Blaze the Cat. Appearances from other characters include Miles "Tails" Prower, Amy Rose, Cream the Rabbit, and Knuckles the Echidna. Each playable character has four moves as well as a variety of "Trick actions" which, when performed, will raise your Tension Gauge.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Rush (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Rush (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rush Adventure (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Rush Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>While flying in their plane across the ocean, looking for a strange energy source, Sonic and Tails' plane is struck by lightning! They plunge into the murky depths of the ocean...and awaken on a small island. A local, a raccoon named Marine, informs them that they are on Southern Island. With Marine and Tails' help, Sonic sets about to explore the nearby islands. Sonic Rush Adventure is a side-scrolling adventure game, and the sequel to Sonic Rush. Sonic's goal through these platform levels is to zip through as quickly as possible. By pressing the B Button while in the air, Sonic can increase his Tension Gauge by performing aerial tricks.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Rush Adventure (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Rush Adventure (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders Extreme (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Space Invaders Extreme</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The pixelated aliens are back to celebrate their 30th anniversary! Taking a cue from other recent arcade classic updates, Space Invaders Extreme takes the gameplay of the 1978 classic, and reinvents it, giving power-up blasters, boss aliens, and an electronic soundtrack that plays in sync with the onscreen action. Basic gameplay remains the same: Players guide a ground based cannon either left or right, blasting an oncoming fleet of invaders before they reach the ground. The main objective is to get as many points as possible before running out of lives.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20080703T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Space Invaders Extreme (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Space Invaders Extreme (Europe) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man 2 (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A pseudo 3D (game is played on a 2D plane, but the stages will rotate around Spider-Man at certain points) beat-em-up/adventure game. Vicarious Visions' first title on the Nintendo DS, the game puts the player into the role of Peter Parker (AKA Spider-Man) playing through various missions with varying objectives and pitting him against the likes of Mysterio, The Vulture, and the main villain, Doctor Octavius. The missions themselves vary from missions requiring you to find all hostages to bomb defusal missions and fast paced boss battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Vicarious Vision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spider-Man 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spider-Man 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox Command (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Star Fox Command</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Star Fox Command lets you hop into your fight through a unique branching storyline of missions, all rendered in gorgeous 3-D. This game brings a whole new strategic element to the series, with a commander's view of the mission. Using the touch screen, players can draw the routes they and their teammates will take. Battle the enemies they encounter as they take over bases and strategically advance across the map. Players can also blow their friends out of the sky, as they dogfight 8 players over a local wireless connection -- or take on 4 players from around the world on Nintendo Wi-Fi Connection.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Q-Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Fox Command (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Fox Command (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario, Luigi, and Wario have all gone to the Mushroom Palace for some of Princess Peach's famous home made cake. However, when they don't return its up to the heroic dino Yoshi to find out what's wrong. In this portable remake of the original Super Mario 64 You' are able to play as different characters from the Mario franchise. Wario, Yoshi, Luigi, and of course Mario. Each character has different abilities to be made use of during the games expanded quest. The game now features 150 Stars to collect up from the previous 120, new stages with new bosses, changes to old stages and bosses, and a multiplayer in which player compete to get the most stars.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050311T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario 64 DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario 64 DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Princess Peach (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Super Princess Peach</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>For once, Bowser has changed his tactics. Instead of grabbing the Princess every chance he gets, he's gone straight to the source of all his problems this time around. The two people who always get in his way and halt his chances of owning Mushroom Kingdom all himself. Mario and Luigi are suddenly whisked away, and only one person can save them... Princess Peach, always the one in distress, will use all her unique abilities and items to travel the length of the Kingdom to save her heroes. Her main attack uses a parasol on enemies, which can also double as the perfect way to float down from the heights. Princess Peachs' emotions will also come into play.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20060227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Princess Peach (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Princess Peach (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Tetris DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>At its base, Tetris DS is the same Tetris gameplay that's been around for years: rotate and arrange Tetriminos to create full lines and make them disappear. However, it also has a style very different from earlier Tetris games, new play modes, and online play. Graphically and aurally, Tetris DS is based on classic NES games. A portion of the graphics are sprites directly ripped from Mario Bros., Super Mario Bros., Super Mario Bros. 3, Donkey Kong, Balloon Fight, Metroid, Yoshi's Cookie, and The Legend of Zelda. Remixes of music from these games are also used.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tetris DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tetris DS (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's American Sk8land</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The portable addition of Tony Hawk's latest skating craze (American Wasteland) provide an altogether different experience, especially in terms of the visual presentation. Pushing aside realism, Sk8land goes with a cel-shaded atmosphere, where the same gameplay mechanics of skaing around each park completing objectives and challenges are as addictive as always. Nintendo DS players will also take Sk8land online through the wi-fi mode, along with touch screen controls. GBA players aren't left behind either, with an updated create-a-park and skater modes and multiplayer to boot.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's American Sk8land (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Viva Pinata - Pocket Paradise (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Viva Pinata: Pocket Paradise</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Grab your shovel and tend a virtual garden with Viva Piñata: Pocket Paradise! Dig, plant, water and landscape in an effort to attract many different species of Piñata in the hope of becoming a master gardener. Viva Piñata: Pocket Paradise is essentially a handheld version of Viva Piñata with some tweaks and improvements. The game features a more streamlined tutorial mode, as well as more tie-ins to the TV show. Video clips from the show are given as rewards for completing certain parts of the game. There are also 'Episodes' - mini missions where the player must complete a certain task to succeed.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Viva Pinata - Pocket Paradise (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Viva Pinata - Pocket Paradise (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario - Master of Disguise (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Wario: Master of Disguise</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When Wario sees a television series about a thieving master of disguises, he dives through the TV screen, steals the thief's quick-change wand and takes over the whole show. Episode after episode, he breaks into exotic locations, like a luxury liner, watery ruins and an Egyptian pyramid!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20070305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wario - Master of Disguise (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wario - Master of Disguise (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Ends with You, The (Europe).nds</path>
		<name>World Ends with You, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The World Ends With You is an action-RPG that puts players in the role of Neku Sakuraba, a sullen, loner of a teenager who wakes up to find himself in modern day Shibuya, Japan, with no memory of how he got there and a ticking clock in his hand that tells him to complete the mission... or face erasure. Neku and his partner Shiki Misaki find themselves as "Players" in a game that lasts seven days. Each day, players are given various missions to perform by the "Reapers" within a certain time limit, or be erased from existence. Players use collectible pins to amplify their combat powers against "The Noise", animal-like creatures which can corrupt the people and environment around them.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20080418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jupiter / Future Creates</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/World Ends with You, The (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/World Ends with You, The (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow - Definitive Edition+ (v2.2) (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow: Definitive Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow - Definitive Edition+ is ROM hack that serves as a vastly improved version of the original Definitive Edition hack. This hack has a myriad of improvements, such as bug fixes, Quality of Life, and rebalancing changes to create the best way to play Dawn of Sorrow.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20050930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow - Definitive Edition+ (v2.2) (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Dawn of Sorrow - Definitive Edition+ (v2.2) (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Continue the Wind Waker adventure in Link's first DS game. The epic story of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker continues as Link finds himself lost and alone in unknown seas in a new adventure. Featuring intuitive touch-screen controls and innovative puzzles, The Legend of Zelda: Phantom Hourglass offers new challenges for fans of the series and an easy-to-grasp introduction for gamers new to The Legend of Zelda. But time grows short, and only the Phantom Hourglass can buy Link the minutes he'll need to survive. Many months have passed since the events of The Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker, and Link, Tetra and Tetra's band of pirates have set sail in search of new lands.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20071019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/The Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/The Legend of Zelda Phantom Hourglass (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./007 - Blood Stone (USA).nds</path>
		<name>007: Blood Stone</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blood Stone 007 is an action game for Nintendo DS. Full of gunfights and chases by boat or car, the adventure makes us travel to the four corners of the world in order to stop a terrorist threat. There is also a multiplayer mode for four budding spies.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>20101105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>n-Space</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/007 - Blood Stone (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/007 - Blood Stone (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Age of Empires - Mythologies (USA) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Age of Empires: Mythologies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Featuring three playable civilizations with individual campaigns - the Egyptians, Greeks and the Norse - Age of Empires: Mythologies will allow players to lead mighty fearless heroes and legendary monsters, even call down divine powers of the gods! You can change the tide of battle with an all-new active combat system. Age of Empires: Mythologies will also offer a spectacular multi player experience with unique maps, customizable rules, a new skirmish mode and single-cart game sharing, allowing players anywhere to go head-to-head World Wide.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Age of Empires - Mythologies (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Age of Empires - Mythologies (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Age of Empires - The Age of Kings (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Age of Empires: The Age of Kings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based upon Ensemble Studios classic Age of Empires II: The Age of Kings, this latest addition to the 'Age' series shifts it from its real time strategy roots to a DS exclusive turn-based strategy title, though the same goals still apply. Command and rule.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20061110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Age of Empires - The Age of Kings (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Age of Empires - The Age of Kings (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).nds</path>
		<name>Aliens: Infestation</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>GAME OVER, MAN! The Xenomorph, the ultimate killing machine, returns. Only the Universe's toughest, the Colonial Marines, can exterminate the galaxy's most feared species. Can you fight off the terror of the alien infestation? -Choose you squad and watch the dynamic story system adapt -Pick up where the Aliens crew left off and fight through the U.S.S. Sulaco, planet LV-426, and more! -Load up with iconic weapons from the film, including pulse rifles, smart guns, and flamethrowers.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Wayforward</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Aliens - Infestation (USA) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bleach - The Blade of Fate (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Bleach: The Blade of Fate</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Just as the highly-anticipated second season launches, you'll get to experience the Soul Reaper fighting action of Bleach with up to three of your friends simultaneously. Bleach follows the life of a 15-year-old boy who is able to see spirits and discovers he has supernatural powers. Playing as one of your favorite 28 characters from the series, you will master their special attacks, Bankai transformations and Zanpaku-to as you battle a wide variety of opponents in a twisting storyline filled with surprises.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20080229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bleach - The Blade of Fate (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bleach - The Blade of Fate (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disgaea DS (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Disgaea DS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Disgaea DS is a port of the PSP version. While it still has the same story from its predecessor, it features some tweaked gameplay and interfaces that utilizes the DS' dual-screen and stylus pen. It features new objects that have been introduced such as Geo Cubes that enchances players abilities as well as summon monsters that can attack opponents. Demon Gadgets are also present which are randomly scattered throughout battlefields that can level up an unit as much as 30 levels at once. Classic characters from the original Disgaea and its sequel can also be unlocked along with bosses that can be unlocked and used including Overlord Zetta. There is also multiplayer capabilities that can allow two human players to play co-op.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20080923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NIS America</developer>
		<publisher>Nippon Ichi Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Disgaea DS (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Disgaea DS (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest Monsters: Joker 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dragon Quest Monsters: Joker 2 gameplay follows closely to its predecessor. Players explore areas and tame wild monsters into their party. Monsters fight in turn-based combat and grow stronger. The battle system itself is very similar to previous Dragon Quest Monsters games. The player controls up to three monsters that make up the party, and can issue them direct orders or set them to one of 4 AI settings. This game features two new monster sizes: large monsters, which use up two spaces on one of the player's two benches, and gargantuan monsters, who take up an entire bench on their own. The main character, who is henceforth referred to as the Hero, does not directly participate in battles except for when the player uses items.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Quest Monsters - Joker 2 (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Coming to North America for the first time, Dragon Quest VI: Realms of Revelation for Nintendo DS brings the classic console title into the handheld scene. Explore two parallel worlds while distinguishing reality from illusion and seeking to discover the true meaning of your very existence.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arte Piazza</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon Quest VI - Realms of Revelation (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy IV (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy IV</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Final Fantasy IV is a remake of the classic Japanese RPG that was first released for SNES, known as Final Fantasy II in the West. Unlike the many subsequent ports (to Playstation, GameBoy Advance, etc.), this release is a full remake, programmed from scratch with real-time 3D graphics. The characters have a "super-deformed" touch. There is also voice acting during cut-scenes. A new option has been added to the menu, which allows the player to read a conversation between party members and receive advice from them. It also features many gameplay additions.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy IV (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy IV (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Poppycock! When the number one pompous adventurer, Henry Hatsworth, discovers a golden hat deep in the jungle, it makes him twenty years younger - but it also unleashes another world, releasing hordes of nasty monsters! To top it off, the number two pompous adventurer, Weaselby, is one step ahead of Hatsworth - eager to snag up the remaining pieces of the Golden Suit and claim the number one position in the Pompous Adventurer's Club for himself! Who can grab the suit, put Weaselby in his place, and seal up the other world, all before Tea Time? Why, Henry Hatsworth, of course!</desc>
		<releasedate>20090317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Henry Hatsworth in the Puzzling Adventure (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ivy the Kiwi (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Ivy the Kiwi</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Players of all ages are encouraged to aide Ivy on her journey, utilizing the Wii Remote or Nintendo DS stylus to create the stretchy and flexible vines that propel Ivy forward, over and through obstacles before her. Players encounter crows, rats, raindrops and more, all of which aim to hinder Ivy's progress. But every story's hero finds a way, and Ivy soon finds an ally in the unlikeliest of places-the strange vines that erupt forth to guide, protect and propel her on her way. As skill improves, players must more carefully and quickly manipulate the trusty vines in new ways and utilize the game's distinct mode of transport.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xseed Games</developer>
		<publisher>Rising Star Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ivy the Kiwi (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ivy the Kiwi (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga (USA).nds</path>
		<name>LEGO Star Wars: The Complete Saga</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>From the Trade Federation's "negotiations" with Obi-Wan Kenobi and Qui-Gon Jinn in The Phantom Menace to the space battle above Endor in Return of the Jedi, The Complete Saga allows players to kick some brick through 36 Story Mode levels, including Episode II's newly added high-speed pursuit of bounty hunter Zam Wessell. Traveller's Tales has revamped levels from the original LEGO Star Wars to match the gameplay evolutions found in LEGO Star Wars II, and Prequel Trilogy characters can now be mixed and matched with those from the Original Trilogy - more than 160 in all.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/LEGO Star Wars - The Complete Saga (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia - Curse of the Sinistrals (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Lufia: Curse of the Sinistrals</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Sinistrals, legendary beings of monstrous power, have returned to crush humanity. It's up to the fiery monster hunter Maxim and his eclectic band of adventurers to put a stop to them. Their adventures will take them across an expansive world packed with dangerous enemies, powerful items, and diabolical puzzles!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20101012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lufia - Curse of the Sinistrals (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lufia - Curse of the Sinistrals (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem! (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 2) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Mario vs. Donkey Kong: Mini-Land Mayhem!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>At the grand opening of Mario's third theme park, the first 100 guests receive a new Mini Pauline toy. Donkey Kong arrives as the 101st guest and finds himself out of luck. He grabs Pauline and heads into the park with Mario and his Mini Marios in hot pursuit. The fourth game in the series adds new challenges and new opportunities for users to share what they have created.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem! (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 2) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario vs. Donkey Kong - Mini-Land Mayhem! (USA) (En,Fr,Es) (Rev 2) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Slug 7 (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Metal Slug 7</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Peregrine Falcon Strike Force, the Ikari Warriors, and the SPARROWS are once again on a search for General Morden and his army. Their mission is to catch General Morden and prevent his attempts at another coup d'état on the government. However, as soon as Morden was defeated, a strange army from the future came to his aid. Now, they must face Morden once again and this time, put a stop to his plans once and for all.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081121T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metal Slug 7 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metal Slug 7 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Prime Pinball (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime Pinball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this pinball game based on Metroid Prime, Samus gets knocked and rolled around the table in Morph Ball form; the table contains Metroids, which can latch onto her and suck away health. Tables include the surface of Tallon IV, the Space Station, the Phazon Mines, and more can be unlocked by searching for artifacts and collecting bounties, which are found by destroying Space Pirates and other dangerous creatures. Metroid Prime Pinball is a pinball game with a Metroid theme. Players can collect power-ups such as missiles and super bombs, which can be helpful when defeating bosses. There are also missions to be completed within a time limit;</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20051024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fuse Games</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metroid Prime Pinball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metroid Prime Pinball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Conquest (USA, Australia) (Rev 1) (NDSi Enhanced).nds</path>
		<name>Pokémon Conquest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Pokémon Conquest, players take on the role of a young Warlord who is linked with a Pokémon . Together, they must set out to recruit Warrior allies to strengthen their growing kingdom. Along their journey, players will encounter a variety of Pokémon , as well as Warriors and Warlords inspired by the Japanese feudal era. The game contains nearly 200 Pokémon , including many from the recent Pokémon Black Version and Pokémon White Version games, which have sold more than 4 million copies combined in the United States. As the battlefield unfolds in Pokémon Conquest, players must choose the correct Pokémon type to inflict maximum damage on their opponents.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20120618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pokemon Conquest (USA, Australia) (Rev 1) (NDSi Enhanced).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pokemon Conquest (USA, Australia) (Rev 1) (NDSi Enhanced).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Retro Game Challenge (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Retro Game Challenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Arino wants to be the greatest gamer in the world, but he's continually defeated by his friends at every new game that comes out. His obsession has spawned a digital version himself within his own Nintendo DS. This digital version of himself has come to be known as "Game Master Arino", who haunts gamers around the world with retro game challenges. You have been chosen by Game Master Arino, and are now trapped in the 1980s until you can defeat his game challenges. Retro Game Challenge, based on the Japanese TV show Game Center CX, has you playing faithfully-recreated clones of popular NES-era games, attempting to complete challenges and freeing yourself from Game Master Arino.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20090210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indies Zero</developer>
		<publisher>Xseed Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Retro Game Challenge (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Retro Game Challenge (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Retro Game Challenge 2 (Japan).nds</path>
		<name>Retro Game Challenge 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the game a demon version of Arino transports the player to the 1980s as a kid where he or she must test their gaming skills by completing a series of challenges in various fictional video games. Unlike the first Game Center CX, which only featured NES styled games, the sequel contains titles based off several systems including the SNES, Game Boy, Game Boy Color, Game &amp; Watch and the MSX. Some of the games are sequels or remakes of games from Retro Game Challenge while many are completely new titles.</desc>
		<releasedate>20090226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Indies Zero</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Retro Game Challenge 2 (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Retro Game Challenge 2 (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rune Factory - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Rune Factory: A Fantasy Harvest Moon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You awaken to find yourself in an unfamiliar village with no memory of who you are or how you arrived. Mist, a beautiful young woman comes to your aid and helps you start to build a life for yourself on a farm. Till the land, grow crops, raise animals, catch fish and battle monsters!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070814T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rising Star Games</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rune Factory - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rune Factory - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rune Factory 2 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Rune Factory 2: A Fantasy Harvest Moon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Rune Factory 2 the player, Kyle by default, is an amnesiac who wanders into the town of Alvarna and is discovered by a girl named Mana. Like in the first Rune Factory game, the gameplay is a mix of the farming found in the Harvest Moon series and battling. The player must grow and maintain crops and build up their home, and there are also dungeons to battle and befriend monsters in. The stamina of your character still depends on the meter of rune points, and once it is depleted it will start draining the meter of health points. The player will marry a potential girl in the town and have child with her, the gender of the child will be of the player's choosing.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marvelous Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Marvelous Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rune Factory 2 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rune Factory 2 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rune Factory 3 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Rune Factory 3: A Fantasy Harvest Moon</name>
		<sortname>Rune Factory: A Fantasy Harvest Moon</sortname>
		<desc>In Rune Factory 3 the player, Micah by default, is an amnesiac who wanders into the town of Sharance and is discovered by a girl named Shara. Micah is a half human, half monster who can shift between human and wooly forms. Like in the other Rune Factory games, the gameplay is a mix of the farming found in the Harvest Moon series and battling. The player must grow and maintain crops and build up their home, and there are also dungeons to battle and befriend monsters in. The stamina of your character still depends on the meter of rune points, and once it is depleted it will start draining the meter of health points.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2-3</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rune Factory 3 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rune Factory 3 - A Fantasy Harvest Moon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sims 2, The (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Sims 2, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In The Sims 2, you can control your Sims over an entire lifetime for the first time. With the addition of genetics, the game lets your Sims pass their DNA down through generations. Every life choice you make has a relevant and dramatic effect on the lifetime of your Sim. Now it's up to you to take your Sims from the cradle to the grave, while fulfilling their dreams and pushing them to extremes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20051024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Maxis Software</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sims 2, The (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sims 2, The (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Invaders Extreme 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Space Invaders Extreme 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Space Invaders Extreme 2 follows in the footsteps of last year's critically acclaimed Space Invaders Extreme, which was regarded by many as the best remake of the original classic. This year the iconic Invaders are back again and this time the action is even more extreme! The game combines the essence of the original game with a stunning alliance of futuristic graphic design and cutting-edge audio, overhauled gameplay and a whole new range of amazing power-ups.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20091020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Projekt Just</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Space Invaders Extreme 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Space Invaders Extreme 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Proving Ground (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Proving Ground</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Nintendo DS version of THPG has the similar storyline to it's console cousins, but utilizes the stylus pen as well as the D-pad to skate and perform tricks on just about every surface in the game. The player can also create their own skater or skate park in the story mode or can play classic and perform tricks to complete achievements given by famous skaters. It also features Wi-Fi capability, allowing players to skate head-to-head in up to 10 different types including the standard endurance races and challenge matches along with some new ones including red light/green light in which tricks are given points only if they are performed when a green light is present.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20071102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's Proving Ground (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's Proving Ground (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Valkyrie Profile - Covenant of the Plume (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Valkyrie Profile: Covenant of the Plume</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The origins of a cult classic are revealed in VALKYRIE PROFILE: Covenant of the Plume, the third entry in the critically acclaimed VALKYRIE PROFILE series. Development studio tri-Ace returns to craft a gameplay experience that boasts a captivating storyline with ties to Norse mythology and a familiar yet refreshing battle system enhanced with deeper strategic elements</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20090316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Valkyrie Profile - Covenant of the Plume (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Valkyrie Profile - Covenant of the Plume (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ace Attorney Investigations - Miles Edgeworth (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Ace Attorney Investigations: Miles Edgeworth</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ace Attorney Investigations: Miles Edgeworth is the fifth game in the Ace Attorney series. It is an interquel set between Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trials and Tribulations and Apollo Justice: Ace Attorney. This game is a standard "point and click" adventure, with the player controlling Edgeworth's movements and what he interacts with. For each case, the goal is to collect evidence to determine who the perpetrator is, how the crime was committed and their motive. This is presented as a combination of a third-person view showing the characters at the crime scene and through animated close-up images of the characters, annotated by text dialog. In some cases, still images are used to highlight dramatic scenes.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20100216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ace Attorney Investigations - Miles Edgeworth (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ace Attorney Investigations - Miles Edgeworth (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman - The Brave and the Bold - The Videogame (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Batman: The Brave and the Bold: The Videogame</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Batman: The Brave and the Bold the Videogame fully immerses fans into the vivid animated world of the successful TV series where kids can play as Batman or together with family and friends in two-player co-op mode. Players can choose from iconic characters Robin, Green Lantern, Blue Beetle, along with drop-in heroes such as Aquaman to help solve puzzles and fight foes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100916T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Batman - The Brave and the Bold - The Videogame (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman - The Brave and the Bold - The Videogame (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Call of Duty - Black Ops (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Call of Duty: Black Ops</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Call of Duty: Black Ops for the Nintendo DS will feature six-player online multiplayer mode with a new Perks System, as well as a unique two-player Co-Op mode and Arcade and Challenge Modes that allow gamers to replay the single-player missions to earn extra points to unlock additional achievements.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20101109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>n-Space</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Call of Duty - Black Ops (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Call of Duty - Black Ops (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy III (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 2006, Final Fantasy III reached North American shores in an official update/remake for the Nintendo DS, finally bringing all of the main Final Fantasy entries to the United States for the first time. Raised as an orphan by Nina and Elder Topapa in the village of Ur, Luneth, his shy friend Arc, the rebellious Refia and the brave soldier Ingus are chosen as the Four Warriors of Light to send to restore balance to the crystals, and save the world from imminent destruction. Taking the original game which debuted on the NES, Square-Enix had updated the title with a new cinematic intro, improved graphics and a touch-screen interface to move characters and utilize selection menus.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20061114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy III (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy III (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon DS - Grand Bazaar (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon DS: Grand Bazaar</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Zephyr Town's bazaar was once the grandest in the world, drawing customers and peddlers from all four corners of the Earth. These days, though, the bazaar has more tumbleweeds than customers. It's up to the player to turn its fortunes around! They'll raise animals, harvest crops, craft rare delicacies, and then sell their wares at their very own shop. If players can bring prosperity back to Zephyr town, its bazaar will thrive once again, packed with exotic wares that they can purchase to expand their farm!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20110930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Harvest Moon DS - Grand Bazaar (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Harvest Moon DS - Grand Bazaar (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Infinite Space (USA).nds</path>
		<name>Infinite Space</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Growing up as a second class citizen on a back-water planet, Yuri dreamed of being able to travel the stars. After many years he saved up enough credits to buy transport off the planet, but space travel is forbidden to second class citizens, and he is chased by the security forces of the corrupt owner of the planet. To survive the dangers of space Yuri must become a captain, buy and customize star ships, and fight against hostile enemies both on the ground and in space. The majority of Infinite Space's gameplay involves space ships, both in fighting and in modifying. All ships have a certain amount of space for extra modules to be added, and the abilities and shape of modules must be considered when choosing how to outfit a ship.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100316T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nude Maker</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Infinite Space (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Infinite Space (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Luminous Arc 2 (Europe).nds</path>
		<name>Luminous Arc 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>More Strategy, More Witches, More Fun! As the threat of a rogue Witch looms over Carnava, the Queen calls upon the Magic Association to save the land. Beautiful hand drawn graphics and a stunning score from Yasunori Mitsuda's Procyon Studio combine with multiplayer support to create the must-have strategy RPG of the year! "Engagement" System - Gain potent Witch powers with this intriguing new tactical feature. Refined Mechanics - Upgraded interface, polished touch controls, and rebalanced gameplay.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20081118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epoch</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Luminous Arc 2 (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Luminous Arc 2 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pipe Mania (USA) (En,Fr).nds</path>
		<name>Pipe Mania</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alfonso Senior, having made his fortune from the original Pipe Mania, has retired to Paradise Island. Unfortunately, the island has an alarmingly high number of plumbing-related problems. Alfonso's retired, but he's called in his kids Junior and Fawcett to fix up the island, and maybe learn a few things about plumbing along the way. Gameplay is similar to the classic Pipe Dream/Pipe Mania, but with a more mission-based structure, and more unusual modes. Missions can be replayed to get a higher grade, and high grades can unlock various treasures, such as movies, character bios, and new game modes. Pipe Mania even has a multiplayer mode; compete against a friend for points, or use your attacks to damage your opponent's pipes.</desc>
		<releasedate />
		<developer>RazorWorks</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pipe Mania (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pipe Mania (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Runaway - A Twist of Fate (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Runaway: A Twist of Fate</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Brian and Gina are back in a new adventure, a bit darker than the previous one but still loaded with an omnipresent humor and based on a production worth a big 2D animation film. For the first time in Runaway history, you will take the control of Brian but also of his girlfriend, Gina! Following the story line of the previous episode, A Twist of Fate is also an independent new adventure that players who have never played Runaway before will fully enjoy.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20100429T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cyanide</developer>
		<publisher>Focus</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Runaway - A Twist of Fate (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Runaway - A Twist of Fate (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Runaway - The Dream of the Turtle (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).nds</path>
		<name>Runaway: The Dream of the Turtle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>At the end of Runaway Brian and Gina finally had the time to be together on a tropical island called Mala, but the good times don't last long. One day they decide to go on a trip and fly over the island in a plane. Everything goes well until the engines s</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20071130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Focus</developer>
		<publisher>Cyanide</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Runaway - The Dream of the Turtle (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Runaway - The Dream of the Turtle (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic &amp; SEGA All-Stars Racing (USA) (En,Fr,Es).nds</path>
		<name>Sonic &amp; Sega All-Stars Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a frantic battle to the checkered flag, Sonic and friends speed around tracks set in medieval castle ramparts, lush rainforests and bustling cities, all taken from the visually rich and varied universes of Sonic and SEGA. Fan favorites such as Dr. Eggman, Tails, AiAi, Amigo and many more will join Sonic in their custom built vehicles, revving their engines and jostling to stay ahead of the pack. Each character will speed around the track in cars, planes, motorbikes, and in Aiai's case -- a banana mobile! Secret short cuts, swift handling and avoiding strategically placed obstacles are certainly the best way to get to the top of the podium.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20100226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic &amp; SEGA All-Stars Racing (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic &amp; SEGA All-Stars Racing (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Chronicles - The Dark Brotherhood (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Chronicles: The Dark Brotherhood</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sonic Chronicles: The Dark Brotherhood is a Nintendo DS console role-playing game based on the Sonic the Hedgehog series. It focuses on the events surrounding the kidnapping of Knuckles the Echidna and the disappearance of the Chaos Emeralds, which leads into a much larger story. This game is notable for being the first (and so far only) RPG in the Sonic series. The story of Sonic Chronicles: The Dark Brotherhood is split into ten chapters. The first six take place in Sonic's world, with the team attempting to find Knuckles, and trying to stop the Master Emerald from being taken by the Marauders.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20080930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BioWare</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Chronicles - The Dark Brotherhood (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Chronicles - The Dark Brotherhood (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Colors (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).nds</path>
		<name>Sonic Colors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An extraordinary amusement park has been seen orbiting around the home planet of Sonic the Hedgehog, and rumors are spreading that an alien race of Wisps, who have a unique colorful energy, are being held captive there by the evil Dr. Eggman. Soon after arriving at the amusement park, Sonic discovers he is able to use these mysterious alien forces to help the Wisps escape!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20101116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dimps</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Colors (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Colors (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>