<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Dreamcast</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Border Down.chd</path>
		<name>Border Down</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A futuristic sci-fi shooter in which you play a test pilot strapped to the brand new RAIN combat simulator which allows you to remotely control fighters as they immerse themselves in the midst of enemy territory.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>G.Rev</developer>
		<publisher>G.Rev</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Border Down.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Border Down.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cannon Spike.chd</path>
		<name>Cannon Spike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Somewhat similar in style to Smash T.V. in gameplay, you do battle in ten levels, containing two to four areas each. Players can choose from a variety of characters including Mega man (or Rockman) from the Mega man series, Knight Arthur from Ghost 'N' Goblins series, Charlie and Cammy, both from Street Fighter series and B. B. Hood from Darkstalkers as well as two original characters: Shiba and Simone. The different characters use slightly different attacks but each share the setup of one regular ranged attack and one powerful ditto as well as one regular and one powerful mêlee attack.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020503T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cannon Spike.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cannon Spike.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Elemental Gimmick Gear.chd</path>
		<name>EGG: Elemental Gimmick Gear</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A mysterious planet Fogna you awaken one day after a prolonged sleep, look around and realise you have been asleep for quite a while - thousands of years. The people who saw you during your sleep named you the Sleeper. You were discovered by an archaeological team, and an ancient machine, which was dubbed "Elemental Gimmick Gear" by the archaeologists, was found near you. You are a young man, but in fact you are several thousand years old.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Elemental Gimmick Gear.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Elemental Gimmick Gear.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GigaWing.chd</path>
		<name>GigaWing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the World of GigaWing, many wars have been fought for the divine stone Medallion. Entire civilizations were destroyed in the struggle for gaining control of the legendary item. Now, in the year 2050, four pilots have set off, each carrying a mysterious stone. The stones are said to be the only way to destroy Medallion once and for all. The player can choose to complete the journey for any of the four pilots.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/GigaWing.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/GigaWing.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunbird 2.chd</path>
		<name>Gunbird 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the arcade sleeper Gunbird blasts its way onto Sega's Dreamcast! Take flight as one of seven crazy characters as you battle the Queen Pirates in search of the world's biggest treasure hoard! This Dreamcast version features a guest appearance by Capcom's Morrigan Aenslaed as a playable character, who never appeared in the arcade version.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psykio</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gunbird 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gunbird 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Grind Radio.chd</path>
		<name>Jet Grind Radio</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tokyo-to, a city not unlike Tokyo, somewhere in Asia, in the near future. This is the story about the GG's, one of three rival teenage gangs who ride motorised inline skates and are tagging the streets with graffiti. There is a turf war going on between the gangs GG's, the Poison Jam, and the high-tech freaks, the Noise Tanks. The evil Rokkaku Corporation has the corrupt police in their grasp, and, headed by Captain Onishima, the cops are hell-bent on subduing the unruly teen protagonists.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smilebit</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jet Grind Radio.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jet Grind Radio.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mars Matrix.chd</path>
		<name>Mars Matrix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mars Matrix features unique gameplay based on the "mosquito" system. By holding down the fire button, your ship can absorb shots and then "spit' them back at the enemies. Additionally, each destroyed enemy (and reflected shot) releases experience cubes of various values, which can multiplied by chaining. This experience is used to power-up your ship, and also acts as a multiplier for your score. The Dreamcast port also includes some extra features that can be unlocked by accumulating points in the game. These features include replay videos, an image gallery, a score attack mode for perfecting individual levels, and even a complete extra game mode with a new enemy sequence.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Takumi</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mars Matrix.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mars Matrix.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA 2K2.chd</path>
		<name>NBA 2K2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NBA 2K2 is the third game in SEGA's NBA 2K series of basketball simulations. This is the first game in the series to be released for multiple platforms (instead of solely for the Dreamcast). In addition to updated graphics, rosters, arenas, team uniforms, and signature moves for the 2001-2002 season, the 2K2 edition now supports zone defenses (a new NBA rule where you have to choose to play man or zone defense), intercepting of passes, and making adjustments and actions in mid-animation.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA 2K2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA 2K2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL 2K1.chd</path>
		<name>NFL 2K1</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NFL 2K1 is the follow-up sequel to the popular NFL 2K for the Dreamcast. NFL 2K1 provides several upgrades to the series, including individual team playbooks, an improved passing model, an improved running game, and online play. This game features all 31 NFL teams, season and franchise modes, a practice mode, a play editor, over 2000 motion-captured animations, and the ability to download updated information from the Internet.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NFL 2K1.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NFL 2K1.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Outtrigger.chd</path>
		<name>Outtrigger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You might be good enough to join Interforce, a private enterprise formed to fight terrorism, but to lead the team, you'll have to prove you're better than the other members. Outtrigger is a combat game that features both first- and third-person perspectives, and while it comes with a batch of single-player scenario missions, the game favors multiplayer mayhem.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Outtrigger.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Outtrigger.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Slave Zero.chd</path>
		<name>Slave Zero</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>500 years in the future, man and machine are virtually one and the greatest megacity in the world is locked in brutal war. You are the ultimate saboteur and part of an elite fighting force. Your mission: steal the largest, most sophisticated biomechanical attack weapon ever designed and kick some serious ass.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Slave Zero.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Slave Zero.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spawn - In the Demon's Hand.chd</path>
		<name>Spawn: In the Demon's Hand</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Todd McFarlane's dark comic book anti-hero, Spawn, is ready to give your Dreamcast hell. Play as Spawn (a.k.a. Al Simmons), or any of the anti-heroes or villains from the comics, such as Clown, Twitch, Overtkill, Angel, Redeemer and more in a battle royale blastfest. Not up to killing just anyone? Play Team Battle and join with a friend to blast those other guys! Just do your best to get to the big guy downstairs: Maelebogia, to reclaim your soul and return to life.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spawn - In the Demon's Hand.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spawn - In the Demon's Hand.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man.chd</path>
		<name>Spider-Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Spider-Man is the first 3D game to star the popular web-slinger. It is loosely based on Spider-Man: The Animated Series and Spider-Man Unlimited and features some of the voice cast from each and similar character designs. Peter Parker is attending a demonstration of the reformed Dr. Otto Octavius's new invention when an imposter Spider-Man steals the device. Spider-Man must work to clear his name and uncover the sinister motives behind the device's theft.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spider-Man.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spider-Man.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sports Jam.chd</path>
		<name>Sports Jam</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Foot ball, Baseball, Basketball, Hockey, Tennis, Soccer, Golf, and Cycling! You must master skills from each of these sports to take on competitors in your quest to earn the title of King of Sports! Each game features full 3D characters and background graphics detailing your accomplishments or defeats. Play well and you'll learn what it feels like to be a champion in the greatest sports the world has to offer !</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010720T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wow Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sports Jam.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sports Jam.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Episode I - Jedi Power Battles.chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I: Jedi Power Battles</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Choose your jedi (including Qui-Gon Jinn, Obi-Wan Kenobi, Mace Windu, Plo Koon, and Adi Gallia) and fight the forces of the Trade Federation through the planet Naboo, facing plenty of droids and Darth Maul himself.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20001018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Episode I - Jedi Power Battles.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Episode I - Jedi Power Battles.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Headhunter.m3u</path>
		<name>Headhunter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After awakening from a coma in a sterile hospital room, Jack Wade realizes that his memories, his identity, and even his mind have all been stolen. In order to regain what he has mysteriously lost, Jack must embark on a shadowy quest that puts his headhunting skills to the test. As Jack or his accomplice Angela Stern, you must use stealth tactics or your arsenal of weapons to fight through seedy biker hangouts, gas-filled shopping malls, and futuristic laboratories.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Amuze</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Headhunter.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Headhunter.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue II.m3u</path>
		<name>Shenmue II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Shenmue II is the sequel to the innovative free-roaming RPG Shenmue. Continuing on exactly from where the original left off, Shenmue II furthers the story of Ryo Hazuki and his search for his fathers murderer, Lan-Di, as well as the events surrounding the murder. Taking place in China, Shenmue II contains a real world gameplay system first seen in the original Shenmue.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shenmue II.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shenmue II.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skies of Arcadia.m3u</path>
		<name>Skies of Arcadia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Arcadia is a world where continents float high above, and people travel by airships. Among the countries of this world, the most powerful one is the Empire of Valua. Guided by its greedy admirals, Valua strives to possess all the power in Arcadia. The boy Vyse and the girl Aika are members of the Blue Rogues - noble pirates who attack only Valuan war ships. During one of their confrontations with a battle ship, they encounter a girl named Fina, who is on an important mission whose secret she cannot tell yet. Involved in the conflict with the Empire of Valua, the trio of the heroes must explore the whole world of Arcadia in order to defeat the admirals.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Overworks</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Skies of Arcadia.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Skies of Arcadia.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sturmwind.cdi</path>
		<name>Sturmwind</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You found the way in now find the way out! Survive 16 levels and even more big grumpy boss enemies</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20130424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Redspotgames</developer>
		<publisher>Redspotgames</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sturmwind.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sturmwind.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Godzilla Generations v1.001 (1998)(Sega)(NTSC)(JP)[!][HDR-0004-0010 2MB3, 2MB5, 2MM1].chd</path>
		<name>Godzilla Generations</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Godzilla Generations you play as either Godzilla or Mechagodzilla and have to rage havoc in the city and fend of the army before time runs out. You can unlock other monsters such as First Generation Godzilla, USA Godzilla and Minira by playing through the game. There are five cities that you can lay to ashes, all located in Japan. Each city has two stages to play through. Each monster has a range of moves which range from swiping his tail, using his claws or shooting rays from his eyes or hands. Each monster can also heal himself.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19981127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>General Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Godzilla Generations v1.001 (1998)(Sega)(NTSC)(JP)[!][HDR-0004-0010 2MB3, 2MB5, 2MM1].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Godzilla Generations v1.001 (1998)(Sega)(NTSC)(JP)[!][HDR-0004-0010 2MB3, 2MB5, 2MM1].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights v1.001 (2000)(Mattel)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia: Arabian Nights</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Sultan of Persia and his son-in-law are visiting the Sultan's brother, Assan. The friendly family meeting soon turns into a nightmare: Assan kills the young Prince's bodyguards, locks him up in a prison, and captures the Sultan. The reason is a little disagreement between the brothers regarding matrimonial arrangements: it appears that the Sultan had promised his daughter to Assan's son, Rugnor, and later broke his promise by letting her marry the Prince. In the resulting turmoil, the Sultan is killed, and the Princess is kidnapped by Rugnor, a ruthless half-tiger creature. The Prince must figure out a way to find Rugnor, defeat him, and rescue his wife.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20061206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights v1.001 (2000)(Mattel)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Prince of Persia - Arabian Nights v1.001 (2000)(Mattel)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rainbow Cotton v1.009 (1999)(Success)(NTSC)(JP)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Rainbow Cotton</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Another shooter in the Cotton saga. Trouble brews in the homeland of Cotton's long time friend Silk, as the evil demon Suede steals the legendary Willow candy from the queen's castle. Seeing as how no one can face Suede and his forces Silk drafts Cotton in order to restore peace to her land, but she may have forgotten that Cotton is a big fan of Willow candies.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Success</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rainbow Cotton v1.009 (1999)(Success)(NTSC)(JP)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rainbow Cotton v1.009 (1999)(Success)(NTSC)(JP)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AeroWings 2 - Airstrike.chd</path>
		<name>AeroWings 2: Airstrike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Whereas the first AeroWings game was all about flight acrobatics, AeroWings 2: Air Strike is a fighter jet game. The most important modes selectable are free flight, which as the name implies gives you freedom to fly what you want (land it in the middle of a freeway if you'd like or next to skyscrapers) and over what type of weather and the split-screen versus mode (2 player).</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/AeroWings 2 - Airstrike.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/AeroWings 2 - Airstrike.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crazy Taxi 2.chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the smash hit Crazy Taxi puts you in the drivers seat once again with 4 new drivers to choose from, and a brand new city to wreck havoc with, New York City. In Crazy Taxi, you crashed your taxi through the streets as fast as possible, making money by performing stunts and picking up/dropping off passengers to certain destinations. For Crazy Taxi 2, you can pick up more then one passenger at a time, meaning more money faster, new stunts including the 'hop', which allows you to hop over buildings and take the quick route past the traffic, and plenty of mini games, such as Crazy Golf.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crazy Taxi 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crazy Taxi 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cosmic Smash.chd</path>
		<name>Cosmic Smash</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player controls a semi-transparent human male in third-person view. The goal is to clear each level from a set of different blocks at the far end of the room within a given time limit. Additional time is given at the start of the next level depending on how well the player did. To clear the room, the player has to hit a ball with a racket at the correct angle. The ball bounces back from the blocks and walls. The blocks have different properties, for example, some have to be hit multiple times before they disappear, while others move around thus making them harder to hit.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cosmic Smash.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cosmic Smash.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dead or Alive 2.chd</path>
		<name>Dead or Alive 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The arcade conversion adds an improved tag feature, with new stadiums to fight in, new character moves to play with, and plenty of windows, walls and ledges to fall over and crash through. Unlike Tekken Tag Tournament, however, DOA2 also includes a single player mode, a dodge button (allowing you to move left and right away from attacks), and multi-level arenas.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20000428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dead or Alive 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dead or Alive 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Airforce Delta.chd</path>
		<name>Airforce Delta</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Airforce Delta, known as Deadly Skies in Europe, is a video game released in 1999 for the Dreamcast. It was both developed and published by Konami. Deadly Skies on dreamcast Place you in an imaginary context following the Cold War. Players take control of a mercenary that has been contracted to complete a number of strategic military missions. Each mission completed earns the player money, and the more money that is accumulated, the more sophisticated aircraft the player can purchase. Players select from a myriad of fighters and take to the skies to defend a newly independent republic from its many enemies?for fame, for glory, and most of all: for a price.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Airforce Delta.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Airforce Delta.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Draconus - Cult of the Wyrm.chd</path>
		<name>Draconus: Cult of the Wyrm</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Draconus: Cult of the Wyrm is a sword and sorcery action game. Adventurers play as a male knight, Cynric or as the female sorceress Ayowen. The heroes battle their way through a dark fantasy world where they must ultimately defeat the dragon lord. A story driven game where players use a combination of cunning swordplay and magic spells deal with enemies that stand in their way. The story unfolds over 12 huge levels and is played in 3rd person perspective in real-time.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000228T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Draconus - Cult of the Wyrm.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Draconus - Cult of the Wyrm.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles.chd</path>
		<name>Evil Twin: Cyprien's Chronicles</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Evil Twin: Cyprien's Chronicles is a surrealistic 3D platformer from France. The player guides the orphan boy Cyprien through a darkly comical environment spanning 8 distinct islands and about 70 stages, in a mission to save his 4 friends, find his talking teddy bear, and confront his inner self. Cyprien is helped and hindered through his quest by an assortment of strange beings, from an elephant named Wilbur, who makes his entrances and exits on a swing, a tribe of demis - creatures cut in half, a giant termite queen, a dark root, and many many more. He is not helpless in his battle against the odds however.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020412T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>In Utero</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Evil Twin - Cyprien's Chronicles.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa.chd</path>
		<name>F355 Challenge: Passione Rossa</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>F355 features a number of game modes: the Arcade mode which is the same as the checkpoint arcade version; Championship mode where you race a total of 6 races for the combined highest score; Single play which is the same as Arcade mode but with no time limit; Versus play with a two player split screen; and Network Race where you can connect to the Internet and race a time attack against other players ghost cars. The courses that are available to race on are Motegi, short and long versions of Suzuka, Monza, Sugo, Long Beach, Atlanta Motor Speedway, Nurburgring (GP track), Laguna Seca, Sepang, and Fiorano (Ferrari's test track).</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F355 Challenge - Passione Rossa.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Force 2.chd</path>
		<name>Fighting Force 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fighting Force 2 is a beat-em-up/adventure game set in the not-to-distant future. Human cloning has become a real possibility, but has been banned by an international treaty. The Knackmiche Corporation has been suspected of researching cloning, and you, Hawk Manson, are sent in on a covert mission to investigate. This game features large levels and both hand-to-hand and weapons combat.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Core Design</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fighting Force 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fighting Force 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fighting Vipers 2.chd</path>
		<name>FV2: Fighting Vipers 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is a sequel to Fighting Vipers, a 3D fighting game that allows you to face adolescents and adults that comes from different "urban tribes", but also, in that second version you can choose or beat another time the most charismatic characters of FV1 and some unedited characters never seen again (either in FV2 arcade, version appeared in 1998 on Model 3 arcade board). FV2, as in FV, has the incentive to destroy the fight arena walls with the last combat impact.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fighting Vipers 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fighting Vipers 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frogger 2 - Swampy's Revenge.chd</path>
		<name>Frogger 2: Swampy's Revenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the Original classic (and the so-so 1997 release) changes the way you look at frogs! The stage is set for a totally new adventure where Frogger and his female friend Lillie Frog will need to leap over, dive under, hop through and climb above endless new obstacles and challenges to save the Frog Babies from Frogger's new arch enemy, the dastardly Swampy the Crocodile.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20001013T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hasbro Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Frogger 2 - Swampy's Revenge.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Frogger 2 - Swampy's Revenge.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto 2.chd</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lie, cheat, and steal your way through three districts of a huge city in the follow-up to Grand Theft Auto. Earn the respect of 7 different gangs as you demolish the town in your attempt to make lots of cash.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>DMA Design</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Grand Theft Auto 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Grand Theft Auto 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gundam - Side Story 0079 - Rise from the Ashes.chd</path>
		<name>Gundam Side Story 0079: Rise from the Ashes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gundam Side Story 0079: Rise from the Ashes is a mech combat simulation set in the Gundam universe. Created to celebrate the 20th anniversary of the franchise, it presents an original story set during the One Year War between the Earth Federation and Zeon, parallel to the events of the first Gundam TV series. It takes place in Australia and stars the mobile suit team White Dingo, a guerrilla combat unit supporting the main forces of a Federation counteroffensive against the Zeonic forces.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000428T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gundam - Side Story 0079 - Rise from the Ashes.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gundam - Side Story 0079 - Rise from the Ashes.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gunlord.cdi</path>
		<name>Gunlord</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gunlord is a Eurostyle Platformer with emphasis on exploring huge worlds and blasting off enemies. This game features 8 stages of exciting 2D game play with over 45 unique enemy types. Blast yourself through giant landscapes, explore caverns and reveal all secrets!!</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20120621T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gunlord.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gunlord.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hydro Thunder.chd</path>
		<name>Hydro Thunder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Port of Midway's arcade boat-racer. The premise is non-existent, you simply rev up the engines and go on 13 water courses set in Antarctica, the far east, the Greek isles, etc. on different types of futuristic boats. Races use the usual arcade checkpoint system and scattered across the courses you'll find an assortment of power-ups and upgrades like nitro boosters. Graphics are entirely 3D with reflective water effects and realistic bouncing and bucking in the boats. Multiplayer competitions are supported for 2 players on the PlayStation version.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Eurocom</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hydro Thunder.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hydro Thunder.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Coaster Works.chd</path>
		<name>Coaster Works</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Coaster Works puts the player in the role of a roller coaster engineer, recently hired to help construct several different roller coasters for different amusement parks. The construction part is set up with a screen divided in four camera angles and a grid based building tool. Using vector pieces, the player has to make a roller coaster that meets the requirements of the specific park. The pieces can be tilted, elevated, lowered and turned to make sure the ride is as exciting as possible. After the roller coaster is done it will be tested with a crash test dummy.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bimboosoft Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Xicat Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Coaster Works.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Coaster Works.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver.chd</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain: Soul Reaver</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Soul Reaver is a third-person perspective action game with puzzle-solving and some platforming elements. The game follows Raziel on his quest to purge the land of vampires and take revenge on Kain and his brothers, leaders of the six clans.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magforce Racing.chd</path>
		<name>Magforce Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>If you need an adrenaline rush, Killer Loop might be just your thing: Step into your magnetic glider and race through lots of roller-coaster like tracks full of curves and loops, psyched up by pumping techno beats. There are of course power-ups scattered on the track that may be picked up, including weapon systems to get rid of your enemies. Similar to Wipeout, this is a game for speed freaks.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>VCC</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Magforce Racing.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Magforce Racing.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maken X.chd</path>
		<name>Maken X</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Maken X is a sword - a "Soul Sword" that possesses a unique ability called brainjacking. It can take over the mind and the body of another creature and adapt all its strength and weaknesses. Maken X is also the hero of the game - a wandering mutant spirit of the sword. The ability to manipulate a person's "psi", or soul, was discovered in a research lab. The chief scientist is kidnapped by terrorists and his daughter Kay awakens Maken X who now must assist her on her dangerous mission. Maken X is a first-person action-adventure game with emphasis on melee combat, that offers the player the possibility of controlling minds and bodies of thirteen characters the player may meet while journeying.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Maken X.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Maken X.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MDK 2.chd</path>
		<name>MDK 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>MDK with enhanced graphics, new weapons and gadgets, new playable characters, deeper storyline, focuses on different types of gameplay (i.e. puzzle solving, shoot 'em up, sneaking around). You progress through the game as a team of three characters playing each one at a time: Kurt Hectic - janitor with a sleek coil suit (good for sniping and long distance fighting), The Doctor- a scientist, inventor, and Kurt's employer, and Max- the lovable six legged robotic dog built by the Doc. As the Doc you have to find different parts and put them together to make weapons to defeat your enemies, and as Max it's an all out gun battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BioWare</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/MDK 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MDK 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metropolis Street Racer.chd</path>
		<name>MSR: Metropolis Street Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Enter a new age of driving, a new form of thinking and feeling, and totally immerse yourself in the most advanced driving game ever created. Your 'Kudos' is the only path to success, since this is a unique test of skill, style and precision, which spans the streets of London, Tokyo and San Francisco. Be astounded by the realism, push your limits round 250+ different circuits, in hundreds of challenging events. Indulge up to 8 people in a unique multiplayer experience, and prepare yourself for the ultimate internet Kudos Challenge.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bizarre Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metropolis Street Racer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metropolis Street Racer.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nomad Soul, The.chd</path>
		<name>Omikron: The Nomad Soul</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The futuristic city of Omikron on the planet Phaenon is sprawling beneath a huge crystal dome. It was erected to protect the city against the ice age which descended upon the planet after its sun ceased to exist. In the beginning of the game the player is contacted by an Omikronian police officer named Kay'l 669, who begs him to leave his dimension, possess Kay'l's body, and enter Omikron to investigate a series of strange murders.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quantic Dream</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nomad Soul, The.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nomad Soul, The.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ooga Booga.chd</path>
		<name>Ooga Booga</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Focusing on the combat of "Kahunas" using thrown shrunken heads, riding animals, staffs, or using spells. The storyline is that Ooga Booga is a volcano goddess that creates islands, and has leaders of tribes, the Kahunas, that battle for her favor. It has a distinct Polynesian style and tone, and has many multiplayer islands and characters which can be unlocked. It was one of the last online games for the Dreamcast.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ooga Booga.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ooga Booga.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone 2.chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The world's most revolutionary fighting game does it again! Power Stone 2 takes go-anywhere, grab-anything combat, and introduces awesome new innovations to the hit arcade fighting series. Now, up to four players wage insane battles in fully interactive, multi-level stages. Master over 120 different items used in battle - weapons, vehicles traps, power-upsand more! As if chaotic swashbuckling battles weren't enough, combine forces with other players to battle monstrous bosses to win the game!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000824T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Power Stone 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Power Stone 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Re-Volt.chd</path>
		<name>Re-Volt</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>For years, the Toy-Volt company has been producing toys and games for children all over the world. Within months of introducing their first products, Toy-Volt shot to the top! No one could put their finger on exactly what it was that made the toys so popular. Sure, they employed the best designers and marketers in the world, but there was something else about Toy-Volt toys, something almost magic. Now, their newest R/C cars really start to live! Re-Volt is a racing game where you take control over one of more than 28 R/C cars and drive on one of the 13 tracks.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Re-Volt.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Re-Volt.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Record of Lodoss War.chd</path>
		<name>Lodoss: Record of Lodoss War</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this game the player takes the role of an ancient warrior who has been brought to life by the benevolent wizard Wart. It seems that the evil goddess Kardis is about to be resurrected by her faithful servants. The only way to stop them is to gather famous heroes from Lodoss War universe and to defeat the evil ones in a battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Swing! Entertainement</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Record of Lodoss War.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Record of Lodoss War.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Red Dog - Superior Firepower.chd</path>
		<name>Red Dog: Superior Firepower</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The agreement between the Earth Council and the Haak Delegates came about, not through political or military means, but by financial measures. Three years after their mother-ship first orbited the earth the Haak were invited to the surface in peace and in the search for mutual rewards.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Argonaut</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Red Dog - Superior Firepower.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Red Dog - Superior Firepower.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rez.chd</path>
		<name>Rez</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rez is a fast-action shooter that takes you deep into the world’s computer network. The “Project K” Network has recently been upgraded to handle the rapid expansion of the information age and the core, known as “Eden,” holds the most advanced artificial intelligence the world has ever seen. Unfortunately, Eden cannot handle the ability to create her own thoughts and buckles under the pressure in an existential breakdown. She is lost deep inside the system, and you’re the only one that can bring her back online, saving the world from utter chaos.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>United Game Artists</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rez.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rez.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./San Francisco RUSH 2049.chd</path>
		<name>San Francisco Rush 2049</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Unlike the previous San Francisco Rush titles, this racing game is set in the future. The same rules apply though, get to the finish before everyone else while avoiding massive crashes and taking as many shortcuts as possible. Along with the usual race style, you now have the ability to fly, allowing you even more speed, stunts and shortcuts to the finish line. While the tracks themselves include moving ramps and switches to other shortcuts. Modes include time trials, stunt mode including unique track designs to get the most out of your stunts, and a four player 'Battlematch' mode that adds weapons to the action.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/San Francisco RUSH 2049.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/San Francisco RUSH 2049.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega GT.chd</path>
		<name>Sega GT</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>With a nod towards GT2, Sega tosses in their entry in the race-career-category, meaning that this game is all about racing. Racing to win competitions, cars, money and other prizes (such as licenses for bigger cars), buying new cars to race in, upgrading cars to race in and gaining licenses to race with. It features realistic controls, graphic and physics, and spans over career, multiplayer or arcade modes, and hundreds of cars to boot.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20001201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sega GT.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sega GT.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silver.chd</path>
		<name>Silver</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An RPG set in a medieval land where all the women have been kidnapped and it is up to you to get them back. What starts as a mission to save the women soon turns into a battle against good and evil to the death.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Silver.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Silver.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure.chd</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Yet again Sonic and friends find themselves wrapped up in the schemes of Dr. Robotnik. This time he plans to exploit the power of Chaos, a malevolent being that feeds upon the power of the Chaos Emeralds. In their own ways five heroes will do what they can to save Station Square and, perhaps, the entire world.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sonic Team</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Adventure.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Adventure.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Adventure 2.chd</path>
		<name>Sonic Adventure 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sonic has returned! This time, his nemesis Dr. Eggman has teamed up with Shadow, a dark hedgehog with a mysterious past, and is aiming once again (like he doesn't) to rule the entire world with the power of the Chaos Emeralds! It's up to Sonic and his friends to stop Eggman and put him out of business for good! With new features such as a story line told from the view of both the good guys and the villains, greater speed, and an improved A-Life system, Sonic Adventure 2 is poised to be Sonic's greatest and most dangerous mission yet!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Adventure 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Adventure 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speed Devils.chd</path>
		<name>Speed Devils</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A straightforward racing game. You race for money to upgrade your car and open up new tracks. Each track can be played at a different time of the day and with different weather conditions.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Speed Devils.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Speed Devils.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Episode I - Racer.chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I: Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based upon the Pod Racing scenes of Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace, your mission as young Anakin Skywalker or as one of a collection of strange characters from around the Galaxy is to compete, survive and win in the high speed challenge of Pod Racing. Each character has a unique Pod that can be upgraded with the credits you win after each race. Finish first to gain the most prestige and compete in greater and more challenging tracks, including the now famous race along the sand dunes of Tatooine that determined the destiny of many lives.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000404T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Episode I - Racer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Episode I - Racer.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Magnetic Neo.chd</path>
		<name>Super Magnetic Neo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Super Magnetic Neo, a gang lead by evil, foul-mouthed baby Pinki has taken over Pao Pao Park. The professor must stop her, so her sends Super Magnetic Neo, a little boy robot with a powerful electromagnet on his head. The game has some resemblance to the Crash Bandicoot series in that some levels have you running toward the camera, have a side-view, or have you riding an animal.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Magnetic Neo.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Magnetic Neo.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sword of the Berserk - Guts' Rage.chd</path>
		<name>Sword of the Berserk: Guts' Rage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After saving a traveling performer named Rita from bandits while on their way to Elfhelm, Guts, Casca, and Puck come to a small castle town to rest. Upon arriving, they learn of a disease that transforms its victims into "Mandragorans", making them go berserk and kill people, even their loved ones, without thinking. The ruler of the castle, Baron Balzac, learns of Guts killing a Mandragoran and brings him to the dungeon where people infected with the disease are kept. Balzac brings Guts to his laboratory while explaining that he is searching for a supposed cure. Guts learns from Balzac that the disease comes from an unusual plant, the Mandragora that grew into a tree located in a nearby village on the borders of his domain.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sword of the Berserk - Guts' Rage.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sword of the Berserk - Guts' Rage.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater, released as Tony Hawk's Skateboarding in the UK, Australia, New Zealand and parts of Europe, is a skateboarding video game developed by Neversoft. Published by Activision in 1999, it is the first entry in the Tony Hawk's series of video games. Development began after Tony Hawk's debut stint at the 1998 X-Games.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Under Defeat.chd</path>
		<name>Under Defeat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Under Defeat is a top-down vertical shooter originally released for Naomi arcade machines, and later "ported" to Dreamcast as one of the last games to be released on the system. The game is set in an alternative universe's World War II, where the players pilot the newest machines of war - prototype helicopters. While the gameplay is fairly typical for a vertical shooters.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20060323T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>G.Rev</developer>
		<publisher>G.Rev</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Under Defeat.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Under Defeat.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./V-Rally 2 - Expert Edition.chd</path>
		<name>V-Rally 2: Expert Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Need for Speed returns to dirt racing again in this sequel to Need for Speed: V-Rally. The most significant differences are the track editor, improved graphics, and new game modes. There are 84 tracks and the game supports multiplayer with up to four players. This second installment comes with four game modes: an arcade mode for casual rally fans, a championship mode for people who want to compete against other rally cars for a title, a trophy mode, and a time trial mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eden Games</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/V-Rally 2 - Expert Edition.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/V-Rally 2 - Expert Edition.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vampire Chronicle for Matching Service.chd</path>
		<name>Vampire Chronicle for Matching Service</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Vampire Chronicle for Matching Service is a 2D beat' em up game from Capcom in the same style as the classic Street Fighter series. It uses the CPS-2 system (the same as Street Fighter Alpha series, which makes gameplay of these two titles very similar). Vampire Chronicle is, in fact, a collection of all 18 characters and 4 different play modes available in the whole Vampire (Darkstalkers) series. The originality of this game lies on the possibility of controlling monsters and supernatural creatures, such as vampires, werewolves, demons, zombies and mummies, instead of regular boxers or kung-fu and karate fighters.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20000810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vampire Chronicle for Matching Service.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vampire Chronicle for Matching Service.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vanishing Point.chd</path>
		<name>VP: Vanishing Point</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Vanishing Point is an arcade style racer featuring real cars and road course style tracks. The main difference between Vanishing Point and countless other racers is that you are never racing directly against other cars, but rather are racing against the clock. Your position at the end of the race depends solely on your time, not on your finishing position relative to other cars. What's more, there are loads of computer controlled cars that are there simply to slow you down.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clockworks Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vanishing Point.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vanishing Point.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Fighter 3tb.chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Fighter 3tb</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Virtua Fighter 3tb (Team Battle) is a port of the arcade game Virtua Fighter 3 to the Dreamcast. The "tb" adds a team battle mode which was not present in the coin-op. For those that do not know, the Virtua Fighter series is your classic beat-em-up, with a bunch of characters all trying to kick, punch, throw and body slam the bejesus out of each other. Each of the characters has over a hundred possible moves and the game plays very faithfully to the original. The game features interesting arena to fight in which are more like real locations in they are not flat and some parts can be broken away during the match.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Virtua Fighter 3tb.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Virtua Fighter 3tb.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Walt Disney World Quest - Magical Racing Tour.chd</path>
		<name>Disney's Walt Disney World Quest: Magical Racing Tour</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A cart racing game featuring Disney Characters Starring Jiminy Cricket, Chip, and Dale, and a few characters created specifically for the game. The catch is that all of the tracks are actually based on rides at all of the four Walt Disney World Parks (Haunted Mansion, Splash Mountain, Space Mountain, Rock'n'Rollercoaster, Typhoon Lagoon, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000719T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Walt Disney World Quest - Magical Racing Tour.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Walt Disney World Quest - Magical Racing Tour.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soldier of Fortune.chd</path>
		<name>Soldier of Fortune</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A terrorist organization has stolen nuclear weapons from a facility in Russia, intending to sell them to various third-world nations, initiating a global conflict. The player takes the role of John Mullins, a US mercenary working for an organization known as "The Shop". The goal is simple: hunt the villains across the globe, thwart their evil plans, and save the world! Like most 3D shooters, Soldier of Fortune consists mainly of exploring the environments and killing the enemies that try to impede the player's progress.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Raven Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Soldier of Fortune.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Soldier of Fortune.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Story 2 - Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue!.chd</path>
		<name>Disney·Pixar's Toy Story 2: Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Woody has been stolen from the bedroom, ready to be sold to the highest bidder by an evil toy collector. It's up to good friend Buzz Lightyear to fight his way through from the bedroom to the outside world in order to save Woody from the toy market and bring him home. All of the character from the 3D animated movie appear through-out the side scroller to help Buzz get to where he is needed. Along with the use of his cannon, Buzz can jump to hard to reach places, also useful in collecting the hidden coins that open bonus levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Toy Story 2 - Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue!.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Toy Story 2 - Buzz Lightyear to the Rescue!.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow Man.chd</path>
		<name>Shadow Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You're the Shadow Man, a person who can switch between the world of the dead and of the living. In Shadow Man your mission is to prevent 5 serial killers from bringing the total armageddon. In the world of the living, you're mortal and have conventional weapons. When you die, you are transported to the world of the dead and you become Shadow Man once again. Which means you're not really mortal. In the world of the dead you can't use normal weapons, your gun shoots ghosts which kill the zombies and the other ugly creatures which live there. You also have different voodoo powers and weapons. And you're carrying a large inventory around.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadow Man.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadow Man.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Carrier.chd</path>
		<name>Carrier</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Carrier is the first survival horror game released for the Dreamcast. As the game starts you are Jack Ingles, a member of a special forces team. You are sent in by Helicopter to investigate a carrier that has not been responding to radio contact after completing a mission. As you approach the deck of the carrier, your helicopter is shot down. After crash landing on the deck, it is your job to investigate what exactly is going on, and escape alive. The game is played from a third person perspective.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010705T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Carrier.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Carrier.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gauntlet Legends.chd</path>
		<name>Gauntlet Legends</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As many as four (Expansion Pak required) can band together in an epic quest through seven magical worlds -- three of which are brand-new to the home version -- to defeat the vile Skorne. The nonlinear action begins in a hub, which leads to the worlds, each with two to five levels. You can complete a level in one world, then move to another world, returning later to finish a new level in the first world.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20000727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gauntlet Legends.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gauntlet Legends.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Illbleed.chd</path>
		<name>Illbleed</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>B-movie horror-film producer Michael Reynolds offers a million dollars to anyone who can survive his terrifying movie-themed park, Illbleed. Four teenage horror fans, Eriko Christy, Kevin Kertsman, Randy Fairbanks, and Michel Waters, receive invitations to the ghastly park. Filled with enthusiasm, Kevin, Randy, and Michel carelessly rush to Illbleed, leaving behind young Eriko. Eriko eventually heads to Illbleed to search for her now-missing friends. Eriko must find her friends, survive the horrors of Illbleed, and get out alive, if she can.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Illbleed.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Illbleed.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./D2.m3u</path>
		<name>D·2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the middle of a raging blizzard, Laura opens her eyes to find herself inside a mountain cabin. She was saved by Kimberly, one of the passengers of the wrecked plane. Ten days have passed since the crash but Laura can remember nothing, not even her name. The door of the cabin opens and one of the terrorists enters. While Kimberly and Laura stare in horror, he transforms into a hideous monster. He is not the only one. Other crash survivors and locals have mutated into terrifying monstrosities and attacked people.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>WARP</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/D2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/D2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./L.O.L. - Lack of Love.chd</path>
		<name>L.O.L.: Lack of Love</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>L.O.L: Lack Of Love, is an evolutionary adventure game developed by Love-de-Lic and published by ASCII Entertainment for the Sega Dreamcast. The game was released exclusively in Japan on November 2, 2000.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/L.O.L. - Lack of Love.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/L.O.L. - Lack of Love.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Napple Tale - Arsia in Daydream.cdi</path>
		<name>Napple Tale: Arsia in Daydream</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player controls Arsia, a young girl, wandering around Napple town and levels themed around the four seasons. To restore peace, Arsia and her pet creatures will have to collect six "petals". Although the game is primarily a platform game, there are many people to talk to and a complete story accompanying the action. Exploration parts mainly develop in Napple with a third person view, while the platformer levels, the four seasons, gets a 2D side-scrolling camera.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20001019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Chime Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Napple Tale - Arsia in Daydream.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Napple Tale - Arsia in Daydream.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.chd</path>
		<name>JoJo's Bizarre Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the Japanese manga/anime of the same name, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure is a 2D fighter from Capcom. Take on the role of one of 18 characters and battle your friends in Arcade Mode, or take on the role of Jotaro "JoJo" Kujo and his friends in Super Story Mode as they battle their way to the evil vampire, Dio Brando, in order to save the world! A Dreamcast version also exists, but without the Super Story Mode and a couple of missing characters. Both games were ports of Capcom's arcade fighter, JoJo's Venture and its update, JoJo's Bizarre Adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jojo's Bizarre Adventure.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mr Driller.chd</path>
		<name>Mr. Driller</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mr Driller's world has been covered with mysterious blocks. Armed with only a mighty drill, you'll have to dig your way down to safety before his air supply runs out! Mr Driller is a real-time puzzle game that relies solely on quick-thinking and a bit of planning. Gameplay is a combination of Tetris and Boulder Dash: You have to drill down through multi-colored blocks to reach the bottom while avoiding the consequences of reckless drilling (blocks may fall on you and crush you).</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mr Driller.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mr Driller.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pro Pinball - Trilogy.chd</path>
		<name>Pro Pinball Trilogy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This compilation contains the following three tables of Empire's Pro Pinball series: Pro Pinball: Timeshock! Pro Pinball: Big Race USA Pro Pinball: Fantastic Journey The first part of the series, Pro Pinball: The Web, is not included.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>20010608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cunning Developments</developer>
		<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pro Pinball - Trilogy.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pro Pinball - Trilogy.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien Front Online v1.000 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Alien Front Online</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alien Front Online is a tank driving shoot-'em up that focuses on online play. The premise is a classic alien invasion of earth. Non-friendly aliens descend to the earth and put up strongholds around globe. You can choose to fight the resulting battles from the side of the army or the side of the aliens.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010809T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wow Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien Front Online v1.000 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien Front Online v1.000 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Floigan Bros. - Episode 1 v1.001 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Floigan Bros.: Episode I</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hoigle and Moigle Floigan are brothers who live in a junkyard. Hoigle is the elder of the two. He's also the smaller of the two, and by far the smarter. In this game you control Hoigle as he helps his large but slow-witted younger brother Moigle to build a secret invention.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Floigan Bros. - Episode 1 v1.001 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Floigan Bros. - Episode 1 v1.001 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Heavy Metal - Geomatrix v1.001 (2001)(Capcom)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Heavy Metal: Geomatrix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the Heavy Metal world created by Kevin Eastman and Simon Bisley, this fighting title allows you to take control of a team of three fighters, ranging from a basic all-rounder, or a lightning fast female to a huge bulky mass of power. Of course, they are all a mix of human and humanoid, and depending on their strengths, have a range of different moves.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Heavy Metal - Geomatrix v1.001 (2001)(Capcom)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Heavy Metal - Geomatrix v1.001 (2001)(Capcom)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./House of the Dead 2, The v1.001 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!][13S].chd</path>
		<name>House of the Dead 2, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The House of The Dead 2 is a conversion of Sega's popular light gun arcade game. In this game you play the role of a detective out to stop a madman who has unleashed zombies and other horrid creatures on an Italian city. You have to kill the monsters, save people and find out the plans behind this mayhem. The game uses a auto game camera which pans around in a preset manner as you venture through the city killing the creatures and rescuing people. Extra modes like training and time trial are included for replayability.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/House of the Dead 2, The v1.001 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!][13S].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/House of the Dead 2, The v1.001 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!][13S].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kao the Kangaroo v1.002 (2000)(Titus)(US)(en-es)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Kao the Kangaroo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A kangaroo named Kao was playing with his friends in his native Australia, when suddenly evil hunters appeared, put him in a cage, and took him away. They didn't know that Kao was quite proficient in the art of boxing, so freeing himself from the trap wasn't particularly hard. However, Kao finds himself far away from home, and must fight and hop his way back.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>X-Ray</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kao the Kangaroo v1.002 (2000)(Titus)(US)(en-es)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kao the Kangaroo v1.002 (2000)(Titus)(US)(en-es)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Plasma Sword: Nightmare of Bilstein</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein is the successor of Star Gladiator released for Playstation. Like it's predecessor it was first released on Arcade before ported to the Dreamcast.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Plasma Sword - Nightmare of Bilstein v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psychic Force 2012 v1.010 (1999)(Taito)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Psychic Force 2012</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Psychic Force 2012, the sequel to Psychic Force, is a one-on-one fighting game with a twist. The matches take place inside a giant floating cube. You are able to fly, using your psychic abilities, around a 3D arena with six walls. Each of the ten available characters, Might, Regina, Wendy, Emilio, Setsuna, Patty, Gudeath, Genshin, Carlo, and Gates, are controlled with three buttons: guard, weak attack and strong attack. The effect varies with the distance. Next to the regular life meter, there is also a power meter. By using special moves, the meter is drained and your moves are limited.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Psychic Force 2012 v1.010 (1999)(Taito)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Psychic Force 2012 v1.010 (1999)(Taito)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TimeStalkers v1.002 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Time Stalkers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are walking down a lonely country road, thinking about a girl when suddenly you are attacked. You fend him off with your sword, he runs. You are Sword the mighty warrior, so you give chase and find yourself, eventually, in a land that is a quiltwork of different cultures and styles.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19990930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Climax</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/TimeStalkers v1.002 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/TimeStalkers v1.002 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Series Baseball 2K2 v1.000 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!][3S].chd</path>
		<name>World Series Baseball 2K2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>World Series Baseball 2K2 features a complete 2002 roster list and various game modes. You can compete in a standard exhibition game, go for a franchise, skip directly to the playoffs, compete in a home run derby, or play online.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20020101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/World Series Baseball 2K2 v1.000 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!][3S].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/World Series Baseball 2K2 v1.000 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!][3S].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF Royal Rumble v0.800 (2000)(THQ)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>WWF Royal Rumble</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Brutal chaos has hit with havoc wrestling that is a royal rumble where you can take up to 9 people in the ring at a time fighting to win. Fight as your favorite super star like The Giant, Gold Berg, and The Rock, and many more. Fight in different modes like "Cage Match" where you fight multiple players to see who can defeat all and climb out, or a "Belt Match" where you can defeat all and get a latter to get the belt off the top of the ring. Bone crunching multiplayer that lets you fight up to 4 people against each other to see who's best.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/WWF Royal Rumble v0.800 (2000)(THQ)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WWF Royal Rumble v0.800 (2000)(THQ)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Industrial Spy - Operation Espionage v1.001 (2000)(UFO)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Industrial Spy: Operation Espionage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blending the stealth, RTS, and RPG genres, Industrial Spy has the player leading a team of superspies (Espion Agents, part of the Blitzstrahl corporation) infiltrating various locales like museums, a military installation, and even a German-style castle full of traps. Each of the agents has his own specialties, like computer hacking, rollerblading, handguns, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NEC Home Electronics</developer>
		<publisher>U.F.O. Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Industrial Spy - Operation Espionage v1.001 (2000)(UFO)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Industrial Spy - Operation Espionage v1.001 (2000)(UFO)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis.chd</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Three years ago a brilliant scientist disappeared while researching a new form of energy. The government that funded his research wrote the whole affair off as a loss, which made it all the more upsetting when reports of Dr. Kirk's good health and nearly finished research came in. A special forces team is sent to the doctor's private island laboratory to extract him and his research, but they are totally unprepared for some of the side effects of his developments. Side effects that come from 100 million years in the past.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NexTech</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dino Crisis.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dino Crisis.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daytona USA 2001.chd</path>
		<name>Daytona USA 2001</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Just like the arcade version, pick one of three tracks (beginner, advanced, or expert) and either automatic or standard transmission. A pounding music soundtrack kicks in as you are slapped into your car to await the green light. The game offers both a traditional arcade mode with checkpoint time splits and a special PC mode that pits you against the other cars over different race distances. The PC mode also offers more car choices, with a variety of speed, acceleration, and grip characteristics.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amusement Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Daytona USA 2001.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Daytona USA 2001.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Expendable.chd</path>
		<name>Expendable</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 2463 a race of vicious aliens has invaded human planets, wiping out the population of Novocastria first. Only the Millennium Soldier can lead the human fightback. In this sci-fi action game, reflex shooting dominates over planning or tactical play. Expect non-stop action from fighting and relentlessly killing off tons of bad guys across more than 20 levels of 3rd person 3D action, taking place inside and outside. Powering up your weaponry is crucial - there are 18 different ones to collect, from pulse cannons to particle accelerators and rockets to missiles. Two player cooperative and deathmatch modes are provided.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rage Software</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Expendable.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Expendable.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chicken Run.chd</path>
		<name>Chicken Run</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tweedy's Farm is home to a bunch of chickens, who are falling behind on their work load (laying eggs). So Mrs Tweedy decides to go into a new business, Chicken Pie making. The chickens leader, Ginger, is in desperate need of a good escape plan, and when Rocky flys in from the US to lend them a hand, the gang decide that the only way out of the farm is to fly out. But of course, chickens can't fly!! So it is up to you to collect the pieces for the flying machine so you and your fellow chickens can escape.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blitz Games</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chicken Run.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chicken Run.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Centipede.chd</path>
		<name>Centipede</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is a remake or "modernaization" of the classic arcade shooter Centipede, originally released in arcades by Atari in 1980. This remake keeps some of the original game's shooter-style gameplay while mixing in more console-style exploration. Gameplay progresses through five "worlds": Weedom, Frostonia, Infernium, Enigma, and Evile. Players blast away at the classic centipedes, spiders, fleas, and scorpions while fighting new enemies like the mosquito, cockroach, and killer mushroom. A "classic" mode is also included, which allows players to play the classic game in a new "3D" isometric perspective.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19991123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Leaping Lizard Games</developer>
		<publisher>Hasbro Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Centipede.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Centipede.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./HALF-LIFE.chd</path>
		<name>Half-Life</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Deep in the bowels of the Black Mesa Federal Research Facility, a decommissioned missile base, a top-secret experiment goes terribly wrong. As aliens come through the walls and a military death squad shoots everything in sight, young research associate Gordon Freeman must scramble to stay alive. Find your way through the monster-ridden areas of Black Mesa using your wits, limited security clearance, and a variety of weapons, ranging from a crowbar and pistols to a rocket launcher and grenades. With split-screen deathmatch and its exclusive "Decay" single-player and multiplayer cooperative modes, Half-Life is an action experience like no other. Cancelled.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valve</developer>
		<publisher>Havas Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/HALF-LIFE.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/HALF-LIFE.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SnoCross - Championship Racing v1.000 (2000)(Crave)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>SnoCross Championship Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Strap on your goggles and helmet, choose your favorite Yamaha sled, and hit the courses. Gain experience day and night, sun rain or snow, racing on the icy flats of Vladivostok, the slopes of Aspen, and the tunnels of Nagano. But, the real challenge starts when you enter the race circuit. Start with the 500cc sleds, win races, upgrade your snowmobile, and unlock higher end sleds and new courses. And, if you're looking for even more challenges, race head-to-head with your friends, go vertical on hill-climbing tracks, or create your own courses with the included track editor.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Uds</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/SnoCross - Championship Racing v1.000 (2000)(Crave)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SnoCross - Championship Racing v1.000 (2000)(Crave)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms Armageddon v1.001 (1999)(MicroProse)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Worms: Armageddon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>For those who've never played Worms, it's at heart similar to the old game Artillery, which you control an artillery piece. In essence, you give it a shot angle and shot power, and try to hit your enemy, despite wind effects and the enemy firing back at you. Worms puts you in command of a team of Worms, but not only can you move around the landscape, you can use many types of weapons to try to dispatch the enemy, from bazookas to mini-guns to exploding sheep.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>MicroProse</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Worms Armageddon v1.001 (1999)(MicroProse)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Worms Armageddon v1.001 (1999)(MicroProse)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Worms World Party v1.001 (2001)(Titus)(US)(M9)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Worms: World Party</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Worms are back, deadlier than ever. You're going to learn that there's nothing more dangerous than a Worm with a bazooka or a shotgun. At first sight, Worms World Party may seem very similar to Worms Armageddon. However, this time the game has been specially designed with multiplayer in mind. Up to 6 players can battle out at the same time on local networks or on the internet, using Team17 own matchmaking service, called Wormnet.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team 17</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Worms World Party v1.001 (2001)(Titus)(US)(M9)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Worms World Party v1.001 (2001)(Titus)(US)(M9)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Rally 2 v1.003 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Sega Rally 2: Sega Rally Championship</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sega Rally 2 is the sequel to Sega's hit arcade game, Sega Rally. This game, like it's predecessor, is based on Rally racing. Rally racing is unique in that races take place on both race tracks and off-road courses. The courses in this game reflect this nicely. Some take place in the desert or forest, others take place in cities.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sega Rally 2 v1.003 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sega Rally 2 v1.003 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Toy Commander.chd</path>
		<name>Toy Commander</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Some of the greatest adventures that kids have growing up occur in their imaginations as they play with their toys. Toy Commander is a game that attempts to capture these adventures in an interactive, three dimensional world. The player's perspective is that of the toy vehicles that inhabit a house. The various gameplay areas are all based on rooms in this giant house. Gameplay in Toy Commander is mission based. In each mission, you control one or more toy vehicles to accomplish certain objectives. The objectives in each mission vary widely.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>No Cliché</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Toy Commander.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Toy Commander.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unreal Tournament.chd</path>
		<name>Unreal Tournament</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Unreal Tournament is completely different to Unreal - it's now mainly based on multiplayer, like Quake 3. At the beginning, you have to play classic deathmatch rounds. After you have successfully won some of them, a new game mode becomes available, domination. In domination there are about 3 or 4 different areas scattered around the map to be controlled by your team. For a certain amount of seconds you control one area, a point is added to your score. The more areas you control, the faster your team's score rises.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Secret Level</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Unreal Tournament.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Unreal Tournament.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness.chd</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man: Maze Madness</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A combination of exploration and classic Pac-Man (or in this case, Ms. Pac-Man) action, Ms. Pac-Man Maze Madness has Ms. Pac-Man saving Pac-Land once again, although this in full 3D. The four Wonders, mystical regions separated from the rest of Pac-Land by force fields, contains four Gems of Virtue: Generosity, Truth, Wisdom and Courage, each holding enough power to help keep Pac-Land safe from evil. However, an unknown enemy has transformed the Enchanted Castle into a haunted house, in turn starting a chain reaction of evil all around Pac-Land and the four Wonders. It is up to Ms. Pac-Man to enter the 3D designed worlds of the four Wonders and put the evil to rest for good.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ms. Pac-Man - Maze Madness.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lost Golem, The (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam &amp; Cargodin v1.0] [n].chd</path>
		<name>Golem no Maigo (The Lost Golem)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The king has gotten lost looking for his daughter, so a golem sets out on a journey to find him and help him out. The Lost Golem is a puzzle game where the player must guide the king to a door in each stage by pushing walls around. Each stage is made up of walls, gates, and holes.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CaramelPot</developer>
		<publisher>CaramelPot</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lost Golem, The (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam &amp; Cargodin v1.0] [n].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lost Golem, The (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam &amp; Cargodin v1.0] [n].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Submarine No. 6 - Time and Tide (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam &amp; Esperknight B6] [n].chd</path>
		<name>Blue Submarine No. 6: Time and Tide</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blue Submarine No. 6: Time and Tide is an post-apocalyptic underwater-exploration game with RPG elements and not-linear adventure. Developed by SEGA and released for the Dreamcast in 7 Dec. 2000. The game follows the exploits of a deep-sea salvage crew as they recover treasure.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19700101T010000</releasedate>
		<developer />
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blue Submarine No. 6 - Time and Tide (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam &amp; Esperknight B6] [n].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blue Submarine No. 6 - Time and Tide (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam &amp; Esperknight B6] [n].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire Pro Wrestling D (Japan) [T-En by Irvgotti452].chd</path>
		<name>Fire Pro Wrestling D</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fire ProWrestling D is a wrestling simulation game featuring over 200 wrestlers from many well known North America and Japanese wrestling organizations, Fire Pro D allows you to simulate classic matches or matches that have never taken place before. It also allows Ultimate Fighting matches and includes an octagon cage for those contests. Fire ProWrestling D has over thousands of wrestling moves and holds available</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>S-Neo</developer>
		<publisher>Spike</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fire Pro Wrestling D (Japan) [T-En by Irvgotti452].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fire Pro Wrestling D (Japan) [T-En by Irvgotti452].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Frame Gride (Japan) [T-En by DCHQ Final].chd</path>
		<name>Frame Gride</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Frame Gride is a Japanese mecha fighting game made for the Sega Dreamcast by FromSoftware. Similar to From's Armored Core series, the mecha in the game are heavily customizable. The game had a single-player mode, a local two-player mode, and an online two-player mode when it was released on 15 July 1999, but the online network was discontinued on 31 January 2001.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990715T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>From Software</developer>
		<publisher>From Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Frame Gride (Japan) [T-En by DCHQ Final].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Frame Gride (Japan) [T-En by DCHQ Final].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Karous (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam v1.0].chd</path>
		<name>Karous</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this unique vertically-scrolling shooter you take the role of a mysterious girl named Karous, who commands a tiny fighter ship and attempts to destroy an evil armada bent on world domination.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20070308T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Karous (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam v1.0].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Karous (Japan) [T-En by Rolly &amp; RafaGam v1.0].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shenmue.m3u</path>
		<name>Shenmue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>That day in November when the snow turned to rain. Ryu Hazuki arrives home just in time to see his father killed by Lan Di, a man Ryu's father obviously knew very well. Ryu attempts to stop Lan Di, but is effortlessly beaten to within an inch of his life. After recovering from his injuries Ryu sets out to track down his father's murder as well as uncover his family's secrets and the mystery of the Phoenix and Dragon mirrors that Lan Di seeks.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shenmue.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shenmue.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deep Fighter.m3u</path>
		<name>Deep Fighter</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As a private in the defense force by The General, players take on deadly missions to seek out and destroy enemies, perform reconnaissance into uncharted waters and rescue damaged craft and installations. Meanwhile, droids and drones scuttle around busily, maintaining and repairing the slowly crumbling city. With the ultimate objective of the construction of a giant mothership, the Leviathan, that will transport the entire civilization away from hostile waters.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Software</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Deep Fighter.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Deep Fighter.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Demolition Racer - No Exit.chd</path>
		<name>Demolition Racer: No Exit</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to Demolition Racer. Race 14 tortuous tracks with mines and crates all over the place slowing you down, racing over 16 savage cars to a sports car to a hearse with its own characteristics to win the race. New game mode "last man standing" where you face all cars in race not for position, but to wreck each other going down a track to see who's last, and "demolition derby" where you fight cars in a arena to see who's last by hitting each other with state-of-the-art graphics where you can see tires, doors, hoods, bumpers, etc. go everywhere.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20001023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pitbull Syndicate</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Demolition Racer - No Exit.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Demolition Racer - No Exit.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Channel 5.chd</path>
		<name>Space Channel 5</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hey there, Space Cats! Some pesky little aliens called Morolians are trying to take over Earth, and they're forcing the population to dance endlessly! Space Channel 5, the planet's news channel, has sent the grooviest reporter they have, Ulala, out to cover the latest happenings, but those little Morolians also have to be taught a lesson! So it's now up to Ulala to dance and groove with the aliens to beat them at their own game and free the population of Earth! Get dancin', Space Cats, 'cuz we're gonna give those aliens a little taste of their own groove!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Space Channel 5.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Space Channel 5.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Atari Anniversary Edition v1.001 (2001)(Infogrames)(US)[!][compilation].chd</path>
		<name>Atari Anniversary Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Atari Anniversary Edition features 12 classic Atari games, whereby two versions of this game exits. One for Dreamcast/Windows and the other one for PlayStation.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Atari Anniversary Edition v1.001 (2001)(Infogrames)(US)[!][compilation].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Atari Anniversary Edition v1.001 (2001)(Infogrames)(US)[!][compilation].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grandia II.chd</path>
		<name>Grandia II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ryudo has been hired to protect a young priestess who must participate in a ceremony to halt the encroaching rebirth of Valmar, the God of Darkness. Embroiled between the forces of good and evil, Ryudo must follow his destiny and save the people he detests so much.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Grandia II.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Grandia II.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Code Veronica.m3u</path>
		<name>Resident Evil – Code: Veronica</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Three months after the events of Resident Evil 2, Claire Redfield is still looking for her brother Chris. She infiltrates Umbrella Corporation's headquarters in Paris, where she is captured and knocked out. When she comes to, she finds herself in a prison on a remote island. Freed by a friendly guard, Claire faces several problems. Not only is the island under attack by an unknown assailant, but there has been another outbreak of the T-Virus and the island is crawling with zombies and other mutated creatures. Claire not only has to face the undead, but also the commander of the base, a mad aristocrat with family ties to the origins of Umbrella Corporation and the T-Virus.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000526T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Resident Evil - Code Veronica.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Resident Evil - Code Veronica.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grinch, The.chd</path>
		<name>Grinch, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As the Grinch, you're going to make sure that Whoville will NOT celebrate Christmas this year Your missions, should you choose to accept them, includes breaking presents, build some of your nasty gadgets (rotten egg launcher, slime shooter), messing with the mail and more. Explore four large environments in search of your blueprints for your "weapons". Even summon your pal Max for a little assistance at times.</desc>
		<rating>0.3</rating>
		<releasedate>20001215T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Grinch, The.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Grinch, The.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare.m3u</path>
		<name>Alone in the Dark: The New Nightmare</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Edward Carnby, private eye of the paranormal, is back. Carnby's best friend, Charles Fiske, has been found dead near Shadow Island, a mysterious island near Maine. It is your duty to take up the investigation and find out the secrets of Shadow Island. But you're not going alone, your companion will be a redhead by the name of Aline Cedrac who has her own reasons for tagging along. Aside from being a woman and inexperienced in the world of danger, she is the only one with the knowledge for translating the ancient Abkhani tabloids which may hold the secrets behind Carnby's friend's death and the disappearance of Aline's father.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20010622T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Darkworks</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alone in the Dark - The New Nightmare.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Army Men - Sarge's Heroes v1.001 (2000)(Midway)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Army Men: Sarge's Heroes</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One morning Sarge is resting in his cot when the Tan launch a surprise attack on the Green base. Sarge and the Colonel are forced to retreat just as the base is overrun. But in the chaos, Sarge's entire team of elite soldiers has been kidnapped by the Tan. Worse yet, the Tan have made an amazing discovery: blue portals that lead to the real world! They use these portals to take amazing weapons of war from the real world into the plastic world including magnifying glasses, deadly robot action figures, and fire crackers.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saffire</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Army Men - Sarge's Heroes v1.001 (2000)(Midway)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Army Men - Sarge's Heroes v1.001 (2000)(Midway)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bangai-O.chd</path>
		<name>Bangai-O</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ever wanted to just unleash the ultimate weapon? Blow up 500 enemies at once? Cause the ultimate amount of mayhem ever? In true Treasure fashion you just got that power! As the pilots of the Bangaioh mech, you've got to stop a mad group from taking over the world by giving them a little dose of insane destruction. Wanna just be crazy and let them kill you? Go ahead just hit that trigger before it happens. The Nintendo 64 version was only released in Japan. The Dreamcast version exists in the U.S. and Europe.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Conspiracy</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bangai-O.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bangai-O.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX.chd</path>
		<name>Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tony Hawk proved the skating games can work to great effect. Now Dave Mirra is here to prove that BMX is here to stay, thanks to the boys at Acclaim Entertainment. Choose from all of the current crop of BMX champs, including 10 times world champion Dave Mirra, Ryan Nyquist, Joey Garcia, Shaun Butler &amp; heaps more, and ride your way through 12 highly detailed environments, with vert ramps, huge jumps and track racing. Multiplayer gaming is also thrown in, allowing two players to go head-to-head in a game of B-M-X (a unique variation of the HORSE basketball game). All this plus official sponsors clothing, bikes and advertising boards plus a huge soundtrack featuring Cypress Hill, Deftones and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Z-Axis</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dave Mirra Freestyle BMX.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bomberman Online.chd</path>
		<name>Bomberman Online</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Multiplayer is up to ten players online similar to Atomic Bomberman for PC with traditional four-player game on one system. The game includes the ability to edit characters, to gather to keep or trade collectibles, a super weapon called the Hyper Bomb, new rules, exclusive stages, and finally, never-before-seen modes like the Panel Mode (like Othello, you must flip panels to match your color) or Battle Royale (where you must attempt to ring-out your opponents).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bomberman Online.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bomberman Online.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NHL 2K2.chd</path>
		<name>NHL 2K2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NHL 2K is a series of hockey games by 2K Sports for the Dreamcast, PlayStation 2, Nintendo GameCube, Xbox, iPhone, Xbox 360, PlayStation 3, and the Wii. Initially discontinued after the release of NHL 2K11 in 2010, the brand was revived on mobile devices in 2014. The games are officially licensed from the National Hockey League and NHL Players Association. While its games were released on consoles, its main competition was EA Sports' NHL video games.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treyarch</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NHL 2K2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NHL 2K2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Striker 2.chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Striker 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's here, Virtua Striker 2 V2000.1 has come to Dreamcast in all its arcade-perfect glory. Play any of the new modes - including 'Ranking' and 'Leagues' - or just sit back and enjoy the original arcade mode from the comfort of your armchair. You can save the best goal on your VM unit and use it when your competing in two-player mode. Football has never looked so good and felt so right you can almost taste the pie and Bovril at half time.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Virtua Striker 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Virtua Striker 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blue Stinger.chd</path>
		<name>Blue Stinger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After an object from outerspace hits Dinosaur Island and surrounds it in a protective cocoon, you are left stranded to uncover the secret that could end life on Earth as we know it. You play sea rescue expert Eliot Ballade, or weapons specialist Dogs Bower. Explore the island, solve puzzles and avoid hazards in seven areas and 230 locations. You can swim, drive, climb and fight, hand-to-hand or with the arsenal at hand.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax Graphics</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blue Stinger.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blue Stinger.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ChuChu Rocket!.chd</path>
		<name>ChuChu Rocket!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>ChuChu Rocket! is an action puzzler, designed predominantly as a multi-player game. You have indirect control over mice, and must guide them to the safety of a rocket, and away from a cat. You do this by placing arrows on the ground, which they will follow. The multi-player game is a frantic all-against-all duel, in which each player's mice will only follow instructions of their own colour. You can play this mode on your own against CPU opponents, or take on a series of predefined puzzles</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000512T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/ChuChu Rocket!.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ChuChu Rocket!.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)(Disc 1 of 2)[!][Leon].chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 (Disc 1)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is set two months after the events of the first Resident Evil, in the Midwestern American mountain community of Raccoon City. Nearly all of its citizens have been transformed into zombies by an outbreak of the T-virus, a new type of biological weapon secretly developed by the pharmaceutical company Umbrella. The game's two protagonists are Leon S. Kennedy, a rookie police officer on his first day in the local force, and Claire Redfield, a college student looking for her brother Chris.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Resident Evil 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)(Disc 1 of 2)[!][Leon].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Resident Evil 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)(Disc 1 of 2)[!][Leon].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)(Disc 2 of 2)[!][Claire].chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 (Disc 2)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is set two months after the events of the first Resident Evil, in the Midwestern American mountain community of Raccoon City. Nearly all of its citizens have been transformed into zombies by an outbreak of the T-virus, a new type of biological weapon secretly developed by the pharmaceutical company Umbrella. The game's two protagonists are Leon S. Kennedy, a rookie police officer on his first day in the local force, and Claire Redfield, a college student looking for her brother Chris. Game Note: You need to finish Disc 1 (Leon) before playing Disc 2 (Claire)</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Resident Evil 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)(Disc 2 of 2)[!][Claire].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Resident Evil 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)(Disc 2 of 2)[!][Claire].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./102 Dalmatians (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Disney's 102 Dalmations: Puppies to the Rescue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game itself follows the films' storyline loosely. The player can choose the role of one of two dalmatians, Oddball or Domino, who are out in the backyard looking for treasure. It is not long before the player realizes that a toy found buried in a park was made at one of Cruella de Vil's toy factories; this alludes to the fact that Cruella's toy sales are down, which ultimately leads to the problem in the storyline. Facing financial ruin from lack of sales, Cruella sets an evil plan in motion - to reprogram her toys to capture any pets in sight.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/102 Dalmatians (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/102 Dalmatians (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers.chd</path>
		<name>Disney's Donald Duck: Goin' Quackers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play as Donald in this 3D platform action game. Donald's girlfriend, Daisy is a reporter for a television station in Duckberg. While doing a story on the secret temple of the terrible magician Merlock, Daisy is kidnapped. Now, it is up to Donald to get her back. Along the way he will have help from his nephews, Huey, Dewey, and Louie, and the inventor Gyro Gearloose. He will also have competition from Gladstone Gander, who is also trying to save Daisy.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20001213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2.chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the award winning PSX and N64 title, Tony Hawk 2 adds heaps of new tricks, as well as those from the original, and a complete roster of all the greatest skaters worldwide. Fly through some of the greatest skate parks in the world, or create your own, and share them with your mates. You can also create your own skater, with a choice of clothing and official skateboards. Improved graphics and a choice of alternative or hip-hop music add to the endless options and full on action.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Neversoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evolution - The World of Sacred Device.chd</path>
		<name>Evolution: The World of Sacred Device</name>
		<sortname>Evolution 1</sortname>
		<desc>Evolution is a dungeon crawling game that follows the adventures of Mag Launcher. Mag Launcher and his companions use Cyframes, technology discovered in ancient ruins. These Cyframes are sought after by adventurers who explore caverns to find them.nnCombat in Evolution is non-random and occurs whenever the character touches an enemy. The battle system uses 3D graphics and is turn-based, with each individual combatant having their own turn.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Evolution - The World of Sacred Device.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Evolution - The World of Sacred Device.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Evolution 2 - Far Off Promise.chd</path>
		<name>Evolution 2: Far off Promise</name>
		<sortname>Evolution 2</sortname>
		<desc>Evolution 2 is a direct sequel to World of Sacred Device. The events of the game take place six months after the conclusion of the previous game. Mag Launcher, the son of a great adventurer of the past, has earned the title of "best adventurer" in the town Pannam. The adventurer guild (called the Society) sends him to the south.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sting</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Evolution 2 - Far Off Promise.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Evolution 2 - Far Off Promise.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter III - Double Impact.chd</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III: Double Impact</name>
		<sortname>Street Fighter III 1</sortname>
		<desc>After years of waiting, the true third sequel to Street Fighter is upon us. 3 Familiar faces in Ryu, Ken and Akuma appear in the roster, with 12 new faces including Sean, Yun, Yang, Alex, Ibuki, Elena, Dudley, Oro, Necro, Hugo, Urien and Gill. But even though they are new, the moves will seem familiar for those who have played other versions in the SF series.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter III - Double Impact.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter III - Double Impact.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter III - 3rd Strike.chd</path>
		<name>Street Fighter III: 3rd Strike</name>
		<sortname>Street Fighter III 2</sortname>
		<desc>3rd update to Street Fighter III, Capcom's classic 2D fighter. The new version includes new music and artwork, more super arts for each character, a grading system, a manual throw system, path selection and new characters including (YES!) Chun-Li. The Dreamcast port also offers a training record option were you can record a certain move or combo and have it play against you over and over to see how you can parry it, plus a "system direction" option which allows you to modify practically every aspect of the game (air-blocking, combo limits, etc.) to customize it to your liking.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter III - 3rd Strike.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter III - 3rd Strike.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./hexquake.cdi</path>
		<name>Quake</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Quake, the player takes the role of the protagonist known as Ranger who was sent into a portal in order to stop an enemy code-named "Quake". The government had been experimenting with teleportation technology and developed a working prototype called a "Slipgate"; the mysterious Quake compromised the Slipgate by connecting it with its own teleportation system, using it to send death squads to the "Human" dimension in order to test the martial capabilities of humanity.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>id Software</developer>
		<publisher>id Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/hexquake.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/hexquake.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F1 World Grand Prix II for Dreamcast.chd</path>
		<name>F1 World Grand Prix II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>F1 World Grand Prix II is a game for the Dreamcast. Unlike its namesake for the Nintendo 64 it features the '99 season instead of the '98 season. The game includes sixteen official tracks and all the racers and teams that come with the FIA license. The Dreamcast version features improved graphics over the Nintendo 64 original. The game allows you to fine-tune your car to your own preferences and features Exhibition play, Grand Prix, Time Attack, Challenge and Match Race. You can tweak the settings of your car before each race and the game features various types of weather. The cars feature realistic damage models.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/F1 World Grand Prix II for Dreamcast.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F1 World Grand Prix II for Dreamcast.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC.chd</path>
		<name>NBA Show Time: NBA on NBC</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NBA Show Time: NBA on NBC is a descendant of the original NBA Jam, and is created by some of the key team members. The game follows in the footsteps of NFL Blitz, featuring the option to save personal records and a cheat code system operated by pressing a sequence of buttons. It also features unlock-able characters, including NBA team mascots, and the "On-Fire" option that defines Midway's sports games. Players are able to perform special moves such as the alley-oop, the spin move, and the double dunk. The game also features a Create-a-Player mode that allows custom players to have tweaked abilities by winning matches.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA Showtime - NBA on NBC.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Project Justice.chd</path>
		<name>Project Justice</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Project Justice is the sequel to Shiritsu Justice Gakuen: Nekketsu Seishun Nikki 2. It once more thrusts you into the shoes of a team of students, trying to find out what is causing all the bizarre events. Players pick a school to fight for and smash their way through the other schools, questioning them until you find out what is happening. The gameplay is very similar in style to the original Rival Schools, featuring bombastic special moves and team-up attacks, along with the same, highly caricatured students.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Project Justice.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Project Justice.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quake III Arena v0.800 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Quake III Arena</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The third game in the Quake series is a departure from the previous games, focusing exclusively on multiplayer arena fighting with no story-driven singleplayer part - directly competing with Epic Games that did the same with the contemporary Unreal Tournament. The offline part takes the player through a number of one-on-one and team-based challenges against AI-controlled opponents, slowly ranking upwards in difficulty, as the character of the player's choosing.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>id Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Quake III Arena v0.800 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Quake III Arena v0.800 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./StarLancer v1.002 (2000)(Crave)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>StarLancer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's 2160, and the Eastern Alliance has launched a surprise attack on the Western Coalition's fleet and decimated it. The call has gone out for volunteers to become Alliance fighter pilots, and you have signed up with the 45th Volunteer Squadron.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Anvil</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-6</players>
		<image>./boxart/StarLancer v1.002 (2000)(Crave)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/StarLancer v1.002 (2000)(Crave)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tee Off.chd</path>
		<name>Tee Off</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One of the few golf games for the DC, with a cartoony style. Contains arcade mode, tournaments, five different courses and 15 characters (11 unlockable). Lots of different equipment (balls and clubs mostly) and even a futuristic cyber mini golf game are thrown in.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tee Off.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tee Off.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Test Drive Le Mans.chd</path>
		<name>Test Drive: Le Mans</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take on the LeMans endurance racing challenge! Join one of the 25 factory teams take one of the over 50 vehicles (designed with assistance of actual teams) on the eight different LeMans circuits. The actual wear and tear are simulated. Tire wear, oil and fuel consumptions Day and night and back to day driving.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20001113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Melbourne House</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Test Drive Le Mans.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Test Drive Le Mans.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./TrickStyle.chd</path>
		<name>TrickStyle</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is set in the future and based around the sport of Hoverboarding. The player can race or do stunts through metropolis versions of London, Tokyo, and Manhattan Island, or in a massive practice arena called the Velodrome.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/TrickStyle.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/TrickStyle.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wacky Races.chd</path>
		<name>Wacky Races</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>For those who can remember the cartoon series, this will be a blast from the past. Choose from all your favourite characters including Peter Perfect, Penelope Pitstop and, of course, Dick Dastardly and Muttley, and wind your way through cartoon like environments in the familiar vehicles of each character. Simply get to the end of the race first to open up new tracks, and use weapons to pick off the rest of the cast, and aid your progress.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wacky Races.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wacky Races.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wetrix+.chd</path>
		<name>Wetrix+</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The idea for this game is that you must build barriers on the arena to stop the water from leaking out. As you go along, rain starts to fall onto the arena, so you better keep the walls as high as possible. Too much on the screen, though, will start and earthquake. Ice blocks fall to freeze the water. Bombs drop, leaving holes in your walls and fireballs dry up the water. Simply go as long as possible to get as high a score as you can. There is a practice mode available, and you can play against a friend.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zed Two</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wetrix+.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wetrix+.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xtreme Sports.chd</path>
		<name>Xtreme Sports</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Xtreme Sports, also known as Sega Extreme Sports in Europe and Japan (Dreamcast version) and as Pepsi Max Extreme Sports (PC version), is a sports game developed by Norwegian video game development company Innerloop Studios and published by French holding company Infogrames for the Dreamcast and Microsoft Windows, and Sega for the European Dreamcast version, but was developed by WayForward Technologies for the Game Boy Color.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Xtreme Sports.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Xtreme Sports.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Confidential Mission v1.004 (2001)(Sega)(US)(M5)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Confidential Mission</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Confidential Mission is a light-gun compatible shooting game most easily likened to Sega's Virtua Cop series. You play as either Howard Gibson or Jean Clifford, both super-agents a la James Bond, and you are taken through scenarios shooting enemies and attempting to avoid civilian casualties.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010520T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Confidential Mission v1.004 (2001)(Sega)(US)(M5)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Confidential Mission v1.004 (2001)(Sega)(US)(M5)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Incoming.chd</path>
		<name>Incoming</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Incoming aliens! Incoming aliens! They've already attacked the international moonbase, and they may already have a base in the Arctic! Earth is building a huge tracking station as first part of the counterattack, but now you detect incoming aliens and they don't look friendly! Defend your base against the initial incursion by manning turret, tank, helicopter, harrier jet, and even captured alien fighter as you battle the aliens in various continents.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xicat</developer>
		<publisher>Rage Software</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Incoming.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Incoming.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Looney Tunes Space Race.chd</path>
		<name>Looney Tunes: Space Race</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Looney Tunes: Space Race features eight all-time favorite characters, including Bugs Bunny, Daffy Duck, Taz, Sylvester, Yosemite Sam, and Wile E. Coyote. The 12 tracks include shortcuts, jumps, and traps, and there are over 40 competitive events. Players can pummel opponents with gags like the portable hole, falling elephants, retractable boxing glove, and instant storm. Up to four players can race at a time.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001103T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Looney Tunes Space Race.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Looney Tunes Space Race.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel vs. Capcom - Clash of Super Heroes.chd</path>
		<name>Marvel vs. Capcom: Clash of Super Heroes</name>
		<sortname>Marvel vs. Capcom 1</sortname>
		<desc>Marvel vs. Capcom : Clash of Super Heroes is a 2D fighting game that combines characters from Capcom's videogames with characters from the Marvel comic universe, similar to Marvel Super Heroes Vs. Street Fighter. The game takes place in a Marvel universe where Professor Charles Xavier asks the heroes to help him before he merges with the consciousness of Magneto to form the being known as Onslaught, the final boss.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Marvel vs. Capcom - Clash of Super Heroes.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Marvel vs. Capcom - Clash of Super Heroes.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tech Romancer.chd</path>
		<name>Tech Romancer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tech Romancer is a 3D beat-em-up with a difference; the difference being that, rather than controlling one of a set of martial artists, you control one of a set of huge robots (or mecha). Ranging from the absurd (A huge, spherical mech with a boat and bus for feet, a house for a head, train for one arm and office building with wrecking ball for another) to the "typical" anime styled mecha (Beam-firing chest gem, detatchable rocket-powered fists) to a more westernised idea of a mech (Huge, sluggish, equipped with heavy cannon, rockets, missiles and land-mines), you're bound to find at least one which suits you.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tech Romancer.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tech Romancer.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Samurai Spirits Tenkaichi Kenkakuden.chd</path>
		<name>Samurai Shodown VI: Tale of the World's Greatest Swordsman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Among other series changes, aerial blocking was removed entirely, and the switch-around move, which enabled a player to shift quickly behind the other's back, as well as the dodge (evade, side-step), in which the move virtually brings a semi-3D environment to the defense in attempt to use each sword more effectively.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Samurai Spirits Tenkaichi Kenkakuden.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Samurai Spirits Tenkaichi Kenkakuden.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F1 World Grand Prix for Dreamcast.chd</path>
		<name>F1 World Grand Prix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>F1WGP features the official license of the 1998 season, it features all the drivers for that season (except Jacques Villeneuve that was replaced with a blank photo and Driver 1). There are four main modes in Formula 1 World Grand Prix. Single Race lets you race around in any car on any track for a quick spin, Championship allows you to take part in the 1998 season, Time Trial pits you against the clock and Match Race offers some multiplayer fun.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/F1 World Grand Prix for Dreamcast.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F1 World Grand Prix for Dreamcast.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vigilante 8 - 2nd Offense.chd</path>
		<name>Vigilante 8: 2nd Offense</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>More drivin' &amp; blastin' fun in this sequel to Vigilante 8. The Coyotes gang returns with a shocking new leader to seek revenge on OMAR, and the Vigilantes gang. New cars, weapons and landscapes add new excitement to the game. There are 18 charcters with storylines to walk through, which in turn affects the other characters in the game, and how well you do in the single player missions will determine what happens in the later levels. The Dreamcast and N64 versions both have 4 player modes, while the PSX sticks with 2 player gaming.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20000218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Luxoflux</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vigilante 8 - 2nd Offense.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vigilante 8 - 2nd Offense.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ECCO the Dolphin - Defender of the Future.chd</path>
		<name>Ecco the Dolphin: Defender of the Future</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Hundreds of years in the future, mankind and dolphins live peacefully together and share the earth. Dolphins, who are much more intelligent than they seem, act as the earth's caretakers, while dolphins and humans explore the galaxy. An alien force, known as the Foe, seeks to end this happy existence. The Foe damages the Earth's defense system, and alters history for the worse. One extraordinary dolphin, Ecco, must travel through time to set things right. Ecco is a 3d underwater adventure game. There are more than 25 aquatic environments to explore. Ecco must communicate with other ocean creatures and learn to manipulate his environment if he is to succeed in defeating the Foe.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Appaloosa Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/ECCO the Dolphin - Defender of the Future.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ECCO the Dolphin - Defender of the Future.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dolphin Blue.chd</path>
		<name>Dolphin Blue</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sammy's Atomiswave arcade shoot-em-up in the vein of Metal Slug, where players ride dolphins and destroy fleets of enemy ships and submarines. Unfortunately, this arcade shoot-em-up was never ported to any home console.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sammy Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Sammy Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dolphin Blue.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dolphin Blue.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Bass Fishing v1.000 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!][8S].chd</path>
		<name>Sega Bass Fishing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Explore the exciting sport of bass fishing! Based on the arcade hit, explore eight fishing locations as you try to catch the biggest fish possible! You can choose between fourteen different lures, and compete in four tournaments, starting with you as an amateur, up to a Masters Classic tournament!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19991006T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sims</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sega Bass Fishing v1.000 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!][8S].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sega Bass Fishing v1.000 (1999)(Sega)(US)[!][8S].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Bass Fishing 2 v1.080 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Sega Bass Fishing 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>SEGA Bass Fishing 2 is the obvious sequel to SEGA Bass Fishing. Like the previous game in the series this simulation game allows the player to fish for bass on various lakes. At the start of the game the player can pick one of various characters. Each character has his or her own stats such as casting distance, which makes them all unique. Each character's appearance can be altered by the player as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wow Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sega Bass Fishing 2 v1.080 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sega Bass Fishing 2 v1.080 (2001)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Marine Fishing v1.001 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Sega Marine Fishing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to the arcade and Dreamcast title SEGA Bass Fishing, this game features deep-sea fishing where you can catch must more than just bass. The game offers 15 types of fish, 5 different locales, and 16 types of lures with many more unlockable. By catching fish, you earn item cards with equipment, boats, accessories, fish and artifacts for an aquarium.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wow Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sega Marine Fishing v1.001 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sega Marine Fishing v1.001 (2000)(Sega)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Demolition (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars: Demolition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A demoliton derby in the Star Wars universe. Essentially, Vigilante 8 with Star Wars vehicles. Use anything from a Swoop Bike to a mind controlled Rancor. You can even play as Boba Fett. Boards include all of the worlds visited in the Star Wars movies (Tatooine, Hoth, Death Star, Endor, Dagobah, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Luxoflux</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Wars - Demolition (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Wars - Demolition (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tokyo Xtreme Racer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tokyo Xtreme Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tokyo Xtreme Racer is a racing video game for the Sega Dreamcast. Released in 1999 as one of the console's launch titles, the game was one of the first mission-based racing games.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19990909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Genki</developer>
		<publisher>Genki</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tokyo Xtreme Racer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tokyo Xtreme Racer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2.chd</path>
		<name>Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2, known as ShutokÅ Battle 2 (é¦–éƒ½é«˜ãƒ ãƒˆãƒ« 2) in Japan and Tokyo Highway Challenge 2 in Europe, is the sequel to Tokyo Xtreme Racer, which is also on the Sega Dreamcast. Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2 has been enhanced with better sound quality and graphics over its predecessor. The game managed to produce two more sequels. It is the last game in the series that was produced for Sega Dreamcast. Some of the game's mechanics were implemented into Daytona USA 2001.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crave Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Genki</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tokyo Xtreme Racer 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Rogue Spear + Mission Pack - Urban Operations (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six: Rogue Spear</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Dreamcast port of the second Rainbow Six title includes both the original game and its add-on Urban Operations.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pipe Dream Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Pipe Dream Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Rogue Spear + Mission Pack - Urban Operations (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six - Rogue Spear + Mission Pack - Urban Operations (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Triggerheart Exelica</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the distant future humanity will develop intelligent weapons called Trigger Hearts. Despite their awesome offensive strengths, Trigger Hearts aesthetically closely resemble humans, and overtime even develop unique personalities. Of three existing Trigger Hearts one, named Faintear, has mysteriously vanished two years ago.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20070222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warashi</developer>
		<publisher>Warashi</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Triggerheart Exelica (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trizeal (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Trizeal</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A sci-fi vertical-scrolling shooter directly ported from its arcade incarnation. Using polygonal graphics, but retaining a completely 2D gameplay, Trizeal puts you in command of two tiny starfighter as you attempt to clear several stages filled with enemy ships and creatures gunning for you.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20050407T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Triangle Service</developer>
		<publisher>Triangle Service</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Trizeal (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Trizeal (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF Attitude (USA).chd</path>
		<name>WWF Attitude</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>WWF Attitude was the third wrestling game by Acclaim for the Sony Playstation. It was also the second WWF 3D wrestling game for the system. This game was the followup to the commercial success WWF War Zone. At the time it was the wrestling game to have featured the most modes. The 20 or so game modes included specialty matches like royal rumble, survivor series, tornado matches and more. Also featured was a new career mode compared to that of WWF War Zone, realistic entrances and a first ever Create a PPV mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19991101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/WWF Attitude (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WWF Attitude (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Capcom vs. SNK.chd</path>
		<name>Capcom vs. SNK: Millennium Fight 2000</name>
		<sortname>Capcom vs. SNK 1</sortname>
		<desc>Two of the worlds greatest arcade fighter developers, Capcom and SNK, join forces to finally answer the question asked by many for years: Who is the dominant fighter? A range of fighters from both worlds are available to choose from, with two different fighting styles (Capcom and SNK, of course) meaning that players of both worlds can fit into the game easily, while new gamers can try Ryu using the SNK format.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Capcom vs. SNK.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Capcom vs. SNK.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Capcom vs. SNK 2 - Millionaire Fighting 2001.chd</path>
		<name>Capcom vs. SNK 2: Millionaire Fighting 2001</name>
		<sortname>Capcom vs. SNK 2</sortname>
		<desc>Aspects of the first game were tweaked, including the Ratio system. In contrast to the fixed system of the original, players can now freely select characters and assign each of them a number from one to four (or "Ratio") determining their relative strength, adding up to a maximum team ratio of four. Teams can now consist of a maximum of three characters, as opposed to four in the first game. Additional characters were added, including more characters from Capcom and SNK titles outside of the Street Fighter and King of Fighters series.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Capcom vs. SNK 2 - Millionaire Fighting 2001.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Capcom vs. SNK 2 - Millionaire Fighting 2001.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dynamite Cop!.chd</path>
		<name>Dynamite Cop!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pirates have kidnapped the President's daughter and are holding her on a hijacked cruise ship. Now it's up to an elite police force to get them back, using whatever means necessary. The action takes place on both the cruise ship and the pirate's island hideaway. You play as one of three cops, in this beat-em up fighting game from Sega. Dynamite Cop features similar gameplay to Die Hard Arcade. As your character enters an area, you have to beat up everyone there. Once they are gone, you continue to the next area.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dynamite Cop!.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dynamite Cop!.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fatal Fury - Mark of the Wolves.chd</path>
		<name>Fatal Fury: Mark of the Wolves</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's been several years since Geese Howard was defeated in a battle with Terry Bogard, a young man looking to avenge his father. Rather than looking to be saved from death after falling off his office balcony, Geese instead decided to die, and left behind his young son, Rock. Terry took Rock in and became like a big brother to him, raising the boy throughout his life. Now Rock is a teenager, and Terry is a man in his 30s, and both are about to come together in a new clash, new faces and old come together for the greatest battle yet!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20011102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Fatal Fury - Mark of the Wolves.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Fatal Fury - Mark of the Wolves.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GigaWing 2.chd</path>
		<name>GigaWing 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It is a top-down, vertical-scrolling shoot-em-up featuring four-player simultaneous action, high-res 3D graphics, and an orchestral score. There are four characters to choose from, each with his own storyline and fighter/spaceship. Each ship has its own weapon type and speed. Like the previous GigaWing and Mars Matrix games, gameplay is designed around bullet absorption/reflection mechanics, large numbers of enemies, and giant boss fights. Giga Wing 2 adds the ability to choose from two different bullet reflection powers: reflect force and reflect laser. The reflect force repulses enemy shots, while the reflect laser uses them to charge up a beam weapon.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/GigaWing 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/GigaWing 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guilty Gear X.chd</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear X</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When the humans created artificial beings named "gears" in 22th century, they didn't expect that their creation will eventually turn against them. Because gears had no will of their own and could only obey humans. Only one gear, named Justice, was able to transfer his will onto other gears and to rebel against the humans. In year 2180, Justice was killed as a result of a bloody tournament organized by the Sacred Order of Holy Knights.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001214T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Arc System Works</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Guilty Gear X.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Guilty Gear X.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ikaruga.chd</path>
		<name>Ikaruga</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Vertical shoot-em-up ported from the Naomi Arcade version. Ikaruga is more or less a sequel to Radiant Silvergun by Treasure, on the Sega Saturn. Based on a two-colors system, the player has to switch between the black &amp; white sides of his ship during gameplay. The black side is immune to black enemy bullets which it consider as bonus, and dies on impact with a white enemy bullets. Your own black bullets damages white enemies twice as more as white bullets. And vice-versa for the white side. Those properties makes a balance between protecting yourself well and killing enemies fast.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Entertainment Software Publishing</developer>
		<publisher>Treasure</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ikaruga.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ikaruga.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Blade 2.chd</path>
		<name>Last Blade 2: Heart of the Samurai, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>More than a dozen Samurai blade masters are summoned to compete in a challenge that has only one victor - and no other survivors. The Last Blade 2 Heart of the Samurai recreates 1864 Japan in all its feudal glory . Players are swept into 1-on-1 death matches against the living and the dead in a quest to bring honor to their master's clan. Each character wields their favorite weapon with a deadly accuracy that is sure to leave the players breathless - all in a split second! Practice each of the lightning-quick moves to perfection, or else prepare to be counted amongst those slain in battle.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Last Blade 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Last Blade 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Marvel vs. Capcom 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Marvel vs. Capcom 2: New Age of Heroes</name>
		<sortname>Marvel vs. Capcom 2</sortname>
		<desc>The game allows you to tag in all three players (instead of two, while the third is only used for special attacks, in the predecessor). There are now up to 56 characters to use (most you have to unlock), including new characters like Jill Valentine from Resident Evil and Tron Bonn from Mega Man Legends. Another new gameplay feature allows your team mates to come in during battle and give you a little health boost. This helps in lasting the distance in Survival mode, but they can also be hit by on coming attacks from the enemy.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Marvel vs. Capcom 2 v1.001 (2000)(Capcom)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat Gold.chd</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat Gold</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first and only Mortal Kombat title to make onto the Dreamcast console, Mortal Kombat Gold offered players a carbon-copy of the arcade edition of Mortal Kombat 4, along with additional features and characters never before included in the arcade game. Using the exact same engine found in Mortal Kombat 4, the game performs flawlessly on the Dreamcast platform, while also running at a higher resolution than its arcade counterpart.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19990101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mortal Kombat Gold.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mortal Kombat Gold.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Stone.chd</path>
		<name>Power Stone</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The creators of Street Fighter add a new dimension to 3D fighting. In Power Stone, 2 fighters take to multi-level arenas with Power Stones and other weapons lying around for use. Each game contains Power Stones. When you have enough stones (between three to five), your character transforms into an almost unbeatable warrior, with an all-new range of moves (although this does not last for long).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eidos Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Power Stone.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Power Stone.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ready 2 Rumble Boxing.chd</path>
		<name>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing is a boxing video game developed by Midway and published in 1999 for the Dreamcast, PlayStation, Game Boy Color, and Nintendo 64. The success of the Dreamcast version led to it becoming one of the few Sega All Stars titles. Like Nintendo's Punch-Out!! series, it features many characters with colorful personalities (i.e. Afro Thunder, Boris "The Bear" Knokimov, etc.); however, unlike the Punch-Out!! series, Ready 2 Rumble Boxing is in 3D.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ready 2 Rumble Boxing Round 2.chd</path>
		<name>Ready 2 Rumble Boxing: Round 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ready 2 Rumble: Round 2 is a cartoon style boxing beat 'em up with plenty of strange looking characters to choose from and beat the hell out of. You can train your character up to the best of his/her ability and then fight the best in the world for the championship belt. Round 2 adds some new play modes and characters into the mix of previous fighters. In this round, there are now 3 levels to the RUMBLE combo gauge (much like a Street Fighter game). Once you reach the third level, you can hit your enemy for six, out of the ring and into the crowd.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing Round 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ready 2 Rumble Boxing Round 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 3.chd</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Street Fighter Alpha 3 explodes onto the Sega Dreamcast with new features and astonishing arcade perfection. Choose from over 30 characters, each with 3 different fighting styles. Street Fighter Alpha 3 is loaded with new enhancements and modes of play -- like the around-the-world, skill building World Tour Mode and amazing 3 player Dramatic Battle. If it's a fight you're looking for, this is your game!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter Alpha 3.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter Alpha 3.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters '99, The - Evolution (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>King of Fighters '99: Evolution, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Welcome back to the King of Fighters tournament with this, the latest installment of the legendary SNK fighting game series! Taking elements from both KOF '99 and the new KOF 2000, KOF Evo brings hardcore fighting game action, slick characters, newcomers, oldcomers, and everyone in between back for one of the greatest fighting game experiences you'll ever see!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Agetec</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/King of Fighters '99, The - Evolution (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King of Fighters '99, The - Evolution (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters 2000, The.chd</path>
		<name>King of Fighters 2000, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The King of Fighters 2000 is a 2000 competitive fighting game produced by SNK for the Neo Geo arcade and home platforms. It is the seventh installment in The King of Fighters series for the Neo Geo, and marks the final game in the series produced by SNK before the bankruptcy. The game was ported to the Sega Dreamcast (in Japan only) and the Sony PlayStation 2 in 2002. The PlayStation 2 version of the game was released in North America in a two-in-one bundle with its immediate sequel, The King of Fighters 2001, as the first two games to be published by SNK Playmore USA.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/King of Fighters 2000, The.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King of Fighters 2000, The.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters 2001, The.chd</path>
		<name>King of Fighters 2001, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The King of Fighters 2001 (stylized as KOF '01) is a 2001 competitive fighting game produced by Eolith for the Neo Geo. It is the eighth game in The King of Fighters series and the first game produced following the closure of the original SNK. The game was produced by the Korean-based company Eolith and developed by BrezzaSoft and Eolith, a company formed by former SNK employees. The game was ported to the Sega Dreamcast in Japan only and Sony PlayStation 2. The stand-alone Sony PlayStation 2 version was released in North America and Europe in a two-in-one bundle with the preceding game in the series.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20021226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Playmore</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/King of Fighters 2001, The.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King of Fighters 2001, The.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters 2002, The.chd</path>
		<name>King of Fighters 2002, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The second plotless "dream match" in The King of Fighters series, this game sports 39 normal characters and 5 hidden characters, some of whom haven't appeared since KOF98. The King of Fighters 2002 also has five characters exclusive to the X-Box, the PS2 and/or Dreamcast systems: Shingo Yabuki, King, Geese Howard, "Riot of the Blood" Iori and Leopold Goenitz. Shingo and King are available on all the non-Neo Geo systems, while Geese and the rest are only available on the PS2 and X-Box platforms. The gameplay system has also changed. The striker system and four-character teams found in the last three KOF releases have been totally removed.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20030619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/King of Fighters 2002, The.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King of Fighters 2002, The.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./kofxi.chd</path>
		<name>King of Fighters XI, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The eleventh game in the KOF series following The King of Fighters 2003. According to Sega: 'For over 10 years, the King of Fighters series has been the choice of game players around the world. The 11th team of fighters continues this tradition. KOF11 is suited for one to two players, with continuous buy-in. Choose from 33 fighters, including 4 new characters. A fifth control button was added to enhance your skills by delivering a devastating blow to your opponent, if hit at the right time. A New Skill Gauge performs a variety of tag-off moves and new attacks. A player can also custom construct a Three-Fighter Tag-Team by selecting three choice combatants.'</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20050101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK Playmore</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/kofxi.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/kofxi.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Fighting Championship.chd</path>
		<name>Ultimate Fighting Championship</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ultimate Fighting Championship is based on the no-holds-barred martial art tournament of the same name. What makes the game (and the real-life counterpart) distinct from wrestling, boxing, and other fights is the variety of fighting styles in use; it is perfectly possible to end up with a judo master facing a kickboxer. The actual gameplay is simple enough. You have various basic moves, combos, holds, and so on.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anchor</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultimate Fighting Championship.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultimate Fighting Championship.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zero Gunner 2.chd</path>
		<name>Zero Gunner 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Zero Gunner 2 would on first inspection appear to be a bog-standard 2D shooter. However this import game actually has a bit of a unique "spin" on the shooter genre. Most noticable, all backdrops and vehicles in this game are modelled in 3D. The textures are quite highly detailed and this adds more depth than standard 2D shooters. Secondly, since your craft is a helicopter, a unique "target and spin" feature has been added whereby you can both rotate your craft to better attack an enemy or alternatively to lock on a particular point in space and rotate around it while still firing.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010906T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Psikyo</developer>
		<publisher>Psikyo</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zero Gunner 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zero Gunner 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombie Revenge.chd</path>
		<name>Zombie Revenge</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A top secret government plan to use undead soldiers has gone horribly wrong. Just before it was ready to be put into operation, someone unknown interfered. Now a year later the city is the home for the undead. Three agents, Stick Breitling, Linda Rotta and Rikiya Busujima, who have come together from various paths of fate, now join together to do battle against the army of the undead and rid the streets of the zombie scum!.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000609T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AM1</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zombie Revenge.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zombie Revenge.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4x4 Evo (USA).chd</path>
		<name>4x4 Evo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>4x4 Evolution is a racing game featuring real-life pickup trucks and SUV's. Actual trucks from manufacturers such as Chevrolet, Ford, Dodge, Nissan, Toyota and more are included.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Terminal Reality</developer>
		<publisher>Gathering of Developpers</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/4x4 Evo (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4x4 Evo (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./AeroWings (USA).chd</path>
		<name>AeroWings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Aerowings is a simulation that allows you to fly as a member of a jet aerobatics team. Aerowings contains a variety of jet-powered aircraft that you can fly.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>Crave Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/AeroWings (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/AeroWings (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Surfer (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Championship Surfer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this surfing game the player can choose from 10 of the best beaches the world has ever seen, and attack them with the help of 8 championship surfers, including Cory Lopez and Shane Beschen. There are plenty of moves to perform with each surfer, but the best points come in the bigger waves (including the half pipe).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010810T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krome Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Mattel Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Championship Surfer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Championship Surfer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cyber Troopers - Virtual On - Oratorio Tangram (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Cyber Troopers Virtual On: Oratorio Tangram</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Virtual-On: Oratorio Tangram on Dreamcast is a fighting game in which you can see colossus of steel face off against each other. Choose your mecha-robot (big robot) and activate the machine. Whether it's with a cyber sword or your rockets, smash your opponents into a junkyard before they cut your batteries.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cyber Troopers - Virtual On - Oratorio Tangram (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cyber Troopers - Virtual On - Oratorio Tangram (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ESPN International Track &amp; Field (USA).chd</path>
		<name>ESPN International Track &amp; Field</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Compete in twelve international track &amp; field events ranging from 100m dash to hammer throw. Most of the action is done via button mashing and timed button presses, similarly to the now classic NES Track &amp; Field games.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/ESPN International Track &amp; Field (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ESPN International Track &amp; Field (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Iron Aces (Europe).chd</path>
		<name>Iron Aces</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Iron Aces is fictional World War 2 flight simulator. What that "fictional" means is that great liberties have been taken with the historical accuracy of the world and events. The most obvious point is that although most planes come from real World War 2 aircraft, the theatre of operations is a bit unique; The four major sides to the conflict (American, British, German, Japanese) are all fighting one another over a group of islands somewhere in the Pacific. Thus each of these nations is represented in close proximity and in direct conflict to one another.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20010629T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Marionette</developer>
		<publisher>Xicat Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Iron Aces (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Iron Aces (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Hoopz (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NBA Hoopz</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NBA Hoopz is an arcade-style game and not meant to be realistic: players can jump twenty or thirty feet in the air, dunk the ball from 20 feet (6.1 m) away, and do otherwise physically impossible things. Fouls are only called on flagrant pushes, foul shots are rare (and only after a number of fouls are accumulated), and there is no out of bounds. In addition, after a player makes three consecutive shots he becomes "on fire" which allows him to make almost any shot as well as goaltend without penalty.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20010313T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA Hoopz (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA Hoopz (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NCAA College Football 2K2 - Road to the Rose Bowl (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NCAA College Football 2K2: Road to the Rose Bowl</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NCAA College Football 2K2: Road to the Rose Bowl is an American football video game developed by Visual Concepts in association with 2K Sports. It was released in 2001 for only the Sega Dreamcast. The cover athlete is former Purdue standout quarterback Drew Brees.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010829T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NCAA College Football 2K2 - Road to the Rose Bowl (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NCAA College Football 2K2 - Road to the Rose Bowl (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL 2K2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NFL 2K2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NFL 2K2 is a complete football simulation, giving you a variety of ways to play. You can compete in a single exhibition game, start up a franchise, or move directly to the playoffs. NFL 2K2 uses a TV-style presentation, featuring telestration, action replays, sideline animations, stadium lighting and a director feature that zooms in on the play.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20010919T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NFL 2K2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NFL 2K2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NFL Blitz 2001 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>NFL Blitz 2001</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>No refs, No rules Just 'classic' gridiron. Late hits, pass interferences, and other penalties are encouraged (though you can't run offside). Cheerleaders in, well, cheerleading uniforms liven up the end of the first and third quarter and there's enough stats to make the mathematically inclined happy. However, the teams features are not entirely based on real life (Indy was at the top), and it is not as addictive as the old-fashioned PC games of the early 1990's, but still a good game for someone who doesn't mind not-so-classic, almost XFL style football.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20000914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalanche Software</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NFL Blitz 2001 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NFL Blitz 2001 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sega Worldwide Soccer 2000 - Euro Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).chd</path>
		<name>Sega Worldwide Soccer 2000: Euro Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is an upgrade to Sega Worldwide Soccer 2000, with an improved graphical engine and the possibility to let you play the Euro 2000 celebrated in Holland and Belgium. Other available game modes are the World Cup (where you could compete as any of the 64 best teams in the world), National leagues (Italian, Spanish, English, German, Japanese, etc), International leagues and friendly match. Regarding player licenses, this game takes the same position as World League Soccer 98; that is, player names will resemble those of their real life counterparts, but will not be exactly the same (although curiously, game commentators will pronounce them correctly).</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000526T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon Dreams Studio</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sega Worldwide Soccer 2000 - Euro Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sega Worldwide Soccer 2000 - Euro Edition (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Charge 'n Blast (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Charge 'N Blast</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Charge 'n Blast on Dreamcast is an action-shooter game adapted from the arcade title of the same name. The game takes into account the differences between the weapons and the difficulties to aim inherent in the weight of each.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20010207T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>Xicat Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Charge 'n Blast (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Charge 'n Blast (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crazy Taxi.chd</path>
		<name>Crazy Taxi</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Crazy Taxi is an arcade-like racer where the player takes the role of a taxi driver who weaves his way through crowded streets, across sidewalks and even under water, in a wild and frantic race to deliver passengers on time. The courses are largely set inside cities crowded with general traffic and pedestrians (which can't be run over, they dive away). The main goal is to bring as many customers as possible to their destination in time.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Crazy Taxi.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Crazy Taxi.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bust-A-Move 4 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move 4</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The 4th edition of Bust-A-Move adds some great new characters to choose from, as well as a Story mode, where you win Tarrot cards from each puzzle you complete. Player VS. CPU has two different modes: Story mode sees a story unfold as you defeat each CPU character (and changes depending on the character you start with) and Win Contest is a simple "how many games can I win in a row" against the computer. Finally, if you complete the Challenge mode (where you must complete certain puzzels as fast as possible, and get judged on technique, speed etc.) the Edit mode will become available. In here you can put together your own puzzles for you or your friends to complete.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20000707T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Club Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bust-A-Move 4 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bust-A-Move 4 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stupid Invaders.m3u</path>
		<name>Stupid Invaders</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Five aliens crashland on Earth, and hide out in an abandoned house while they repair their spaceship. In the meantime, Dr Sakarin, an evil alien-collecting scientist has found out about them, and sends out his evil henchman Bolok to capture them. You play as each of the five aliens, and must help them escape.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20010504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Xilam</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Stupid Invaders.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stupid Invaders.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Armada (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Armada</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ten millennia after the initial wave of colonization of the universe, humans have developed into distinct races adapting to their newfound homes. While there is peace between the races, there is no sense of unity. This all changes when, without warning, a bio-mechanical Armada wages war on the whole of humanity. Now as a starship captain representing one of the six main races of humanity, your charge is to take the fight to the Armada and save humanity.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Metro 3D</developer>
		<publisher>Metro 3D</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>4+</players>
		<image>./boxart/Armada (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Armada (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Intrepid Izzy (USA) (Unl).cdi</path>
		<name>Intrepid Izzy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>From the creators of Beats of Rage and Rush Rush Rally comes an action adventure whose gameplay and graphics are like a wonderful marriage between classic and modern gaming. Explore a colourful and imaginative world as the lovable, witty and above all intrepid Izzy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20210821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Senile Team</developer>
		<publisher>Senile Team</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Intrepid Izzy (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Intrepid Izzy (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NEO XYX.cdi</path>
		<name>Neo XYX</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NEO XYX is early 90is style maniac shooting game. Fast and intense. Game Features: 6 stages with varied and colorful settings 6 endbosses 5 midbosses 16-bit hand-drawn graphics (dot graphics) Switchable between vertical (TATE) and horizontal controls (YOKO) The HUD/score/lives/bombs etc. switch between TATE and YOKO too. Maniac shooting gamnn Professional printed CD</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20140217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/NEO XYX.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NEO XYX.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Power Jet Racing 2001 v1.002 (2001)(CRI)(JP)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Power Jet Racing 2001</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Surf Rocket Racers is a jet-ski racing game for the Dreamcast. As in most aquatic racers, success here depends on your ability to smoothly handle unpredictable waves and aggressive competition at the same time.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>20010322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CRI</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Power Jet Racing 2001 v1.002 (2001)(CRI)(JP)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Power Jet Racing 2001 v1.002 (2001)(CRI)(JP)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psyvariar 2 - The Will to Fabricate (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Psyvariar 2: The Will to Fabricate</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Psyvariar 2 is another specimen of the recent breed of "newschool" arcade shoot'em'ups (other examples being Ikaruga and Border Down). As many other recently released shoot'em'ups, it combines basic arcade shooter gameplay with modern 3D graphics to liven up the genre. The level backgrounds as well as all enemies are modeled in full 3D, with the action taking place in a vertically scrolling two-dimensional plane which moves through the level.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20040226T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>Success</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Psyvariar 2 - The Will to Fabricate (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Psyvariar 2 - The Will to Fabricate (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puyo Puyo Fever (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Puyo Puyo Fever</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Puyo Pop Fever on Dreamcast is a puzzle game in which the goal is to align the Puyos of the same color in order to make them disappear. If you manage to make several lines in a row, you can block your opponent who is solving the same puzzle as you. In addition to the classic mode, discover variations of the game that allow you to see the gameplay from other angles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Puyo Puyo Fever (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Puyo Puyo Fever (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rippin' Riders Snowboarding v1.001 (1999)(Sega)(NTSC)(US)[!].CHD</path>
		<name>Rippin' Riders Snowboarding</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game, called Rippin' Riders in the United States, Snow Surfers in Europe and Cool Boarders Burrrn in Japan, is a snowboarding game. If you like extreme sports, Snow Surfers is a pleasure to watch. It's almost as if you can feel the cold mountain air on your face as you prepare to descend the slopes at high speed. There are so many game modes and options here that it's hard to know where to start. Suffice it to say that you'll need the nimblest fingers to beat your opponents in competition, and there's a plethora of tricks and maneuvers to try. This will keep you busy for hours.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19991110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>UEP Systems</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rippin' Riders Snowboarding v1.001 (1999)(Sega)(NTSC)(US)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rippin' Riders Snowboarding v1.001 (1999)(Sega)(NTSC)(US)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Shikigami no Shiro II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Shikigami No Shiro II is a shoot'em up on Dreamcast. In the purest tradition of the genre, avoid the myriads of energy balls and lasers of all kinds that are thrown at you by enemies. Dodge and attack with equal fervor and defeat Shikigami Castle.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Alfa System</developer>
		<publisher>Alfa System</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shikigami no Shiro II (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Puzzle Fighter II X for Matching Service (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Puzzle Fighter II X for Matching Service</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Burst right into the feverish puzzle action that combines irresistable, addictive fun with famous Capcom characters. Beat your opponent to the punch by stacking block after block in strategic patterns and color combinations. Be the first to fill the opponent's screen with blocks and K.O. You win! But get ready for more because you can't play just once!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010705T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Puzzle Fighter II X for Matching Service (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Puzzle Fighter II X for Matching Service (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Street Fighter II X for Matching Service (Japan).chd</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II X for Matching Service</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Street Fighter II X for Matching Service is a fighting game developed by Capcom, and one of many updates to the popular fighting game, Street Fighter II. This version was released for the Sega Dreamcast exclusively in Japan in 2000. It is an enhanced port of Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge, known as Super Street Fighter II Turbo in the west. The game is virtually identical to other ports of Super Street Fighter II X/Super Street Fighter II Turbo, but is compatible with Capcom's "matching service", meaning players can compete online.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20001222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Street Fighter II X for Matching Service (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Street Fighter II X for Matching Service (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xeno Crisis (Unl).chd</path>
		<name>Xeno Crisis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Xeno Crisis is an arena shooter in which up to two players enter a ravaged research outpost to confront an alien menace and get out alive! Run and gun your way through thousands of adversaries as you search for the source of the deadly alien outbreak.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>20191028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bitmap Bureau</developer>
		<publisher>Bitmap Bureau</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Xeno Crisis (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Xeno Crisis (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Captain Tomaday.cdi</path>
		<name>Captain Tomaday</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Stop the “Eggplant Aliens”! In this vertically scrolling shoot'em up, you play Captain Tomaday, a mutant tomato capable of firing with great precision at its enemies. Our hero has the ability to transform himself in order to acquire new powers!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20190601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>JoshProd</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Captain Tomaday.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Captain Tomaday.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Redux Dark Matters.cdi</path>
		<name>Redux: Dark Matters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Shooter and action game Redux: Dark Matters immerses you in gameplay punctuated by fast-moving actions. You will have to go through 7 totally different worlds but respecting a common characteristic, the permanent difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20140127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ReduxGame</developer>
		<publisher>Hucast Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Redux Dark Matters.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Redux Dark Matters.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Channel 5 Part 2.chd</path>
		<name>Space Channel 5: Part 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's the 25th century. Several lunar cycles have passed since Ulala saved human kind and repelled the Morolian invasion against Earth through dance. Life is quiet too quiet for Ulala until Chief Director 'Space Michael' reports that a mysterious dancing group is forcing innocent bystanders to dance and then whisking them awayâ€¦Here starts another swinging report show from Ulala!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20020214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>United Game Artists</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Space Channel 5 Part 2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Space Channel 5 Part 2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arcade Racing Legends.cdi</path>
		<name>Arcade Racing Legends</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Get your old Dreamcast's engine warmed up and show off your driving skills as you take the wheel of one of the dozens of legendary cars included in Arcade Racing Legends game! At full speed, on an original soundtrack you will try to control your vehicle on 7 varied circuits.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20201031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intuitive Computer</developer>
		<publisher>JoshProd</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Arcade Racing Legends.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Arcade Racing Legends.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Force Five.chd</path>
		<name>Force Five</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An unreleased Atomiswave fighting game developed by Anchor Inc. that would later be reskinned and released as Jingi Storm: The Arcade. Enter to system menu - press A+B and click START Navigate in system menu - click START for select next option, hold START for enter!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Anchor Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>-unreleased-</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Force Five.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Force Five.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kenju.chd</path>
		<name>KenJu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>KenJu is an unreleased Atomiswave 2.5D fighter made by Dream Factory. A rom for the game was recently discovered, and despite being unreleased, the game is very near finished, having a few minor bugs and couple debatably unfinished characters. The game features 12 characters (14 counting the normally unplayable SekiSyuSai and boss ZINE), a stage for each, and two options for arcade mode as well as versus.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20201031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dream Factory</developer>
		<publisher>-unreleased-</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kenju.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kenju.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./PenPen v1.030 (1999)(Infogrames)(PAL)(M6)[!].chd</path>
		<name>Pen Pen: TriIcelon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A racing game where you play as one of several animals known as Pen Pens. The goal is to walk, swim, and slide across the finish line the fastest. Unlike other racing games though where you hold a button for gas or tilt forward to run, you have to tap the A button in a rhythmic manner to match your strokes with the motion of your Pen Pen.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19991014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>General Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/PenPen v1.030 (1999)(Infogrames)(PAL)(M6)[!].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/PenPen v1.030 (1999)(Infogrames)(PAL)(M6)[!].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Last Hope - Pink Bullets.cdi</path>
		<name>Last Hope: Pink Bullets</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is an updated edition of Last Hope. The game is basically the same, but some modifications have been made to decrease the difficulty. This includes, for example, more levels of difficulty to choose from, and starting with a better equipped and faster moving ship. Further, the standard enemy shots are now coloured in bright pink (thus the name of the re-release) to make them more visible, and the general colour themes of the stages have been adapted to increase the visibility, too.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20090618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>NG:Dev.Team</developer>
		<publisher>NG:Dev.Team</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Last Hope - Pink Bullets.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Last Hope - Pink Bullets.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chaos Field.chd</path>
		<name>Chaos Field</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Chaos Field is a top-down space shooter similar in concept to the Gradius series, or Ikaruga. You control one of three ships, each with their own pilot and unique weapon systems. The game takes place over 5 phases, in each phase you face a number of boss battles. Unlike other games if this genre, almost the entire game is composed of boss battles, each boss requiring a different strategy to defeat.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Chaos Field.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chaos Field.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX.chd</path>
		<name>Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Legendary BMX rider Mat Hoffman leads a cast of some of the best riders on the planet in this Tony Hawk's Pro Skater style title. Perform tricks and make the points to proceed through each level of Street, Vert, and Dirt courses, or take on a mate in 2 player split screen mode and see who has the best bike in town. Career mode allows you to build up your chosen character and make, as it mentions, a Career. And the BMX Course Editor allows you to build your own Street, Vert and Dirt courses for multiplayer action.</desc>
		<rating>0.35</rating>
		<releasedate>20010911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rune Craft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Millenium Racer - Y2K Fighters.chd</path>
		<name>Millenium Racer: Y2K Fighters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Millennium Racer: Y2K Fighters is a 3D racing game set in the 3rd millennium. Race virtual bikes on multi-level tracks in a virtual world set in the Internet to a background of techno music. Choose the player’s look including color and face type or use your own picture. There are eight different bike colors to choose from and four different engine types from fast with no grip to tight grip and good acceleration.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19870101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Creat Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Creat Studio</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Millenium Racer - Y2K Fighters.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Millenium Racer - Y2K Fighters.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Panzer Front.chd</path>
		<name>Panzer Front</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Panzer Front is a realistic World War Two tank combat simulation spanning the summer offensive into Russia of 1941 to the fall of Berlin in 1945. Nearly 25 historical missions are provided in which the player can control USA, Russian or German forces. Nearly 30 realisitically modeled tanks are playable along with 7 fictional ones and dozens of other vehicles that make up friendly and enemy forces.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991222T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shangri-La</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Panzer Front.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Panzer Front.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2 - The Great Escape.chd</path>
		<name>Rayman 2: The Great Escape</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A gang of pirates have invaded Rayman's world to seize its unique creatures and sell them to an intergalactic circus. Our mighty hero, Rayman, has been captured and stripped of his powers. He flees captivity and embarks on a dangerous mission to return to his conquered world where he must liberate all of his imprisoned friends from the pirates. Just like Bugs Bunny: Lost in Time, the game is rendered in full 3D and contains action, adventure and mind twisting puzzles!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>20000301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rayman 2 - The Great Escape.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rayman 2 - The Great Escape.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tennis 2K2.chd</path>
		<name>Tennis 2K2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sequel to the original game which was released two years prior. The games graphics have been improved, and there is a greater roster of players to choose from. The most noteworthy addition is that of female players, such as Monica Seles and Venus and Serena Williams. You cannot however play as a male against a female.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011024T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tennis 2K2.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tennis 2K2.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.chd</path>
		<name>18 Wheeler: American Pro Trucker</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The main purpose of the game is to make it to the finish line with the truck's cargo. Players are given a set amount of time, but can ram into special vans that will add three seconds to the timer. There are several characters to choose from, each with a unique truck and attributes. The game starts out in Key West and players travel across the United States, ending in San Francisco.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>20010106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/18 Wheeler - American Pro Trucker.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4x4 Jam.cdi</path>
		<name>4x4 Jam</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When speed and haste go hand in hand! 4X4 Jam sends you on various courses where you will have to cross the crossing points before your competitors. There is no fixed route, so you can take whatever path you like. Win the stages to climb to the top of the online rankings.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20170930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Invictus Games</developer>
		<publisher>JoshProd</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<image>./boxart/4x4 Jam.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4x4 Jam.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 3: Nemesis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The survival horror Resident Evil 3: Nemesis on Dreamcast takes place during the events of Resident Evil 2. This time you play as Jill Valentine, and must escape alive from Raccoon City, ravaged by zombies. Nemesis, the exterminating monster of the last survivors is on your tail.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20001115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Radirgy.cdi</path>
		<name>Radirgy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Radirgy is a vertical-screen top-down bullet-hell shooter originally developed by Milestone for Naomi arcade system and later released on Dreamcast. Setting itself apart from many other top-down shooters on the system, the game features bright, cartoony, cell-shaded graphics. At the beginning, the player is given a choice of three different mecha-ships - one with a spread-gun, a weak homing laser, or a slow but powerful bubble gun.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20060216T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Milestone</developer>
		<publisher>Milestone</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Radirgy.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Radirgy.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Calibur.chd</path>
		<name>Soul Calibur</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A fighting game to end all fighting games. A sequel to Soul Blade, Soul Calibur takes place in a time inspired by a mixture of 16th-century ancient China and oriental medieval fantasies and legends. All characters have weapons and distinct fighting styles with over 100 individual moves per character.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19991126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Soul Calibur.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Soul Calibur.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Typing of the Dead, The.chd</path>
		<name>Typing of the Dead, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is essentially the same game as the arcade light-gun rail-shooter House of the Dead 2, except they've turned it into a edu-tainment typing trainer. Instead of guns, your characters have keyboards strapped to them, and instead of shooting the zombies that constantly jump out at you you'll need to type out the words attached to the zombies in order to kill them before they crack open your head and feast upon the goo inside. The game ranks you on your typing speed and provides various tutorials and other edu-tainment sundries.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Smilebit</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Typing of the Dead, The.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Typing of the Dead, The.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Virtua Tennis.chd</path>
		<name>Virtua Tennis: Sega Professional Tennis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Play as one of eight licensed players and uncover the secret stars. As well as the traditional arcade mode you can play in the exhibition mode, with 4 player action via doubles play. Once you've mastered those modes take on the world in the world circuit mode, with unique training games, diffrent challenges and shops to buy clothing, equipment, stages and playing partners. Virtua Tennis, so realistic you can almost taste the strawberries and cream.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000908T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hitmaker</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Virtua Tennis.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Virtua Tennis.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./4 Wheel Thunder.chd</path>
		<name>4 Wheel Thunder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>4 Wheel Thunder is the off-road racing sequel to the popular power-boat racing game, Hydro Thunder. In this game, players race around two types of courses; huge outdoor tracks and smaller indoor tracks. All in all, there are 24 areas in which to race, including various day/night, rain/sunshine variations. The game includes the standard championship, practice race, and 2-player modes. The thunder series of games is unique in that the key to winning the race lies not in careful steering and braking, but in finding the "boost" power-ups that lie around the tracks.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20000101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Kalisto</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/4 Wheel Thunder.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/4 Wheel Thunder.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Fighters, The - Dream Match 1999.chd</path>
		<name>King of Fighters: Dream Match 1999, The</name>
		<sortname>King of Fighters '98</sortname>
		<desc>A special Dreamcast conversion of KOF '98 (NOT '99) with several additions for Sega's console. The game remains the same as the original arcade version, but now includes new backgrounds (some with some polygonal enhancements) and a series of complementary bonus materials like conceptual galleries, sound test modes, etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19991022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<image>./boxart/King of Fighters, The - Dream Match 1999.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King of Fighters, The - Dream Match 1999.mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>