<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Family Computer Disk System</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula (English).zip</path>
		<name>Akumajō Dracula (Castlevania)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Transylvania enjoyed a century of peace thanks to the legendary hero, Christopher Belmont, a vampire hunter who vanquished Count Dracula one hundred years earlier with a holy whip named Vampire Killer. While the Easter celebration carried on with a grand carnival, evil men gathered in a monastery at the edge of the village and conducted a black mass to resurrect Count Dracula.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Akumajou Dracula (English).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Akumajou Dracula (English).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. English.fds</path>
		<name>All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. (Super Mario Bros.: The Lost Levels)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. was a promotional item given out as a contest prize by the Japanese radio show All Night Nippon to celebrate its twentieth year on the air. It is mainly a graphical hack of Super Mario Bros. (although a handful of levels are from Super Mario Bros. 2.) Some of the games sprites have been changed to look like famous Japanese celebrities and other people related to the All-Night Nippon program.</desc>
		<releasedate>19861022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. English.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/All Night Nippon Super Mario Bros. English.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic (Japan) [En by Vice v1.0] (~Dream World Doki Doki Panic!).fds</path>
		<name>Yume Kōjō: Doki Doki Panic (Dream Factory: Heart-Pounding Panic)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Yume Kōjō: Doki Doki Panic follows a story book structure, and is made out of seven chapters (areas) and twenty pages (levels). Interestingly, although the player can play the Doki Doki Panic with any character, it has to eventually defeat the evil Mamu with all four to finally beat the game (the player can separately save each character's progress).</desc>
		<releasedate>19870710T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Fuji Television Network</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic (Japan) [En by Vice v1.0] (~Dream World Doki Doki Panic!).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Yume Koujou Doki Doki Panic (Japan) [En by Vice v1.0] (~Dream World Doki Doki Panic!).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Falsion (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Farushion (Falsion)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Humanity has colonized most planets in our galaxy, the Milky Way, and they now look towards expanding their reach by using an experimental travel technology called "Hyperzone Drive". However, a race of aliens who have already mastered that technology are currently invading planets at a quick pace, closing in on our solar system. The invaders attack humanity's colony on Pluto and conquer it with little resistance, since human civilization doesn't have the technology to defend itself.</desc>
		<releasedate>19871012T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Falsion (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Falsion (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid.fds</path>
		<name>Metoroido (Metroid)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's you against the evil Mother Brain in the thrilling battle of Metroid! You're inside the fortress planet Zebes. The planet of endless secret passageways where the Metroid are multiplying. Left alone the Metroid are harmless. But in the wrong hands they could destroy the galaxy. It's up to you to prevent the Mother Brain that controls Zebes from using the Metroid for evil purposes. But that won't be easy. You'll have to use your spacesuit to absorb valuable energy for your search to gain the use of power items like the Ice Beam, Wave Beam, High Jump Boots and Varia. If you survive, it will be you and your acquired powers against the Mother Brain.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19860806T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metroid.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metroid.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Moero TsuinBī: Shinamon-hakase o Sukue! (Burn TwinBee: To the Rescue of Dr. Cinnamon!)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Moero TwinBee can be played by up to three player simultaneously: the first two players control TwinBee and WinBee (the ships from the previous game) using the standard Famicom controllers, whereas the third player controls GwinBee (a green ship) by connecting an additional controller into the console's expansion port. Unlike the original TwinBee, which only featured vertical-scrolling stages, Stinger adds side-scrolling stages to the mix as well.</desc>
		<releasedate>19861121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./boxart/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Moero TwinBee - Cinnamon Hakase wo Sukue! (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Otocky (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Otocky</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Otocky can be described as a musical side-scrolling shoot 'em up. The player's spaceship has a ball for a weapon, which can be fired in eight directions; each direction corresponds to a different musical note. The note plays when the player presses the fire button, and is also quantized in time so that it matches the beat playing in the background. By using the weapon selectively the player can improvise music while playing.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870327T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Scitron, Art SEDIC</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Otocky (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Otocky (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puzzle Boys (English Rev A).fds</path>
		<name>Puzzle Boys</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A puzzle game in which you must control a potato character and navigate mazes by pushing blocks and solving puzzles to rescue his vegetable friends in a deep labyrinth.</desc>
		<releasedate>19901116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Atlus</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Puzzle Boys (English Rev A).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Puzzle Boys (English Rev A).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Lode Runner (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Super Lode Runner</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Douglas E. Smith's Lode Runner was introduced to Japan in 1983 on various popular Japanese home computer platforms, including the MSX, Sharp X1, and NEC PC family computers. Hudson Soft licensed the rights to bring the game to Nintendo's Famicom, and it was released in 1984 as one of the first 3rd party games ever made for the system and it was an incredible hit. Around the same time, Irem licensed the rights to produce an arcade version of Lode Runner which they also released in 1984, along with three other sequels through 1986.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Lode Runner (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Lode Runner (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Lode Runner II (Japan) (Disk Writer).fds</path>
		<name>Super Lode Runner II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The second compilation of levels from Irem's Lode Runner Arcade series. Developed for the Famicom Disk System, it was never released outside of Japan. Irem created four Arcade versions of the original Lode Runner, each with a unique set of levels as well as added features like a co-operative mode for two players. For the FDS home versions, Irem compiled several levels from each of these Arcade versions onto one disk. Super Lode Runner II has fewer single-player levels than its predecessor, but contains more co-op levels to make up for it.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Lode Runner II (Japan) (Disk Writer).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Lode Runner II (Japan) (Disk Writer).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Brothers (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Do you have what it takes to save the Mushroom Princess? You'll have to think fast and move even faster to complete this quest! The Mushroom Princess is being held captive by the evil Koopa tribe of turtles. It's up to you to rescue her from the clutches of the Koopa King before time runs out. But it won't be easy. To get to the princess, you'll have to climb mountains, cross seas, avoid bottomless pits, fight off turtle soldiers and a host of black magic traps that only a Koopa King can devise. It's another non-stop adventure from the SUPER MARIO BROTHERS!</desc>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Brothers (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Brothers (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Brothers 2 (Japan) (En).fds</path>
		<name>Super Mario Bros. 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Mario Bros. 2 is divided into 13 new worlds of the Mushroom Kingdom, each of which have four levels like in Super Mario Bros. Mario and Luigi have to get to the end of the level by jumping over various gaps and avoiding or defeating the members of the Koopa Troop on their way.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19860603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Brothers 2 (Japan) (En).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Brothers 2 (Japan) (En).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nazo no Murasame Jou (English v1.1).fds</path>
		<name>Nazo no Murasame Jō (The Mysterious Murasame Castle)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In feudal Japan, an evil alien descends upon Murasame castle and takes over a giant statue, which then continues to spread its influence over four neighbouring castles. The samurai apprentice Takamaru is thus summoned to recapture the castles and then take on the alien itself.</desc>
		<releasedate>19860414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nazo no Murasame Jou (English v1.1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nazo no Murasame Jou (English v1.1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vs. Excitebike (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Vs. Excitebike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Vs. Excitebike is a motorcross racing simulation game developed by Nintendo as a sequel to Excitebike for the Famicom Disk System. It was also released in the arcades but the Famicom Disk System is arguably better with additional features. It comes with some improved features, including a simultaneous two player mode that the original game lacked, and an improved track save system (the tracks were saved to the writable portion of the disk). The music is completely different; none of the songs from the original game are present in this version, and a background theme is played during gameplay.</desc>
		<releasedate>19881209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vs. Excitebike (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Youkai Yashiki (Japan) [En by KingMike v1.0] (~Ghost Manor).fds</path>
		<name>Yōkai Yashiki (Monster House)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Yōkai Yashiki, you control a boy armed with a flashlight who must explore five stages and locate five talisman before locating and gaining access to a stage boss. The flashlight serves as a weapon against the monsters which inhabit each stage. Your life meter takes the form of a set of batteries. As your life diminishes, the batteries drain and the power of your flashlight, that is the distance that the beams can travel, decreases.</desc>
		<releasedate>19871023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Casio</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Youkai Yashiki (Japan) [En by KingMike v1.0] (~Ghost Manor).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Youkai Yashiki (Japan) [En by KingMike v1.0] (~Ghost Manor).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yuu Maze (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Yuu Maze</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Yuu Maze ("Maze Play") is a single-screen maze game akin to Namco's classic Pac-Man and its many other imitators in that the goal of the game is to drive the futuristic vehicle around a maze collecting dots while avoiding (or temporarily eliminating) the enemies. Taito, one of the largest manufacturers of Arcade games at the time (not to mention the creators of Space Invaders), would produce similarly Arcade-reminiscent games for the system in order to tap into the portion of the market nostalgic for classic Arcade experiences.Yuu Maze adds a few innovations to the format.</desc>
		<releasedate>19881028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Daiei Seisakusho</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Yuu Maze (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Yuu Maze (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hikari Shinwa - Parthenon no Kagami (Japan) (v1.1) [b].zip</path>
		<name>Hikari Shinwa: Parutena no Kagami (Kid Icarus)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a time where humans and gods coexisted in harmony, the kingdom of Angel Land was ruled by two goddesses, Palutena the Goddess of Light and Medusa the Goddess of Darkness. While Palutena administered the light and helped the mortals cultivate their crops, Medusa despised the mortals and used the darkness to destroy their crops and turn the mortals into stone. Enraged, Palutena transformed Medusa into a hideous monster and banished her into the dark Underworld.</desc>
		<releasedate>19861219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hikari Shinwa - Parthenon no Kagami (Japan) (v1.1) [b].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hikari Shinwa - Parthenon no Kagami (Japan) (v1.1) [b].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kikikai-kai - Dotou Hen (Japan) [b].zip</path>
		<name>KiKi KaiKai</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game follows the adventures of "Sayo-chan", a young Shinto shrine maiden living in Feudal Japan. One night, while Sayo-chan is fanning a ceremonial fire, she is visited by the Seven Lucky Gods, who warn her of a great, impending danger. Suddenly, a band of mischievous goblins appear and kidnap the gods, quickly retreating to a faraway mountain range. Sayo-chan, determined to help the gods, sets off on a journey across the countryside, where she confronts a number of strange creatures from Japanese mythology, including yokai, obake, and yurei-like monsters.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kikikai-kai - Dotou Hen (Japan) [b].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kikikai-kai - Dotou Hen (Japan) [b].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (English v1.1).zip</path>
		<name>Za Hairaru Fantajī Zeruda no Densetsu (The Hyrule Fantasy: The Legend of Zelda)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The player controls Link from a flip-screen overhead perspective as he travels in the overworld, a large outdoor map with varied environments. Link begins the game armed only with a small shield, but a sword becomes available to Link after he ventures into a cave that is accessible from the game's first map screen. Throughout the game, various characters aid Link by giving or selling equipment and clues. These people can be found in caves scattered throughout the overworld; some are readily accessible, while others are hidden behind obstacles such as rocks, trees, and waterfalls</desc>
		<releasedate>19860221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (English v1.1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zelda no Densetsu - The Hyrule Fantasy (English v1.1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Armana no Kiseki (English Patched).zip</path>
		<name>Arumana no Kiseki (Miracle of Almana)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A magic red jewel known as the Almana is stolen from an unnamed village. A thief runs off with the jewel and turns the entire village into stone. The player takes the role of Kaito a hero who resembles Indiana Jones and must travel through six cavernous levels in search of the lost jewel. Kaito's main source of transportation is unique. Besides just walking and jumping, like most platform games, he must also use a special grappling hook to reach platforms that are too high. To make things a little more difficult, the grappling hook can only be launched from a diagonal direction and not just straight above.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Armana no Kiseki (English Patched).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Armana no Kiseki (English Patched).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knight Move (Japan) [En by PentarouZero v1.0].fds</path>
		<name>Knight Move</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is based around the concept of how a knight piece is moved in the game of chess. The player controls a knight chess piece that is constantly jumping and must continually choose which of the possible legal moves to make before the knight lands back on the board.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JV Dialog</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Knight Move (Japan) [En by PentarouZero v1.0].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Knight Move (Japan) [En by PentarouZero v1.0].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Esper Dream (Japan) (v1.1) [En by Mute v1.0].zip</path>
		<name>Esupā Dorīmu (Esper Dream)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is a story that occurred in the distant village from where you live. This village was filled with a beautiful, quiet, and mysterious aroma. However, the villagers suffered from an unexpected tragedy.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Esper Dream (Japan) (v1.1) [En by Mute v1.0].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Esper Dream (Japan) (v1.1) [En by Mute v1.0].mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race.fds</path>
		<name>Famicom Grand Prix: F1 Race</name>
		<sortname>Famicom Grand Prix 1</sortname>
		<desc>Famicom Grand Prix: F1 Race gives you 10 tracks to race on with either dry or rainy conditions. On top of keeping all four wheels on the road, tire wear, damage, and fuel must be managed to secure victory. Stopping into the pit for maintenance at the right moment can mean the difference between victory and defeat. There are also 24 different cars to purchase with your winnings with varying attributes including speed, fuel efficiency, body strength, and tire endurance.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19871030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Famicom Grand Prix - F1 Race.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally English.fds</path>
		<name>Famicom Grand Prix II: 3D Hot Rally</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The second game in the Famicom Grand Prix series. In a departure from its predecessor, Famicom Grand Prix II features a behind-the-car view similar to Outrun and Rad Racer. Rather than consisting of a handful of short tracks, 3D Hot Rally provides three long tracks consisting of a variety of different terrain types giving the feel of an actual rally race. Each track has multiple routes to the finish line, requiring you to find the best path to victory. The game features three cars to choose from: the speedy Kattobi coupe, the balanced Yonque truck, or the rugged Monster buggy.</desc>
		<releasedate>19880414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally English.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Famicom Grand Prix II - 3D Hot Rally English.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).fds</path>
		<name>Ai Senshi Nikoru (Love Warrior Nicol)</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Help the brave inventor Nicol rescue his kidnapped girlfriend Stella from a Demon Bull King from the planet Dairass in this overhead action game. Control Nicol through 7 continents as he recovers 3 pieces on each level to his dimensional transporter invention that the Demon King stole and encased in diamonds. You'll blast away at various minions and avoid treacherous terrain while exploring multiple floors of each continent searching out the diamonds to be re-united with Stella and defeat the evil Demon King!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19870424T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ai Senshi Nicol (Japan).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Eggerland (1987)(Hal Laboratory)[tr en].fds</path>
		<name>Eggerland</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Eggerland series is better known outside of Japan as The Adventure of Lolo series.The game is often referred to as "Syodai", or the "first one". The game is a remake of "Meikyuu Shinwa" (Eggerland 2; lit. "Labyrinth Myth") for the MSX2 Home Computer System with updated graphics and different music. Furthermore, in this remake the location of some special rooms was swapped, and a final boss battle was introduced.In this Eggerland, Lolo must navigate his way through a non-linear series of rooms, the majority of which occupy a 10x10 arrangement along the main floor of a castle.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870129T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Eggerland (1987)(Hal Laboratory)[tr en].jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Eggerland (1987)(Hal Laboratory)[tr en].mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>