<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<provider>
		<System>Super Nintendo</System>
		<software>Skraper</software>
		<database>ScreenScraper.fr</database>
		<web>http://www.screenscraper.fr</web>
	</provider>
	<game>
		<path>./True Lies (USA).zip</path>
		<name>True Lies</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Take charge of gun toting Arnie in this top down omni-scrolling action shooter. Arnie takes on the terrorists using a variety of weapons in all the locations from the movie of the same name. In each location you have a mission such as retrieve data or capture a terrorist.This usually involves searching around for your goal while dispatching enemies and trying to minimise civilian casualties. The emphasis is on action and weapons, in particular Arnold's favourites: flame thrower and the uzi. He also has a diving roll to help him dodge the enemies bullets and come back guns blazing..</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/True Lies (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/True Lies (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Uncharted Waters (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Uncharted Waters: New Horizons</name>
		<sortname>Uncharted Waters 1</sortname>
		<desc>The Franco family used to be one of the influential houses of Portugal. That is until the head of the family sailed out of a disastrous voyage to find the kingdom of Prester John. The disarray that followed brought about an end to the nobility of the Franco name. 100 years have passed and Portugal has prospered through it's sailing and trading empires. Young Leon Fanco wishes to restore his family's good name and make a name for himself as a sailor. At the heart of his ambition is the fair lady, Christiana, who is desired by the likely heir to the kingdom.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19930102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Uncharted Waters (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Uncharted Waters (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wild Guns (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Wild Guns</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>KABOOM! Annie &amp; Clint, two gunslingers, arrive at Carson City and get caught up in a gunfight. It's raining bullets and there are explosions everywhere. After an intense battle they enter the saloon where they dispose of every cowboy in sight while redecorating the interior. Our heroes flee the scene by climbing on the roof, but what's that sound? t's a HUGE robot! Wild Guns is a shooter with a western &amp; Sci Fi theme.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wild Guns (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wild Guns (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ys III: Wanderers from Ys</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Adol's long time friend, Dogi wishes to return to his home town of Redmont after hearing about strange disturbances that are happening there. Always looking for an adventure, Adol joins him and soon finds out the cause of this new evil. Ys III breaks away from the "bumping into enemies" battle system of the first two games and allows Adol to control his sword in a variety of directions.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>Tonkin House</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ys III - Wanderers from Ys (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Saturday Night Slam Masters (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Saturday Night Slam Masters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Slam Masters is an arcade conversion of Capcom's wrestling game of the same name. Ten wrestlers with different fighting styles and individual special attacks are available. They are controlled with three buttons; one for jumping, one for attacking and one for pinning. When close to your opponents, you can grab them to perform various moves ranging from ordinary attacks to body slams to throws. Since the action takes place in a ring, it is also possible to climb the turnbuckle or use the ropes to your advantage. You can also leave the ring for a limited amount of time to fight with different weapons that can be found outside the ring.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Saturday Night Slam Masters (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Saturday Night Slam Masters (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Tales of Spike McFang, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Twisted Tales of Spike McFang, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Twisted Tales of Spike McFang is an action-rpg starring the titular hero, a young vampire prince who must rescue his parents and save the inhabitants of the Vladamasco Islands from the evil Von Hesler. But is it really his handiwork, or is there someone else controlling him? Unravel the mystery while traveling to various locales, fighting Von Hesler's henchmen and picking up (CPU-controlled) companions along the way. Spike McFang has three main methods of attack: by striking out with his cape, throwing his hat like a boomerang, or using a magic card.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naxat Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet Proof Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Twisted Tales of Spike McFang, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Twisted Tales of Spike McFang, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Troddlers (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Troddlers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Troddlers is a puzzle game in the vein of Lemmings. The player takes control of an animal-like wizard who can create and remove blocks; these blocks are useful for both jumping onto and redirecting the path of the little Troddlers that you have to direct towards the exit. The tricky bit is that the Troddlers can climb walls and ceilings, following the edge of the world and the exit is often in the middle of the screen or with an obstacle in the way.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Troddlers (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Troddlers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./U.N. Squadron (USA).zip</path>
		<name>U.N. Squadron</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Side-scrolling shoot-em-up, in a similar style to such games as Gradius, R-Type and Scramble. The aim is to wipe out the enemy, which has gathered around the allied airspace of 'Area 88', in a series of military aircraft-based scenarios. You choose one of three unique pilots; Shin Kazama, Micky Schymon or Greg Gates, each with varying abilities at damage repair, weapon handling and flying skill, and engage the enemy over a series of challenging missions.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/U.N. Squadron (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/U.N. Squadron (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Uniracers (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Uniracers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>What do you get if you cross Sonic the Hedgehog with Tony Hawk's Pro Skater? It might seem an odd combination, but it describes Uniracers perfectly. One of the more successful releases of the Super Nintendo's twilight era, Uniracers mixes platform-based high-speed racing, with crazy stunts and tricks.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19941202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Uniracers (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Uniracers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario's Woods (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Wario's Woods</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Wario's Woods is a puzzle game similar to Tetris or Columns, but with a twist. Instead of directly controlling the monsters and bombs that are falling down, the player controls Toad who has to carry around stacks of monsters and bombs and to combine them in the right way. One bomb plus at least two monsters of the same color have to be combined to make them disappear. If five or more objects are cleared at the same time, a diamond will appear. Destroying the diamond will clear all monsters of the diamond's color. There are four different ways to pick up objects.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Wario's Woods (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Wario's Woods (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WeaponLord (USA).zip</path>
		<name>WeaponLord</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A barbarian battleground. Seven different warriors, eached armed with a unique weapon set forth on a fighting game quest where they will clash and conflict with one another in this fighting game from Namco. Their ultimate foe is the mysterious Demonlord. An early relative of the popular Soul Calibur series, the main claim to fame of this game is the weapon play. Blocking and combos are present along with special "frenzies" of increased attack and death combos. The backgrounds are all hand drawn and meticulously detailed. Each character carries their own storyline with them between arenas, jungles and firey mountains on a quest to oppose the Demonlord.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/WeaponLord (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WeaponLord (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse (USA).zip</path>
		<name>X-Men: Mutant Apocalypse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Because of a rise of anti-mutant activity in Genosha, Professor Xavier uses Cerebro to scan the island nation and discovers Apocalypse's presence there. Genosha's government is apparently using Apocalypse to bring their mutant population under control. However, Xavier suspects Apocalypse to follow his own plans and sends five X-Men, Cyclops, Wolverine, Psylocke, Beast and Gambit, to investigate.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/X-Men - Mutant Apocalypse (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Cookie (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Cookie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A Japan-only edition of Yoshi's Cookie developed to promote A new Kuruppon oven. While an identical copy of the SNES version of Yoshi's Cookie is included, an additional mode is available in which Yoshi moves around on a map similar to Super Mario World's, navigating a small, unknown island. By surveying around and selecting areas, Yoshi is able to cross bridges, hop over blocks, and swim river streams. Along his tour, Yoshi teaches recipe tutorials in the local buildings that players can use to bake real versions of the cookies featured in the game such as Checkerboard Cookies, Heart Cookies, and Flower Cookies.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullet Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>Bullet Proof Software</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Yoshi's Cookie (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Yoshi's Cookie (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Whirlo (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Whirlo</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A platformer title starring Valkyrie's lizard friend Xandra. In the game, which plays as a prequel of the Valkyrie games, you control Xandra as he leaves his enchanted forest in order to get help for his family. This will eventually lead him to meet up with our beloved Valkyrie and mark the beginning of their adventures. Xandra has all the abilities of a standard platformer character, which allow him to jump around and navigate the many obstacles found in the game. Additionally he's armed with a pitchfork which he can use to impale his enemies and stick to some surfaces. Collecting coins allow him to purchase extra lives, but there are no added weapons or spells as in the Valkyrie games.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Whirlo (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Whirlo (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Gear 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Top Gear 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This third-person racing game resembles Gremlin's earlier Lotus series, in terms of its general look and feel, right down to the text font used in the game. Your task is to race through 16 countries, each of which features four races, with many real-world circuits recreated in incongruous locations (such as the Monza layout in Ayers Rock, and the old Hockenheim in Vancouver).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gremlin Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Top Gear 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Top Gear 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Zombies Ate My Neighbors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the game you are a male or female protagonist (Zeke or Julia), fighting the vampires, mummies, zombies, etc. on over 50 levels (not including secrets) and saving all of the people you find. There are defined number of neighbors you save on every level. When they are free then "Exit" door opens and you jump on next level.The levels differ from mall and grocery store to beaches and football fields. Using different weapons such as bazooka or water gun you have to kill the bosses such as huge babies, dragons or ants at the end of levels. You can play the game with two players cooperatively.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zombies Ate My Neighbors (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./S.O.S - Sink or Swim (USA).zip</path>
		<name>S.O.S.: Sink or Swim</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your name is Kevin Codner – rescue mariner extraordinaire, answering the distress call of a sinking cruise liner, the SS Lucifer. You set off in your little submarine and board the ship where a horde of passengers desperately need your keen oversight and "shipsmarts".</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19960102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Zeppelin Games</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/S.O.S - Sink or Swim (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/S.O.S - Sink or Swim (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turn and Burn - No-Fly Zone (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Turn and Burn: No-Fly Zone</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Turn and Burn: No-Fly Zone the player gets in the cockpit of the famed F-14 Tomcat and launches into a series of sorties on enemy fighters. The game is a simulation with real instruments and gauges and authentic weapons such as Sidewinders, Phoenix missiles and the M61A1 Vulcan Cannon to shoot down enemy fighters scattered throughout the stages. Players also land on their carrier in both daytime and night time missions. The game also features Mode 7 scaling.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Turn and Burn - No-Fly Zone (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Turn and Burn - No-Fly Zone (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Trials of Mana (World) (Rev 1) (Collection of Mana).zip</path>
		<name>Trials of Mana</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Trials of Mana is set in the same world as the two previous Mana games (Final Fantasy Adventure, and Secret of Mana). The mysterious power of Mana is also the center of all events in Trials of Mana. Years have passed, and all the destructive powers of Mana have been securely sealed by Mana Swords into eight seeds, all placed in eight different kingdoms. But some people know about those sealed powers, and they don't want to free them for the sake of humanity, but for their own gain - such as the kingdom of Altena, which is slowly freezing and which can be saved only by the legendary powers.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>20190611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./boxart/Trials of Mana (World) (Rev 1) (Collection of Mana).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Trials of Mana (World) (Rev 1) (Collection of Mana).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Gear 3000 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Top Gear 3000</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The last game of the Top Gear series for the SNES exceeds ordinary dimensions and goes into outer space. Face the challenges found in 48 exciting tracks and become the best pilot in the entire galaxy! Just like the previous games, Top Gear 3000 comes with a password system that allows the player to continue a game in progress. The upgrade system of Top Gear 2 gained new breath and now comes with newly designed parts: ranging from tires to engines up to atomic turbos! As players travel from one planet to another via spacecraft, they race on various planets in different systems, getting progressively harder.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Top Gear 3000 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Top Gear 3000 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A spinoff of the Aero the Acrobat games, Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel is an over-the-top platformer that plays much like Sonic the Hedgehog. In the Aero the Acrobat games, Zero is one of the villains. However, this time around Zero is fighting to save his homeland from an evil lumberjack.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Zero the Kamikaze Squirrel (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xardion (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Xardion</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Xardion tells the tale of 3 warring planets that are home to 3 distinct alien races. Their fighting is interrupted by the threat of invasion from a much more potent alien race. The 3 planets find that they are able to set aside their differences long enough to battle their shared menace.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jorudan Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Asmik</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Xardion (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Xardion (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family Values (USA) (En,Fr,De).zip</path>
		<name>Addams Family Values</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The evil Debbie Jelinksi is harming the Addams family once again She has kidnapped Baby Pubert, and Uncle Fester is the one who must find him and to bring him back to his loving family. The game is based on the live-action movie of the same name.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Addams Family Values (USA) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Addams Family Values (USA) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family, The - Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Addams Family: Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Addams Family: Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt is a side-scrolling platformer based on the second animated TV series The Addams Family (1992). The player takes the role of Pugsley who gets challenged to a scavenger hunt by his sister Wednesday. He has to retrieve six items which are of course hidden in six levels which can be accessed in any order. The gameplay follows the usual platforming standards: Pugsley moves from left to right while jumping a lot, avoiding enemies and sometimes solving switch puzzles.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Addams Family, The - Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Addams Family, The - Pugsley's Scavenger Hunt (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Konami's game based on the 90s animated series starring the Caped Crusader sends him against his most famous enemies in a platforming/beat'em'up title. Each level sends Batman against one particular villain. Most levels present Batman with a large number of henchmen to take out and environmental dangers to avoid on his way to one or more boss battles. Besides kicks, throws and punches, Batman can use a variety of equipment against the enemies. Always available are Batarangs and the grappling hook. Before each mission.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Adventures of Batman &amp; Robin, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero Fighters (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Aero Fighters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Aero Fighters is a vertical scrolling shooter and a port of the arcade game of the same name. There are four pilots from four countries (Japan, Sweden, United Kingdom and United States) involved in a war. Each country each has their own plane: F18, FSX, AJ-37 or AV-8. Every plane has a different upgradeable primary and special weapon. The game features overall seven levels and a few of them are presented in a random order.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Video System</developer>
		<publisher>Video System</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Aero Fighters (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Aero Fighters (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alien 3 (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Alien³</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Alien³ on Super NES immerses you immediately after the end of the movie "Aliens". Ellen Ripley, the main character in the saga, is dormant cryogenically aboard the Sulaco Ship. An alien has infiltrated on board, decimating the crew and causing the ship to crash on the planet Fiorina 161. Help Ripley to survive and rescue the prisoners from the clutches of the aliens until help arrives.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LJN</developer>
		<publisher>Probe Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Alien 3 (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Alien 3 (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arkanoid - Doh It Again (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Arkanoid: Doh it Again</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A sequel to the arcade game Arkanoid. Use your paddle to move the ball around and hit bricks to clear the level. Once all the bricks are gone in the current level, you go on to the next level. Power-ups, like lasers and paddle lengthening will help you during the levels. Unlike the arcade version, the sequel has boss battles and somewhat of a storyline.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Arkanoid - Doh It Again (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Arkanoid - Doh It Again (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Axelay (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Axelay</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This planet was once a quiet, peaceful place to live, until they came, An unknown alien race came to this planet and promptly laid waste to it. The remaining defense force has been sent out to try and defeat them. One lucky person gets to fly the latest line of defense ships made: the AX-77 Axelay. However, these ships are still in the prototype stage, and as such, only one exists. So get out there and head to the alien's homeworld. With some luck, you may just be able to take them out at the source.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Axelay (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Axelay (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./B.O.B. (USA).zip</path>
		<name>B.O.B.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>When B.O.B. crashes his dad's space car on the way to pick up his date, he finds himself stranded on a hostile asteroid filled with enemies. By collecting Thiagotch's and using fast reflexes, B.O.B. tries to find his way off the asteroid and to his date. B.O.B. fights his way through three strange worlds in total, encountering several particularly enormous or swift enemies (bosses) along the way, and participating in several cart-race levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930602T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gray Matter</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/B.O.B. (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/B.O.B. (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Battletoads &amp; Double Dragon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Earth is under fire by Colossus, a battleship the size of a city. Using powerful laser cannons, it has destroyed most of Earth's defence forces, while its many troops clean up the rest of the planet. All expect for 5 warriors. The Battletoads, who are well aware of evil forces in the galaxy, join forces with Billy and Jimmy Lee from Double Dragon to defend Earth from the deadly ship and its troops. Using a range of special moves you must fight your way through the streets into the heart of the ship and destroy it.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Battletoads-Double Dragon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Biker Mice from Mars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Biker Mice from Mars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on the cartoon of the same name, Biker Mice From Mars is a racing game very similar to Rock 'n Roll Racing. Races are shown from an isometric perspective and you can choose between six different drivers that differ in acceleration, top speed and grip. During the races, you can use weapons such as mines or missiles to slow down your opponents and pick up random bonuses ranging from money to making you temporarily invincible. After each race, you will receive money that can be spent on better tires, armor, engines or weapons. There's also a two-player mode that lets you play the main race with a friend or compete in a one on one race.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Biker Mice from Mars (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Biker Mice from Mars (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blackthorne (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Blackthorne</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Blackthorne is an action-adventure game that takes place on the planet Tuul. Tuul was a peaceful place, until the evil warrior Sarlac used the power of the Darkstone to take control. Blackthorne's father, the good King Vlaros, sent him to Earth just as his kingdom crumbled around him. Now, 20 years later, Blackthorne is grown and must return to Tuul to free it from the clutches of Sarlac. This game is played from a side-view with non-scrolling backgrounds. It has strong similarities to Prince of Persia, except you battle your foes using guns and bombs instead of a sword.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blackthorne (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blackthorne (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Boogerman - A Pick and Flick Adventure (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Boogerman: A Pick and Flick Adventure</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>He thinks he's a hero, but he's snot! He's mean. He's green. And he nose how to pick a fight! He's BOOGERMAN, as slick as he is deep, and he's on a pick 'n' flick adventure to save the world. He's stretched to the limit of blowing away the vile slimebags who are bent on sticking it to Planet Earth, any way, every way, and everywhere they can.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Boogerman - A Pick and Flick Adventure (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Boogerman - A Pick and Flick Adventure (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a distant land, peace was maintained for thousands of years by a fearful dragon clan who could transform into powerful monsters. One day they discovered a goddess who could fulfill their every wish. Greed split the clan into Dark and Light Dragons, each battling the other to win her magic. One member of the Light Dragons, along with seven of his companions, emerged to keep the opposing forces from destroying their world. Using six magical keys, they sealed the goddess into another realm.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Breath of Fire (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Breath of Fire (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Breath of Fire II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Breath of Fire II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ryu was a young boy who has memories of a strange village far away and a magical doorway which sucked him through. However those are only distant memories. Ryu and his best friend Bow are apprentices in the Ranger's Guild. As adventurers they take on posted jobs needed by the townspeople. However it isn't long before one job goes awry and Bow is accused of stealing a valuable item. In order to clear his friend's name and find the meaning of his dreams, Ryu will explore the world, eventually discovering the meaning of his dreams and hidden abilities inside himself.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Breath of Fire II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Breath of Fire II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bugs Bunny - Rabbit Rampage (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Bugs Bunny: Rabbit Rampage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A fiendish animator has gone crazy and has started painting Bugs Bunny into all sorts of messes across reused cartoon landscapes. Bugs is getting into trouble from all kinds of characters including Elmer Fudd, Marvin the Martian, Crusher the wrestler, Yosamite Sam, the three little pigs. Bugs will need to use his experience, wit, and arsenal of wacky ACME weapons in order to defeat the challenges of each location.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Viacom New Media</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Bugs Bunny - Rabbit Rampage (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Bugs Bunny - Rabbit Rampage (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Puzzle Bobble - Bust-A-Move (Europe) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Bust-A-Move</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bust-A-Move (also known as Puzzle Bobble) is a real-time puzzle game in which the player controls a device called "pointer" at the bottom of the screen, aiming and releasing randomly colored bubbles upwards. Depending on the aiming, the bubbles may float up directly or bounce off the walls, changing their trajectory. The goal is to aim the bubbles in such a way that they will touch identically colored ones. When such bubbles form a group of three or more, they pop and disappear from the screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950113T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Puzzle Bobble - Bust-A-Move (Europe) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Puzzle Bobble - Bust-A-Move (Europe) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Captain Commando (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Captain Commando</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Metro City, 2026. A corrupt mutant group by the name of "Scumocide" plot to control the universe. The hero, Captain Commando assembles a team of three renegades; Ginzu the Ninja, Baby Head, and Mack the Knife; to help him foil Scumocide's plans. This task will not be easy as many of Earh's institutions are infested with Scumocides minions, but strength and persistence runs the team into the crusade. The player chooses one of these four characters, who must fight their way through an army of genetically engineered super-criminal, traveling through a series of locations such as the bank, museum, circus, aquarium, and several others, right through to a planet called "Callisto", where the evil behind "Scumocide" awaits.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Captain Commando (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Captain Commando (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Dracula X (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Castlevania: Dracula X</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Transylvania, people lived in fear of the evil Count Dracula. The ultimate embodiment of evil, Dracula swept his dark hand over the land, making the people mere sheep for his thirst for blood. But when a young woman named Sonia Belmont came forth to confront him, he made a horrible mistake: he underestimated her. Thus, the battle between Dracula and the Belmont family began. Now, in the late 18th century, the battle still rages on.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Castlevania - Dracula X (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Castlevania - Dracula X (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Trigger (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Chrono Trigger</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>What begins as a carefree day at the Millennial Fair for a young man named Crono turns into his ultimate adventure. When Crono meets a young girl named Marle, little does he realize that this young girl, his best friend Lucca's invention, and a mysterious pendant will thrust him into the ultimate trip through time and space, encountering new friends, defeating the forces of evil, and encountering the one who would destroy the flow of time.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950822T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Chrono Trigger (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Chrono Trigger (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Claymates (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Claymates</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>From the creators of Clay Fighter comes a game about a shape-shifting ball of clay. You play as a boy named Clayton, whose father has developed a serum to turn humans into animals. However, an evil shaman desires this serum, and when he is denied ownership of it, he kidnaps Clayton's father and turns Clayton into a ball of clay. It's up to the unlikely hero to rescue his father, the serum, and the world!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Claymates (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Claymates (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra III - The Alien Wars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Contra III: The Alien Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's time for revenge The hideous Red Falcon, thought to have been destroyed long ago by the Earth's greatest commandos, Mad Dog and Scorpian, has risen again, this time pissed off and thirsty for revenge. His armies are marching through the cities, across the lands, and with the intention of exterminating the human race like a bad case of fleas. Two new commandos, Jimbo and Sully, have come forth now to kick Red Falcon's ass and save what remains of the world from his hideous plans! The Alien Wars begin!!!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Contra III - The Alien Wars (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Contra III - The Alien Wars (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cybernator (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Cybernator</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a future where fossil fuels are limited, major countries and forces of the world are at war with one another over territory. Alliances are made, forming two major sides: The Axis and The Federation. The elite units in these wars are Assault Suits, man-piloted combat mechs called Assault Suits. Jake is one such pilot, drafted into the Pacific States' Marine Corp under the Federation. During his training, the war has grown substantially and upon being assigned to a platoon, he is immediately thrown into combat.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Masaya Games</developer>
		<publisher>Masaya Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cybernator (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cybernator (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Death and Return of Superman, The (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Death and Return of Superman, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>"Doomsday" is here and only Superman can stop him. Unfortunately in doing so he gets killed himself. Now four other characters emerge, each claiming to be the real hero. The story starts you off with Superman, then Steel, the Eradicator, the Cyborg, and Superboy. Each character has slightly varied moves so different strategies apply when playing as them. The gameplay is basically that of a standard beat-em-up, with the punches, throws and specials moves.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Blizzard Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Death and Return of Superman, The (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Death and Return of Superman, The (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Demon's Crest (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Demon's Crest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once, the world of demons and the world of humans co-existed in harmony. But then six mysterious crests fell from the sky onto the earth, crests of six elements: fire, water, air, earth, time, and heaven. The demons became obsessed with the crests and with the power hidden in them, and so a civil war started. Finally, the Red Demon named Firebrand got all the crests but one - the crest of heaven. The Dragon Demon possessed this crest, so Firebrand decided to confront him. He defeated the Dragon Demon, but was himself severely wounded in battle. While flying back, he was knocked down by a mysterious enemy and lost his crests.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19941021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Demon's Crest (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Demon's Crest (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Aladdin</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Disney's Aladdin is based on the 1992 Disney animated film. For the GBA and the SNES editions development was handled by Capcom. Like other versions, the game is a side-scrolling platformer where the player controls Aladdin through locations from the movie like the city of Agrabah, the Cave of Wonders, and Jafar's palace. Some locations not appearing in the film include a trippy, candy-colored world inside the Genie's lamp and an ancient pyramid. Enemies standing in Aladdin's way include the Sultan's guards, animals and various magical creatures. They can be dispatched by jumping on top of them or by throwing apples at them.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Aladdin (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Aladdin (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goof Troop (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Goof Troop</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Goofy and his son Max were enjoying a peaceful day of fishing, when Keelhaul Pete absconds with Pete and PJ. Now it's up to Goofy and Max to travel to Spoonerville Island and venture through the jungle to rescue their friends. As either character, you'll take on an army of surly swashbucklers as you dodge exploding cannon balls and search dank dungeons on your way to the final showdown with Keelhaul Pete. Along the way, you'll have to dig for treasure and solve puzzles to find the keys that will allow you to enter the pirate's hideout and face Pete.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Goof Troop (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Goof Troop (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse, The (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Magical Quest Staring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This was the first Mickey Mouse game for Super NES, featuring a traditional platform gameplay and colorful Disney-like graphics. Mickey's mission is to save his dog Pluto, who's been kidnapped and kept inside emperor Pete's castle, in a magical land, guarded by mysterious creatures. The originality of the game lies on the possibility of wearing different costumes to incorporate different characters, all taken from old Disney cartoons. Each one has a special ability. As a wizard, Mickey has magical powers; as a fireman, the mouse can deal with fire; and, as a climber, he can reach the top of high platforms.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse, The (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Magical Quest Starring Mickey Mouse, The (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mickey Mania (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Mickey Mania</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mickey Mouse gets a chance to go down memory lane and walk through the timeless adventures he has lived. Mickey Mania is a platformer where all the levels are based on Mickey's most famous cartoons. The levels range about 75 years, starting off with "Steamboat Willie" and going all the way to "The Prince and the Pauper". The gameplay consists mostly of jumping and marble throwing at enemies, with an occasional puzzle element.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mickey Mania (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mickey Mania (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Lion King</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Young Simba just can't wait to be king. His father is the current King of the Savannah and the young prince is able to frolic the lands at will; jumping on and around other subjects of this animal kingdom. When Simba's father, King Mufasa, is killed and his evil brother Scar takes over the kingdom, Simba is banished from the lands of his birthright and has to grow up fast, honing his skills, for the day of his return.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lion King, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lion King, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 2: Diddy's Kong Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Donkey Kong has been kong-napped by the nasty K.Rool and the Kremlings, and it is up to Diddy Kong and his girl-friend Dixie Kong to save him. All the familiar enemies and helpful friends return, along with some new characters, including the wise Wrinkly Kong who will teach you some important lessons in gameplay. Again the emphasis is on banana collecting, where as every 100 bananas makes one extra life. Apart from beating K. Rool and rescuing Donkey Kong, there are extra missions that can be completed. Collect enough K. Rool Krem Coins to open up the routes to the Lost World, while every level has a hidden Hero Coin to collect.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19951205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA) (En,Fr) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon View (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Dragon View</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Solve puzzles and fight monsters in order to save your love. She's been taken by Giza an evil sorcerror bent on destroying all life in the world. You'll journey through different lands in search of clues and powerful items and magic. This game is a 3D side scroller. You fight in real time.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Dragon View (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Dragon View (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./E.V.O. - Search for Eden (USA).zip</path>
		<name>E.V.O.: Search for Eden</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The storyline of E.V.O.: Search for Eden follows the same patterns as modern Evolution theories. The players first controls a prehistoric sea organism, and fights to gain evolution points with which he can improve his fish's body parts and upgrade his attack/defense abilities. The gameplay is not completely linear, which means that certain choices of paths and stages will affect the player's success. The game is composed of a series of stages, in which the sea organism slowly evolves into an amphibian, and later a land-only creature. The physical changes are fairly scientifically accurate which gives the game a semi-educational purpose as well.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/E.V.O. - Search for Eden (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/E.V.O. - Search for Eden (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./EarthBound (USA).zip</path>
		<name>EarthBound</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 199X, in the village of Onett, on the continent of Eagleland. Young Ness was asleep one night when a loud crashing noise awoke him suddenly. As he rushes out of bed and up to a nearby hill, he encounters a strange meteor, carrying a single passenger: a mysterious insect-like being named Buzz Buzz. Buzz Buzz tells him that in the future, an evil alien being known as Giygas has conquered the world, and the only one who can stop him are 4 young kids: 3 boys and a girl. Ness, of course, is one of the chosen ones.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ape Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/EarthBound (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/EarthBound (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Earthworm Jim 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>An ordinary average earthworm named Jim goes about his normal daily life, cruising around avoiding crows and doing other general worm-like things. Jim is suddenly struck by a very large ultra- high- tech- indestructible- super- space- cyber- suit. Through sheer luck, Jim rests safely in the neck ring of the suit. Suddenly, the ultra-high-tech space particles of the suit begin interacting with Jim's soft wormy flesh. A radical light-speed evolution takes place. Jim soon realizes he is in control of the suit. Gameplay is similar to the first game, with Jim jumping and running through the levels. There are 5 weapons more than the original game to collect. Characters like Princess Whats-Her-Name and Psy-Crow appear.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Earthworm Jim 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Equinox (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Equinox</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game is based upon solving puzzles to progress to the next dungeon. In the game you play the son of the hero in the first game; Shadax. Shadax has been kidnapped by an evil witch and it is up to you to rescue him. There is a wide range of weapons and powerful magic spells you can use throughout your quest, some of which are required to solve puzzles.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19931112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Equinox (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Equinox (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero (USA).zip</path>
		<name>F-Zero</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>F-Zero is a futuristic racing game, set in the year 2560. The player chooses one of the four available hovercars and then can race with other hovercars in one of the gameplay modes - "Practice" or "Grand Prix". In "Practice" mode, the player chooses one track where he competes with one other hovercar to win the race (or there can be no rival at all, if you so wish). In "Grand Prix", the player must complete a series of races with several competitors. Each race consists of five laps.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/F-Zero (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/F-Zero (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy II (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The military country of Baron is one of the strongest in the land, with a proud army and a majestic air force known as the Red Wings. But, while their armies are kind and loyal, the recent actions of the King are anything but. The young Captain of the Red Wings, Cecil, is ordered to steal a crystal from a village of innocent magicians, and when he questions the actions of his King, Cecil is immediately thrown out of the country and sent off to kill strange monsters. Little does he realize the price the King's actions will pay, and what the true secret of the crystals, and their powers, truly is.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy II (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy II (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy III (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy III</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the sixth entry in the Final Fantasy series. It was called Final Fantasy III because three of the five previous installments of the series were never released outside of Japan. 1,000 years ago, the War of the Magi occurred. People remember it as one of the most horrible tragedies in history. Since the War of the Magi, magic has been all but forgotten, technology began to grow, and people returned to seemingly normal lives. The only true worry people had was the Empire, whose leaders were looking to revive the great force once known as "magic". But then something happened that would change the course of history forever.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy III (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy III (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Final Fight 2 is the SNES exclusive sequel to Final Fight which was released on the same platform. Like the original outing, this game is a sidescrolling fighter (i.e. Double Dragon).</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fight 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fight 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fight 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fight 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Final Fight 3 is almost identical to the previous two SNES installments. The Mad Gear gang was destroyed and with this, the Skull Cross gang has gone rampant in Metro City. Now, it is up to mayor Mike Haggar and Guy (along with the newcomers Dean and Lucia) to stop them once and for all. Like the previous games, this game is a side-scrolling fighting game (i.e. Double Dragon, Streets of Rage). Instead just using various punches, kicks and special attacks, you can also use various melee weapons that are just laying there on the street. Such as bottles, lampposts, metal pipes, barrels etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19951221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fight 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fight 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Firemen, The (Europe) (En,Fr,De).zip</path>
		<name>Firemen, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play as a firefighter, together, you and your squad are sent in into a big building which is on fire. Your mission is to rescue the people inside the building and also put out the fire. Use your watercannon to put out fire or use your waterbomb to put out bigger flames. Be sure to listen to every word your squadmate tells you, or you may be toast.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Human</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Firemen, The (Europe) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Firemen, The (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Firepower 2000 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Firepower 2000</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A secret "underground race" on an island in the mid-Atlantic ocean has stolen top military vehicles and equipment from around the world and have rebuilt powerful war machines from them. They are even piloted by robots with one mission: to destroy. Military and intelligence officials of major countries have detected them, but they are afraid that they will be unable to prepare against an assault by this underground race. Their plan is to send you in to infiltrate their base and destroy them before they have a chance to unleash the war upon the rest of the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SCi Games</developer>
		<publisher>Time Warner Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Firepower 2000 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Firepower 2000 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Flintstones, The - The Treasure of Sierra Madrock (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Flintstones: The Treasure of Sierra Madrock, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Great Poobah has retired and is looking for a successor. Since there are so many candidates, it is decided that the person who finds the Great Treasure of Sierra Madrock will become the new Great Poobah. The player takes control over Fred and Barney who also participate in the treasure hunt in order to make Fred the New Great Poobah. The Flintstones: The Treasure of Sierra Madrock is a side-scrolling platformer that includes several board game elements. On a world map, Fred and Barney throw dices to determine how many fields they can move.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Flintstones, The - The Treasure of Sierra Madrock (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Flintstones, The - The Treasure of Sierra Madrock (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ghoul Patrol (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ghoul Patrol</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The main attractions at the library's Goblin exhibit have come to life! As the Ghoul Patrol, go back in time and de-spook an encyclopedia of zombified historic dudes. Vaporize garbage-can ghosts and Ninja spirits, rescue bug-eyed librarians and wigged-out pirates, dodge flying books and adolescent-eating plants, and ultimately put the beastly spirit back in the history books!</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JVC</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ghoul Patrol (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ghoul Patrol (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius III (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Gradius III</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gradius III is the third game in Konami's long-running space shooter series, which also includes Life Force and Nemesis. As with most Gradius titles, you control the highly advanced Vic Viper space fighter against hordes of foes. Weapons can be selected from pre-arranged loadouts or you can create your own custom loadout. The game can be played by a single player, or by two players in alternating turns. The game offers three levels of difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gradius III (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gradius III (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gradius_III_SA-1_Enhancement_USA.sfc</path>
		<name>Gradius III: SA-1 Enhancement</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Gradius III: SA-1 Enhancement is the third game in Konami's long-running space shooter series, which also includes Life Force and Nemesis. As with most Gradius titles, you control the highly advanced Vic Viper space fighter against hordes of foes. Weapons can be selected from pre-arranged loadouts or you can create your own custom loadout. The game can be played by a single player, or by two players in alternating turns. The game offers three levels of difficulty.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19901221T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Gradius_III_SA-1_Enhancement_USA.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Gradius_III_SA-1_Enhancement_USA.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hagane - The Final Conflict (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Hagane: The Final Conflict</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Fuma clan protects the Holy Grail which is said to possess the power to destroy the world. When the Koma clan attacks and steals the Holy Grail, only one ninja survives. Transformed into a cyborg, it is his task to retrieve the Holy Grail and save the world. Hagane is an action-oriented platformer, featuring five stages, divided into several sub-stages, filled with lots of enemies, jumping puzzles, mid- and endbosses.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>CAProduction</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hagane - The Final Conflict (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hagane - The Final Conflict (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game follows a young man charged with maintaining the farm he inherits from his grandfather. The primary objective is to restore and maintain a farm that has fallen into disrepair. The player decides how to allocate time between daily tasks, such as clearing land, planting crops, selling harvests, raising livestock, attending festivals, building relationships with villagers, and foraging.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19970601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pack In Video</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Harvest Moon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Harvest Moon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Home Alone (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Home Alone</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Kevin is left alone at home while his family is celebrating the holidays elsewhere. Unfortunately for him, two burglars have entered the house to keep him company. Kevin must avoid being caught by the burglars while he gathers all the family belongings and bring them to safety. To aid him in his quest, Kevin has a slingshot and a water pistol, but equally important is proper handling of the environment - a banana skid placed in the right spot or a bowling ball on top of a cupboard will help Kevin in his cause against the robbers.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19911202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Altron</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Home Alone (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Home Alone (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Hyper V-Ball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Hyper V-Ball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A volleyball simulation seen from a side-view perspective, meaning it is only possible to move players to the left or right. The player can choose between three different leagues: Men's League, Woman's League and Hyper League, which is a league for robots. Two buttons are used to control the ball, one for normal actions and one for "Hyper Plays", special attacks that can only be learned and used in the Hyper League. How a player will block or attack depends on the ball's speed and the players position. Team members who aren't under the player's direct control will also act on their own by positioning themselves or preparing spikes.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Hyper V-Ball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Hyper V-Ball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ignition Factor, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ignition Factor, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Ignition Factor has the player take control of one of the most dangerous jobs, a firefighter, as they progress through several stages including a museum, a mine and a variety of buildings including a skyscraper. Before each mission, the player can look at a map and learn of trapped victims and dangerous hot spots and choose their equipment that include a chemical &amp; electrical fire extinguisher, an oxygen tank, a rope and an axe among others. However, the more equipment that the player is carrying, they will not be able to run or kick, limiting the firefighter to just merely walking.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19950102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ignition Factor, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ignition Factor, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Illusion of Gaia (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Illusion of Gaia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Will is a young boy whose father disappeared long time ago. Now Will lives in a small town with his grandparents. He possesses unusual abilities of pushing and pulling things without touching them. One day, he finds in his house a girl, who soon turns out to be the princess Kara. Kara's father, king Edward, wants her to marry a mysterious person called the Jackal. Kara asks Will to help her to escape the palace, and soon they both get involved in a string of mystery and conspiracies.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Illusion of Gaia (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Illusion of Gaia (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Indiana Jones gets the Super Star Wars treatment for SNES. The title consists of platform levels from the first three Indy films: Raiders of the Lost Ark, Temple of Doom, and Last Crusade. Players get to use Indy's trademark whip, as well as guns, grenades, and his fists to get through the game. Indiana Jones Greatest Adventures also features special levels such as running from the giant boulder (Raiders), the Mine Cart chase (Temple of Doom), flying a biplane (Last Crusade), and fighting a Nazi commander on a tank heading off a cliff (Last Crusade).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950330T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Indiana Jones' Greatest Adventures (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Inspector Gadget (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Inspector Gadget</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Inspector Gadget is on yet another mission against the evil Doctor Claw and his army of M.A.D. (Mean And Dirty) agents. This time it's personal because Doctor Claw has captured Gadget's niece, Penny. With the help of his trusty dog, Brain, and his suit full of special gadgets, Inspector Gadget must save Penny and defeat Doctor Claw and his minions!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19931202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Inspector Gadget (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Inspector Gadget (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./International Superstar Soccer Deluxe (USA).zip</path>
		<name>International Superstar Soccer Deluxe</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the sequel to International Superstar Soccer, Konami's saga of soccer games. This Deluxe version was published first to the SNES, then the Mega Drive and Playstation. ISS Deluxe has realistic animations and player sprites. You can compete with 36 national teams with recognizable celebrity players (like Valderrama, Baggio, Ravanelli, Petkov), but their names are fictitious. You can choose too from 16 formations and 8 strategies to win. The competitions available are: International Cup, World Series (League), Scenario Mode and customizable mini-cups/leagues.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/International Superstar Soccer Deluxe (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/International Superstar Soccer Deluxe (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Joe &amp; Mac - Caveman Ninja (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).zip</path>
		<name>Joe &amp; Mac: Caveman Ninja</name>
		<sortname>Joe &amp; Mac 1</sortname>
		<desc>Joe &amp; Mac: Caveman Ninja features the characters Joe and Mac as cavemen ninjas in a multi-level platform area where the player has to jump and club incoming enemies. They can also throw at them from distance using such weapons as boomerangs, bones, fire, flints, electricity and stone wheels. The objective of the game is to rescue a group of girls who were kidnapped by a rival tribe.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Joe &amp; Mac - Caveman Ninja (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Joe &amp; Mac - Caveman Ninja (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Joe &amp; Mac 2: Lost in the Tropics</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This sequel puts you back into the roles of the cavemen, Joe and Mac. This time, a caveman named Gork has stolen the crown belonging to the Chief of Kali Village, and it's up to you to retrieve it by using the 7 Rainbow Stones you will collect on your journey. Along the way, you will fight dinosaurs, cavemen, and other prehistoric enemies as your travel through the jungle, or through the ice and snow, or even through a volcanic wasteland. Along the way, you can pick up upgrades for your club, or pick up projectiles from eating certain health-recovery items.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Joe &amp; Mac 2 - Lost in the Tropics (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The SNES game based on the film Jurassic Park is an action title that combines top-down and first-person perspectives. Playing as Dr. Alan Grant, the player's ultimate goal is to escape the Jurassic Park island. To reach that goal, several other tasks must be completed, including restoring power to the park and destroying a Velociraptor nest.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jurassic Park (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jurassic Park (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues (USA) (En,Fr,De,It).zip</path>
		<name>Jurassic Park Part 2: The Chaos Continues</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One year after the events of the Jurassic Park, John Hammond wants to bring Jurassic Park back and he sends Dr. Alan Grant to aid a team of heavy armed men down to the former park to restore order. Meanwhile, Biosyn Corp has sent men down the former park so the company can gain control of the park for themselves.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues (USA) (En,Fr,De,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jurassic Park Part 2 - The Chaos Continues (USA) (En,Fr,De,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ken Griffey Jr. Presents Major League Baseball (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Ken Griffey Jr. Presents Major League Baseball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ken Griffey Jr Presents Major League Baseball is a baseball simulation featuring Ken Griffey Jr. of the "Nintendo Owned" Seattle Mariners. This licensed game allows you to play with all 28 Major League Teams in their own stadiums and over 700 player names (not likenesses). You control your pitcher or batter as well your fielders. The game allows you to play and save a 26, 78 or 162 game season.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ken Griffey Jr. Presents Major League Baseball (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ken Griffey Jr. Presents Major League Baseball (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kendo Rage (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kendo Rage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Josephine is a teenage girl who is currently attending Honest Osaki's Kendo School and Used Car Sales to learn Kendo swordsmanship. The old man Osaki teaches his students the art of psychic powers so they can better defeat the forces of evildoers. Josephine is given the Zopikki Talisman; a powerful artifact which transforms Josephine's normal self into a battle warrior. Gripping the bamboo sword and focusing her psychic powers, Josephine must defeat ghosts, pandas and all kinds of other strange creatures which look to cause trouble.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Affect</developer>
		<publisher>SETA Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kendo Rage (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kendo Rage (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Killer Instinct (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Killer Instinct</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the distant future, a monopolistic and technological corporation called Ultratech organizes a fighting tournament known as "Killer Instinct". Many fighters answer the challenge to participate, including several of Ultratech's experimental warriors. To increase the tournament's challenge, Ultratech utilizes a technology that can create bridges between alternate dimensions, releasing a creature known as Eyedol. Eyedol is a two-headed ancient warrior that was imprisoned along with his bitter rival, Gargos. Some warriors enter the tournament to seek glory or escape. Other fighters are attempting to bring an end to Ultratech's corruption.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Killer Instinct (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Killer Instinct (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King Arthur's World (USA).zip</path>
		<name>King Arthur's World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is a 2D side scrolling strategy game. You take the role of King Arthur and lead your army into battle against evil. You'll travel to many worlds including fighting dark knights, underworld orcs, and cloud giants. One of the few games that is Super NES Mouse capable. You are given a certain amount of troops each level. Passwords are used to save your progress between levels. The levels have enemies you must thwart, traps you should avoid, and gold to be won.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/King Arthur's World (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King Arthur's World (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./King of Dragons (USA).zip</path>
		<name>King of Dragons</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The King of Dragons is a fantasy themed side-scrolling beat'em up. There are five different characters to choose from: a fighter, a cleric, an elf, a wizard and a dwarf. All characters have different strengths and weaknesses in speed, attack power and magic. After choosing an appropriate character, the player has to fight his way through numerous short levels guarded by an equally high number of bosses; gaining better weapons and shields/magic in the process.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/King of Dragons (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/King of Dragons (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby Super Star</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>"Kirby Super Star" is another platformer in the Kirby series, distinguished for having an unusually versatile character, who can fly and gain the abilities of his foes. The game is actually a set of seven main games: Spring Breeze, Dynablade, Gourmet Race, The Great Cave Offensive are unlocked at first, and later Metaknight's Revenge, Milky Way Wishes and The Arena become available, as well as a couple of minor minigames.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19960920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby Super Star (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby Super Star (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Avalanche (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Avalanche</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The First Annual Dream Land's Avalanche Competition is about to get under way, and as Kirby and a host of characters from the Kirby series, you can join the tournament and become Avalanche king. Avalanche is similar to Puyo Puyo, and has you stacking colored blobs similar in a way to Tetris. When a certain amount of one color is stacked, an explosion occurs and the screen clears of those blobs, which then appear in the other players screen (either the CPU or a second player). When your screen is cleared before the other player, you move onto the next round, and so on until the final boss. The winner of that match is then crowned the Avalanche king.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Banpresto</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby's Avalanche (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby's Avalanche (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Course (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Course</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After his adventures in Dream Land we find him in this mini golf game where Kirby himself is the ball, and you must guide him around each hole using the sort of bar system that you see in most golf games. Where this game differs, however, is in the fact that you need to eliminate all on-screen enemies before you can guide Kirby into the hole and complete it. As per usual in golf games, the more strokes it takes you to complete the whole, the lower your score - so make sure you aim Kirby just right! You'll find eight courses and a total of sixty-four holes in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby's Dream Course (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby's Dream Course (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby's Dream Land 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Kirby's Dream Land 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>That mean old King Dedede is at it again! He's causing his mischief and Dreamland's in trouble! Kirby, the resident hero of Dreamland, sets out to teach Dedede a lesson, this time with the help of many of his good friends! But wait! Something's wrong! Dedede doesn't seem to be himself. Looks like Kirby has to stop Dedede and find out what is wrong with him! It almost seems like something's controlling him.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19971127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Kirby's Dream Land 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Kirby's Dream Land 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Knights of the Round (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Knights of the Round</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Knights of the Round, play the role of one of three knights from the Arthurian legends. The three characters are Sir Lancelot, Sir Percival, and of course King Arthur. The story tells of a man who pulled the mighty sword Excalibur from a rock which no one else could achieve. This feat signified that he should be king of the Britons and lead them to peace. The trouble is there is mass chaos in the land and the only way Arthur can stop it is to find the holy grail which has been hidden for over a thousand years. Aurthur is joined by Percival and Lancelot on his quest to find the grail.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Knights of the Round (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Knights of the Round (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Goemon (Kid Ying) and Ebisu-Maru (Dr. Yang) are enjoying themselves at home, when they hear about strange spirits sighted at the temple and taking control of the other villagers. Concerned, that a new evil has appeared, the two set out to confront it at the temple. This is just the beginning of a new adventure that will take them Goemon and his partner all across Japan; into moutain villages, amusement parks, castle fortresses and more!.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of the Mystical Ninja, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Looney Tunes Basketball (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Looney Tunes Basketball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Looney Tunes work hard at Warner Bros. studios acting in cartoons for all to enjoy. It's tough work, and afterwards they just want to relax and maybe shoot a few hoops in the parking lot. Of course they can't entirely leave their wild antics inside the studio, and will certainly bring some kind of zany onto the basketball court. Looney Tunes B-Ball is a 2-on-2 Basketball game, similar to the more well known NBA Jam. However, Looney Tunes is much more informal and silly, though this level of silliness is set by the player via the Wackiness Meter on the main menu.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Looney Tunes Basketball (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Looney Tunes Basketball (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia &amp; the Fortress of Doom (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Lufia &amp; the Fortress of Doom</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The hero Maxim and his group defeat the Sinistrals on Mt. Doom (as portrayed in Lufia II), and all is peaceful. With such a great peace, the defense forces of the world become lax. One hundred years later attacks begin taking place, supposedly by the Sinistrals. It's up to the descendant of the hero, and his childhood friend Lufia, to form a new band of champions to save the world. Gameplay is fairly standard for RPGs, with turn-based battling by way of a menu of icons, and random battles. There's also a higher-than-normal emphasis on puzzles within dungeons.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19931204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lufia &amp; the Fortress of Doom (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lufia &amp; the Fortress of Doom (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Lufia II: Rise of the Sinistrals</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lufia II is an RPG with many puzzle elements thrown in. In this game, the prequel to Lufia I, you are Maxim, a monster hunter. During your journey, you will find new party members, explore and conquer various dungeons, and solve many puzzles. Lufia II was an innovative game in many regards. It made extensive use of puzzles in its dungeon layouts. It also featured "Capsule Monsters" which would fight alongside your party in battle. They would evolve when fed weapons, armor, or special fruits. You could also gamble away your money in minigames at the casinos found in various towns.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960831T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neverland</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lufia II - Rise of the Sinistrals (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MechWarrior 3050 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>MechWarrior 3050</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>MechWarrior 3050 is the second Battletech based game from Activision for the Super NES. This time around its viewed in an isometric view as opposed to the first person view of the previous game. The game also features a unique 2 player mode where one player controls the bottom half of the mech to navigate it around the map while the second player controls the upper torso which moves independently.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Malibu Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/MechWarrior 3050 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MechWarrior 3050 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man 7 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man 7</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>At long last, Mega Man had finally manage to beat the evil Dr. Wily! With this defeat, Wily was thrown in jail, seemingly for good. The world would no longer be subject to his madness. But remember, Dr. Wily is mad, but he's not stupid. He had a backup plan and all he had to do was just wait. 6 months had passed, and somewhere from deep within Wily's abandoned lab, 4 hidden capsules activated and opened. His backup plan was in action. he had hidden 4 new Wily Robots that would spring him out of jail so he could continue his mad reign.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man 7 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man 7 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man X</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mega Man X is a robot designed by Dr. Light to choose his own path in life. Years after he is created, Dr. Cain finds X and mimics his design to create a race of such robots called reploids. When the sigma virus infects these reploids, causing them to commit acts of evil, it is up to Mega Man X and his partner Zero (who is quite powerful, contrary to what his name implies) to stop it.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man X (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man X (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man X²</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sigma, the leader of the Maverick army, was destroyed when he underestimated his opponent: a lone warrior, awakened into a time he never knew X. 6 months had passed, and X rose to the rank of leader of the Maverick Hunters. His first task was to eliminate the last of the Mavericks. But as he began his assignment, a mysterious group of Reploids calling themselves the X-Hunters appeared with a message to X: the remains of his fallen comrade, Zero, were in the hands of the X-Hunters, and they planned on resurrecting Zero to fight alongside them and for their fallen leader, Sigma. X must now stop the X-Hunters and rescue Zero, and once again prevent Sigma from rising back into ultimate power.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950303T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man X2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man X2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mega Man X³</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A Reploid scientist named Dr. Doppler begins creation of a new city for Reploids, which will bring a new era of peace to the Reploids and humans. But something goes terribly wrong, and now Mavericks have begun to appear everywhere! It's up to X and Zero to find out who is behind this Maverick revolt and bring them down for good!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega Man X3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega Man X3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega-lo-Mania (Europe) (En,Fr,De).zip</path>
		<name>Mega-Lo-Mania</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>First you choose one out of four different characters to represent you, Scarlet (red army), Oberon (yellow army), Caesar (green army), or Madcap (blue army). The game is split into 10 levels - the first 9 are groups of 3 territories which can be completed in any other, while the final 'Mother of All Battles' has its own surprises. Land is mostly of sand, grass or ice. You start with 100 men and you can use whatever quantity you find necessary on each island. The rest men left will go to another level with another new 100. In the second half of the game you can freeze men to save them for the Mother of All Battles.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sensible Software</developer>
		<publisher>Imagineer</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mega-lo-Mania (Europe) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mega-lo-Mania (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Warriors (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Warriors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Get deployed in your own giant mech and battle through nine linear levels against the evil Dark Axis forces. Eject and switch robots, piloting one of the six "Battledroid" suits; but watch out because there are no save games and no continue codes. For the best of Metal Warriors, grab a friend for some head-to-head combat in the PvP mode. The variety of robots and levels means the matchups stay surprising and interesting.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19950402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metal Warriors (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metal Warriors (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ms. Pac-Man (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ms. Pac-Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In 1982, a sequel to the incredibly popular Pac-Man was introduced in the form of his girlfriend, Ms. Pac-Man. This sequel continued on the "eat the dots/avoid the ghosts" gameplay of the original game, but added new features to keep the title fresh. Like her boyfriend, Ms. Pac-Man attempts to clear four various and challenging mazes filled with dots and ever-moving bouncing fruit while avoiding Inky, Blinky, Pinky and Sue, each with their own personalities and tactics. One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Ms. Pac-Man.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19960901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Digital Eclipse</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ms. Pac-Man (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ms. Pac-Man (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Give 'n Go (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NBA Give 'N Go</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NBA Give 'N Go is a port of the arcade version basketball game. The game is different from usual basketball games of the era because it is played in a vertical view. Most basketball games previously had a side scrolling or isometric view. Building upon this technique, the game features large player sprites and graphics. The game features the NBA roster from 1995 complete with player ratings. Gameplay consists of true 5 on 5 basketball but in a more arcade like style with alley-oops and high flying dunks. The audio includes action oriented commentary, in the style of NBA Jam.</desc>
		<rating>0.45</rating>
		<releasedate>19950705T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA Give 'n Go (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA Give 'n Go (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NHL '94 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NHL '94</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Aside from the licenses, the gameplay for this edition sees for the first time the inclusion of the devastating one-timer shot, but to keep forwards (literally) in check, defenders also feature harder body checks, with new animations. For an additional challenge, players can also choose to control the goalkeeper manually. A popular feature in previous editions, fighting is completely removed from the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19931002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./boxart/NHL '94 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NHL '94 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NHL 96 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NHL 96</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NHL 96 was the first EA Sports game to feature Virtual Stadium technology, which resulted in a 3D feel and multiple camera angles. The NHL license ensures that real teams and players of the era are included, with a full league and playoff system. Many game options can be toggled - the infamous fighting is option, as are the penalties and offsides. The control system makes it possible to execute one-touch passes, and several special trick moves to quickly advance the ball. As a bonus feature, it included 'Hockey Card' profiles of every player on CD, and interviews with the stars of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19950901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Score Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/NHL 96 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NHL 96 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NHL 98 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NHL 98</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NHL 98 features much faster and refined gameplay (now using four action keys instead of two, removing the need to double-tap to perform some actions), along other new features such as "in-the-fly" tactics developed by Marc Crawford, then manager of the Colorado Avalanche and new commentary lines from Jim Hughson and Darryl Reaugh and a re-worked interface. Graphics are improved from the previous version with the players being less angular, and thanks to 3Dfx support, with less pixels showing in the textures. The in-game presentation follows a TV-style script, zooming in players while displaying stats during clock stoppages.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19971201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/NHL 98 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NHL 98 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninjawarriors (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ninja Warriors</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The land is under the grip of a tyrant named Benglar, who is able to brainwash those he captures. Using this ability he has taken over the military forces and now appears unstoppable. However, resistance forces lead by Mulk have been developing a new weapon: Cybernetic Special Forces with the ability to think, dubbed the Ninja Warriors. Untested, these machines are given the orders to assassinate Benglar.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ninjawarriors (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ninjawarriors (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lost Vikings 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Lost Vikings 2: Norse by Norsewest</name>
		<sortname>Lost Vikings 2</sortname>
		<desc>Get ready for more nights of masochistic puzzle goodness, because the Lost Vikings need your help once again! The brothers (Erik the Swift, Baleog the Fierce and Olaf the Stout) are trying to get back home and you need to guide them through. Two brand new characters (Fang the Werewolf and Scorch the Dragon) also join the fray. Each character has their own special talents and they must be used in concert if you are to win.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19970501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Blizzard Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lost Vikings 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lost Vikings 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nosferatu (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nosferatu</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Nosferatu is a platform game similar to Prince of Persia in gameplay and presentation. The protagonist travels on platform structures and relies on acrobatics moves to overcome traps. He fights enemies with his bare fists. Like in Prince of Persia, there is a time limit (which can be extended by picking up the hourglass power-up). Other power-ups include colored crystals that heal the protagonist or increase his life energy.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SETA Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nosferatu (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nosferatu (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ogre Battle - The March of the Black Queen (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Ogre Battle: The March of the Black Queen</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Lead the rebellion and lead your army to reclaim your land from the evil Zenobian Empire in this real-time strategy game. Free towns and collect items and tarot cards to increase your strength, as well as recruit allies to join you in your crusade. But when you finally win the day, will you be a benevolent leader, or an become an evil despot yourself? You must decide.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ogre Battle - The March of the Black Queen (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ogre Battle - The March of the Black Queen (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Out of this World (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Out of This World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play Lester, a young physics professor, who suddenly finds himself in a strange alien world after a lightning struck during his particle experiment. Now he must fight for his life, first with his bare hands, then with a gun he finds. But what gives him courage is that he is not alone. One of the aliens, who together with him escapes from the prison, helps him on his dangerous quest. Friendship can overcome all the obstacles. Out of This World is an action adventure game, where the adventuring element is concealed behind what looks like a typical platform shooter. The gameplay is based mainly on physical and environmental puzzles.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Delphine Software International</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Action-Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Out of this World (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Out of this World (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Out to Lunch (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Out to Lunch</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Pierre Le Chef is famed worldwide for his mouth-watering recipes involving the freshest ingredients. So, when the vegetables start attempting to run away from him, he has no choice but to chase after them. Out To Lunch is a platform game set across 6 countries, starting off in Switzerland and finishing in Paris. To recollect the vegetables he must first stun them, either by firing at them or jumping on them, then walk over them, in a manner similar to Fire &amp; Ice. Unusually, the game was converted from the SNES to the Amiga, not the other way around.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19931102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mindscape</developer>
		<publisher>Mindscape</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Out to Lunch (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Out to Lunch (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parodius (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Parodius</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is mostly the parody of Gradius (Nemesis on some systems), with some flavor from other shoot-em-ups, like Twinbee. The series is available on numerous platforms. The game is a right-to-left scrolling shoot-em-up. You can choose from 4 different flying creatures, with different weapons. You must finish 7 stages, each having a boss at the end. You may start at either one, but must complete every level to advance to the final stage.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920703T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Parodius (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Parodius (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Peace Keepers, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Peace Keepers, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's the year 2015 and the most powerful organization of the planet, a company named Deutschland Moldavia, is threatening to take over the world by genetically manipulatin humans into mindless slaves or powerful monsters. The Peace Keepers is a side-scrolling fighting game similar to games in the Final Fight series. The player can choose from four characters (plus two that become available later in the game) with different strengths and weaknesses.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19940501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Jaleco</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Peace Keepers, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Peace Keepers, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phalanx (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Phalanx</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A futuristic shooter, Phalanx is the name of the prototype starfighter flown by Wink Baufield, a genetically enhanced pilot. It is sent to protect and reclaim Delia IV, a planet in the Andromeda galaxy, which has been colonized by humans for interstellar research purposes. However, an unknown and powerful alien force has overtaken the planet, the military defenses have been completely overwhelmed, and all hope rests on the Phalanx. You fly through eight levels, first through various locations in Delia IV, and then you invade the aliens themselves. Like most shooters, you can upgrade your weapons by picking up bonus items dropped by enemy craft.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19921002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Kemco</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Phalanx (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Phalanx (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantom 2040 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Phantom 2040</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The cartoon mini-series: Phantom 2040, right here. It is the aforementioned year, 2040, and the city of Metropia is in total chaos.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Viacom New Media</developer>
		<publisher>Viacom New Media</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Phantom 2040 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Phantom 2040 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pilotwings (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pilotwings</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Fly a selection of aircraft (including training vehicles, fighter planes and helicopters) through a range of training programs and missions. The more training you complete, the better the chance that you will complete the even bigger missions. Try your hand at landing, taking off, party tricks, fly through bad weather and shoot down targets.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pilotwings (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pilotwings (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Plok (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Plok</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>At one day, Plok awakes to find out that his flag has been stolen. He spots it on a neighboring island and travels there to get it back. However, as he returns to his home, he realizes that all flags on his island have been replaced with flea-flags. This is only the beginning of his problems though, and he has to face many more challenges before the end of the game. Plok has to jump and fight his way through numerous levels, trying to find the exit or fulfilling certain missions such as killing a set number of fleas.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Plok (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Plok (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pocky &amp; Rocky</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play as the Princess Pocky and her Racoon Rocky. Run through each level beating the enemies and you'll face a goofy boss at the end. Beat him and you're on to the next level. You fight and shoot your way through numerous levels based on temples and shrines. Pocky shoot playing cards and Rocky shoot leaves for long range attacks. For short range Pocky uses a rod and Rocky his tail. Pocky also has a spin attack and Rocky can freeze into a invulnerable statue. (Think Tanuki Mario)</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pocky &amp; Rocky (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pocky &amp; Rocky (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pocky &amp; Rocky 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Princess Luna has been kidnapped by a gang of evil demons and its up to Shinto priestess Pocky and her raccoon buddy Rocky to rescue her. As in the previous game, the gameplay involves taking control of either character to clear stage after stage of enemies in classic top-down shooter manner by blasting them with your magic cards or other collectable unique powers. New for the sequel is the ability to play with optional AI-controlled partners that add team-up special moves required to beat certain bosses as well as unique abilities that take the game in different directions.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pocky &amp; Rocky 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pop'n TwinBee (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Pop'n TwinBee</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Another top-down shooter in the Twinbee "cute'em up" franchise. Heroes Light and Pastel decide to go out and help a young maiden bring sense back to her scientist father, who apparently has bumped his head and transformed into a evil mastermind that seeks world domination. As the other games in the series Pop'n Twinbee is a vertically-scrolling arcade shooter in which you and a friend get behind the controls of Twinbee and Winbee, the cutest starfighters ever created, and try to clear stage after stage of enemies with your weapons.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pop'n TwinBee (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pop'n TwinBee (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pop'n TwinBee - Rainbow Bell Adventures (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Pop'n TwinBee: Rainbow Bell Adventures</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play as either Twinbee, Gwinbee or Winbee. Cooperative play is also available. In this mode the second player takes control over one of the two characters left. Either way your task is to find and defeat the evil Dr. Warmon who tries to enslave the islands of Dunburi. To deal with the many villains Dr. Warmon throws at you, you need to collect colored bells. Depending on the color of the bell you can use different attacks like a laser (blue bells) or a lash (orange bells). But even without the bells you're not defenseless. Your standard-attacks include a shock wave and the ability to fly.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pop'n TwinBee - Rainbow Bell Adventures (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pop'n TwinBee - Rainbow Bell Adventures (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Populous (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Populous</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play a god, gaming against other gods in a celestial game of conquest. To win, you must help your chosen people take over the world and wipe out the vermin who worship that other god. Each god starts out with a single human, dumped into the middle of the wilderness. Sometimes there is inhabitable land in sight, sometimes not. To get win, you must change the landscape, creating flat land for your followers to build on. The more followers you have you have, the more powerful you will be, so take care of them. Build as fast as you can, because the other god is doing the same. When you have enough followers, you can make the leader of your people into a hero.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19910902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Populous (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Populous (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Primal Rage (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Primal Rage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A meteor struck the Earth, and caused great chaos. Seven gods from ancient times awoke, and are now attempting to take control of the post-apocalyptic world.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bitmasters</developer>
		<publisher>Time Warner Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Primal Rage (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Primal Rage (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prince of Persia (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Prince of Persia</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Grand Vizier Jaffar has thrown you into a dark dungeon and plans to marry the girl of your dreams in an hour. You're not going to let that happen are you? Try to escape from the dungeon, take out Jaffar's guards, find your way through the Sultan's palace and defeat Jaffar himself. Now go, you've got 60 minutes! Prince of Persia is a 2D platformer with run and jump gameplay. Your hero must avoid deadly traps, solve some simple puzzles and engage in sword fights with the guards.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930422T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arsys</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Prince of Persia (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Prince of Persia (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type III (USA).zip</path>
		<name>R·Type III: The Third Lightning</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>UNDER A NEW BYDO THREAT, EARTH RETALIATES It was believed on Earth that the deadly BYDO Empire had been destroyed--but now they've returned, as nasty as ever. Their ships and armies are more powerful than before, and Earth will surely be conquered unless the new R-90 ship can destroy them. Powered with engines that launch it into different dimensions, and armed with the Round, Shadow, and Cyclone Forces, R-90 has what it takes to wipe out the BYDO threat. Then, the BYDO mother ship must be found and destroyed to entirely erase the species from our galaxy.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/R-Type III (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/R-Type III (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rock N' Roll Racing (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rock 'n Roll Racing</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Rock 'n Roll Racing is an arcade combat racing game. Combat plays a heavy role in the game, as each car has a frontal weapon, such as a laser or missile, and a drop weapon, such as spikes or mines. As you complete races, you get more money to upgrade your car. The soundtrack features "Born to Be Wild," "Bad to the Bone," "The Peter Gunn Theme," "Highway Star" and "Paranoid."</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon &amp; Synapse</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rock N' Roll Racing (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rock N' Roll Racing (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocky Rodent (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Rocky Rodent</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mafia member Don Garcia has kidnapped Melody, the daughter of the owner of the Rose Restaurant. Rocky Rodent agrees to rescue her in exchange for an all-you-can-eat meal. In order to find Melody, Rocky Rodent has to complete a number of fast-paced, side-scrolling platformer levels. While he can also defeat enemies by jumping on them, his most important weapons are four different hairstyles.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Rocky Rodent (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Rocky Rodent (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Run Saber (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Run Saber</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2998, the brilliant Dr. Bruford is experimenting with genetic structures and radiation. He hopes to create new functions in nature that will remove the pollution from the Earth before it is too late. Unfortunately Dr. Bruford's experiments go wrong and genetic monsters are unleashed upon the world. The only thing that can stop these creatures are Dr. Bruford's previous achievement: Genetically enhanced warriors known as the Run Sabers. Two of the Run Sabers, Sheena and Allen are ready to activate.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Horisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Run Saber (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Run Saber (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret of Evermore (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Secret of Evermore</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You start out as a nameless boy and his dog, literally from the town of Podunk. You chase the dog into an old abandoned mansion, where a scientist lived 30 years ago. Some of his equipment is still operational, and when your dog chews on it, you're both sent to the strange world of Evermore. Now you must try to get back. The action-RPG gameplay is very much like Secret of Mana, with a few key changes. Multiplayer is out. Rather than three characters, there are just the two. The equivalent of magic is alchemy, where each effect requires several base ingredients which you gather as you go along.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Secret of Evermore (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret of Evermore (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Secret of Mana (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Secret of Mana</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once upon a time, the power of Mana was used by all people and helped their civilization grow. But as evil forces took control of Mana Fortress, there was no way out but a war which destroyed the Mana-based civilization but eventually brought peace to people. The events of the past became but legends to the new generation of humans. But history repeats itself. One day, a young village boy finds a rusty sword stuck at the bottom of a river. He doesn't know this sword is the famous Mana sword, the one that won so many battles before. By drawing the sword out of the river bottom, the boy unwillingly summons hordes of monsters, and is expelled from his village.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931003T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Square</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<image>./boxart/Secret of Mana (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Secret of Mana (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowrun (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Shadowrun</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The SNES version of Shadowrun appeared earlier than the Genesis one, and it is an entirely different game, with different story and gameplay, although it is also based on a pen-and-paper RPG of the same name. Your hero, Jake, is attacked by assassins, and appears to be dead. However, a mysterious dog approaches his lifeless body, transforms into a woman, and casts a spell on him. After that Jake wakes up in the morgue. He doesn't know what happened to him, he doesn't even remember his own name.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Beam Software</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Shadowrun (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Shadowrun (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SimCity (USA).zip</path>
		<name>SimCity</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>SimCity sets you as the mayor of a new municipality, with the responsibility of building and maintaining a place where citizens can move to and work and be happy. The first task is to place essentials such as housing, transport links, schools, factories and shops.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maxis Software</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/SimCity (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SimCity (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Simpsons, The - Bart's Nightmare (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Simpsons: Bart's Nightmare, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Bart has to stay up late and write a paper for class tomorrow. For once, he is determined to get a good mark. However, very quickly, he falls asleep. Nightmare after nightmare haunt his subconscious, and it is up to you to get over each one, so that Bart will eventually wake up. From such dreams as being in an episode of Itchy &amp; Scratchy to swimming through his own bloodstream, this platformer offers a nice challenge through its many diverse levels.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Simpsons, The - Bart's Nightmare (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Simpsons, The - Bart's Nightmare (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Skyblazer (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Skyblazer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Arianna, a young sorceress, has been kidnapped by Ashura. Sky has pledged his life to rescuing her. Sky must venture through many colorful stages and nice background effects. Skyblazer is a blend of side-scrolling fighting with magical skills. Locating potions to recover energy and gaining magic points to thrash the enemies becomes a major part of the gameplay. Sky can also stick to and climb vertically up walls.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Skyblazer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Skyblazer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Blast Man II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Sonic Blast Man II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Heavy Blast Man is once again trying to take over the Earth. People are being turned into hideous monsters and being made to serve him. Sonic Blast Man returns along with some new friends, Sonia and Captain Choyear. Together, they battle Heavy Blast Man and his minions to save the Earth from destruction. You control one of three characters in this side-scroller, as you fight your way through various levels filled with enemies and bosses. Beat them up with the basic punches and kicks or use your super moves to get out of tight spots.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19940426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sonic Blast Man II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sonic Blast Man II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Soul Blazer (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Soul Blazer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You have been called by the Master to restore life to the Friel empire. The ruler, King Magridd, struck a deal with the evil Deathtoll - in exchange for the soul of one living being, Deathtoll will give him a piece of gold. Magridd's greed got the better of him, and, thinking of the millions of souls of every living creature around the world, readily agreed to the deal. But Magridd himself has since disappeared, and the the land is now devoid of life - instead only filled with Deathtoll's monstrous minions. Will you be able to save Friel's subjects from their horrible fate? Soul Blazer is an action RPG in the top-down style of The Legend of Zelda.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Soul Blazer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Soul Blazer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Space Megaforce (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Space Megaforce</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Compile's Aleste series lands on the SNES with the appropriately named Super Aleste. Taking the role of a lone starfighter pilot, you are tasked with destroying an evil alien armada in standard 2D shooter fashion. And while you may be alone, you certainly won't be underpowered, with eight different types of weapons, each having six power-up levels for a grand total of 48 firing modes (not counting bomb power-ups) Super Aleste boasts one of the largest arsenals in 2D shooter history.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19921202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toho Company</developer>
		<publisher>Compile</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Space Megaforce (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Space Megaforce (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sparkster (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Sparkster</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Sparkster is a 2D side-scrolling platformer starring the eponymous hero who previously appeared in Rocket Knight Adventures. It is very different from the contemporary Genesis title Sparkster, as it does not continue the story from the first game and has completely different levels, enemies and gameplay mechanics. In that way it can be considered a spin-off in the series. The introduction merely shows how an elderly man captures a girl and takes her into his airship. At that point Sparkster appears and he decides to chase them.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sparkster (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sparkster (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man - Venom - Maximum Carnage (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Spider-Man and Venom: Maximum Carnage</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Loosely based on the comic book series, the story opens as Carnage breaks out of the insane asylum and wreaks mayhem. Spiderman immediately acknowledges the new job at hand and sets out to stop him. You start off with Spidey but in certain parts you get to choose between him and Venom, which takes you through an alternate routes. The gameplay is your standard beat-em-up, the regular punching and jump-kicking, with the addition of the all important webbing - ie web swinging, web shield etc.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940902T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>LJN</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spider-Man - Venom - Maximum Carnage (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spider-Man - Venom - Maximum Carnage (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spindizzy Worlds (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Spindizzy Worlds</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>On it's most basic level, Spindizzy Worlds is, like its predecessor, similar to Marble Madness. Controlling GERALD, you must move through the isometrically viewed landscape (largely flick-screen on the ST). There are two skill levels; the harder one features more of the precarious ledges and falls of Spindizzy. Each one takes you to a different matrix of levels, which can be played in different orders and each consist of 10 screens, with a bonus level at the end.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>ASCII Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spindizzy Worlds (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spindizzy Worlds (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox (USA) (Rev 2).zip</path>
		<name>Star Fox</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the first SNES title using the Super FX chip; you are flying ace Fox McCloud, who with his trusted wingmen and his powerful Arwing starfighter, must rid the Lylat System of the evil that surrounds it.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Fox (USA) (Rev 2).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Fox (USA) (Rev 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Star Fox 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>After his defeat in the original Star Fox, the game's antagonist, Andross, returns to the Lylat system and launches an all-out attack against Corneria, using his new fleet of battleships and giant missiles launched from hidden bases to destroy the planet. General Pepper again calls upon the Star Fox team for help. Armed with new custom Arwings, a Mothership, and two new recruits (Miyu, a lynx, and Fay, a dog), the Star Fox team sets out to defend Corneria by destroying Andross's forces before they can inflict critical damage on the planet.</desc>
		<rating>0</rating>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Star Fox 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Star Fox 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II: The World Warrior</name>
		<sortname>Street Fighter 1</sortname>
		<desc>The original Street Fighter II is a famous fighting game. Players select from one of eight characters: Ryu, Ken, Blanka, E. Honda, Zangief, Chun Li, Guile and Dhalsim to do battle with. They must then use their combat strengths to defeat the other seven fighters followed by four boss characters: M. Bison, Vega, Sagat and Balrog. Each character represents a certain country and has their own reasons for wanting to win against the others.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920610T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II Turbo (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II Turbo: Hyper Fighting</name>
		<sortname>Street Fighter 2</sortname>
		<desc>Choose from twelve street fighters from around the world, skilled in a variety of martial arts -- for instance, a character named E.Honda is a sumo wrestler from Japan, while Ken is a master of Tae Kwon Do from the United States. Journey to different countries to defeat other fighters, eventually leading up to a battle with evil man M.Bison. Besides the standard punches and kicks, each character can also execute special moves, such as energy projectiles or lightning-fast kicks, for more damage or to create a chain of hit combos.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter II Turbo (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter II Turbo (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Street Fighter II (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Street Fighter II: The New Challengers</name>
		<sortname>Street Fighter 3</sortname>
		<desc>This is the sequel to the super hit Street Fighter II Turbo and Street Fighter II Championship games for the SNES and Genesis. This port of the arcade game featured all 4 new characters and stages making a total of 16 playable. The game was packed into massive 32Meg and 40Meg cartridges for the SNES and Genesis. Featured many multiplayer modes in addition to the single player mode. There was the returning elimination group battle where you and a group of people played until one person was the champ. The Point Battle where the person with the most points wins. Newer modes included Tournament where you had an 8 man double elimination tournament.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930911T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Street Fighter II (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Street Fighter II (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Street Fighter Alpha 2</name>
		<sortname>Street Fighter 4</sortname>
		<desc>Another Street Fighter sequel (this time for Street Fighter Alpha) adds even more to the classic fighting series. New characters in this version include Gen (a wise kung-fu master), Rolento (who you may remember from another Capcom classic, Final Fight) and Sakura, a young school girl who follows her hero Ryu so close, she has the same type of moves. Dhalsim and Zangief also return to the fight with some news moves. The other major difference is the loss of chain-combos and the gain of a custom combo system. Once you reach the required level (which is 1 at the least) you can execute a custom combo by combining any of the buttons (which there are 6 in total) or any of the special attacks (fireballs, etc.)</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19961101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Fighter Alpha 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Racer (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Street Racer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Street Racer is a kart racing game similar to Super Mario Kart. Up to four players can play by split-screen. If there are no human opponents, the player can drive against seven computer opponents in three leagues. If the player wins the first league, they can play the second and so on. The game has eight different vehicles with different skills in speed, haste or resistance. There are also some power-ups on the tracks such as bombs, nitro fuel, and health packs.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vivid Image</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Street Racer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Street Racer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stunt Race FX (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Stunt Race FX</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Thanks to an improved version of the SuperFX Chip, Stunt Race FX was the first racing game for the SNES to feature fully polygonal cars and levels, which made it possible for the game to include gradients and obstacles that could not be realized in earlier, "flat" racing games.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Stunt Race FX (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Stunt Race FX (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sunset Riders (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Sunset Riders</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game, which is set in a fanciful version of the American Old West, revolves around four bounty hunters named Steve, Billy Cool, Bob, and Cormano Wild, who are out to claim rewards offered for eliminating the most wanted outlaws in the West. At the beginning of each stage, the players are shown a wanted poster for the outlaw they will face at its end.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Sunset Riders (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Sunset Riders (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Adventure Island (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Adventure Island</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You are a caveman named Master Higgins. You have a beautiful girlfriend, and you like spending time sunbathing together on high trees and other places on the tropic island Waku-Waku. But all of a sudden, an evil magician turns your wife into a stone! As you begin to realize what happened, a bird grasps you and throws down somewhere on the island. You have to find your way back and to save your girl from the grim reality of petrification.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Adventure Island (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Adventure Island (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Adventure Island II (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Adventure Island II</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Master Higgins finally marries his lovely girlfriend Tina. But out of nowhere, a powerful tropical cyclone destroyed the idyllic mood of their honeymoon. And not only this: it separated the ardent lovers again. After the winds stopped blowing, Tina found herself somewhere on a tropical coast. As for Master Higgins, he went to the king of Waku-Waku and, along with his main quest to save his brand new wife, got an assignment to save also a princess, whom the king was about to marry. Is there a connection between those two events?.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Adventure Island II (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Adventure Island II (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomberman</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Bomberman is the first Bomberman game on the Super NES. Like most games in the Bomberman series, Super Bomberman features a normal game as well as the famous battle mode. In the normal game, Mr. Karat and Dr. Mukk have been terrorizing Diamond City. You must go from board to board, defeating the bad guys and solving puzzles to move to the next board. In battle mode, up to four players go head to head in a battle to the death. Players can be computer controlled or human controlled via the Super MultiTap.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Bomberman (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Bomberman (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomberman 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is the second game in the Bomberman series for the Super Nintendo. This game is much like the first in gameplay but has new levels and a new story to play though. The graphics are slightly different from the first game but in general the game holds most of the same style as the first. There are a few new features such as colour coded bomb blasts and a few different powerups but other than that the second game is the same as the first.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Bomberman 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Bomberman 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bonk (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bonk</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Bonk allows Bonk to travel through time from his prehistoric levels, the insides of a dinosaur, a version of modern Chinatown, and even the moon! Along the way, Bonk can find power-ups that can change his form to creatures such as a shooting Bonk crab, a dinosaur form called "Big Kronk", find candies that change his size from tiny to huge, travel through transportation tubes, and find multiple bonus levels. Bonk still uses his head to smash his enemies, propeller seeds that allow Bonk to fly, and for the first time, can carry spring flowers on his head in his continuing battle against his arch nemesis, King Drool!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Bonk (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Bonk (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Castlevania IV (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Castlevania IV</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Simon Belmont returns in the first Castlevania title to grace the SNES. The console may be different, but the setup is very familiar: The place is Transylvania. The villain is Count Dracula. Belmont has the classic Castlevania assortment of weapons (the famous whip, daggers, axes, fire bombs, boomerangs) at his disposal, and he gains strength and points by collecting various-sized hearts, coin purses, and pork chops. Like most Castlevania games, Super Castlevania IV is a 2D side-scrolling action game. However, it is 2D with more depth than ever before. Parallax scrolling and rotating chambers are some of the "Mode 7" effects made possible by the SNES hardware.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Castlevania IV (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Castlevania IV (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Double Dragon (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Double Dragon</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Billy and Jimmy Lee return for another adventure. This time, fellow martial arts instructor and narcotics investigator, Marian, has disappeared while attempting to infiltrate the ruthless criminal mob known as the Black Shadow Warriors. Once again it is up to you (and a friend) to battle your way through a selection of side-scrolling beat 'em up levels to defeat the Shadow Warriors and their leader Duke, and save Marian.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tradewest</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Double Dragon (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Double Dragon (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super_Ghoulsn_Ghosts_USA_-_Restoration.sfc</path>
		<name>Super Ghouls'n Ghosts</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>4 years after Arthur saved Princess PrinPrin from the evil demon Loki, a wonderful celebration is about to take place! Arthur and the Princess are engaged, and the wedding is to take place at last! Thousands from around the kingdom have come to witness this joyous event! But somewhere in the darkness of the forest lurks a horrible evil. Arthur and PrinPrin are spending a quiet moment locked in embrace, when she is suddenly snatched away by a huge demon! As her screams echo through the night, Arthur rushes from the castle, and pursues the demon to the graveyard, where he is greeted by hundreds of horrible ghouls and monsters! Now, this time, they've gone too far, Arthur is ready for them.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super_Ghoulsn_Ghosts_USA_-_Restoration.jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super_Ghoulsn_Ghosts_USA_-_Restoration.mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario All-Stars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario All-Stars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Mario All-Stars is a collection of previously released Super Mario NES platform games. Each title is presented with its original gameplay and level design, but has been given a makeover in the graphics and sound department. A save option has been added allowing players to store the session data.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario All-Stars (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario All-Stars (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario All-Stars + Super Mario World (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario All-Stars + Super Mario World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Put quite simply, this is the amalgamation of the previously released Super Mario All-Stars compilation with Super Mario World added. While games already in the All-Stars bundle have major graphical and audio improvements, the only change made to Super Mario World is a slight tweak of Luigi's graphic sprites, making him slightly thinner and taller (rather than being the same height and stature of Mario) which does not affect gameplay.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario All-Stars + Super Mario World (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario All-Stars + Super Mario World (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Kart (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario Kart</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A collection of Super Mario characters, including Mario, Luigi, Yoshi, Peach, Bowser and Donkey Kong Jr., are out to win the Super Mario Kart championship. Using Mode 7 scaling, the first true kart game on the SNES has you collecting coins to boost your speed while using shells and bananas to stop others on the track. There are 4 cups in all to race for, Mushroom Cup, Flower Cup, Star Cup and Special Cup, each with a selection of tracks to race on (based in Bowser's Castle, Super Mario World and more). Plus, a 2 player battle mode is on offer, where the first to pop the three balloons wins.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario Kart (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario Kart (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game starts off like almost every other Mario game, with Bowser kidnapping Princess Toadstool. However, when Mario goes to Bowser's Keep to save her, a giant sword made by the evil Smithy crashes into the castle and sends Mario, the Princess, and Bowser flying to separate parts of the world.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19960513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario World (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once again, the evil Bowser has captured Princess Peach (while on a holiday on Yoshi's Island), and it's up to Mario to save her. To aid him in his quest, Mario must use the flying ability of the feather to get him to places hard to reach. But what's even more important is his new friend, the dinosaur Yoshi, who Mario can ride through each level and eat the enemies. Over 90 levels are on offer.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19910813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario World (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario World (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA, Asia) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The events of Yoshi's Island take place in the past. Mario was one of two twin brothers whom the evil Magikoopa Kamek tried to kidnap. Kamek kidnapped one of the brothers, but the second, Mario, fell down on Yoshi's island, where Yoshis live. The Yoshis decided to carry baby Mario and to bring him to his parents. But Kamek has sent troops and hordes of monsters to stop the Yoshis and to kidnap Mario.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19951004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA, Asia) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA, Asia) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Metroid (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).zip</path>
		<name>Super Metroid</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Metroid is a follow-up to Metroid II, and once again features bounty hunter Samus Aran. She heads to planet Zebes in order to hunt down the leaders of the Space Pirates, who kidnapped an unique Metroid larva. Super Metroid is a platform game, which, like the previous Metroid games, is not divided into separate levels; the planet Zebes is an open world which Samus traverses back and forth. This world is divided into rooms separated with doors which must be shot to be opened. Shooting is also used to open up secret passages, some of which contain nifty bonuses, but finding most of them is required to proceed in the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Metroid (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Metroid (Japan, USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Ninja Boy (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Ninja Boy</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>One day a spaceship came down from the heavens and into the skies of Chinaland. It began broadcasting an image of peace. Soon Emperor Chin was holding a peace conference with the space ship's leader, Rub-A-Doc. Rub-A-Doc visited with some of the other places in the world before departing to the heavens and leaving the world. All seemed peaceful however there seems to be trouble starting up, strange monsters have been seen throughout Chinaland. Could the increase in monsters be somehow related to the recent visit from Rub-A-Doc? The ninja masters of Mount Edin, Jack and Ryu are sent to investigate.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Culture Brain</developer>
		<publisher>Culture Brain</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Ninja Boy (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Ninja Boy (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Punch-Out!! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Punch-Out!!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Your dreams are finally going to come true! All the years of training, all for that day where you'd finally step into the ring, amidst the roar of the excited crowd, to square off against the best of the best, you tighten your fist and hear your gloves tighten with them you take a step foward the door opens before you and the boxing ring beckons your name! 16 world champs are here, with the same dream as you: to win the WVBA Championship! Welcome to the world of boxing, kid! Give 'em an uppercut or two for your fans!</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Punch-Out!! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Punch-Out!! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash T.V. (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Smash T.V.</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The year is 1999. The world's most popular television show is Smash T.V., an ultra-violent contest between two armed-to-the-teeth combatants, set loose in a series of deadly arenas that are filled to bursting with hordes of mindless beasts and killer robots. The aim of the game is to blast everything in sight and try to grab more cash and prizes than the other guy. Toaster ovens, VCRs, fancy cars and luxury holidays are there for the taking for anyone who can survive long enough to enjoy them.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19920201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Smash T.V. (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Smash T.V. (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Soccer (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Soccer</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Let's play soccer - the world's favorite sport! In Super Soccer you can choose between an Exhibition mode and a Tournament mode. While the first mode lasts a single game only the Tournament mode challenges you with 16 consecutive games, facing the Nintendo Allstar Team in the final round. The field is shown in a top-down perspective. Scrolling is done by Mode 7 chip. Difficulty varies with the opponent team, ranging from easy to hard in later games in the tournament. After winning a match in the tournament mode, you will be rewarded witch a code in order to pick up the game in the same round of the tournament later on.</desc>
		<rating>0.55</rating>
		<releasedate>19920501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Soccer (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Soccer (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Star Wars (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Star Wars</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The story of this game is based on Episode IV: A New Hope, the first of the original Star Wars movie trilogy. The player initially controls the movie's main hero, Luke Skywalker, but two more controllable characters join later: the careless captain Han Solo and his Wookie side-kick, Chewbacca. The game generally follows the movie plot, allowing the player to experience some of the most important sequences, such as the search for Obi-Wan Kenobi, rescuing princess Leia, and the final confrontation against Death Star and its TIE Fighters, led by the mysterious Darth Vader.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Star Wars (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Star Wars (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Star Wars: Return of the Jedi</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You select your character from the movie (Luke Skywalker, Han Solo, Princess Leia, or Chewbacca) before each level, as each one has different abilities, and go try to beat levels based on the movie's scenes brandishing lightsabers, blasters or crossbows, etc. depending on your choice of character. Gameplay consists of standard platform action spiced up with some slightly different (gameplay-wise) sequences. Race to Jabba the Hutt's palace in a speeder, fight your way through Jabba the Hutt's minions before killing Jabba himself, control speeder bikes and the Millennium Falcon, and much more.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Star Wars - Return of the Jedi (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Super Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The sequel to Super Star Wars is, as the name implies, based on Episode V: The Empire Strikes Back, the second of the original Star Wars movie trilogy. The game features familiar locations and events from the film, such as the ice planet Hoth, the search for Yoda on the jungle planet Dagobah, and the fight against Darth Vader. Several locations are expanded, adding places and boss enemies that did not exist in the movie, and certain key events in the story are omitted or changed. As in the previous game, the player is able to control three characters: Luke Skywalker, Han Solo, and Chewbacca.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>JVC</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Star Wars - The Empire Strikes Back (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Tennis (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Tennis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The world circuit of tennis awaits you. Select from 20 male and female players, each with their own style of game play (strengths and weaknesses) and play singles, doubles either against or with a human opponent or a CPU controlled player(s) on all the major surfaces (clay, grass &amp; hardcourt). The circuit mode is the meat of the game. Here, using a password save system, you play a selection of tournaments all around the world. The more games you play and win, the more points you receive. These points go towards your rank in the world tour rankings. There are 4 major tournaments (as in real life) and many minor tournaments to play.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19911101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tokyo Shoseki</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Tennis (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Tennis (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Turrican (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Turrican</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Turrican is the next generation installment of the famous Turrican Series. Once again it is up to the U.S.S. Freedom Forces to get into their Turrican Assault Suits and drive back the forces of "The Machine". Similar to it's predecessors, Super Turican features large levels that are crammed with secrets and can be explored freely and in any direction.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Turrican (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Turrican (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Turrican 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Turrican 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Super Turrican is back, and once again the USS Freedom Forces have to prevent the evil Machine from harming innocent civilizations. This requires the player to jump and shoot his way through large levels filled with lots of enemies. To get rid of all the enemies, several different weapons can be used, most of which are already familiar to players from previous installments of the series: a Laser, a Spread-shot, and a(improved) Rebound. There is also the option to go into "wheel-mode" for a limited time to become invincible, lay mines and shoot rockets. The Flamethrower is new to the series as well as the Rope, which can be used to climb walls, cling to platforms or pick up out-of-reach items.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Turrican 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Turrican 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Super Bowl</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Tecmo returns to the gridiron with this new version of Tecmo Super Bowl for 16-bit console systems. Play with real National Football League players and teams in this 2D, side-scrolling arcade game. All of the features from the 8-bit game remain intact, with brand new ones added for even more electronic football fun! Additions include updated player rosters, options for weather effects (rain, snow), multiple season play (three regular season schedules available in all), adjustable game time length, and an offensive playbook that can be edited even during a game.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19931101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tecmo Super Bowl (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tecmo Super Bowl III - Final Edition (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tecmo Super Bowl III: Final Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A late entry in what was once the premiere football simulation, TSB III has updated rosters and teams for the 1994-1995 season and is licensed by both the NFL and the Players group. Features real NFLP players and photos, the real NFL schedule, and weekly standings. You can change defensive and offensive formations, create your own Pro Bowl, fake punts and field goals, go for the two point conversion, and call audibles. Updates to the game itself include new cinema screens, superstar mode, free agency system, improved graphics, larger field simulation, passing modes, and improved speech and music. Horizontal scrolling. Also features battery back-up.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tecmo Super Bowl III - Final Edition (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tecmo Super Bowl III - Final Edition (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV: Turtles in Time</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Doesn't this Shredder dude ever take a break? Now he's gone and kidnapped Channel 6's own reporter babe April O' Neill again, and just as the Ninja Turtles were about to kick his butt, he tore open some kinda time portal thingy and flung them back into the past! Now Leonardo, Raphael, Donatello, and Michaelangelo have to fight their way through time and tons of Foot Soldiers, mutant wackos, and more in order to save April and slam Shredder's butt all the way to Dimension X! Go, Turtles! Kick some shell and save April!</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles IV - Turtles in Time (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Tournament Fighters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The game features the original 4 turtles from the previous games in the series, as well as other fighters. The game is very much in the tradition of the Mortal Kombat or Street Fighter series, pitting you against opponents one at a time. Some fighters (besides the turtles) will be familiar, such as the Rat King, or even Shredder (now called "Cyber-Shredder" here).</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles - Tournament Fighters (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Terranigma (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Terranigma</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In "Terranigma", you play a young boy named Ark. He has grown up in his little village, isolated from the outer world by a stream of lava, and has never seen anything else beside it. One day, he and some other boys hear mysterious voices coming from beyond a door the village elder forbade them to open. Unable to resist their curiosity, the boys open the door, and Ark finds a box with a strange creature inside. By opening the box, Ark damages the balance between two co-existing worlds, and all the village people are turned into stones.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19961219T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Terranigma (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Terranigma (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Two of the most popular puzzle games return, but now together in an exclusive compilation for SNES. The games have a slight graphical update when compared with the original Game Boy and NES games, but the gameplay remains totally faithful to the games released for both platforms. In Tetris, the main objective is to pile blocks that will fall down continuously, in order to create a row or "line" without spaces. For this collection, the game comes with two bonus options: 2 PLAYER GAME (absent in the NES version) and VS. COM (absent in both versions), with 3 CPU opponents available, each one representing a difficulty level (EASY, MEDIUM, and HARD, respectively).</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tetris &amp; Dr. Mario (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Attack (USA) (En,Ja).zip</path>
		<name>Tetris Attack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>All is not well on Yoshi's Island! The devious king Bowser has cast a spell on the island's inhabitants, turning them into his mindless slaves. Only Yoshi has escaped its effects, and so he must set off to free his friends, and to defeat Bowser and break the spell. Tetris Attack is a fact-paced action puzzler featuring the colorful cast of characters from Yoshi's Island. A stack of blocks continually rises from the bottom of the screen, and the player controls a cursor which can swap any two blocks horizontally. Make a row or column of three or more and they'll clear, potentially creating combos from new blocks falling to take their place.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19960801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tetris Attack (USA) (En,Ja).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tetris Attack (USA) (En,Ja).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Venture back to Hyrule and an age of magic and heroes. The predecessors of Link and Zelda face monsters on the march when a menacing magician takes over the kingdom. Only you can prevent his evil plot from shattering the land of Hyrule. In your quest, you'll venture into twisting mazes, dungeons, palaces and shadowy forests. Test your mettle with mighty swords and magical weapons. Or heft a boulder and hurl it at your enemies. If the going gets tough, dive into a river - you can swim to escape! Learn the powerful spells, locate magical artifacts and solve the mysteries of the evil magician and the hidden realm of Hyrule.</desc>
		<rating>0.95</rating>
		<releasedate>19920413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Theme Park (Europe) (En,Fr,De).zip</path>
		<name>Theme Park</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Dominating the exciting world of Theme Park ownership is your goal in this strategy game from Bullfrog. The first task is to set up your rides within the available land, structuring convenient paths and queues and ideally leaving some space for bigger rides once they become available, and include some lakes and trees to increase the park's allure. Rides range from Teacups and Haunted Houses to the biggest most elaborate roller-coaster you can design, and water rides that loop around other rides.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19961111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bullfrog</developer>
		<publisher>Bullfrog</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Theme Park (Europe) (En,Fr,De).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Theme Park (Europe) (En,Fr,De).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose! (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Tiny Toon Adventures: Buster Busts Loose!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>You play Buster Bunny, in a series of levels, featuring characters from the Tiny Toon Adventures cartoon. Most of the six levels are platform levels, where Buster has a number of attacks to defeat the enemies he faces. These include kicks and jumps, and a dash ability that lets you slide into enemies to defeat them, and also climb walls. The fourth level is an exception, and consists of a game of (American) football, played with a simplified version of the rules.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19930801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose! (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Tiny Toon Adventures - Buster Busts Loose! (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Top Gear (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Top Gear</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the first of three released games for Super NES, players can choose among 4 different cars, each one with different attributes (maximum speed, fuel consumption, boost power and tire grip) to face 32 challenging courses situated in several places around the world as Brazil, USA, France, Japan etc. In more longer tracks, players will find a Pit Stop section, where they can enter to replenish the fuel meter (total or partially).</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19920401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kemco</developer>
		<publisher>Gremlin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Top Gear (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Top Gear (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Paint (Japan, USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mario Paint</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Mario Paint is an education tool that allows anyone to create simple pictures, paint over black and white pictures, or free draw their own, using the specially developed SNES Mouse. You can also create your own piece of music using a selection of notes and themes, create greeting cards and animations, or play a game of "Gnat Attack", where you use the mouse to control a swatter to swat the many flies.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mario Paint (Japan, USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mario Paint (Japan, USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Five Hundred years ago, an ancient and well respected Shaolin fighting tournament, held every 50 years, was corrupted by an evil and elderly sorcerer by the name of Shang Tsung. Shang was accompanied by Prince Goro, a warrior of the Shokan race (a four armed half-human/half-dragon). Knowing that if ten tournaments in a row were won by the Outworld champion, the Earth Realm would be conquered by evil and fall into darkness, Shang entered Goro in the tournament and had him defeat the great Kung Lao.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930913T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mortal Kombat (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mortal Kombat (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat II (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat II</name>
		<sortname>Mortal Kombat 2</sortname>
		<desc>The Mortal Kombat fighters, plus several new ones, return for a tournament held by the evil Shang Tsung of the Outworld. The action is one-on-one as before, and famed for its high level of violence and blood (other than the sanitised Nintendo version). There are 5 difficulty levels and optional credits, as well as the usual two player mode including same character duels.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mortal Kombat II (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mortal Kombat II (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Shao Kahn has won. The Earthrealm is no more. In order to revive his Queen Sindel, the emperor Shao Kahn used the Outworld Tournament from Mortal Kombat 2 as a diversion while his Shadow Priests revive his fallen Queen on Earth. Once enacted, the dimensional bridge between the two realms connects, allowing Kahn's extermination squads to invade and destroy Earth, and enslave the population's souls.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat 3, Ultimate</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 combines the best of all the Mortal Kombats into a single cartridge. 23 playable characters are immediately available, such as Reptile, Cyrax, Scorpion, Sub-Zero, Jax, Katana, Sonya, and more. There are two bosses that are unlockable, as well as additional characters. There is a variety of new levels, some of which are interactive. Characters can uppercut someone, causing them to hit the ground hard and crash through to the bottom floor, or they can knocked someone off a bridge, landing in a pit of spikes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19961001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Ultimate Mortal Kombat 3 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Championship Soccer '94 (USA) (En,Fr,De,It).zip</path>
		<name>Championship Soccer '94</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>It's addictive! No other soccer game compares. Created for hardcore soccer fans, Championship Soccer '94 delivers the ultimate in speed, game control and ultra-realistic gameplay. It's the perfect soccer game for players who demand an unbeatable combination of strategy and action. Take charge of one of 100 European club or national teams from around the world. Superb gameplay featuring unique after-touch control of height and curve of ball.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Renegade Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sensible Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Championship Soccer '94 (USA) (En,Fr,De,It).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Championship Soccer '94 (USA) (En,Fr,De,It).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Choplifter III - Rescue-Survive (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Choplifter III: Rescue-Survive</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Choplifter III for the SNES features entirely different levels from the Game Gear and GameBoy versions, and plays slightly different than other Choplifter games. While the controls and basic gameplay haven't changed significantly, and the main goal of each level is still rescuing a certain number of hostages, Choplifter III is faster and more action-oriented than earlier Choplifter games.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19940808T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Beam Software</publisher>
		<genre>Shoot'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Choplifter III - Rescue-Survive (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Choplifter III - Rescue-Survive (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Desert Strike - Return to the Gulf (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Desert Strike: Return to the Gulf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The first game in the Strike series. A year after the Gulf War, a self styled General named Kilbaba (Muababa in the GBA version) takes over an Arab Emirate and threatens to start WWIII against its enemy in the West, the U.S. The whole world holds their breath as the President chooses you to destroy Kilbaba and his terrorist army before he launches a nuclear attack on the world!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Desert Strike - Return to the Gulf (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Desert Strike - Return to the Gulf (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Earthworm Jim (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Earthworm Jim</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>A crow is chasing a worm named Jim while in outer space Psy-Crow is chasing a renegade ship. The ship's captain has stolen an ultra-high-tech-indestructible-super-space-cyber-suit and Queen Slug-for-a-Butt has ordered Psy-Crow to get it, since it can make her more beautiful than Princess-What's-Her-Name. Psy-Crow blasts the captain and the suit falls to Planet Earth. Back on earth Jim wonders if he is finally safe when an ultra-high-tech-indestructible-super-space-cyber-suit lands on him. Luckily Jim rests in the neck ring of the suit. Then the space particles begin interacting with Jim, causing a light-speed evolution. Jim soon realizes he is in control of the suit.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shiny Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Earthworm Jim (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Earthworm Jim (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jungle Strike (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Jungle Strike: The Sequel to Desert Strike</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Some time after Operation Desert Strike, Ibn Kilbaba, son of Kilbaba S.R, threatens to annihilate America. After his father was killed, the people who were under his control, sent his son running off, along with his father's money and nuclear weapons program. Kilbaba, more ruthless than his father, longs for revenge of his father's death and decides to shed the blood of those who killed him, the Americans. Already armed, Kilbaba hires Carlos Ortega to help him set up his Nuclear Weapons program, deep in South America. Carlos Ortega, the world's most notorious druglord, also yearns to seek revenge. With his own private army, armed with the most hi-tech weapons, he's ready to fight America at all costs.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Score Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Jungle Strike (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Jungle Strike (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lost Vikings, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Lost Vikings, The</name>
		<sortname>Lost Vikings 1</sortname>
		<desc>Three Vikings, Eric the Swift, Olaf the Stout and Baleog the Fierce, were kidnapped by the alien Tomator, the evil Croutonian ruler, who is collecting unique life forms to display in his gallery. The three Vikings will have to combine their unique skills to defeat Tomator, as well as a vast array of aliens, robots, giant snails, big lizards and more.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19930402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Silicon &amp; Synapse</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lost Vikings, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lost Vikings, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lucky Luke (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Lucky Luke</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the game you as Lucky Luke have to arrest four Dalton brothers – Averell, William, Jack, and Joe. On your mission you will progress from level to level shooting bad cowboys, jail-breakers, and bad Indians with your revolver; collecting bullets, dynamites, sheriff stars, and other useful items; running, jumping, ducking, and climbing. The locations vary from Forts, Towns, and Jails to Mines, Train, and Saloon with Ghosts. On every level you have to complete different submissions to progress – either to free a Bank Director, or to collect Three Nuggets for Miner to obtain a Nitroglycerine, or to build a Totem for Apaches, etc.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Lucky Luke (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Lucky Luke (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Disney's Donald Duck takes the starring role in this sidescrolling platform game. As the detective Maui Mallard, he's on the trail of a long lost Idol, which has recently vanished. Early on, Maui can also switch between his normal self and Ninja Maui, and with all the creepy voodoo enemies he'll encounter throughout his adventure, he's going to need all the help he can get.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Eurocom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Maui Mallard in Cold Shadow (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NBA JAM: Tournament Edition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game lets you play two-on-two arcade basketball with players from all the NBA teams. Gameplay is fast and action-packed, with few rules, no fouls, and deliberately unrealistic jamming. Players are rated on eight ability categories, from steals and blocks, to dunks and 3-pointers. Up to four human players can take part, each always controlling a single player for their team, and AI for missing players. This allows for four players to face each other in teams of two, or for two players to team up against a third player with a CPU team-mate.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19950223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA Jam - Tournament Edition (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Live 96 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>NBA Live 96</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As with all games in the NBA Live series you can draft, trade and edit players. Play a full season, exhibition or just the playoffs. 96 includes 29 teams including the expansion Toronto and Vancouver teams.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19951001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Sports</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA Live 96 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA Live 96 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Mario Land (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Land</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>New Super Mario Land is a new homebrew release that re-imagines Super Mario Land, the iconic Game Boy title, on the Super Nintendo. The game introduces a graphic style taken from the New Super Mario bros series from the Nintendo Wii. There's also detailed backgrounds with great parallax scrolling and reflecting water effects.</desc>
		<releasedate>20191121T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/New Super Mario Land (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/New Super Mario Land (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Side Pocket (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Side Pocket</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The main objective is to cross different USA cities and reach the predetermined scores to go ahead. But remember: you'll have only 16 balls and every error can be lethal! The game also comes with modes for 2 players with two variants: 2P Pocket Game (the traditional mode) and 2P 9-Ball Game, where the premise is to sink 9 balls before the other player makes them first. If you prefer, test your target in Trick Game or even hear your favorite song in Jukebox. After each stage completed (and some luck), a bonus stage will appear, as well as the chance to earn extra balls. You will only need a good target in the parquet block!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Data East</developer>
		<publisher>Data East</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Side Pocket (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Side Pocket (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Smash Tennis (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Smash Tennis</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The controls of Smash Tennis work similar to other tennis games and especially Namco's previous tennis game World Court Tennis: the player moves the athlete over the court and presses buttons with the correct timing in order to win the match. This time there is no story mode, but a tournament mode instead. Here the goal is to win the Grand Slam by playing various tournament matches. However. a match only has a single set. There are 20 athletes (both male and female) to choose from which have different advantages and drawbacks.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930625T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/Smash Tennis (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Smash Tennis (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SOS (USA).zip</path>
		<name>SOS</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The date is Tuesday, September 13th, 1921. It's a stormy night, and the luxury ocean liner "Lady Crithania" is about to be capsized by an enormous wave. Many of its crew and its 2300 passengers will be killed outright in the initial overturning; in the transfigured catastrophic ship environment, most of the remainder will be unable to locate, reach and secure a safe exit from the sinking ship before it floods entirely. Will you?</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19940402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human</developer>
		<publisher>Vic Tokai</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/SOS (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/SOS (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./2020 Super Baseball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Baseball 2020</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the year 2020, baseball finally evolved. There is no longer conventional professional baseball in 2020. Baseball designed by the Super Baseball Association has been very popular and is the best sport. However, the truth is that the association has used a colossal sum of money to promote Super Baseball as show business. They have manipulated each player's ability using the control computer to secretly decide victory or defeat in every game. The players who knew this removed the connecting parts of the computer to play their own game of baseball. Finally, a fair game is going to be played at Cyber Egg Stadium.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19930713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pallas</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/2020 Super Baseball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/2020 Super Baseball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Bomberman 3 (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Super Bomberman 3</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game was an overhaul of the entire system of bombermans from before. Again there are new levels and a new story but there are also a lot of new features. Super Bomberman 3 adds in 5 player support using a multitap and the extra controller slot. The "revenge" or "miso bomber" feature was introduced in this game. That is when a player dies they can still throw bombs in from the sidelines in an attempt to swap places with a player that is still alive. Many new powerups were added in this game including the Kangaroo which in addition to giving a player and extra hit allowed them to have some extra ablity including jumping, laying rows of bombs, and high speed running.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19951015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-5</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Bomberman 3 (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Bomberman 3 (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Horizons (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Uncharted Waters 2: New Horizons</name>
		<sortname>Uncharted Waters 2</sortname>
		<desc>In the first Uncharted Waters game, it was the 15th century and the New World was discovered. Now in New Horizons, it is the early 16th century and the age of exploration and sea trade is underway. Players choose from any one of six adventurers (scenarios), each with their own distinctive but intertwining plot, to embark on a quest of sailing, seamanship and exploration.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/New Horizons (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/New Horizons (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./WWF Raw (USA).zip</path>
		<name>WWF Raw</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>WWF Raw is a professional wrestling game featuring 10 superstars from the World Wrestling Federation. The wrestlers you can choose from include Bret "Hit Man" Hart, Bam Bam Bigelow, 1-2-3 Kid, Diesel, Doink, Lex Luger, Luna Vachon, Owen Hart, Razor Ramon, Shawn Michaels, Undertaker, and Yokozuna. In this game, you attempt to pin your opponent to the mat by reducing his power meter until he can fight no more. There is a large number of moves to perform, including turnbuckle maneuvers and "illegal" acts such as hitting your opponent with a metal folding chair.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LJN</developer>
		<publisher>Sculptured Software</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/WWF Raw (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/WWF Raw (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cannon Fodder (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Cannon Fodder</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Guide a team of up to four soldiers through 72 levels of combat in this innovative top-down action/strategy hybrid, best thought of as Lemmings crossed with Commando crossed with Dune 2. The characters are controlled indirectly using the mouse, as you activate each soldier or group of them by highlighting them, click the left button to move them to a particular spot, and the right button for them to fire guns at an enemy. You can also pick up grenades, which can be used to destroy groups of enemies or buildings (by pressing both buttons at once).</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sensible Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sensible Software</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Cannon Fodder (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Cannon Fodder (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Valis IV (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Super Valis IV</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Once upon a time, there was a prince named Gallagher. He was entrusted with a magical ring that granted him great powers. But he was too weak to control the power of the ring, and became possessed by it. The mad prince was sealed into a crystal, but many years later managed to break out, planning to wreak havoc on the Dream World and to conquer it! Yuko, the heroine of the three previous Valis games, is no longer a sacred Valis warrior - she has become a goddess. Lena, a young girl who wants to become a Valis warrior, is the new main character, who must prove to Yuko she is worthy to wield the sword of Valis, that will eventually stop the evil plans of Gallagher.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19930201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Telenet</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Super Valis IV (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Super Valis IV (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Batman Returns (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Batman Returns</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The successful movie sequel Batman Returns spawned many different game adaptations. The SNES version presents the story of Batman's encounter with the Penguin and Catwoman as a side-scrolling beat'em'up, with one Batmobile driving sequence thrown in. There are two varieties of the beat'em'up levels. One plays like Final Fight and similar games: Batman can move in two dimensions, beating up his enemies with various punches, kicks, combos and special moves.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19930402T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Batman Returns (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Batman Returns (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Blues Brothers, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Blues Brothers, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Jukebox Adventure is the sequel to The Blues Brothers. Once again, the player has to choose a favourite Blues Brother and take him through different side-scrolling platform levels. He needs to collect records and use them as defence by throwing them towards enemies. There are also power-ups that can be gathered until the jukebox to progress to the next level is found.</desc>
		<rating>0.4</rating>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Blues Brothers, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Blues Brothers, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's The Great Circus Mystery Staring Mickey &amp; Minnie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Starring Mickey and Minnie Mouse, the two plan to spend the day at the Circus only to find that it's deserted. Believing that someone is responsible, you must dress up in different outfits such as Safari and Western, as you try to find clues to solve the mystery behind the disappereance of the performers, including your pals Donald Duck and Pluto.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19941001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Great Circus Mystery Starring Mickey &amp; Minnie, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country (USA) (Rev 2).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>King K. Rool has stolen Donkey Kong's banana stash, and Donkey Kong needs your help to get them back. In search of K. Rool, the Kremling horde impedes your progress. Kremlings, crocodile-like creatures, include Kritters (they succumb to a simple jump on the head), Krushas (they are virtually indestructible), and others.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19941125T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong Country (USA) (Rev 2).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong Country (USA) (Rev 2).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA) (En,Fr).zip</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This time both Donkey Kong and Diddy Kong have been kong-napped by a mysterious new leader of the Kremlings, and it's up to Dixie and new team mate Kiddy Kong to save the day. New elements to the series includes the Brother Bears, thirteen Bears who, if you pay them with Bear Coins found in each level, will aid you in your quest by building certain items. Also, new bonus mission have you playing a 1st/3rd person shooter style party game. Plus a host of new enemies, the usual huge end of world bosses and a collection of the Kong family who will help you out as best they can.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19961122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rareware</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA) (En,Fr).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA) (En,Fr).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Movie (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers: The Movie</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This game is loosely based off of the movie of the same name, where the player can take control of either the Yellow, Black, Pink, Blue, Red or White Ranger in a side-scrolling beat-em-up in an attempt to stop the evil Ivan Ooze who is trying to control the universe.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19950601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Movie (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers - The Movie (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Mighty Morphin Power Rangers</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>This is a one-on-one fighting game for one or two players. Single players pick a Ranger (Red, Pink, Blue, Yellow, Black, or the unlockable Green) and take him or her through a series of battles against Rita's monsters. After one normal battle, the monster grows very large, and then it is time to take out the MegaZord.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Beat'em up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Mighty Morphin Power Rangers (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MLBPA Baseball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>MLBPA Baseball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The strategy of baseball is merged with a fast-paced arcade game in MLBPA Baseball from Electronic Arts. Details designed to appeal to the die-hard fan include: real players with statistics based on the 1993 season; a full 162 game season mode; stadium music; animated scoreboards; defensive alignments; cut-off plays; run-downs; and even the double switch. Features meant to appeal to the casual fan include: large colorful arcade graphics; one stadium with animated crowds; a simplified pitching interface allowing players to steer the ball; and a batting interface that relies on timing instead of aiming cursors.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19940302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
		<publisher>EA Sports</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/MLBPA Baseball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/MLBPA Baseball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nightmare Busters (USA) (Unl).zip</path>
		<name>Nightmare Busters</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Synchronized with the wavelengh of dreams, the miserable Tyrant has discovered a way to enter them and convolute what children see, hear and feel while they sleep - all for the benefit of his twisted amusement. Enter Flynn and his twin brother Floyd, two virtuous leprechauns who refuse to sit idly by while the Tyrant weaves his dreadful delusions. Get going, gents! There's no time to lose!</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20131223T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arcade Zone</developer>
		<publisher>Nichibutsu</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nightmare Busters (USA) (Unl).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nightmare Busters (USA) (Unl).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./On the Ball (USA).zip</path>
		<name>On the Ball</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>There's a kind of knick-knack you may find in dusty games rooms, a maze through which you navigate a marble by subtly tilting the board, dancing with gravity and momentum, deftly rolling your sphere out of dead ends and around the obstacles posed by holes in the board. Marble Madness explores this theme in a fudged 3-D perspective, Cloud Kingdoms in a flat 2-D one -- both by directly influencing the actions of the ball. The game takes a different approach toward a similar end; instead of moving the ball around the board, you move the board around the ball.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19921101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/On the Ball (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/On the Ball (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pirates of Dark Water, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pirates of Dark Water, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The watery world of Mer is threatened by the deadly Dark Water. Prince Ren and his companions must find the Treasures of Rule to control the Dark Water and return Mer to its former glory. Always hot on their heels is the evil pirate-lord Bloth who wants to find the treasures to rule over Mer.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19940502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pirates of Dark Water, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pirates of Dark Water, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./ActRaiser (USA).zip</path>
		<name>ActRaiser</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>ActRaiser was one of the early SNES games, drawing upon the success of side-scrolling platform action titles and the building model of Sim City. You play "The Master", and must save the world from evil. First you purge the land by sending your spirit into a warrior with a big sword and magic powers. This side scrolling portion puts you in many different locales, from swamps and forests, to pyramids and snowy mountaintops. As you eliminate evil from different parts of the land, you allow villagers to return and build their towns. You then control an angel who helps guide the villagers in their town building, and can send down miracles to aid them in their needs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19911102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quintet</developer>
		<publisher>Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/ActRaiser (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/ActRaiser (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Asterix &amp; Obelix (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Astérix &amp; Obélix</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Astérix &amp; Obélix is a platform game where one player can choose to control either Asterix or Obelix or two players can play simultaneously. The mission of the two Gauls is to acquire artifacts from all across Europe.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Infogrames</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Asterix &amp; Obelix (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Asterix &amp; Obelix (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daze Before Christmas (Europe).zip</path>
		<name>Daze Before Christmas</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>'Twas but Daze Before Christmas and at Santa's shop work on the toys has suddenly stopped! The elves are on strike as Christmas draws near, but much worse than that, there's something to fear! Give Santa the potion to drink and he'll change, he'll become "Anti Claus" on a rampage of rage! He'll break all the toys, he'll ignore his good work. Could it be Santa is just a fat jerk? You must help Santa find his way, fix all the toys and take off in his sleigh. Through 24 levels you'll put up a fight. Can you help save Christmas? Let's find out tonight!</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Funcom</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Daze Before Christmas (Europe).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Daze Before Christmas (Europe).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beauty and the Beast (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Disney's Beauty and the Beast</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Disney's Beauty and the Beast is an action platformer for the SNES. The entire game is played through the perspective of the Beast. As the Beast, the player must get Belle to fall in love so that the curse cast upon him and his castle will be broken, she will marry him and become a princess. The final boss of the game is Gaston, a hunter who will try to steal Belle from the Beast. There is even a snowball fight scene in the middle of the game and cutscenes between stages that tells the story of Beauty and the Beast.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940701T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>Hudson</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Beauty and the Beast (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Beauty and the Beast (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Krusty's Super Fun House (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Krusty's Super Fun House</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Krusty the Clown's Fun House has been overrun by rats. You must help him to herd the rats into trap machines to clear them out. In order to do so, Krusty must manipulate his environment to set up pathways so that the rats are headed in the right direction. Objects that Krusty move around include blocks, fans, and pipe pieces. The trap machines are operated by other recognizable Simpson's characters: Bart, Homer, Sideshow Mel, and Corporal Punishment.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Audiogenic Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<image>./boxart/Krusty's Super Fun House (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Krusty's Super Fun House (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family, The (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Addams Family, The</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Addams Family is a platform game based on the characters and settings from the movie (which, in turn, is based on the famous 1960's television series, which in turn is based on Charles Addams cartoon of the same name, which was featured in the magazine, The New Yorker, in the 30's). The game takes place towards the end of the movie: the Addams Family has been evicted from their home by a court order issued by a backstabbing attorney (there's one for the books), Tully Alford. Even worse, the other Addamses: Morticia, Pugsley, Wednesday, Granny and Lurch have gone missing.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Addams Family, The (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Addams Family, The (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Aero the Acro-Bat 2</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the sequel to Aero the Acro-Bat you have to defeat evil industrialist Edgar Ektor once again. He is back and again with bad ideas, so you - in the role of Aero - have to find and destroy him before he carries out his diabolical "Plan B". Like in the last installment, you have to jump, escape lethal obstacles and progress in time. This game features more moves for Aero, more mechanisms to use and more items to collect.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sunsoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Arcana (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Arcana</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In this game you play as a young boy named Rooks. He's the only one that can save the world from the evil Galneon. With the power of the cards he begins his adventure. All of the people you fight with and against are displayed on cards. They can have an elemental attribute or not. Rooks is able to summon an elemental to aid him. He can only summon one type at a time, and he must find them before being able to summon them.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19920501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>HAL Laboratory</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Arcana (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Arcana (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy: Mystic Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Focus Tower is the center of the world and balances the forces of the world. However 4 monsters have taken the 4 elemental crystals (Earth, Water, Fire, Wind) for their own use, and also taken the 4 keys that for doors inside of Focus Tower. With the balance disrupted, disasters befall the world. A young boy by the name of Benjamin finds his home village destroyed. Meeting a mysterious old man while trying to escape from earthquakes, he soon learns that he is the prophesized hero and the only one who can save the world. Benjamin must recover the 4 crystals, unlock Focus Tower and defeat the ultimate monster before the 5th crystal, the Crystal of Life is corrupted.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19921005T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Final Fantasy - Mystic Quest (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Genghis Khan II - Clan of the Gray Wolf (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Genghis Khan II: Clan of the Gray Wolf</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>As in the first part you could participate in two conquests: Mongol conquest and world conquest. In the first you must unite all the little tribes of the country. The world conquest is more complex: You must use all your senses to make the world as you wish.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Genghis Khan II - Clan of the Gray Wolf (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Genghis Khan II - Clan of the Gray Wolf (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Marines (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Metal Marines</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>The Antimatter Cold War has left Earth ruined as the stockpiled AM weapons of various nations were triggered in a chain effect, vaporizing large portions of the Earth. The once great continents have been drastically changed into thousands of tiny islands and various cities have washed into the oceans. During this turmoil, Zorgeuf the Great rushes to conquer the bewildered world along with a troop of commanders and declares the Earth Empire. The only hope to defeat him lies from without Earth, as the Colonial Forces send a command carrier from the major orbital base. With so many armies gone, the ground infantry unit has been replaced by the Metal Marine, a fifty foot armored robot that can be sent into battle for attack or defense.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19931201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Metal Marines (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Metal Marines (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Natsume Championship Wrestling (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Natsume Championship Wrestling</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Natsume Championship Wrestling is one of the many unlicensed wrestling games released by in the heyday. It contains 12 fictional wrestlers (Asteroid, The Viper, Spike, Python, M. Roach, The Phantom, Big Ape, K-Bruto, H. Snake, Fangz, J. Kraze and Conan). The game modes include 1P v. CPU, 1P v. 2P, a regular and a tag team tournament or a round robin tournament to compete in. Each wrestlers has a very extensive set of moves, where different moves can be performed based on the ring situation (grappling, holds, dashes, on the ground, from ropes...) but in the end every fighter basically has the same set of moves, punch, kick, bodyslam, with a few unique ones like piledrivers and powerbombs.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>19940601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Natsume Championship Wrestling (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Natsume Championship Wrestling (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./NBA Jam (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>NBA JAM</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>NBA Jam is a two-on-two basketball game You can play any NBA team, and you can play as players like Barkley, Starks, Pippen, and Grant. Each human player controls a single player, so choose your squad wisely to take team-mate skill into account. The game is action-oriented, and players can perform unrealistic slam-dunks. Full performance statistics are automatically recorded. The play clock and 3-point line apply, but other rules are largely overlooked.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19940302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<image>./boxart/NBA Jam (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/NBA Jam (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Nobunaga's Ambition (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Nobunaga's Ambition</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In the 16th century, Japan's Sengoku ("Warring States") period divided the nation into numerous feudal states, each ruled by a daimyo. These daimyos would often go to war with each other. Many dreamt of conquering the land, becoming the Shogun and ruling the entire country. One of those daimyos was the ambitious Nobunaga Oda, a merciless ruler and a renowned strategist. Players take on the role of Nobunaga Oda or one of many other daimyos to try to conquer Japan. Nobunaga's Ambition is a turn-based strategy game which can be played in different modes. Gameplay is similar to Koei's better known Romance of the Three Kingdoms game. Players begin by selecting either a 17 regions scenario or a larger 50 scenario.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19931202T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Koei</developer>
		<publisher>Koei</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Nobunaga's Ambition (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Nobunaga's Ambition (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Attack (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Pac-Attack</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Based on Namco's Japanese-only arcade puzzler Cosmo Gang the Puzzle, Pac-Attack is similar to many block-dropping puzzle games from the time, such as Puyo Puyo. The objective of the game is to place ghosts and then, after three pieces (which can include one or two blocks as well), make Pac-Man eat as many ghosts as possible to try and clear up the game area. Pac-Man's directions are chosen at random between left or right, but as he goes moving on the game area (after you place him, of course), if he bumps against a block or a "wall" on the game area, he will change his direction. As with many block-dropping puzzlers, if a line of blocks and/or ghosts reaches the top, the game ends.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19931002T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<image>./boxart/Pac-Attack (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Pac-Attack (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Prehistorik Man (USA) (En,Fr,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Prehistorik Man</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In Prehistorik Man, the player takes control of a neanderthal who is on a quest to travel through various levels, collecting food items to get his village ready for the fast approaching fall feast. Along the way, the player will encounter an assortment of enemies ranging from spiders, giant rats and even the mighty T-Rex. There are five levels in all and the player can upgrade their weapons to axes and mallets throughout the game as well as acquire a hang glider, giving the player the advantage of flight and covering long distances. The main goal of the game is to vanquish enemies, collect food items, and face a boss at the end of each level.</desc>
		<rating>0.85</rating>
		<releasedate>19960102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Titus</developer>
		<publisher>Titus</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Prehistorik Man (USA) (En,Fr,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Prehistorik Man (USA) (En,Fr,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spanky's Quest (USA).zip</path>
		<name>Spanky's Quest</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Spanky's Quest is a game about a monkey who decides to go on a picnic. While on his way through the forest he see's a witch in the sky and out of nowhere bricks begin to make a tower around the area Spanky is in. The witch challenges Spanky to come to the final tower and she will free him but before she flies away she turns the fruits in his knapsack into living fruit monsters. Unknowingly, she drops a magic ball which agrees to help Spanky out on his quest. The object of the game is to get through all six of the towers which consist of 10 levels as well as a boss battle. In order to proceed to the next level, you must acquire the amount of keys the locked door requires.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19920801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Spanky's Quest (USA).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Spanky's Quest (USA).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Speedy Gonzales - Los Gatos Bandidos (USA) (Rev 1).zip</path>
		<name>Speedy Gonzales: Los Gatos Bandidos</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>In a small Mexican village, all the mice were enjoying a fiesta until Los Gatos Bandidos, a group of cats, came and kidnapped them all. Only Slowpoke escaped and sent for his cousin, the fastest mouse in Mexico... Speedy Gonzales! Following the trail of the Bandidos, Speedy will enter each level and try to rescue as many mice as possible while chasing after cheese and avoiding natural hazards. Ariba! Ariba! The gameplay in Speedy Gonzales resembles the Sonic the Hedgehog series of games more than anything else. For the most part Speedy will run, run across fields and up slopes and into tunnels. There are also mousetraps which function similarly to Sonic's trampolines and will propel Speedy into the air.</desc>
		<rating>0.75</rating>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Speedy Gonzales - Los Gatos Bandidos (USA) (Rev 1).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Speedy Gonzales - Los Gatos Bandidos (USA) (Rev 1).mp4</video>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vortex (USA) (En,Es).zip</path>
		<name>Vortex</name>
		<sortname />
		<desc>Vortex was one of the few games designed to use the SNES Super FX 1 chip, a custom-made graphics accelerator RISC processor. The game is a 3D shooter similar to Star Fox by the same development studio, but with some subtle differences. Players can morph their vehicle at any time from the standard walker to a sonic jet, a land burner and a defensive hard shell, each with their own weapons, strengths and weaknesses. The player is cast as a soldier fighting the Aki-Do Forces, an evil empire bent on taking over the entire universe. To stop them, the player has access to an experimental mech, the Vortex, to travel the seven worlds of the Aki-Do system and destroy the bases.</desc>
		<rating>0.65</rating>
		<releasedate>19940901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Software</developer>
		<publisher>Electro Brain Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<image>./boxart/Vortex (USA) (En,Es).jpg</image>
		<video>./snaps/Vortex (USA) (En,Es).mp4</video>
	</game>
</gameList>